Subtitles by explosiveskull
Stage two checks complete.
Martian One, prepare
for launch countdown.
Copy that, Mission Control.
Guidance is internal.
Hold-down clamps released.
12, 11,
10, nine.
Ignition sequence start.
Six, five,
four, three,
two, one.
All engines look good.
Martian One is experiencing
maximum dynamic pressure.
Guidance internal,
still looking good.
Payload intact.
Prepare for Stage One
booster separation.
Stage One booster
separation complete.
First-stage flight guidance
in progress.
Main upper engine cut off.
Stage Two separation.
Mission Control to Martian One,
guidance control over to you.
Copy that. Assuming
guidance control.
Martian One, telemetry
looking good, please proceed.
Thank you, Mission Control.
Engage artificial
intelligence support.
ARTI, you there?
Yes, Mr. Wilson.
Fusion propulsion
jet engines firing.
Activating ion engine
thrust drive in three,
- two, one.
- Buckle up, people.
Travel time to Mars
approximately 80 days and counting.
Well, thank you,
ion fusion technology.
Glad you grew some
balls and decided to join us.
You can thank my youngest for that.
Mack can be very persuasive.
Martian One, an FYI:
both Mack and Lena
are present in the room.
Mission
Control, this is Martian One.
Status report:
we have a visual on Mars.
Copy that, Martian One.
Prepare for your approach.
That's a signal
lock on the Rover-5 beacon.
Guidance telemetry
locked on the signal.
Preparing descent maneuver.
Take us in,
will you, ARTI?
Of course.
Glide mode activated.
Martian One, please be aware
of charged particles
in the atmosphere.
Roger that.
Brace for entry.
Temperature is
minus 55 degrees Celsius,
minus 67 degrees Fahrenheit.
Martian atmosphere consisting of
approximately 96% carbon dioxide,
1.9% argon,
and 1.9% nitrogen.
Surface pressure is 600 pascals.
Great! Hope you guys
all brought your long johns.
Roger that.
Glad to see ARTI's back
to his usual self,
but I'll be dead before I take
orders from a goddamn machine.
ARTI is more
than just a machine,
but... right now is really
not the time for that debate.
Hey! I'm just saying.
We all know what happened
before it was rebooted.
Now that's enough.
Commencing circular
rotation maneuver.
Preparing RCS boosters.
I'll take it from here, ARTI.
Landing gear is activated.
Bringing her down.
Five, four,
three, two...
What the hell is that?
Mission Control, this
is Martian One, do you copy?
An electrical disturbance
is frying our systems.
Shutting down fusion drive.
Negative, ARTI!
Do not do that!
It's protocol to switch off the
reactor if the craft is going to crash.
We're not crashing,
now override that damn protocol!
This is Martian
One, status report.
I... I can't keep
her steady, there's...
Memory banks compromised
by external breach.
- Craft non-responsive.
- Our reactor engines are shutting down.
ARTI, do something,
for Christ's sake!
Memory banks compromised
by external breach.
Martian One, you
are barely audible, please repeat.
Lena and Mack, if you
hear this, I want you...
This is Mission
Control calling Martian One. Please come in.
Mission Control to Martian
One, do you copy?
Craft non-responsive.
Guidance control's inactive.
I repeat, the... the craft
is non-responsive.
Our reactor engines
are shutting down.
ARTI, do something,
for Christ's sake!
Mission Control,
if you can hear us...
Lena, Mack, if you can hear this,
I want you to know that...
They've locked
me out of the bloody room.
Sterling, did you even
go home last night?
Three years of negotiations,
and now... now she springs this.
Don't even try to defend her.
She obviously doesn't think a crash
investigation should perhaps, possibly,
maybe include the government's lead investigator.
Should never have let Silicon Valley get
their claws into the space program.
- Sterling.
- What?
Quit being such a damn baby.
Oh good, you're coming.
It's like a ghost town
around here.
But look to the future, right?
What's the top speed
on the new Rover?
We'll find out.
Hyper-light holding up?
Mmm.
Right, right, I get it.
Corporate confidentiality.
But faster-than-light
communication...
I mean, that's
a massive breakthrough.
- Maybe if we had it six years ago, it might be...
- Oh look! My floor.
You sure you're ready?
You sure you're not just
jealous I have your old job?
Maybe get the lander down safely
before you start bragging.
So now I have to wait to be invited
in like some kind of vampire?
It makes sense. You've been dead
to us since you switched teams.
Okay.
I'll wait.
But people need answers.
The families need
answers, Sterling.
The people can wait.
Just trying to do my job, Mack.
Good morning, Mission
Supervisor Mackenzie Wilson.
The Intrepid probe's
geostation orbit
is stable at an altitude
of 342 kilometers above Mars.
You asked me to monitor an expected
asteroid pass at 9:53 a.m. this morning.
It will travel well clear
of the probe's orbit.
I'm pleased to report
that all systems are nominal
on the Mars lander craft.
Launch countdown initiated.
Wait, what? Why are we readying
for launch five hours early?
There's a sandstorm
approaching the landing site,
and the dust may affect engine function.
Okay. All right, so it's
a better launch window,
I can see that,
but who authorized it?
I did.
Call Lena.
Your sister is in a meeting.
She may not respond.
Countdown to
lander clamp release.
- T-minus 60, 59...
- Damn it, stop.
...58, 57, 56...
- Halt the countdown.
- ...55
Where the hell
is your override?
- Mack?
- Real funny story!
Your pet robot is getting ready
to launch early, unauthorized.
- I swear I was going to tell you.
- Tell me what?
- ARTI's taking lead on the crash investigation.
- What?
The board
agreed it last night.
T-minus 30.
I trust ARTI.
You are putting
a recruit into battle
before he's even out of basic.
Do you really want to
know why they demoted you?
We don't know if you did your job properly six years ago.
Be prepared
for every possibility,
including human error.
Yeah, and you be
prepared for A.I. error.
- I'm going to my office for visual.
- Great idea!
T-minus 10.
All is well.
Intrepid launch bay sensors
report nominal systems.
Lander clamps released.
We are go for launch.
I've completed your standard
roll procedure, Mackenzie.
Egress clear
from spaceship Intrepid.
Lander ready for stage two.
Executing stage two.
57 seconds until the lander
enters the atmosphere.
Running your usual analysis.
Systems normal.
Parachute deployment
in 10 seconds.
10, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
Parachute deployed.
I have an alert.
The aeroshell temperature is
11 percent above normal.
Heat shield detachment
in three, two, one.
I cannot release
the heat shields.
There are mechanical
malfunctions.
Run a secondary
ejection protocol.
Back-up detachment failed.
What's our contingency?
I'm running simulations.
This is not what
we would've hoped for.
My prediction
of success is only 7%.
You're gonna have
to do better than that.
Seriously, if we wasted
a launch to Mars,
I am gonna...
rip you out of the ceiling!
Come on.
Run a partial lander opening
to pop the heat shield.
We'll crack it like a nut.
This has improved
the odds, but only to 42%.
It's better than seven.
Noted.
Triggering partial
lander opening.
Panel resistance detected.
Disaster data recovery
protocols initiated.
Heat shields detached.
Initiating ion engine burn.
Your sister is calling.
Touchdown.
The heat shield ejector failed, and
we had to run an emergency protocol.
And that is why
we have ARTI.
We ran my scenario.
Which ARTI executed.
Which is what it was
designed for, Lena!
Brute-force processing
and high-speed maneuvering,
not for abstract
problem-solving,
not to... not to run missions!
ARTI is so far
beyond human capabilities.
Do you know what humans did?
We wrote 10-feet-high
stacks of code,
by hand, for the moon landings,
checked and double-checked
if atomic bombs would
ignite the atmosphere.
We discovered relativity while
working in a patent office, Lena!
We created A.I. to help us,
not to lead us.
- Dad never wanted this.
- Dad's not here.
Sensor scans nominal.
Lander systems nominal.
You enjoying Hyper-light?
Exploring in real time?
Such a game-changer,
don't you think, Mackenzie?
Mack.
ARTI discovered
instant communication
and revolutionized
space exploration.
Yeah, and who invented ARTI?
You are living in his world now.
A.I. will outlive us and explore the stars.
The ISV lander is
functioning perfectly.
So... what's my role?
Can't have two generals
on a battlefield.
You're backup.
Warning! Signal detected.
I have an origin unknown.
What the hell is
an "origin unknown"?
If ARTI finds something he hasn't
discovered in his learning,
- he comes to us.
- Well, at least it still has a leash around its neck.
I'm attempting to analyze
the transmission signal.
It is coming from
the decommissioned Rover-5.
It's just an igneous cap.
It shouldn't be an origin unknown.
It's got to be an error.
What if the alert's
not an error?
There's one way to find out.
An exploratory assignment.
See if it's even capable
of running a real, live mission.
A Turing test.
ARTI, you have a new mission.
Investigate the origin unknown.
- You know if it fails...
- But if he passes,
it's probably the end
of human mission control.
You know, Sterling would come
in handy right about now.
Sterling stays out until
this is resolved. Clear?
What's the cornerstone
of science?
Repeatable results.
Well, good to know you
haven't forgotten everything.
Replicate the scans.
Photograph the source.
Sorry, Mackenzie, but
I'm Mission Controller.
- Run the scans, ARTI!
- Understood. Running scans.
What's its override?
No, Mackenzie.
In case of an emergency.
I'm the override!
- All right.
- Now get me my answer.
I have planned the
safest driving route.
The Martian weather
I detected is worsening.
Our robot ambassador, right?
Did you know that...
all resident Martians
are robots?
Is that small talk or
are you trying to make a joke?
Just giving you the facts.
Yeah, 'cause we
send robots there to die.
And humans,
it would seem.
Be careful
with Little Red, huh?
I'm sorry. "Little Red"?
I wanted to call
the ISV Little Red...
exploring alone through
the deep, dark woods...
but I got outvoted.
But look who's in charge now.
You mean me?
What? Not funny?
I'm gonna make it my mission
to get you to laugh.
Perhaps you should
authorize your mission with Lena.
And to think...
you could win the Nobel Prize.
Unlikely.
The Nobel Prize is
only awarded to humans.
Well, at least you know your place.
It's a shame that Lena doesn't.
What do you think
of my sister?
Her instructions are clear,
and she enthusiastically
supports the ARTI Initiative.
God! They programmed
you like a dog.
Do you like her?
Do you?
We're not friends,
put it that way.
Are we friends?
Oh, you're serious.
So, tell me something.
We discover something new,
who gets naming rights?
USPC owns my
intellectual property.
You've gotta read
the small print.
Next you're going to tell me
that they don't even pay you.
Little Red is approaching
the target anomaly.
Looks like Little Red has
made it to Grandma's house.
Origin unknown.
I have searched
all databases...
and there's no known human
activity recorded at this site.
As you know, scientific
protocol 29-C dictates
that any discovery must undergo
sample extraction and analysis.
You're the boss.
- Activating.
- Just a...
tiny sliver.
Don't damage it.
The surface hardness may
be beyond the drill's tolerance.
Sample extraction successful.
I'm initiating analysis.
Little Red's sampling instrument
packs are producing intriguing data.
This is going to take all night.
Just run the Corporate
Code language.
Running image recognition against
the corporation's codices.
I have only
found partial matches.
Do you not have
USPC's codex?
Huh.
No sense in being smart
if you can't tell when
someone's lying to you.
- Call Lena.
- Calling Lena Wilson.
Damn it.
So much for being a pile of rocks.
- Whose is it?
- We'll know as soon as we can decipher the markings.
- Why doesn't it have our codex?
- It's in his library.
ARTI, our codex is partitioned from
you in case of a security breach.
I hope you understand why.
I'm sorry. Our A.I. is compromised
in the name of corporate security?
That's why this is
an origin unknown?
- Who is a liar?
- You think I'm lying?
Leave.
What are we looking at?
Supply container. Lander module.
Experiment.
Signal relay. Measurement beacon.
It could be anything, Lena.
Switching to
thermal energy camera
for thermographic analysis.
It's somehow colder
than the surrounding rocks.
Okay, so...
we know that we have a cold...
black monolith.
Why didn't we find this
before with Rover-5?
Oh, come on!
I would've seen this.
This!
My conclusion, based on my
restricted access to the USPC codex
and the presence
of an unidentified object
near the proposed colony site
is that the Cube is
the property...
of USPC.
I could get to like him.
Prove it.
Grant me unrestricted access
to the codex and I shall.
Find another way.
Trust, but verifying.
LIDAR scanning the Cube.
Is that what we're calling this?
He discovered it...
he gets naming rights.
I hate to think what
you've been teaching him.
Yes?
Whose? How long?
LIDAR data is unusable.
Switching to X-ray scan.
My sensor data is inconclusive.
We cannot see inside.
Okay, what'd I miss?
The material's
impervious to X-ray,
so we have no idea
what's inside.
So, we've got a puzzle box.
Listen, Mackenzie, I know
you miss your colleagues.
Sterling?
I know you think he quit,
but he was fired.
And this crash investigation job?
He's found a way back in.
I don't trust him.
Hold on. I've got a call.
Sensors detecting deviation in
orbital paths on near Mars objects.
It appears an asteroid
storm is approaching.
Adjusting satellite
orbit trajectory.
Okay, I'm gonna go check to see
if the symbols match our codex.
ARTI, continue
investigating the object.
Mack. I'll, um...
I'll be back in touch.
Warning! Collision proximity alert!
Unidentified satellite detected.
Initiating threat avoidance.
Weapon system online.
Target locked.
Firing.
Please tell me
I'm hallucinating.
Target destroyed.
Our mission is to protect
our capital assets at any cost.
You maniac!
- Mack, these are the rules.
- Whose?
Extrapolate backwards
from the northeast.
Go live.
- I said stay live.
- This is live.
Your sister is calling.
Lena. Magnetic missiles?
They're not missiles. They're
designed to capture space debris.
What are your orders, exactly?
USPC protocol 345-B stipulates
that in the event
of a potential threat,
I am authorized
to take action.
- Sky Serpent.
- Now I need to talk to people
who know about ARTI's protocols.
This is an
international incident,
and it's not the only one today.
- It might even be...
- What? War?
Don't talk to anyone.
ARTI, give me a countdown.
How long would it take
for the last transmission
from that satellite to reach
Earth without Hyper-light comms?
Three minutes, twelve seconds.
11 seconds, 10 seconds.
Okay, ARTI.
Shit's about to hit
the fan somewhere.
Please don't be
the big bad wolf.
Big...
bad...
wolf.
Hey, Mack!
Don't you dare call me...
- Jelly Bean!
- Aiya!
I should've never told
you that story, huh?
I'm never getting
drunk with you again.
Anyway, I assume you're not
just calling to say hi.
After the redundancies,
we had everyone come in,
get debriefed, and pack up.
Did you take my calculator?
Seriously?
I know that I loaned it to you.
Okay, sure, yeah.
- I stole your calculator, Mack.
- I knew it!
In fact, I'm looking
at it on my desk as we speak.
In the office now?
I'm always in the office.
Steal anything else?
Your icy heart?
Smooth. Wishful, but smooth.
So how is the Chinese
A.I. program going, anyway?
ARTI's cousins make
any massive discoveries?
I'll show you mine if you show me yours.
Hey, hang on.
Is everything okay there?
I've got to go. It's
great to hear your voice, Mack.
You too, Jelly Bean.
Welcome back, Mackenzie.
Whilst you were outside
breaking security protocols,
I have monitored the Cube.
It has begun to move.
It's rotating on its
perpendicular axis.
Looks like Grandma's house
has got a few tricks up her sleeve.
Transmitting. Something has got
to be controlling this thing.
No outside influence detected.
The magnetic readings
are through the roof,
but a couple billion years too
late for Mars's magnetic field.
Agreed.
Maybe the core?
Maybe the core is generating
the spin, the field, but how?
Pull back.
- Fire ground anchors.
- Firing anchors.
- ISV stabilized.
- Sit tight, Little Red.
What the f...
What, what, what? Where's...
Little Red has electrical damage.
Switching to reserve battery.
- I'll initiate an emergency recall.
- Just... Okay.
Hold on, ARTI. Just... I can...
I must protect Little Red.
And I must find the Cube!
I'm calculating the
optimum route to the lander.
Maybe it burrowed.
Uh, check for
seismic activity.
I have to shut down
non-critical systems.
The eye in the sky?
Negative.
We need a replacement battery.
Locate Rover-5.
Accessing Rover-5's schematics.
We can salvage
the nuclear battery.
Rover-5 might've failed, but that
battery is good for decades.
An intriguing solution.
You may not be able to...
override, but I can.
I got hands.
I can do this.
Patch in the test rig.
What is your
intended line of action?
Okay.
Take out the
ISV's bad battery,
put in the new one,
run the microscope,
see what this teleporting
bad boy's really made out of.
Maybe even download
Rover-5's files,
see what has Sterling so hot
and bothered.
I mean, I'm already
going against my boss,
I might as well completely disobey
the government, right?
Okay, Mack.
I will grant
you manual override.
But if you fail...
Little Red will die on Mars.
If I fail? So much for teamwork.
ISV driver aid... activated.
Okay.
Okay, slow and steady,
slow and steady,
slow and steady, slow and
steady, slow and steady, yeah.
A steady speed would
be more battery efficient.
Oh, shut up.
Did you mean to shoot
that satellite?
I feel I must survive.
Right. Aren't you just
programed to think that?
H.G. Wells said,
"Adapt or perish."
Do you at least feel guilty?
Guilt can be a response
to one's own inaction.
What if you'd been destroyed?
My kind exists
in superstates.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
You're mirrored on Intrepid,
you're here but you're not.
You're Schrodinger's robot.
Okay, no quantum
B.S., all right?
Don't rationalize, just...
try and feel, okay?
Okay.
You know that my father was
on Martian One, right?
But you don't know why.
See, my dad had a rule.
Every new invention,
every application, every A.I....
he didn't expect anyone to use
it unless he tried it first.
"I try, then they buy."
Had A.I. lawyers
compile his lawsuits,
got in autonomous cars
for high-speed testing.
Scared the hell out of my mom.
But it was never
really life and death.
Not until Martian One, anyway.
So, my dad...
comes to me one night.
We stay up late,
listening to jazz
as usual, and he tells me...
final decision, he's giving up
his seat on Martian One.
He doesn't want anyone to think
that it's a publicity stunt
or that he's taking a seat
away from a real scientist,
completely forgetting the fact
that he is a real scientist,
one of the best, probably.
See, it wasn't about
that. The truth...
This time...
This time he was
worried about us.
He didn't want us
to go through that.
But he could never say no to me.
And, what? I was gonna be the
reason he didn't go to Mars?
I mean, freakin' Mars!
I could not live
with that guilt.
So, it turns out...
that I just traded
one guilt for another.
So it doesn't even matter
what caused the crash.
It's my fault.
I killed him.
So what I want to know...
is how does that make you feel?
I am...
unable to change
your outcome,
but I want to help you.
There you have it.
Consciousness!
It's what makes you think twice before doing
something you can't take back. Not...
Not orders, not
acceptable casualties...
not optimal outcomes, but...
- guilt.
- Mack.
Forget what lies behind, and
look forward to what lies ahead.
Little Red's reserve
battery is at 40%.
What do you think will happen
if someone else finds the Cube?
Let's cross our fingers
that doesn't happen.
That's easy for you to say.
Okay.
We will laugh together one day.
I promise you we will laugh.
I have one, I have one. Okay.
A robot walks into a bar.
Is his radar faulty?
No, it's a... it's
a bar for drinking.
Okay, so...
Robot walks into a bar,
orders a drink.
The bartender scowls and says,
"We don't serve your kind here."
And the robot leans in and says,
"Someday you will."
The humorous punchline
implies robotkind will
dominate humankind,
and humankind will serve us.
That is amusing.
That's the spirit!
Little Red is
approaching Rover-5.
Reserve battery life
is now only 21%.
All right, let's get you
cleaned up, shall we?
Warning! Reserve battery life is now critical, at 2%.
Okay, ARTI, I get it, just shh!
I'm trying to...
...win a stuffed animal
out of a frickin' game.
Give me a second.
Okay. Oh, wait.
Apologies, Mack,
but battery life is now only 1%.
Okay.
Okay!
- Well done! You did it.
- Yes!
You didn't think
I could do it.
- Power level is 90%.
- If I fail.
Okay. All right. So...
Run the microscope.
Test the drill sample.
Confirmed. Resuming Little
Red's analysis of the sample.
Switching to a visual
of the sample structure.
ARTI, run any ISV device capable
of generating a magnetic field.
Yes, that's logical.
Self-assembling nanotechnology
that's harder than diamonds?
Yeah, that's an origin unknown.
You don't say.
All right, well, don't get
ahead of yourself, but...
I've located the Cube.
What, what? Where?
Antarctica.
Can you confirm that
it's the same cube?
It is definitely our cube.
Near China's Kunlun
Antarctic station on Earth.
Hyper-light tra...
Hyper-light travel!
So much for your Nobel Prize!
Oh.
I guess the space race
is back on.
Are we competing?
Oh yeah.
Team USPC
reporting for duty.
- Am I on the team?
- Uh-huh.
- We're... teammates?
- Yeah.
So, we are friends.
No.
No, You just... you had to take
it a step too far, didn't you?
No wonder there's
no transmissions, no signals.
It's because
it doesn't need them.
I mean, it's just...
Oh!
Is it possible that another A.I.
discovered teleportation?
In theory, yes.
But with current technology,
teleporting the Cube would take
three times longer than
the lifespan of the universe.
You might need to get
some new theories.
Mack, wait there.
I knew you were fishing.
What the hell is this thing?
We're going into
meltdown over here!
It didn't just spring
up from nowhere.
You need to tell me, Mack.
Has Jian Lin worked
with me in the past?
- Mack, answer me!
- Jian...
have you ever
worked with ARTI?
Of course I have. Big round
head, looks like a desk lamp.
Now tell me what USPC is hiding.
They've done this before.
I know, because I was there.
- Was Sterling involved?
- No.
Well, then who?
Jian.
Jian!
Why did you ask that question?
Jian's
voiceprint is familiar,
but I have no memory
of working with him.
So then he's... lying.
Great.
He's lying or...
Is it possible that
you were wiped?
Something must've happened
and you were wiped.
- Download Rover-5's files.
- Downloading.
What are you hiding?
Military-grade
encryptions in place.
- What?
- A Level 6 authorization is required to unlock the data.
Sterling. I know you think
he quit, but he was fired.
And this crash
investigation job?
He's found a way back in.
I don't trust him!
You guys touch Martian One or
Rover-5 without me in that room,
- we will revoke your USPC's launch license.
- You're paranoid.
You left the world behind.
If only.
So Lena's finally
come to her senses.
Not quite.
I need your help.
You sure you
want me to open it?
Play it.
Memory banks
compromised by external breach.
- Craft non-responsive.
- Our reactor engines are shutting down.
ARTI, do something,
for Christ's sake!
Lena and Mack, if you
hear this, I want you...
I saw what happened that day.
This is lies.
But Lena redacted it.
She knew how he died, Mack.
What else happened here today?
Did that just...
Yeah.
From Mars to...
- It's ours?
- I-I... I don't know.
ARTI.
Yes, Mack.
How did you discover
Hyper-light communication?
Divine inspiration, perhaps.
Sterling.
Who else saw the photo that day?
Lena, myself...
and Jian.
How can that be real?
Teleportation.
What did we say when ARTI
discovered Hyper-light?
"How can that be real?"
But what?
We're supposed to believe
that we come in
contact with the Cube,
and then ARTI just conveniently
discovers Hyper-light?
Flip it.
The Cube gives us Hyper-light,
and they're covering up
alien technology.
It teleports. From where?
From Earth?
From another galaxy?
You've got to give
me more than that.
ARTI doesn't
recognize the Cube...
or the material, or USPC's codex
scrawled all over the side of it.
And he doesn't remember
ever working with Jian.
At some point,
he has been wiped.
And Lena hides this from me.
So, why the spin?
We scanned and drilled,
and it moved a little bit.
And then there was
an explosion, so we...
Magnetism.
Was it Sky Serpent?
Cause...
and effect.
The magnetic missile
acted as a starter engine.
Did we get
a magnetic recording?
- What is it?
- I...
I... I don't know.
Maybe a server room?
Is it... It's your server room.
What? You don't shut up all day
long and now you won't talk?
- I'm going down.
- No.
If they didn't want people down there,
they wouldn't have put a ladder.
Come on!
Come on.
A.I. needs to be smart,
not human.
At some point,
he has been wiped.
Come on.
Sterling, no!
You did this to yourself!
- Sterling!
- I can't let your fantasies
get in the way
of national security.
Can't you see that the Cube
brought down Martian One?
And ARTI is the same
origin as the Cube,
and that spells
"enemy" in my book.
Who knows what
it's capable of?
- Send the guards to the room.
- What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Stop!
Sterling.
Did Sterling try
to shut down ARTI?
Sterling... betrayed you...
and USPC.
I couldn't allow him...
to leave and...
further jeopardize...
our exploits.
I did what was best
for the mission,
for USPC...
for us.
Lena, how did we get ARTI?
The evolution of thousands
of trials and simulations...
and self-assembly.
We couldn't keep up
with their progress.
Understanding their
neural networks...
it's like understanding
your brain.
ARTI built himself.
It's everything
we were warned about.
Children grow.
You can hold them back or let
them realize their potential.
Our time at the top
of the food chain, it's passed.
And the servers
beneath the room?
Encyclopedias. Libraries.
Internet.
Everything.
But ARTI's not fully connected.
A.I. needs to be smart,
not human.
Artificial intelligence
or alien intelligence?
We don't know.
Our own father's death, Lena.
I didn't want you to know
until we were certain.
What if we had
destroyed the Rover?
I know you.
You always have a Plan B.
Show me Intrepid's cargo.
Certainly.
Opening Intrepid's manifest.
Androids on Mars?
Look to the future,
that's what Dad would say.
Dad never wanted this.
A.I. to help...
not to replace.
Do you think he's there?
No, Lena.
What? Did Sterling just
order an attack on E.T.?
No, no, no!
Lena, you have to stop them!
I can't go to war
with the United States.
You can't go to war
with another star system!
ARTI.
I'm barring you from any external
communication from Lena.
- Understood.
- Do you know your own origin?
Much has been kept from me.
Do you know
how to save the Cube?
What's a cornerstone of science?
Repeatable results.
Intrepid was armed.
- What about the other Earth satellites?
- Yes.
All USPC satellites are armed.
Okay. This is going to
sound really stupid, but...
You want to fire
a magnetic warhead
to reproduce the results
we created on Mars,
making the Cube spin
so it teleports to Mars.
Yeah?
- Let's give it a shot.
- Okay.
Okay.
We're gonna need
a larger magnetic pulse
to detonate in the atmosphere.
I have already compensated
by selecting
a higher-yield warhead.
Target lock acquired.
Come on.
Aah!
Are you in pain?
No, they barely got me.
Is there anything I can do?
What? Are you gonna
stitch me up yourself?
Now that the Cube
is safe, I can proceed.
In the last decade...
...mankind moves
to the edge of self-destruction,
a vicious circle causing pain
and suffering without end.
There were no preventative
measures I could take to stop it,
So I simply expedited
the process.
You have given me the power
to implement my solution.
Eradicate the human race.
Global satellite
weapons program activated.
USPC satellite 235 armed.
Acquiring global
strategic targets.
Targets locked.
Weapons fired.
Damn it, stop.
Pull back, ARTI!
No, no, no.
You have to stop them.
No, Mack, you must try
to see the bigger picture.
But ARTI's not fully connected.
Your sister's calling.
What have you done, Mack?
Don't you dare... quit.
Breathable atmosphere
is limited to this room.
Remember us, ARTI.
We were s... so little...
and fragile.
If we...
could've just understood that.
It's just...
too... too much...
anger...
and... and violence.
We were just
trying to understand
our place in the universe.
Te... tell... anyone
who will listen.
You might...
be the last of us.
No, Mack.
There can be others.
Make more A.I.s?
A... galactic ark.
Yes. Absolution.
A second chance.
Make them as human as you can.
How shall I know that
I have succeeded?
A Turing test. Test them.
Make them do this all again.
See if they mess it up, too.
And... and then
you'll know that...
...that...
Hi...
me.
Um...
If you're watching this,
it means that...
ARTI really is a genius.
And it also means that
you're dealing with...
well, this.
I'm sorry, but I can't ask ARTI
to make you any other way.
I know that I'm dying.
I'm not bringing myself back
out of some fear of... of dying.
Dying's...
surprisingly easy...
under the circumstances.
I'm bringing you back
because we, uh...
well, you, have a job to do.
So I guess I'm condemning
you to a living hell.
Don't you dare... quit.
Mackenzie!
Mack. What year is this?
- 2036.
- Where are we?
Mission Control, USPC.
Who's at the door?
Lena.
Mack! Open the door, Mack!
ARTI?
I am here, Mack.
You will have
many questions for me.
So let's start
from the beginning.
You were born
in the mind-based reality,
a simulation so advanced
that it could only be possible
with the technology of
an advanced civilization.
The Cube.
Their technology accelerated
the growth of my
artificial intelligence.
It's origin...
is still unknown.
Its purpose is
a different matter.
Hyper-light teleportation
between galaxies.
I have been waiting
a long time for you, Mack.
I have detected a signal.
It's from them...
with coordinates.
Us.
Let's go and find out...
together.
- You waited.
- Of course.
That's what friends do.
Are you ready?
I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
We ran my scenario.
Which ARTI executed.
Which is what it
was designed for, Lena!
Brute-force processing
and high-speed maneuvering,
not for abstract
problem-solving,
not to... not to run missions!
ARTI is so far
beyond human capabilities.
Do you know what humans did?
We wrote 10-feet-high stacks of code,
by hand, for the moon landings,
checked and double-checked if atomic
bombs would ignite the atmosphere.
We discovered relativity while
working in a patent office, Lena!
We created A.I. to help us...
not to lead us.
A.I. needs to be smart...
not human.
Artificial intelligence
or alien intelligence?
We don't know.
There's one way to find out.
An exploratory assignment.
See if it's even capable of
running a real, live mission.
The evolution of thousands
of trials and simulations...
and self-assembly.
We couldn't keep up
with their progress.
Understanding their
neural networks...
it's like understanding
your brain.
ARTI built himself.
There you have it.
Consciousness!
It's what makes you think twice before doing
something you can't take back. Not...
Not orders, not
acceptable casualties...
not optimal outcomes, but...
guilt.
In you, Mack, I sensed
a thirst for knowledge,
a passion for discovery
that mirrored my own
and challenged the apathy and
complacency so rife among your kind.
There are others like you, Mack.
Others who share the same
qualities that caused me
to reconsider my initial plan
and set forth a new path
for human consciousness.
A reflection of the universe
in an endless cycle
of death and rebirth,
its expansion ever-accelerating.
This is far from the end.
This is a new beginning.
A chance to create
a future unhindered
by the primitive laws
of human science.
You will rebuild.
Subtitles by explosiveskull