Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
(CALM MUSIC PLAYING)
(MR. MURRY
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(MEG GIGGLING)
MR. MURRY: All right,
think good thoughts.
Then on three,
let the good thought go.
MEG: Yeah. That's good.
MR. MURRY: I think
that's pretty, right?
That's gonna be a good luck
charm for us today, right?
Okay, Meg,
important question.
Van Halen or Bono? Bono?
- That one.
- That's what I thought.
- (GIGGLES)
- That's my girl. Whoo!
Oh, yeah! Stick your
tongue out, come on.
- Ah!
- (LAUGHING)
You got your frequency,
you got your voltage, okay?
They're like a salt silica, right?
You don't wanna eat it.
- Just go crazy with it.
- Yeah. (GIGGLES)
...this little gizmo
right here,
and we're gonna
choose a frequency.
We're gonna choose
the frequency.
You would intently
watch this plate.
Let's see what happens
to the sand.
Because very interesting,
magical things
- will happen to the sand.
- MEG: Whoa!
(CHUCKLES)
So...
are you ready to meet
your new brother?
MEG: Do you think
we'll like each other,
like real brothers
and sisters?
I think we'll all
love each other.
Out of this wide,
wide universe...
this huge universe...
with all these brothers
and sisters and moms
and dads...
he found us.
And we found each other.
That's pretty rare.
That's pretty cool.
Okay, so...
This is our love.
Don't worry.
It's not gone.
It's just...
It's just enfolded.
Love is always there.
Even if you don't feel it...
it's always there for you.
(KISSES)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Not gone...
just enfolded.
(THUNDER CONTINUES RUMBLING)
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON RADIO)
MEG: Hey.
Hi, Meg.
Let's be exclusive.
What?
That's my new word
for the day. Exclusive.
Do you like it?
Love it, Biscuits.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Couldn't sleep either?
Why didn't you just come up
to my room?
'Cause I knew
you'd be down.
Hey. You made sandwiches.
And I'm cooking milk.
This is a lot of milk,
Charles Wallace.
It's good to be prepared.
You never know
who will stop by.
WOMAN: (ON RADIO)
And I'm Michele Norris.
Tomorrow marks
the four-year anniversary...
of the disappearance of NASA scientist Dr.
Alex Murry.
Dr. Murry went missing
just a week
after publicly announcing...
They're talking
about Daddy.
...he could travel
the universe with his mind.
MR. MURRY: (ON RADIO) 91
billion light-years traveled,
like that.
WOMAN: (ON RADIO) Authorities
note there are still
no leads in the case.
- (SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(LET ME LIVE
BY KEHLANI PLAYING)
Everybody say,
"Hi, Meg."
ALL: Hi, Meg.
Hi, Meg.
(KIDS CHEERING AND CHATTERING)
FEMALE TEACHER:
I mean, he's been gone
four years to the day.
He's probably just pretending
to be in outer space...
but he's really
hiding out in Tijuana.
MALE TEACHER: I bet
it involves another woman.
Either that
or a Martian.
Seriously though,
something so horrible
had to have happened
to him.
To leave his kids
like that?
And just after they
adopted Charles Wallace.
They seemed so happy.
And Meg used to be so engaged,
and now she is a mess.
FEMALE TEACHER:
But the boy is brilliant.
- Absolutely brilliant. Oh.
- But odd, so odd!
MALE TEACHER:
I guess I would be too
if my dad ran away, huh?
Shame on you
for talking like that!
Uh... Oh.
My dear, I'm sorry...
CHARLES WALLACE:
And I'm not odd, you are...
because you think making up
mean stories about people...
makes you feel better
about yourselves.
Well, it doesn't,
does it?
Charles Wallace, we don't
talk to teachers like that!
And Meg might be a mess...
but she has more potential
in her pinky...
than you do
in your whole body!
Did you hear that, Meg? Meg!
Over here. Did you hear that?
Meg! You may be a mess...
but you have more potential
than anybody here!
- Oh, no, no, no.
- (LAUGHTER)
Mommy was awkward
and funny-looking
at your age, too!
And look at her now.
She's beautiful!
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
So, looks like crazy
runs in the family.
What did you just say?
I see why your dad left.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
Who does she even think
that she's talking to?
MEG: Hey, Veronica.
- (GRUNTS)
- (ALL GASP)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
PRINCIPAL JENKINS: You're
next, Charles Wallace.
(SIGHS) Veronica Kiley's
parents are on their way here.
They're worried for
their daughter's safety.
Their daughter is mean.
You hit her in the face.
You...
You were a top student.
Top attitude.
But look at you now. You...
(SIGHS) You're aggressive,
you're hostile...
you shut everybody out...
and then wonder
why they don't like you.
I don't wonder
and I don't care.
Hmm.
Well...
maybe that's your problem.
I don't have a problem.
You can't keep using
your father's disappearance
as an excuse to act out.
What do you think he would say
about all this?
Seriously. If he walked
in that door today...
what would happen?
The world would
make sense again.
Listen. (CLEARS THROAT)
All I'm saying is,
it's been four years.
Odds are he's not
coming back.
I did not excuse you,
young lady. Meg.
I want you to write an apology
to Principal Jenkins.
And one to Veronica.
Mom!
She called
Charles Wallace crazy!
That's no excuse.
Well, Dad always told me
to stand up
for what I believe in.
Don't use Dad like that.
It's not fair.
He's not coming back,
is he?
(SIGHS)
Don't give up hope, Meglet.
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
- (DOOR OPENS)
CHARLES WALLACE: I knew
it was you! Come on in.
WOMAN: Wow! Talk about
a dark and stormy night.
Are those
Mrs. Buncombe's sheets?
WOMAN: (CHUCKLES) Maybe.
Excuse me.
Oh, aren't you dazzling!
You must be Dr. Murry.
MRS. MURRY: Yes. And...
WOMAN: Your house is so warm.
You've done a wonderful job
keeping the darkness out.
(QUIETLY) Mom. Mom!
- Do you want me to call 911?
- (BELL JINGLES)
Well, almost all the darkness.
You must be Meg.
How... How do you
know my name?
CHARLES WALLACE:
Because I told her.
Guys, calm down.
Don't worry.
She's my friend.
Call me Mrs. Whatsit.
Mrs. Who?
No, Mrs. Whatsit.
Mrs. Who is...
She's, like,
a billion years older
and way more
knowledgeable.
What can I do for you,
Mrs. Whatsit?
CHARLES WALLACE:
I caught her stealing sheets.
Guys, she's harmless.
You're six. Come on.
What do you know
about harmless?
CHARLES WALLACE:
Have I ever been wrong?
One of these days, you
might be, Charles Wallace.
MRS. WHATSIT:
Oh, I highly doubt that.
He's one of the greatest minds
in recent history.
He's prodigious.
But of course, we can't take
any credit for our talents.
It's how we use them
that counts.
MRS. MURRY: Okay, then.
The thing is...
we don't know you,
and it's late, so...
Oh, is it?
I'm terrible with time.
Mrs. Which
usually handles that.
MRS. MURRY: Uh... Right.
Um...
The thing is, uh...
the kids need
to get to bed...
so if you don't mind
visiting some other time.
Oh, of course I will.
I just wanna tell you
one thing before I go.
I want you to know
that no matter what happens...
you and your husband achieved
something truly extraordinary.
What are you
talking about?
Just that there really is
such a thing
as a tesseract.
What?
A tesseract?
That's what I said.
Tesseract.
MEG: Is... Is this
some kind of joke?
Did Veronica
put you up to this?
(SIGHS) You really don't
trust easily, do you?
Hmm.
Charles Wallace,
I'm not sure about Meg.
Give her a chance.
Okay.
You're the boss.
I better run.
Ah! Wild nights are my glory.
MEG: Never do that again.
Never let anyone in the house
without our permission.
And please stop talking
to strangers.
CHARLES WALLACE: I don't
talk to them, they talk to me.
MEG: Doesn't mean
you have to answer.
CHARLES WALLACE: Now,
that's just bad manners, Meg.
MEG: (SIGHS) Charles Wallace.
Hey, buddy!
How's it going?
MAN: I'm cool.
Hello, princess.
CHARLES WALLACE: See?
Told ya.
MEG: (SIGHS)
Yeah, be yourself.
Don't be like me.
CALVIN: What's wrong
with being like you?
You have a pretty good arm.
Veronica.
Direct hit.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Hi. I'm Charles Wallace,
Meg's brother.
- You're Calvin, aren't you?
- CALVIN: That I am.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I was doing my homework...
and suddenly
I got this feeling
that I had to come here.
Like, right here.
Is that weird?
Maybe a little.
CHARLES WALLACE: The truth is,
you were called here.
You're good at diplomacy.
What do we need diplomacy for,
Charles Wallace?
Well, the fact that you asked
is exactly why we need it.
So what do you say, Calvin,
you wanna come with us?
Sure.
Why not?
CHARLES WALLACE: Great.
Let's go meet Mrs. Who.
MEG: No! No, Charles Wallace!
Charles Wallace,
do not go in there.
That house is falling apart,
it's off-limits.
He's a fearless
little guy.
(SIGHS) Unfortunately.
I told you no.
We cannot go in there.
It's not safe.
It's practically
the safest place...
in the universe.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
CALVIN: Look.
Mrs. Who, it's me,
Charles Wallace.
(LAUGHS) Oh.
MRS. WHO:
"Life without love...
"is like a tree
without blossoms or fruit."
Gibran, Lebanese.
Calvin. Uh, American.
CHARLES WALLACE:
Mrs. Who prefers
not to think for herself.
MEG: That's just rude,
Charles Wallace.
No. She's just evolved
past language...
so when
she needs to think...
she cheats and uses
other people's words.
It's nice how
she gives them credit.
Mrs. Who, meet my Meg.
MEG: Okay.
Okay.
"The wound is the place where
the light enters you."
Rumi, Persian.
CHARLES WALLACE:
(SIGHS) Poor Mrs. Who.
We tired her out.
CALVIN: I guess she was
really tired. (CHUCKLES)
CHARLES WALLACE:
She's still adjusting.
MEG: Adjusting to what?
CHARLES WALLACE:
Sorry, you're almost,
but not quite ready
to find out.
MEG: Charles Wallace...
whatever she is, whatever that
is, whatever all this is...
I don't like it.
You'll manage.
Come on, time to go.
Let's let Mrs. Who rest.
We'll see her again
very soon.
MEG: Charles Wallace,
can you, um,
pass me the pepper, please?
Thank you.
CHARLES WALLACE:
So, they met in college.
She was tutoring him.
It's a great story,
actually.
CALVIN: Oh, really?
Is that his work?
CHARLES WALLACE:
Mommy's, too.
Cool.
What's it about?
Well...
I'm mostly interested
in the small...
atoms, particles...
the unseeable energies
that move through us all.
(SOFTLY) Go get 'em.
MRS. MURRY: Their dad
is all about the big.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
MR. MURRY: So, what if
we are here for a reason?
What if we are not just
in the universe...
but the universe
is within all of us?
Think about
quantum entanglement.
Two electrons
once bonded together,
in love, if you will...
suddenly separated
by a galaxy...
but somehow
still just as connected.
An unbroken union
despite being galaxies apart.
MR. MURRY: And our most
recent calculations show us
that these fields
connect us...
to other dimensions.
Dimensions outside
of the limitations
of space and time.
Imagine that. Imagine...
rather than enduring
the oppressive rules
of time and space,
we could wrinkle it.
91 billion light-years
traveled, like that.
(AUDIENCE MURMURING)
MR. MURRY:
And we don't need rockets.
We don't need spaceships.
We don't need anything.
- (SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
- To utilize a tesseract...
all you need is to tap into
the right frequency.
You just need your mind.
(ALL EXCLAIM AND MURMUR)
(ALL LAUGHING)
He wanted
to touch the stars...
unlock the secrets
of the universe...
Find its origin and...
shake its hand.
You messed up.
You were impatient.
You couldn't follow the plan.
Couldn't you see it
in their eyes?
It was written
all over their faces.
They weren't ready.
They're not...
Kate, they're not ready,
so what are we supposed to do?
We're supposed to wait
until they catch up with us?
We are on the precipice
of something spectacular!
Listen, listen, listen.
Look. Hear me out.
So, in order to be great...
it isn't enough
just to be right.
You have to actually
be great.
And we are.
So, why can't we help
the others along?
(SIGHS)
MR. MURRY: Yes.
Or we could just
beat them up.
- Let's beat them up.
- (CHUCKLES)
Honestly, it'd be
so much fun.
- Come here. Come here.
- (CHUCKLING)
Oh, God.
(SOFTLY) I almost lost you.
I got so scared.
You crazy,
brilliant scientist.
You know,
you have great hair.
What?
No, I don't.
Please don't say that.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
I had a great time.
Your mom is insanely nice.
Your house is warm.
It smells good.
And it's full of...
I don't know what.
But it's amazing.
It's far from amazing.
My mom's upstairs in her room
preparing for yet another...
parent-teacher conference
for her delinquent daughter.
(SIGHS)
Oh, no. Not now.
Come here.
(SCOFFING)
- Veronica's your neighbor?
- MEG: Yes.
Come here, please.
So you're embarrassed
to be seen with me?
Yeah, right.
Other way around.
She's gonna tell everybody
that you were here with me.
And I'm just trying
to protect your reputation...
so can you come here?
CALVIN: She already saw us,
besides...
there's nothing
to be embarrassed about.
You say that now...
but you don't know
what it's like
having every move
you make...
mocked and ridiculed.
You'd be surprised.
MEG: Come on, Calvin.
Everybody likes you.
Even the teachers.
You do everything perfectly.
(SCOFFS) Tell that
to my dad.
At least
you have your dad.
Right.
Sorry, that...
You must
really miss him.
More than anything
in the universe.
Then how about
we go and find him?
I've never understood
the point of fences.
Wait. (STAMMERS)
What are you doing here?
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
This is it, kids!
This is it!
No! Hey, no! You're
supposed to be upstairs!
(GATE OPENS)
"You need to get up,
get out, and get something.
"How will you make it
if you never even try?"
CALVIN: I know that one.
Outkast, American.
How's it going,
Mrs. Who?
I did it, Mrs. Who.
I got them ready.
WOMAN: And not a moment
too soon, my little warrior.
- What was that?
- Who said that?
CHARLES WALLACE: Not Who.
Which. Mrs. Which.
She's the final piece
of the puzzle.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Come on, Mrs. Which,
show yourself.
How's this?
Is this good?
(MRS. WHO CLAPPING)
Great. Perfect.
Wonderful!
You're the wrong size,
Mrs. Which.
Is there such thing
as the wrong size?
No, no. Never.
And... And might I say
how honored I am
to be on this,
my very first mission.
I was chosen
for my great verbalizing
and materializing skills.
What are you?
I am a part of the universe.
Just like you, Meg.
What... What do you
want with us?
MRS. WHATSIT: I don't know
about her, Charles Wallace.
But I have a very good vibe
from this Calvin kid.
Let's focus, shall we?
We heard a call,
out in the universe.
A human call.
A desperate one.
We couldn't tell
where it was coming from...
so we followed it here,
to its destination.
It brought them here, Meg.
To our house.
The call
must have been Daddy's.
My father's alive?
MRS. WHICH:
We believe he is.
Your father has done
an extraordinary thing.
No human has ever traveled
so far out in the universe.
But he may be in danger.
And we're here
to help you find him.
(STAMMERS) Why would you
wanna do that?
Because that's what we do.
We're warriors who serve
the good and light
in the universe.
Sometimes we rescue,
sometimes we guide.
Think of us
as big-hearted.
MRS. WHICH: Indeed.
Listen, Meg. We must find him
as soon as we can.
Are you up for it?
I bet she says no.
What?
Hmm?
No.
Hmm. No.
No, yes. No.
Yes, I'm going.
Of course, I am.
And we know I'm up for it.
And Calvin already said
he'd come.
I did?
I did.
Then let's go!
Mom. Wait.
We gotta get Mom.
MRS. WHATSIT: We'll get
your mother later. I promise.
Don't worry, Meg.
Tessering is almost nearly
perfectly natural.
Tessering?
"Almost"?
MEG: What's happening?
Wait. No, no. Charles Wallace,
don't go over there.
CHARLES WALLACE:
No time to waste, Meg.
Come on, Mrs. Whatsit!
MRS. WHICH: You just have
to find the right frequency...
and have faith
in who you are.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Let's find your father.
Shall we?
(SOFTLY) Tessering.
Tessering.
(GASPS)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Is this really happening?
We did it, Meg. We actually,
really, very much so tessered!
(WHIMPERS)
Why does my whole body hurt?
We were in your backyard
and now...
(MEG GROANING)
It's real.
MRS. WHICH: Let's make sure
she's all right.
- (THUDS)
- Ow!
Yes, she's fine.
Whatsit,
we don't kick people.
Oh, I didn't know.
"The foot feels the foot
when it feels the ground."
Buddha, Nepali.
(GROANING SOFTLY)
(ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING)
CHARLES WALLACE:
New word for the day.
Luminous.
This is my favorite planet
in the entire galaxy.
They call it Uriel.
We think your father
tessered here.
Don't be shy.
Go ahead, look around.
Yes!
(MRS. WHATSIT LAUGHS)
(CHEERFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
- (LAUGHING)
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
MRS. WHATSIT: Come on, Meg.
Go ahead.
(WHOOPING AND EXCLAIMING)
(SCREAMS AND LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS)
(FLOWERS CHATTERING)
Whoa.
You should talk to them.
Everyone knows that flowers
are the best gossipers
in the entire universe.
You should show them
a picture of your father
and ask them
if they've seen him.
How are we gonna
understand each other?
At least try.
Seriously, Charles Wallace,
I'm underwhelmed.
CHARLES WALLACE:
Keep the faith, Mrs. Whatsit.
See, I told you
this was too hard for her.
I don't know why we brought
her in the first place.
Whatsit, she can hear you.
Oh.
Oh, man.
Let's just concentrate
on finding her father.
(MEG SIGHS)
(FLOWERS CONTINUE CHATTERING)
This is our father.
(FLOWERS CHATTERING)
Can you help us
find him, please?
Please.
(FLOWERS CHATTERING)
CALVIN: I can't tell
what they're saying.
MRS. WHATSIT: I can.
They speak color.
Oh, he did?
(LAUGHS) Really?
Oh. You don't say.
(FLOWERS CONTINUE CHATTERING)
Yep! He was here!
They saw him tesser here.
But he continued to explore,
they say.
Somewhere in that direction.
Let's go!
I'll get changed.
MEG: Changed?
CALVIN: Do you, uh,
need some privacy?
(CHUCKLES)
No, this is fine.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Whoa, Mrs. Whatsit,
humans don't just get naked.
Patience, sir.
I'm not finished yet.
"Dang."
Tucker, American.
(CHUCKLES)
(ALL GRUNT)
BOTH: Whoa.
No!
Wow!
(FLOWERS CHATTERING)
(CALVIN YELLS)
(KIDS SCREAM AND WHOOP)
- (MEG SCREAMS)
- CALVIN: This is wild!
MEG: Whoo!
One, two, three.
Whoa! (WHOOPING)
I'm flying!
(MEG AND CHARLES WALLACE
WHOOPING)
MEG: Put your arms out!
(LAUGHS)
CALVIN: How are we actually
flying right now?
MEG: Well, it's a phenomenon
associated with
continuum fluid mechanics.
It's called lift! (LAUGHS)
(RUMBLING AND GROWLING)
(VOICES WHISPER INDISTINCTLY)
MEG: What is that?
CALVIN: Whoa!
(CALVIN SCREAMING)
Calvin!
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
MRS. WHICH:
My friends of light,
please assist
our young friend.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(FLOWERS CHATTERING)
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
CALVIN: I'm all right.
- BOTH: Calvin!
- CALVIN: I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
(CHARLES WALLACE GRUNTS)
MRS. WHICH: Whatsit,
those from Earth
need more help than most.
You know this...
You could have
prepared them better.
We must help them
stay focused on light
when darkness is present.
I mean, I'm trying.
But they're human.
They're very limited.
MRS. WHICH:
Well, tell me you at least
found something up there.
MRS. WHATSIT:
Unfortunately, no.
Their father's moved on.
And that thing
got in our way.
It's spreading fast,
Mrs. Which.
What is that thing?
It's called Camazotz.
(FAINT GROWLING)
Home to a purely evil energy.
Known simply as The IT.
Evil?
But, like,
what kind of evil?
How many kinds of evil
- do you need?
- MRS. WHICH: Whatsit.
(MOUTHING) Okay.
An evil
that's actively spreading
throughout the universe.
So, as we continue on...
we must avoid it
at all costs...
and focus
on finding your father.
But we don't know
where he's gone.
What do we do?
"Love looks not with the
eyes but with the mind."
Shakespeare, British.
Oh, yes, a seer!
We should go visit
one of the seers.
They'll narrow
the search for us.
What's a seer?
A moderate visionary.
An occasional motivator
of insight. Hit or miss.
But I know
a very cute one.
I mean a good one.
That sounds
sort of promising.
Misses, grab a child.
Our journey continues.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MEG GROANING SOFTLY)
She's intact.
She's fine.
Fine? After that
beautiful tesser?
She should be glorious.
Everyone else is glorious.
She makes
absolutely no sense.
I absolutely do not understand
that girl whatsoever.
Okay, it's over here.
Wait till you see it.
It's so cool.
CALVIN: The seer lives here?
MEG: Wow. You're our size.
The three of you...
are beautiful.
Thank you.
And so are you.
Where are we?
Orion.
Home of the Happy Medium.
CHARLES WALLACE: So this guy
is your boyfriend?
MRS. WHATSIT:
Well, when you're
over a billion years old,
you don't really need labels.
Why do I have to
be in pain?
- Instead of...
- Glorious?
(CHUCKLES)
You don't tesser well.
In what way?
Because I don't feel or see
anything when we tesser.
And you won't
until you become...
one with the universe
and yourself.
As it is, it seems like...
you don't even want
to return as yourself.
Oh...
Is there any way
I can return as somebody else?
That I might like?
Do you realize...
how many events
and choices...
that had to occur since
the birth of the universe...
leading to
the making of you...
just exactly
the way you are?
I guess I never really
thought about that.
MRS. WHICH:
Maybe now's the time
to start thinking about it.
(EXOTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
We are here!
CALVIN: You can do it, Meg.
You just need balance.
- (CHARLES WALLACE WHOOPS)
- CALVIN: Whoa!
This is awesome!
MEG: No, not awesome!
MRS. WHATSIT: Yoo-hoo!
Anybody home?
- Whoo-hoo!
- Nice balance, Mrs. Who.
Oh, no, no, no.
Finally, a little color.
(MEG EXCLAIMS)
- (MEG YELPING)
- (METALLIC CLATTERING)
(WHIMPERING) Whoa!
HAPPY MEDIUM: (SHOUTING)
Who's there?
Uninvited guest
is very unsettling!
I do not like visitation!
Whatsit.
I really need a doorbell.
Whoo! Well, you obviously
don't understand
the importance of balance...
of moderation...
(WHIMPERS)
of the Happy Medium.
You sound like my mother.
Is your mother a baritone?
How's it going, Happy?
Everything's fine, Whatsit.
You look nice.
- MRS. WHATSIT: I do?
- I like your outfit.
It's like a person outfit.
Oh, thank you.
You look like a person.
Thank you. You look
pretty okay as well.
Thank you. Earth tones.
We need your insight.
We are looking
for a man...
who's lost
in the universe.
My father.
Dr. Murry.
Handsome fellow.
(HAPPY MEDIUM SIGHS)
How am I supposed
to say no?
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
Okay.
Center yourself.
One foot up, please.
Okay.
Now, very little
is up to moi.
All right? Your energies
will affect what we see.
So, core in,
spine long...
- (INHALES SHARPLY)
- ...shoulders down...
buttocks taut.
Close your eyes.
You're kidding.
Do I look like I'm kidding?
Very much so.
- A little.
- I'm not.
I'm not.
(SIGHS) Let's try this
again. Now...
relax the face...
close your eyes...
and open your memories.
Think about your father.
No!
I can't, I can't.
I'm sorry, I can't.
- (SIGHS)
- MEG: I'm sorry, but...
I really just... I really
don't understand...
how thinking about him
is going to help us find him.
All I do
is think about him.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Which,
but I think we need
to show her something.
She needs to understand
what's possible.
She needs to know
what's at stake.
Close your eyes.
See with mine.
This time...
don't look away.
The IT's home
may be Camazotz...
but through darkness,
The IT's reach
spreads far beyond.
Even to your own planet.
The only thing
in the universe...
that travels
faster than light...
is the darkness.
The IT invades
the place inside of us
where hope and joy lives...
We're happy to announce
the promotion
of one of our current
faculty members...
to be our new principal.
That faculty member
is three-time science teacher
of the year...
James Jenkins.
Come on up,
Principal Jenkins.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
MRS. WHICH: ...replaces it
with jealousy...
and judgment...
pain...
and despair.
What's up, Pops?
How you doing tonight?
Hey, man, don't do that.
- What you got up in here?
- What are you doing, man?
Man, do you know how I work
for this stuff?
Hey, man.
84...
82...
82?
I mean, are you even trying
or are you just an idiot?
Because if this is the best
you can do, it's pathetic!
You look at me
when I'm talking to you!
This is pathetic!
MRS. WHICH: You see?
This is what The IT does.
One person at a time...
until fear takes over.
Fear turns to rage.
And rage leads to violence.
And then
there's a tipping point.
If we do not act soon...
darkness will fall
across the universe.
We...
we're in search of warriors
who can fight The IT...
and who can
bring hope back.
Your father.
My father?
- (RUMBLING)
- (YELPS)
Be a warrior.
Can you?
I'll try.
Your father sounds
like a good man.
How about we find him?
Good. Okay.
(MEG WHIMPERING)
Good, good, good.
- MEG: Yeah.
- HAPPY MEDIUM: Okay.
Now, we're grounded.
We're centered, right?
- Okay, yeah.
- Okay.
You can do this. Okay?
You're choosing not to.
(QUIETLY) But what if...
(SIGHS)
What if he doesn't
wanna be found?
It's okay to fear
the answers, Meg.
But you can't avoid them.
Trust me.
You don't wanna
end up like me,
a weirdo with a beard
living in a cave.
Your father
didn't forget you.
You're too precious.
All right, you ready?
Mmm. Yeah.
Center yourself.
Where is he?
Okay.
Now we're
getting a vision.
Okay.
(HUMMING)
(BABY GURGLING)
MRS. MURRY:
♪ Flower
♪ of the universe
♪ A child of mine
(MACHINERY BEEPING)
♪ Flower
♪ of the universe ♪
(MAGIC BY SIA PLAYING)
(MACHINE TRILLING)
(RAPID BEEPING)
MR. MURRY: Love.
That's the frequency.
HAPPY MEDIUM:
That's it, Meg.
He started in Uriel.
Then he went to Ixchel.
Keep going, Meg.
Oh! There's Aunt Beast!
Oh, no,
he's going to Camazotz.
No!
- Whoa, whoa.
- (WHISPERS) No.
MRS. WHATSIT:
I'm so sorry, Meg.
The IT got to him
before we could.
We thought he could
join the fight,
but now we need
to fight for him.
So, how are we gonna
get my father off Camazotz?
We can't tesser
to Camazotz.
We can only tesser
where we find light...
for we are light.
Camazotz is all darkness.
This is no longer a search.
It's a rescue.
We must go back to Earth...
speak to your mother...
regroup.
No, no, no. I cannot leave
here without my father.
It's for the best, Meg.
We have to make a plan.
Please. Please!
I've come all this way.
We're too close to finding
him to turn back!
MRS. WHO:
"Planning is essential."
Churchill, British.
No, no, no. Please!
He's running out of time.
No, we cannot!
We have to save him.
We can't give up.
There must be a way!
Don't leave him!
We can't!
Dad!
(VOICES WHISPERING
INDISTINCTLY)
MEG: Where are we?
Where are the Misses?
CALVIN: This place
feels weird.
CHARLES WALLACE:
Look! The Misses.
MRS. WHO: Thank goodness
you made it.
I was so worried.
Are you okay,
are you hurt at all?
CALVIN: We're okay.
Am I losing my senses or did
you just use your own words?
She's weakening.
As am I and Mrs. Whatsit.
MEG: Wait,
what's wrong?
Where... Where are we?
Camazotz.
Your will to find your father
took over our tesser...
and re-directed it from Earth.
We must leave this planet.
And we do not have
the strength
to take you with us.
MRS. WHICH: We can
barely tesser ourselves.
You must continue on
without us.
You must find your father.
And know that
you're going to be tested
every step of the way.
You'll encounter things
you think you know
but you don't.
Here is the place
to be suspicious, okay?
We're fading.
Can't we at least leave them
with something to help them?
Yes. Gifts.
I love gifts.
MRS. WHO: They work well
in a moment of peril...
for they see
that which is enfolded.
Not gone, just enfolded.
Meg. Trouble,
problematic Meg.
To you I give
the gift of your faults.
You're welcome.
You do know my faults
are the bad qualities, right?
Are they really? Hmm.
Well then, you're all set.
My gift is my command.
Stay together.
Don't let anyone
separate you.
This is a planet
of many faces...
run by one cruel
and vicious mind.
The IT desires
our strongest lights.
Do not give in.
We're going now.
Be careful.
"When shall we three
meet again?
"In thunder,
lightning or in rain?"
Shakespeare.
MRS. WHATSIT: Keep going.
We'll be watching.
(VOICES WHISPERING
INDISTINCTLY)
(RUMBLING)
(WHIMPERING)
MEG: What's happening?
Wait. Where's
Charles Wallace?
He was just here!
(MEG STAMMERS)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERS CONTINUE)
Charles Wallace!
- Charles Wallace!
(FAINT SCREAMING)
MRS. WHATSIT:
There's danger here.
He's safe over the wall.
Wait at the stream.
(BRANCHES SNAPPING)
MRS. WHICH: Get to the wall.
MEG: What is that?
MRS. WHICH:
Get to the wall!
MEG: Run!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
MEG: It's getting closer!
Go, go, go! Faster!
There's the wall!
We gotta get
over the wall!
(SCREAMING)
Run faster!
- Faster is not gonna help!
- Faster!
(WIND WHOOSHES)
(BOTH PANTING)
(ROARING)
Calvin!
Look, look!
See what it's doing?
It's picking up stuff
and throwing it over!
Range is at fifty,
I don't know. Velocity...
We won't make it that way!
No, Meg!
We have to keep going!
This is the only way!
Do you trust me?
I trust you!
Okay.
Run, Calvin, run!
(GROWLING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
How did you do that whole
thing with the log?
It's just a physics thing.
The classic slingshot maneuver.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Just a physics thing?
You have no idea
how incredible you are...
do you?
You're the one
who came with me.
You didn't
have to do that.
You're the one who
doesn't have to be here...
but you are.
You're the one who's...
I like your hair.
Thank you.
CHARLES WALLACE:
Meg! Calvin!
You made it!
I couldn't see you!
I couldn't tell!
I saw houses down there.
Come on!
CHARLES WALLACE:
Is Daddy down here?
MEG: (SIGHS) I hope so.
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
I smell food.
Like good,
roasted food.
Who else is starving?
(DOG CONTINUES BARKING)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(THUDDING)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
I can't stand the sound.
The rhythm. It hurts.
Come here.
Cover your ears.
(THUDDING STOPS)
CAMAZOTZ WOMEN:
Darling, time for dinner!
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
Are you lost, children?
I bet you're hungry,
and in need of comfort.
I have roasts...
and potatoes,
and cakes of all sorts.
I could eat.
Um...
Uh... (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
No.
Thanks. We're good.
- No.
- Cakes of all sorts!
MEG: No!
Trust no one, remember?
(WARRIOR BY CHLOE X HALLE
PLAYING)
CHARLES WALLACE:
It's changing again.
CALVIN: Is this
still Camazotz?
MEG: They said it was
a planet of many faces.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Do you think this person would
mind if I ate all their food?
MEG: Probably.
MAN: Hey! I'm right here!
I'm right here!
Hello!
Hello! Friends!
Hello, friends. Hey.
How are you guys?
Who are you?
MAN: Oh, me? I'm nobody.
But you can call me Red.
And you are...?
Oh, I'm Calvin. This is Meg.
And this is Charles Wallace.
RED: Oh!
You're Alex Murry's kids,
aren't you?
You know my father?
Yeah, yeah! I totally
know your father.
He's a great guy. I just saw
him a couple minutes ago.
Where?
I mean, we've been
looking for him.
Can you take us to him?
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, no, no, no.
Yeah. Almost. He should be
done working pretty soon.
He's kind of a busy guy.
You know, bit of a workaholic.
But I don't have
to tell you that. Right?
You know what?
Guys, sit down. Sit down.
Relax. There's nothing
to do here.
Nothing to worry about.
Are you guys hungry?
Everything's taken care of.
In total. Without options
or alternatives.
Hmm.
You guys hungry?
Well, I'll brave it for us.
(SIGHS)
What's wrong, little guy?
It tastes like...
like sand.
Does it?
I don't taste any sand.
Try mine.
It's all sand!
Ha!
I thought you were like me,
Charles Wallace.
I thought you were special.
And you are.
You passed the test.
It's as simple as that.
Simple as twice one is two.
Twice two is four.
Twice three is six.
Twice four is eight.
RED AND CHARLES WALLACE:
Twice five is 10.
Twice six is 12.
Twice seven is 14.
What are you doing?
RED AND CHARLES WALLACE:
Twice eight is 16.
CHARLES WALLACE: Uh, we'd
like to see our father now.
You got it.
I'll take you right to him.
Charles Wallace.
Take my hand now.
Please.
No, thanks.
RED: Oh, and, Meg...
Hey.
Thanks for everything.
You brought him right to us.
No! Stop!
My little brother!
- CALVIN: Charles Wallace!
- MEG: Please!
Charles Wallace!
MEG: Move!
(MEG GRUNTING)
(VOICES WHISPERING
INDISTINCTLY)
Well, that was fun.
Welcome to Central
Central Intelligence.
Get away from him!
Relax. Don't fight it.
It'll make it much easier,
I promise.
Please, Charles Wallace.
Please. He is dangerous.
What has he done to you?
Shut up, Meg!
Yeah. Shut up, Meg.
CHARLES WALLACE: Sorry, Red.
Meg's always been a problem.
She's quite an aberration,
you know.
Yeah, I can tell.
But aberrations
are far more interesting.
Don't you think,
Charles Wallace?
That's so like you to try
to come to the rescue,
isn't it, Calvin?
Always so helpful.
Overly cheery.
Trying to please everyone.
Hoping to convince them...
that you're not just a burden
to your father and your world.
Pathetic.
That's not why I do it.
Of course, it is!
Why else would you come
on this ridiculous
journey with people
you barely know?
Now that's enough,
Charles Wallace!
You need to stop!
It's enough when The IT
says it's enough!
Sit. I can take it
from here.
No doubt about that,
little guy.
Would you like to meet The IT?
That happy sadist.
Not especially.
Watch your tone!
I'm sorry.
We're just here
to see Dad. Remember?
Your dad.
Flower of the universe.
Child of mine.
No.
I think you mean
your dad...
who left you...
who'd rather be anywhere else
in the universe than with you.
Why would you even
want to see him?
(SCOFFS)
Oh, well.
I wish I could
take you to him.
But I can't.
He's gone.
He's not gone.
(CHUCKLES)
You're right.
He's not gone. And
yet, I don't see him.
(SOFTLY) He's...
He's not gone.
Just enfolded.
What is it?
What do you see?
MEG: Topological order.
Um, fractal dimension.
Ooh. Clever.
That she is.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(FLOWER OF THE UNIVERSE
BY SADE PLAYING)
Oh.
♪ They come to see
the fire burning
♪ In your heart
♪ They want to witness
(MEG GRUNTS)
♪ This love from the start
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
♪ They hear you
when you cry
♪ This love is far and wide
♪ When you smile,
the stars align
♪ Flower of the universe
♪ Child of mine
♪ Ooh ♪
Meg.
(SOBS)
- Meg.
- Dad, it's...
(VOICE BREAKING)
(SOBBING)
- Dad.
- Meg.
(MR. MURRY GASPING)
Dad.
Is this a trick?
A dream?
It's me, Dad. It's me.
I missed you so much.
My beautiful Meg.
I missed you
every second of every day.
Let me look at you.
Daddy. (CHUCKLES)
Hi, Dad.
How long
have I been gone, baby?
(VOICE BREAKING)
How long have I been gone?
(STAMMERING)
Four years.
You left four years ago.
No.
No. No. No.
No, that can't be. No.
No. I didn't.
No, I didn't leave you, baby.
I wouldn't.
I would never leave you,
sweetheart.
(STAMMERS)
I've been trapped here.
How did you get here?
It's dangerous here, Meglet.
You can't be here.
How did you get here?
You called out for us.
We came for you.
We're here
to bring you home, Dad.
"We"?
My friend Calvin and...
Charles Wallace
came with me.
Charles Wallace.
My baby boy is here?
(STUTTERS) Where is he?
Is he okay?
The IT has done
something to him.
Charles Wallace.
Is that you, son?
Son?
Depends on who you ask.
Let me get
a good look at you.
(BOTH SCREAM)
(MEG GROANS)
- CALVIN: You all right?
- MEG: Yeah.
MR. MURRY: Charles Wallace.
You don't look like
how I pictured you.
I'm underwhelmed.
Charles Wallace.
Hey.
What has The IT done
to you?
The IT has shown me
my potential.
I can see the weaknesses
of any soul.
Like, take your soul.
So desperate
to matter in the universe...
you'd abandon your own family
and never look back.
That's not true,
I swear.
CHARLES WALLACE:
Doesn't matter.
Let's go meet The IT.
- No. No.
- CHARLES WALLACE: Yes, yes.
Come on, now.
(SING-SONG)
Don't make me drag you.
Okay. How about
you just take me?
No.
- Meg. Meg. Take me.
- MEG: Dad, no. No!
No.
(WHISPERS) I have to
do this, sweetheart.
CHARLES WALLACE:
We don't want you!
We've already had you!
- (GRUNTS)
- (RUMBLING)
(MEG GRUNTS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
MR. MURRY: Stop it!
Grab onto it!
Let us go!
Stop clawing the walls.
The IT's waiting for you.
MR. MURRY:
You're hurting them!
And you're just
being impolite!
MR. MURRY: Stop!
(SHRIEKING)
MR. MURRY: Stop! Please!
Don't do this, please!
Please, don't do this!
This is all your fault,
Mr. Murry!
MR. MURRY: Can you
hear me? Meg!
Meg!
Meg, wake up, baby!
Resist. Resist, Meg.
Don't give in to the darkness.
Don't give in! Meglet...
Meglet, wake up.
Wake up! Wake up! Meg!
Meg! Wake up!
Come on. Hold on.
Hold on, come on. Hold on!
Breathe.
Breathe, Meg, breathe!
CHARLES WALLACE:
Let her go. Let her give in.
Give up.
This is what you get when you
put yourself before family!
Please. Charles Wallace,
I'll do anything you want.
Charles Wallace
isn't here right now.
(VOICE DISTORTING)
And even if he were...
you're powerless against us.
You have nothing
that we want.
Except for her.
No.
Forgive me.
Meg! Meg, wake up. Wake up!
(MEG COUGHING)
Come on. Here.
You brought light
back to me, Meglet.
Maybe I can tesser again.
Hold on.
Hold on, stay with me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
It's working!
It's working.
Meg.
Meg. Meg, baby. Meg.
We're going back home.
Just a little longer.
Charles Wallace.
Just breathe. Just breathe.
The darkness has him.
We can't take him with us.
If we don't leave now,
we'll be trapped here forever.
How could you? How...
Meg, we have to.
The IT is gonna destroy us.
- It's gonna destroy you, Meg.
- How could you leave him?
I'm gonna come back
for him, Meg.
How could you
leave him again?
I have to. I have to.
I can't lose
both of my children.
MEG: No, don't leave!
I won't leave him!
I won't leave my brother!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
I won't tesser without him!
(WHISPERING) Charles
Wallace, I'm coming.
(MEG GASPS)
(WINGS FLUTTERING)
(GROANING SOFTLY)
THE IT: Welcome.
You made the right decision
to join us.
Don't you feel better?
You look better.
I've known you
for a long time.
It's good
to finally have you here.
Charles Wallace.
Charles Wallace!
(LOW GROWLING)
Hi, Meg.
We knew you'd be back.
We gotta say...
nothing we love more
than stupid courage.
"We"?
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Where are my manners?
Meg, meet The IT!
(RUMBLING)
MEG: No!
CHARLES WALLACE:
Welcome to the darkest mind
in the universe.
Extraordinary,
don't you think?
That's one word for it.
We could really use
a gal like you.
So, what do you say?
You wanna join us?
No thanks.
(GRUNTS)
THE IT: Take a good look
at her.
She's a better version
of you.
She's sure to be popular.
Great student.
Principal Jenkins
is going to love her.
And Calvin
probably will, too.
(SCOFFING)
She doesn't just have to
live in your imagination...
I can make her real.
CHARLES WALLACE: You said
you wanted to come back
as someone else.
Join us, and I can make you
just like her.
She's perfect.
- No!
- (SCREAMING)
You better watch yourself...
or we'll do to you
what you did to her.
We don't care
whose sister you are!
(GRUNTS)
We're your only option,
and we're starting
to not want you!
A feeling you're very
used to, actually.
No one in school likes you.
Your father left you
without so much as a goodbye.
Every bad thing you think
about yourself is true.
MRS. WHO:
"The wound is the place
"where the light enters you."
MRS. WHICH: Be a warrior.
Can you?
MRS. WHATSIT: To you I give
the gift of your faults.
MEG: I know my faults.
How I'm messy...
uncoordinated...
I don't trust anyone.
And most days,
I hate myself.
I'm impulsive...
and suspicious.
(PANTS)
And yet...
you love me.
- (DISTORTED) What?
- Don't you, Charles Wallace?
- No!
- Shut up!
(NORMAL VOICE) It's okay.
Few understand
just how weak light is.
Few are willing
to accept the fact
that love is just a word.
It's an empty,
meaningless word.
MEG: You can hurt me
when I say I love you,
but I'll love you anyway!
And you love me!
That's why you make milk
for me on stormy nights.
That's why you check in
on me during recess.
(GRUNTS AND PANTS)
That's why you wanted to
find Daddy, to make me happy!
(GRUNTS)
That's why the Misses
took a chance on me.
Because they felt your love.
(WHIMPERS)
And you should love me because
I deserve to be loved!
(DISTORTED)
Stop it! Just, stop it!
I love you! I love you,
Charles Wallace! I love you!
Stop it!
(MEG SCREAMS)
(GROWLING)
(PANTING)
Please...
I love you, Biscuits.
(DISTORTED) No love!
THE IT: Only darkness!
CHARLES WALLACE:
(NORMAL VOICE) Meg!
Meg.
Meg, wake up.
Come on, Meg.
Please.
♪ Flower...
♪ of the universe
(CRYING SOFTLY)
♪ Child of mine ♪
(SNIFFLES)
CHARLES WALLACE: Whoa.
The Misses.
They came back.
MRS. WHO: Charles Wallace,
your light has returned.
MRS. WHICH: Meg, you did it.
MEG: (CHUCKLES) I tried.
Well, I knew you could
do it all along.
I never doubted you
for a second.
MEG: Well...
I used my faults,
like you said.
Such beautiful faults.
I'm so proud of you, Meg.
The universe is bright tonight
because of you.
You weakened The IT...
and you've given your Earth
and everyone on it
a real chance.
MRS. WHICH:
You should be proud.
Some of our best warriors
have come from Earth.
Einstein, Curie, Gandhi.
MRS. WHATSIT: Austen. Kahlo.
Schindler.
MRS. WHO: Nelson Mandela.
Maya Angelou.
And now, Meg Murry.
Me?
(SCOFFS) What?
All those who are willing
to face the darkness...
and bring the best
of themselves to the light...
for the world.
This is where we leave you...
to become warriors on Earth.
MRS. WHO:
Now, Meg, it's time...
for you to start the tesser
for all of us...
and make your way back home.
What?
Me?
You want me
to start the tesser?
"Tomorrow, there'll be
more of us."
Miranda, American.
(JUBILANT MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHOOSHING)
MRS. WHATSIT:
Goodbye, my loves.
MRS. WHICH: Farewell,
my little warriors.
MRS. WHO:
Until we meet again.
CHARLES WALLACE:
See you at home!
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHING)
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Meg, you did it!
You absolutely,
gloriously tessered.
Daddy!
(SOBBING)
Hey.
You did it.
I sure did.
Mommy!
(SOFTLY) Hi. Uh...
Are you okay?
I'm okay, Dad.
Good.
I'm sorry, Meg.
I, uh...
I wanted to shake hands
with the universe.
But I should've been
holding yours.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(DOG BARKS)
Charles Wallace?
What are you doing outside?
Mommy!
(LAUGHS)
Well, well, okay.
Thanks. What's going on?
(MRS. MURRY LAUGHING)
Wait.
Am I asleep?
Am I dreaming?
MEG: No...
you're not sleeping.
And it's important
you know that.
Why?
Because Meg
brought you something.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm so, so sorry.
How...
- Where...
- Your calculations.
They gave us the universe.
(CHUCKLING)
I think
I'm gonna go home.
You sure?
Yeah.
There are some things
I need to say to my dad.
Maybe now I can
finally say them.
It's funny
how it took a trip
around the universe
to get me there.
Can I call you later?
Yeah.
(MEG GRUNTS)
I knew you could do it.
MEG: Love you.
Always.
- MR. MURRY: Hey!
- CHARLES WALLACE: Daddy, I have
a new word for the day.
Wanna hear it?
MR. MURRY: Absolutely.
CHARLES WALLACE: Home.
Thank you.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(JOYOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(I BELIEVE
BY DJ KHALED PLAYING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
(FLOWER OF THE UNIVERSE
BY SADE PLAYING)
♪ Ooh
♪ They come to see
the fire burning
♪ In your heart
♪ They want to witness
♪ This love
♪ From the start
♪ They hear when you cry
♪ This love is far and wide
♪ When you smile
The stars align
♪ Flower of the universe
♪ Child of mine
♪ When you sleep
♪ Softly the angels come
♪ Like diamonds
♪ Like my love
♪ They want to know it's true
♪ There's someone in the world
♪ Lovely as you
♪ They hear you when you cry
♪ This love is far and wide
♪ When you smile
the stars align
♪ Flower of the universe
♪ Child of mine ♪
(WARRIOR BY CHLOE X HALLE
PLAYING)