[CHANTING CONTINUES]
[♪♪♪]
♪ Do you wanna be
The President? ♪
♪ Or walk on the moon?
Play at a stadium? ♪
♪ Or would you rather
Dye your hair ♪
♪ Green, purple, or blue? ♪
♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ The world is your canvas
Do what you wanna do ♪
♪ We are who we are ♪
♪ We'll rise to the top ♪
♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ Get ready, 'cause we're
Coming fast, ready or not ♪
♪ Call me crazy, say my head's
Too high up in the clouds ♪
♪ It will make a difference ♪
♪ Yes, I can do anything
I put my mind to ♪
♪ Superstars come in
Many colors ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ We're always dreaming ♪
♪ Superstars come in
Many colors ♪
♪ We are who we are ♪
♪ We love who we love ♪
♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ Get ready 'cause we're
Coming fast, ready or not ♪
♪ Call me crazy, say my head's
Too high up in the clouds ♪
♪ It will make a difference ♪
♪ Yes, I can do anything
I put my mind to ♪
♪ Superstars come in
Many colors ♪
[CROWD CHEERING]
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ We're always dreaming ♪
♪ Superstars come in
Many colors ♪
[REAGAN SIGHS]
[IMITATES EXPLOSION]
[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS]
Today is the big day, Alex.
[♪♪♪]
Think I'm ready.
I think.
But just in case, from
one Number 13 to another,
got any tips for me?
Heh, heh.
LOGAN:
Are you talking to
your poster?
You want a tip?
Push-ups.
One.
Two. Three.
[SCOFFS]
Four. Five. Six. Seven.
LOGAN [DISTANTLY]:
Eight. Nine. Ten. Eleven.
You can stop now.
LOGAN:
Thirteen. Fourteen.
[REAGAN SIGHS]
Today's the big day!
Yes, it is. The Michigan coach
is coming to meet
Logan today after school.
They're talking scholarship.
Yeah, okay, right, but aren't
you forgetting something else?
Is UCLA coming today, too? Uh...
No, no, no, not about Logan,
- or Logan's football, about my...
- [PHONE RINGS]
ANNE:
Excuse me.
Has anyone seen my keys?
Go for Joe.
Hello, Coach.
- ANNE: What?
- [MOUTHS] Alabama.
[WHISPERS]
Yes!
JOE:
Yes, sir?
REAGAN:
Can I get a ride today?
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Uh... Ooh. Hold on, honey.
ANNE [IN NORMAL VOICE]:
Hello?
Clemson.
- Uh, yes.
- Thank you very much, sir.
ANNE:
Thank you so much
for calling.
I'm gonna go move to Alaska
and join a cult.
ANNE:
Oh, yes, we are so proud of him.
He's a great kid.
JOE:
Yes. Absolutely, coach.
Looking forward to it.
REAGAN:
You're gonna
ship my stuff, right?
LOGAN:
Seventy-six, 77, 78.
- [SIGHS]
- LOGAN: Seventy-nine.
[BELL RINGS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
And they totally
forgot about my tryout.
Well your brother kinda
is the best quarterback
this city's ever had.
Et tu, Grace?
Kidding.
I know something
that'll cheer you up.
Have you seen the cute boy
that just moved here?
And I heard he plays soccer.
Hi, Ben!
GRACE:
Ugh, Claire Bishop.
That girl has
to have everything.
Good luck today.
You've got this, Regs.
[CHAIN CLATTERING]
What? Uh.
Oh, no, no, no.
You gotta be kidding me.
[CHAIN CLATTERING]
[♪♪♪]
OZ:
For those of you
who don't know,
I'm John Osbourne.
Coach Oz.
The great and powerful.
But with me, there's no man
behind the curtain.
In your daughter's soccer world,
I'm all powerful.
All knowing.
I wish I could say
welcome to Crush tryouts,
but I'd be lying.
Today's tryouts are a welcome
to a small number of you.
And a wish you goodbye to most.
Even if you played for me since
you were 6 years old,
today you could get cut.
I do not play favorites.
Let me repeat that,
[CLAIRE CLEARS THROAT]
Hey, Claire!
There's my little champion.
Hope we get to see
that kick today. Yeah.
[REAGAN PANTING]
[CHAIN CLATTERING]
I'm not trying to be rude,
I'm just simply stating fact.
We are the number one
girls' soccer club in the state.
We have won the Diamond Cup
three years in a row,
s-so simple math states
that you, you, you...
Not you, girl.
You, you, you or you,
are not Crush material.
Enough with the pleasantries.
Let's get started.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
Yellow brick road time.
Munchkins over there.
Let's go! Pretend like you wanna
play something! Maybe soccer!
[♪♪♪]
OZ:
Waiting to see something
good, ladies.
[CHAIN CLATTERING]
OZ:
You call that soccer?
You need to do better
out there.
All right,
line up for the next drill.
Winners always line up.
[PANTING]
You're late.
REAGAN:
Yeah, I know. I know.
I'm sorry. Um.
My bike chain came off, and I...
- [BLOWS WHISTLE]
- Mm.
That's an excuse.
I don't like excuses.
Y-Yes, yes, yes, sir.
Sorry, sir.
Although, um...
It's not so much an excuse
as it is what happened, and...
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
What position are you?
I'll play anywhere.
But usually striker.
[IN UNISON]
Ooo.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
This is not how
we play Crush soccer!
In fact, this is not how
you play any kinda soccer.
You might as well be playing
baseball or basketball.
That's enough of y'all.
You don't even line up
like Crush soccer.
Hey, Claire!
Focus out there.
Show her who
the real striker is.
[♪♪♪]
Ugh! Ow! Uh!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
Uh, Claire, it was great,
but save it for the game.
Did you see that?
My bad, coach.
I was just trying to
play aggressive like
you always tell us. Not dirty.
Good job.
[GRUNTS]
Sorry, slipped.
Striker.
MOTHER:
It's okay.
There's always next time.
- Hey.
- [IN UNISON] Number 4.
Kids didn't stand a chance.
All right, yes!
My little champion right there.
TOM:
She'll get you another
Diamond Cup, coach.
Let's go, sweetie.
Thanks for coming out.
Keep working hard.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
Sorry, th-that's it?
I've seen enough.
You barely watched me.
Is that my fault?
My bike chain didn't break.
Uh.
That... That's not fair.
Life isn't fair.
Haven't you heard that sports
teaches life lessons?
Yeah, but I think you're
applying it wrong here.
I doubt it.
I've been Coach of the Year
three years running.
Okay, all I want is a chance
to play on your team.
Just... Just a chance.
I'm sorry.
I think that ship has sailed.
Ships sail at 13?
OZ:
In club soccer, they do.
If you were someone,
I would have known you by now.
My girls here who play club
have been playing for me
since they were 8, 9 years old.
Alex Morgan didn't
play club until she...
Yeah, Alex Morgan didn't play
club until she was 13.
Every girl who gets cut clings
to that story like a life vest.
But playing for Crush
is my dream.
Sometimes dreams die.
Life lesson number two.
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
[CHAIN CLATTERING]
[REAGAN WINCING]
REAGAN:
Ow.
[EXHALES]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[♪♪♪]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
JOE:
I can't thank you enough
for being here.
This is just an honor, coach.
Logan has worked so hard
for this moment.
Uh, football is his life.
I hear that you played some ball
yourself, Mr. Wills.
Yeah, until I got hurt
senior year of high school.
Uh, so, that was it.
Sometimes dreams die.
Ahem. But so close.
Anyways,
it's not about me anymore.
Go back, full scholarship?
Full scholarship.
JOE:
Wow. I mean, I just wanna
say thank you, coach.
Thank you. I-I'm gonna
keep saying thank you
until you get tired of me
saying thank you.
I've called everywhere.
And I know the deadline
to sign up for AYSO passed,
but I was wondering
if there's still a spot.
No. No, I... I understand.
Okay. Bye.
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
I guess ships do sail at 13.
[SCOFFS]
Logan's right.
I'm talking to a poster.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTING]
Why won't this come off?
Come on!
[SQUEALS, GRUNTS]
ALEX:
Hello?
Reagan.
Are you all right?
Man, that was a bad fall.
Can you even hear me?
Are you okay?
[♪♪♪]
Reagan, are you all right?
[GASPS]
Wha...?
Mom! I need to go to
the doctor right now!
I hit my head really hard,
and now I'm seeing things!
You're not seeing things.
And now I'm hearing things!
It's okay.
You're just hallucinating.
You're not hallucinating.
I can prove it.
My name is Alex Morgan,
and my birthday is July 2nd.
My parents are Mike and Pam,
and my sisters...
That doesn't prove anything!
This-This could all
still be in my head.
I-I know everything about you.
I'm-I'm your biggest fan.
Do you know I grew up in...
[IN UNISON]
Diamond Bar.
Or that my first
club team was...
[IN UNISON]
Cypress Elite.
Or that my nickname used to be
[IN UNISON]
Baby Horse.
And your college degree
was in political economy.
You have a license
to drive a motorcycle.
Favorite color is pink.
Favorite food is Mexican.
Your favorite song is &quot;Man in
the Mirror&quot; by Michael Jackson.
Wow. I don't even
think my mom knows all that.
[CHUCKLES]
Told ya. Number one fan.
I'm impressed.
Thank you, hallucination.
You're welcome.
Wow.
[LAUGHS]
This feels so real.
Honey, what is wrong?
What happened?
I fell.
And I hit my head.
- And... And, uh...
- This won't end well.
What won't end well?
- Huh? What?
- No, no, not y... Not you, Mom.
Not me what?
- I'll come back at another time.
- No! Don't go.
I'm not going anywhere, honey.
Mom, I'm not talking to you.
Who are you talking to?
Alex Morgan.
Alex Morgan?
You-You didn't just
hear her when she talked?
- Who?
- Alex.
You're hearing voices
from your pennant?
No, not the pennant.
That's crazy.
From the poster.
I'm talking to the Alex Morgan
that's standing right there.
Right where?
There.
Now follow my finger.
[SIGHS]
I know it sounds crazy, Mom.
But Alex Morgan
was standing in my room...
Now follow
this finger. Shh.
It's probably
just a temporary thing
caused by hitting her head.
Some kids see stars.
Our daughter sees soccer stars.
But she'll be fine.
ANNE [MUFFLED]:
Did you know she talks
to her poster?
You sure this
doesn't have something
to do with her brother?
[SCOFFS]
No, Dad.
Shocking, but this was one thing
that was not about Logan.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[♪♪♪]
Hello?
Are you just gonna
stand there and watch?
'Cause you gotta work
on your opposite foot.
You've got a great right,
but your left kinda stinks.
But...
[LAUGHS]
You're not real.
Are you?
If you believe in
a goal or a dream
before it happens, is that real?
What are you doing here?
You said you wanted some tips.
Remember?
Are you a ghost?
Do I look like a ghost?
[SCOFFS]
You look real to me.
Then I guess I must be real.
Let's get started.
Started what?
Training.
You're gonna train me? You?
I can't have my number one
fan quit.
It would look bad.
I-I didn't make Crush.
And the other teams'
rosters are set.
The ship has sailed.
Ships don't sail at 13.
That's what I said!
I got cut from my club team
when I was your age.
I didn't quit.
Turned out okay for me.
[LAUGHS]
[GASPS]
Oh! Sorry, sorry!
I'm practicing with Alex Morgan!
Lock your ankle when you pass.
Like this?
Good. Again.
Okay.
[GROANS]
ALEX:
It's all right.
Don't get frustrated.
Keep your head down,
and just focus on the pass.
Great.
Try your left foot now.
Nice.
[♪♪♪]
ALEX:
That one was really good.
REAGAN:
Thanks. Ha, ha.
ALEX:
Keep going.
Perfect.
Nice.
REAGAN:
Wanna train tomorrow?
Say when, I'll be there.
I'll do what it takes.
ALEX:
Good, because that
is what it takes.
Okay. Ready?
- That's all right.
- REAGAN: Okay.
♪ I was waiting in the moment
For the beat of love... ♪
REAGAN:
Thank you.
Hello.
Cute new boy coming
on your right at 3 o'clock.
Play it smooth. Claire's
getting ready to make her move.
ALEX:
Hey, Reagan.
[GASPS]
I'm so sorry! Oh.
Real smooth, Regs.
[SIGHS]
I thought
we were training today.
Oh, Ben.
Are you okay?
What's your glitch?
No worries. All good.
I, uh...
I am so, so sorry.
I-I-I saw a spider.
[SQUEAKS]
Um, yeah, must have been
a big spider, then, huh?
Y-Yeah. Mm-hm.
I'm Ben.
Ready?
[GIGGLES]
[THROUGH TEETH]
Right now?
Um, I'm pretty sure
I've always been Ben.
I mean, at least
since I was born.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Wait, what? No, no, no!
I'm sorry, no.
No, um, I'm... I'm Reagan.
Whatever it takes. Remember?
This is what it takes.
You said we were
training today. Your words.
If you don't want my help...
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Uh.
I have to go.
GRACE:
Hi. I'm Grace.
Please.
C'mon, Ben.
Come sit with us.
ALEX:
Perfect. Keep going.
Keep going.
Now let's turn it around,
do inside, outside the foot.
REAGAN:
Okay.
ALEX:
Good turn. Good.
- All right, let's do sole rolls.
- REAGAN: Okay.
That was harsh.
At the burger place.
When I was your age,
I practiced every day.
Yeah, but you're Alex Morgan.
Not back then. I was just
a kid with a dream.
Like you right now.
Look around.
How many other people do you
see out here practicing?
Nobody.
ALEX: Exactly.
You know who else used
to do hours of practice?
Not only because she had to,
but because she had a dream?
Mia Hamm.
You know who else used
to do practice rain or shine
on any field or driveway
she could find? Abby Wambach.
[LAUGHS]
You know who never
did extra practice,
who only did what she had to do,
and just hung out
on the weekends?
Who?
Natalie Gunderson.
Who's Natalie Gunderson?
Exactly.
All right, keep going.
Sole rolls.
You're getting
a lot better. Good.
[ALARM BUZZING]
[GROANS]
No.
[ALARM BUZZING]
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[ALARM STOPS]
At 6 a.m.? Seriously?
Rise and shine!
Keep going. You can do it.
Come on.
You're out here working
toward your dreams
while Natalie Gunderson
is sleeping. And done.
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
I am so jealous of
Natalie Gunderson
ALEX:
Good. Turn around.
- Jeez.
- REAGAN: Okay.
ALEX:
Let's see some juggling.
REAGAN:
Okay. One, two,
three, four, five, six.
I think I got this.
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- Hey!
God, that's my
state championship trophy.
Sorry! But you-you
got another, right?
Not the point!
ALEX:
Okay, nice.
Good one.
C'mon.
I wanna see a left.
I will. Later.
If you don't practice it here,
later will never
come when it counts.
[REAGAN GROANS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
What kind of spider
was it this time?
My coach is always telling me
to look up when I dribble.
I need better touches
with my left.
You know, I think
that was a yellow card.
On you or me?
Definitely you.
I've seen you around here
a lot lately.
I come up here to
practice sometimes too.
We just moved in.
Right over there.
Around the corner, on Longridge.
Welcome.
[LAUGHS]
You're really working hard.
I'm trying.
How do you stay so motivated?
[ALEX CLEARS THROAT]
Don't do it. Remember the whole
flashlight-in-the-eyes thing.
[LAUGHS]
I dunno.
Whatever it is, it's working.
Who do you play for?
[SCOFFS]
Nobody.
What? Get outta here.
You're good.
No, I...
You think so?
Yeah.
Well, who do you play for?
United Real.
Oh, wow. They're good.
I mean, they can't be that good.
They let me on the team.
Need any more players?
Um, well,
my-my friend's cousin,
she plays for a small club.
The Breakaways?
She was talking about
how they need one more,
'cause somebody
moved out of town.
If you're interested.
The Breakaways?
I think they're new-ish.
I mean, she said
they're not a great team.
But it's a chance
to play this season.
How not great could they be?
[TRAIN HORN BLARING]
You here to try out?
Uh, yeah... Yeah.
Cool.
What are you waiting for?
Okay.
Who cut you?
Excuse me?
What team didn't you make?
That's why you're here, right?
Somebody cut you or you
didn't make another team?
It's okay.
Nobody joins this team first.
I got cut by the Jags.
Oh.
Crush.
Mm.
You know, this team,
the Breakaways,
it got its name because
it was formed when some girls
'broke away' from Crush, right?
And by broke away,
I mean got cut.
NIGEL [WITH BRITISH ACCENT]:
Jolly good work, girls.
That's it.
Back and forth,
pass the ball, tickety-boo.
Keep it going along.
Great. Right.
Oh, I'd watch out
for the glass and the...
Maybe the live electrical wires.
Don't step on those.
PENNY:
For cryin' out loud, Bug!
Your moves gotta be faster.
You keep stopping and looking
like you're crossing the street.
LEXI:
Haven't you ever
heard the saying:
&quot;Slow and steady
wins the race?&quot;
The race, not the soccer game.
Soccer is about fast.
Like this.
Whoa!
[LAUGHING,
STIFLED]
PENNY:
Don't even.
She's...? She's 13?
GIA:
Bug? No. Nine.
Need the players.
NIGEL:
Codswallop!
I almost caught
a Level 6 Zernorf.
GIA:
Coach.
New girl trying out.
Reagan.
Cheers, Reagan.
Uh, my name's Coach Nigel.
First thing: has Gia
given you the panic word?
Oh, the panic word
is &quot;apricot.&quot;
If you hear
that during practice,
stop whatever you're doing,
and hide till coach
sounds the all clear.
Uh...
It means somebody saw
a city truck.
Don't wanna get busted for
trespassing and lose our field.
[PLAYERS CHATTERING]
Thanks for letting me
try out, coach.
Have you played
the beautiful game before?
- Yeah.
- Right on.
Welcome to the Breakaways,
Reagan.
Don't consider this a tryout.
Consider it your first practice.
Uh...
Hey, look, our first game
is in two weeks.
How many girls do you see here?
REAGAN:
Um... Ten?
But soccer goes up to 11, right?
So welcome aboard!
Get your boots on.
Meet us on the pitch.
Huh? Let's go!
Right-o, everybody!
Let's line up!
Whew.
You just made the cut.
That was a real squeaker.
NIGEL:
the point of
the whole game, isn't it?
REAGAN:
Uh, why...? Why...?
GIA:
Do we practice here?
REAGAN:
Yeah.
GIA:
Some real estate developer
bought the land
where our old field was
to build new apartments
or something.
REAGAN:
Ouch.
It's not so bad here, though.
It's pretty private.
You gotta dive, Lexi!
My allergies are acting up!
[SNEEZES]
She's allergic.
To what?
Grass.
Not quite Crush, huh?
NIGEL:
Come on, Bug.
You're next. Have at it.
Blimey! Don't bimble,
Bug. Come on, fast!
PENNY:
That's what I told her,
but Lexi started
quoting Shakespeare.
Shakespeare? Slow and steady
is the moral
of one of Aesop's fables.
Let's not bicker about
who quoted who.
This is supposed
to be a happy practice.
Coach is a good guy.
He played over in England.
Really? For who?
South... Tetherton
or something. I dunno.
But he's British
so he knows soccer, right?
NIGEL:
No, no, no.
Penny, Penny, Penny.
You... You gotta use
the inside of your foot
if you're gonna dribble.
Like this, right?
Like that. Like this.
All right?
Uh...
He's British.
[NIGEL BLOWS WHISTLE]
Bring it in.
Come on, gather round.
Come on.
All right.
Well let's give
a big Breakaway welcome
to the newest member
of our team...
Apricot! Apricot!
[GIRLS CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[♪♪♪]
GIA:
Come on!
[COUNTRY SONG PLAYING
ON TRUCK RADIO]
MAN 1:
So I was watching The Bachelor.
- They're on this island.
- MAN 2: Uh-huh.
MAN 1:
He's got all these women.
He's got a rose,
but he doesn't have enough
for all the women.
- You with me on this?
- MAN 2: Yeah.
MAN 1
Beautiful island,
women, couple roses.
MAN 2: Like Survivor.
MAN 1: Yeah, but you don't
watch it, do you?
Yeah, I didn't watch it either.
Anyway, they're
on the island, right?
He's got the roses,
and he uses...
- Welcome to the team.
- Yeah, welcome.
Thanks.
Glad to have you, Rachel.
Reagan.
[SNEEZES]
[COUNTRY MUSIC CONTINUES
ON CAR RADIO]
♪ You in my arms
My hands in your hair ♪
♪ Come on, sugar, nothing... ♪
[CAR ENGINE RECEDING]
The goalie is allergic.
To grass.
A soccer goalie.
Allergic. To grass!
Not ideal.
We're practicing on
a city storage area place.
At least it's
super-private.
[SCOFFS]
Hey, it's a chance to play
on a team this season.
Isn't that what you wanted?
I wanted to play for Crush.
If I'd made them, maybe...
Maybe I could be a champion too.
Like Logan.
You wouldn't understand.
[HUSHED, INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I made that team.
Thanks for the tip.
You're welcome.
Keep your head up.
Use your left foot.
[CHUCKLES]
Uh, hello.
Are you not
telling me something?
[GIGGLES]
Clear!
My bad. Sorry, guys.
Must-Must have been
a UPS truck. Okay.
[NIGEL BLOWS WHISTLE]
NIGEL:
Nice hiding. Uh, good hustle.
Let's go, back at it.
Ho, ho, tally ho
for that effort.
All right, Bug.
All right, okay.
Little off the mark.
Let's see it, Gia.
[♪♪♪]
That was a bloody nice try, Gia.
A bit wonky, though, right?
Everybody, if you wanna
hit the ball hard,
you gotta kick with
the tip of your toe.
And keep your head
up, looking at the goal,
so you know what
you're shooting at.
Right? Make sense?
Let's see it, Penny.
Oh, that was
a real corker, Penny!
That's the way you do it!
And remember,
tip of the old toe.
Toe down. Strike through
the ball with your laces,
head down,
eyes following the ball.
All right, you're next,
Reagan. Let's see it.
Hey, coach,
mind if I try it
a different way?
NIGEL [CHUCKLING]:
A different...?
There might be different
ways to kick a ball,
but when I was studying at the
Royal Academy of Soccer, um...
PLAYERS [IN UNISON]:
Wow.
Right. Uh, let's give
Reagan's way
the ole Queen's try, shall we?
Mm-hm.
[TOOL CLANGS]
[POP MUSIC PLAYING
ON CAR RADIO]
♪ Bow-wow-wow-wow, yipee-oh
Yipee-eh ♪
JOE:
♪ Bow-wow-wow-wow, yipee-oh
Yipee-eh ♪
Hi, sweetie.
What's wrong with your bike?
Chain keeps popping.
Want me to take a look at it?
Actually...
I want you to come to my
first game on Saturday.
This Saturday?
- Yes.
- What time?
- Eleven a.m.
- Oh, sweetheart.
Logan and I have a meeting
with a coach then.
You could miss one meeting
with one coach.
You've met, with, like,
50 of them.
Honey, you know how important
that scholarship is.
You know, to Logan.
Hey, to our family.
Well this game
is important to me.
And Mom has to work on Saturday.
Please, Dad.
It's against Crush.
Okay, I'll see
if I can change it.
Really?
Promise?
Yes, I promise.
[GIGGLES]
Thanks, Dad.
You're welcome, now.
Let's fix this again.
[CHUCKLES]
- Okay.
No tape anywhere near...
Let's... Okay, first rule,
chains and tape
don't go together.
OZ:
Champions
get their knees up.
Here we go.
One more time for a champion.
Two times makes you a champion.
One time makes you a runner up.
We're champions,
Crush soccer here.
Sides are next. Right sides.
All right, let's not look
too hunky-dory.
[GRUNTS]
Penny, I think you need
to figure out
how your legs work.
Let's stay on them.
Let's stay upright.
You generally
wanna stay upright.
That's, I think, rule one.
OZ:
Gonna do four of these.
That's what champions do.
Run four times.
Any runner-ups here?
I don't know any runner-ups.
All I know is champions.
All right, this is a right
frog and toad, isn't it?
Yeah, a regular fox and hound.
Well let's not
cat and fiddle it, okay?
Check this out.
I can record all Lilly's games.
That's cute.
Camera one, you a go?
[GIRLS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Camera two?
GIRL:
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'll send you a copy.
[WHISPERS]
Thanks.
- Who are we?
- PLAYERS: Crush!
- Who?
- What do we do?
- PLAYERS: Crush!
In on three! One! Two! Three!
ALL: Crush! Kick! Destroy!
We're gonna play knees up, don't
go to spare if we fall behind.
If I know my onions
about this game,
today won't turn out
to be a damp squib.
Go get 'em! That's good!
We got it! Nice!
I thought they spoke English
in England.
JOE:
Reagan, Reagan.
Hey, uh, the...
The coach didn't get my message,
and he's at the house.
Your Mom's at work,
so I gotta go. I'm sorry.
But, no, but... But, Dad, you...
You promised...
Honey, I'm...
I'm sorry. Okay?
I'm gonna try to come back,
but I gotta go.
He's there by himself,
I gotta go with Logan, okay?
I'm sorry. I'll be back, though.
Okay? Have fun.
I'm coming right now, son.
Have fun!
NIGEL:
Reagan, let's go.
It's kick-off.
TOM:
Hey, Claire.
Remember.
Hey, Jen, my dad usually
gives me 25 dollars a goal.
But when he found out
who we were playing today,
- he dropped it to 10.
- [LAUGHS]
Pretty sure that's not good from
a developmental standpoint.
You're passing up on assists...
Don't bother.
Just let our feet
do the talking.
Oh, I've seen your feet.
Have you listened
to what they're saying?
You can hear my foot
better when I kick your...
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
OZ:
Game time, ladies!
NIGEL:
All right, let's go!
OZ:
Move it, move it!
[GIRLS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[♪♪♪]
OZ:
Hit it up! Steal, steal!
NIGEL:
Good job. Ah.
TOM:
Let's go, Claire.
Come on, Claire.
[NEEDLE SKIPS, MUSIC STOPS]
NIGEL:
Bad.
Worse.
Deplorable.
Nope.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
OZ:
Okay, girls. Bring it in.
NIGEL:
Don't worry.
It's all right.
OZ: Winners bring it in.
NIGEL: We could've lost
- a lot worse than that.
- OZ: That's right.
Claire!
That's my girl.
Hey.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Twenty, 40, 60.
Let's go shopping. Come on.
Wanna get that pony?
CLAIRE: Yeah!
TOM:
Let's get that pony
for your birthday.
You earned it.
[GIRLS CHEERING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[♪♪♪]
So sorry, Regs.
How did it go?
Things ran long. You know.
[SEATBELT CLICKS]
I'm really sorry. I...
The coach just got talking
and then...
How did you play?
Did you girls win?
Did you do good?
I'm really sorry, baby.
I really am.
[♪♪♪]
Hey. Just so you know,
today wasn't my fault.
Or Dad's.
It was just
this huge mix-up.
Just one of those things,
you know?
LOGAN:
Are you really doing
all this stuff?
[GRUNTS]
What happened?
They put up a new lock
on the entire field.
I told you they saw you
sneaking back in after practice.
I forgot my ball!
[SNEEZES]
Well, maybe if someone
had yelled apricot!
It's not my job.
You could've said it!
Yeah, yeah. Don't blame her.
Well it's somebody's fault,
and it surely was not mine,
because...
[ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
NIGEL [WITH AMERICAN ACCENT]:
Oh, stop, stop, stop!
Please stop!
Just stop already! Oh! The
constant bickering and arguing
and fighting is too much!
I can't take it anymore! Okay?
Ugh.
What happened to your accent?
Uh...
[SCOFFS]
[WITH BRITISH ACCENT]
Blimey, heh.
I mean crikey, uh...
[EXAGGERATED BRITISH ACCENT]
Barmy, I guess I've been...
living here across
the pond a bit too long,
my Queen's English has gotten
a wee bit cheeky.
Right? Uh...
[WITH AMERICAN ACCENT]
I can't.
You can't what?
Uh, my name's not Nigel.
It's, um...
It's Nick.
And I didn't grow up
in Birmingham, England.
I'm from Pomona.
What?
I'm sorry. I am.
I'm sorry. I just...
I needed a job
after the sporting goods store
I was working at closed, and...
soccer parents are the most
gullible people I ever met.
They think anybody
who's British knows soccer
and can help their kid
be the next superstar, so...
I watched
the Austin Powers movies,
put up an online ad saying
I played in England, and, uh...
Well the next thing you know,
parents were hiring me to coach
their kids. And this team.
So where did you play
in college?
Mm?
High school?
I was on the bowling team.
[SCREAMS]
Oh! Ah!
So now you're accurate.
[GROANS]
I deserved that.
Aah!
[WHISTLE BLOWS FEEBLY]
That's a foul.
That's a red card.
[SIGHS]
Without a coach, we can't
even finish out our season.
Oh, Regs.
Heard the news.
Bummer.
Hi, Ben!
[IMITATES CLAIRE]
If I'm ever that annoying,
I give you permission
to smack me.
- [SCOFFS]
- I wish I could help.
Wish you could coach soccer.
Okay, everybody, good news.
Our season can continue
PENNY:
How? We don't have a coach.
REAGAN:
We do now, my dad.
He volunteered.
Isn't that awesome?
Has he ever coached?
He coached my first rec team.
Then Logan got great
at football.
[CHUCKLES]
Where is he?
Uh, he's sick.
That's why we're
practicing here.
Across the street from my house.
So he can watch us.
From the window. Ha.
Oh, hi, Daddy! Ha.
Feel better!
So you can coach us soon!
[CHUCKLES]
See? All good.
What...?
What's he doing now?
REAGAN:
Uh, well, he's, uh...
[CHUCKLES]
He's just excited,
and, uh, he wants
to encourage us to, um...
Uh, raise the roof?
Don't overdo it up there, Dad.
You wanna save your energy,
so you can get better.
[♪♪♪]
And now...
Now, until he's better,
I saw some more drills on that
Alex Morgan training video,
so let's go train
on our awesome new field.
This field is so small.
This field is a dump.
I... I can't find
my ball again.
See you next practice.
Hopefully my dad
will feel better then.
He's still not quite
100 percent yet.
[SIGHS]
Hopefully he's turned a corner.
We're pulling for ya, Dad!
[CHUCKLES]
I just need somebody there.
You know, and my mom can't coach
'cause she works a lot
on Saturdays.
You know, I was thinking
of asking our neighbor,
Mr. Dittman, but he's 84 and I
think people would catch on.
- Yeah, that's ridiculous.
- Mm-hm.
Yeah, he uses a scooter.
Why don't you just
ask your dad to coach?
My dad? He won't do it.
He doesn't have time.
You know? I mean...
And I get it.
This is Logan's moment.
[GRUNTS]
Logan works hard
for his dream, though.
You know that, right?
[♪♪♪]
You're right.
REAGAN:
Look, I get he comes first.
But sometimes I wish my dad
would pay a little more
attention to me. You know?
What do you think, Alex?
JOE:
She talking
to the poster again?
REAGAN:
Think?
About what today?
You.
REAGAN:
And sometimes
I feel like...
- Me?
- REAGAN: I'm not even there.
And I'll just talk to him,
but he ignores me sometimes.
I don't know why...
JOE:
Grace?
[SCREAMS]
That's a side effect.
From his medication.
He sounded like a girl.
Yeah, well, the medicine,
it makes his voice
really high-pitched.
Hopefully next week he'll,
you know...
What...?
What are you guys doing?
Leaving.
How is this any better
than what we had with our
'British' coach?
At least he showed up.
Hey, we still have a team.
No, we don't.
We just get together
in a different field.
Don't say that.
Whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
JOE:
Sorry I'm late. Sorry!
Sorry I'm late!
[CHUCKLES]
So sorry.
Hi, I'm Joe, Reagan's dad.
[CHUCKLES]
Nice to... Yes.
You must be, uh...
on the team.
Yeah.
Uh, so I... Sorry. I'm Joe.
Coach Joe.
I'm real sorry. I know we
got off to a rough start, but...
I promise you
I'll be here for you now.
I thought you were still sick?
We just heard you scream.
Yeah, that.
That was a scream of joy
because the doctor
just called me.
He said that all the test
results are clear.
Yeah. I-I'm all better.
[LAUGHS]
It's a miracle.
What did you even have?
I had a... A problem
with my vision.
I couldn't see things that were
right in front of me.
Really important stuff.
You know, we can talk about
all that stuff later.
We gotta get down to business.
Come on, let's...
Let's get our gear on.
Hurry up, come on.
Let's get warming up.
Get, uh... Get those, um...
The balls out of the...
The packs and put them
on the ground and...
There you go.
Uh, how...?
How did you even know I...?
Your Mom. And Gracie, she...
She filled me in too.
[SIGHS]
I am so sorry, Reagan.
I...
I got so focused on that
scholarship, it just...
I'm really sorry, sweetheart.
The only thing is I don't know
anything about soccer.
No, no, no. That's...
That's okay. That's okay.
See, a-as long
as you show up,
I can come up with
the practice plans. Trust me.
- [LAUGHS]
- Okay.
Uh, one question.
Is that child really 13?
Oh, no. No.
Ah. I don't think so.
- Uh, second thing.
- Yeah.
Do my arms really
look like Gracie's?
[CHUCKLES]
[LAWN MOWER BUZZING]
[SIGHS]
[REAGAN LAUGHS]
Hey, what are you doing?
Well I may not know
much about soccer,
but I'm pretty good when
it comes to yardwork, so...
Just don't tell your mother.
Get a rake. Let's go.
Let's get this place
fixed up for you.
We're doing the exact
same thing we did last night?
- Yeah.
- Pretty much.
- I don't care.
- It was fine.
Is this ours?
GIA:
Whoa.
[♪♪♪]
JOE:
Hey. What do you think?
Welcome to the new home
of the Breakaways.
Come on! Let's go!
[ALL CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
JOE:
What's up, Bug?
BUG:
Wow. I'm getting
more practice.
[ALL CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Okay. Okay, nice try, Gia.
But next time you should
try to do the thing
with your foot.
You wanna do the thing
like, um...
You should try a bending shot.
You wanna open up like
you're gonna pass the ball,
but follow through
like you're shooting it.
Like you're shooting it
into the...
- Okay, yep. Um...
- The...
You mean like this, Dad?
Yep. Just like...
Yep, just like that.
JOE:
Okay, for our next drill,
why don't you go ahead
and, uh, ahem, you know,
show everybody, uh...
what I taught you.
When you go at an opponent,
you wanna get them
off balance one way,
and then go the other way.
Too many people focus
on a fancy move,
instead of the reason
you're doing the move
in the first place:
beating your opponent.
Keep it simple. Use balance
and a change of speed.
Wow. Reagan's dad
is an awesome coach.
Mm-hm.
ALL:
Champion on three!
One, two, three, champions!
Okay, guys, uh, just go out
and... And do your best, okay?
Uh, I'm proud of you.
Win or lose, just have fun.
Let's go. Have fun.
Get on out there.
How come we don't have
a team cheer?
Go team.
You gonna dive this time, Lexi?
Yep! My mom gave me
some allergy medicine.
- See? No sneezing.
- Ugh.
[♪♪♪]
[PEOPLE CHEERING INDISTINCTLY]
PENNY:
Lexi! Wake up!
GIRL: Over here, Bug.
JOE: Go, go, go. There you go!
There you go, girls!
PENNY: Get it to Reagan!
JOE: Let's go, Bug!
Come on, Bug.
Bug, move over.
Help Penny out.
Nice job, Penny.
Nice. Nice.
Regs! Move! Move!
Go, go, go!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Whoa!
We're actually tied!
[GIRLS CHEER]
GIA:
Over here, Penny!
REAGAN:
I'm open. In the middle!
Go, go, go. Go!
Uh, last minute. One more
minute! One more minute!
Defense, girls.
Defense, we need defense.
Come on, girls! You've got this!
You've got this!
[PEOPLE CHEER]
COACH:
Good game, ladies.
A lot of hustle out there.
JOE:
Everybody stop.
Now what was the score
of our last game?
Five to 1.
JOE: Before that?
Like, 6-0.
It was 2-1 today.
We're getting better.
All right?
We just need more
game experience.
Against somebody good
that can push you guys.
That's how good teams
get better.
[GIRLS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
BEN:
Yo! Spider girl!
REAGAN:
Thanks for coming.
Ladies, today I want you
to welcome
some of the boys
from United Real,
who have come to our humble
field to practice with us
because, uh...
Because Alex Morgan said...
GIA: What?
PENNY: Huh?
Um, in that...
In that training video,
where she said she got
a lot out of training and...
And... And practicing with...
boys, uh, growing up.
I mean, you remember, right?
Yeah. I do now. I do now.
I gotta get my hands
on all these
Alex Morgan things
she's watching.
- Mm-hm.
- Well, let's, uh...
Let's play some soccer.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go!
Come on, girls!
BOY:
Go, go, go.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Laid back like a movie star
I set it then I broke the bar ♪
♪ It's just right
When I go too far ♪
♪ And everybody's dropping jaw
Just like a moth to flame ♪
♪ Under my spell
And everyone knows my name ♪
BOY:
That's a goal.
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I do my own thing ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I do my own thing ♪
[PLAYERS CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
♪ I don't make mistakes ♪
Don't worry,
I'll take it easy on you.
♪ Nothing in my way ♪
♪ I do my own thing ♪
[GIRLS CHEER]
♪ Ain't sung, but you
Probably heard ♪
♪ Just one look
And I rule the world ♪
♪ I don't try
But I come in first ♪
♪ And that's the way
It always works ♪
♪ Just like a moth
To flame ♪
♪ Under my spell
And everyone knows my name ♪
REAGAN:
Thanks again.
BEN:
That was fun.
The fake injury thing was cheap.
Agreed. But, uh,
I told you
you didn't know all my moves.
[CHUCKLES]
You hungry?
Uh...
you sure your girlfriend
would approve of that?
My girlfriend?
What girlfriend?
Claire... Bishop.
Why would you think that?
I-I see you guys
together at school. A lot.
Yeah. Because she kinda
shows up... a lot.
So...
you're not...?
No. No. I, uh...
met her at a tournament
a couple months ago.
[CHUCKLES]
She is not my type.
Where are we eating?
[♪♪♪]
That was fun.
I'm good. I got this.
I can't believe you scored
Dylan on a one-on-one.
- [LAUGHS]
- BEN: He just...
BEN:
So I know your favorite player
is Alex Morgan.
- REAGAN: Right.
- BEN: How about favorite goals?
REAGAN:
Oh, okay, so that's easy.
My first memory of Alex Morgan,
and it was in the 2012 Olympics.
US versus Canada. Remember when
they were all tied up, 3 to 3?
- Yeah, yeah.
- They have less than 30 seconds to go
Before it would
come down to PKs, right?
Then Abby Wambach got the ball
ten yards above the 18, right?
But then she turned to pass...
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
[♪♪♪]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[SCREAMS]
GIA
Yeah! We won our first game!
[PEOPLE WHOOPING]
JOE:
Hey, wait. Where's Reagan?
[GRUNTS]
Don't look at me.
She's your daughter.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Did you see my goal?
Great job. Although...
Although what?
You could have had another goal
if you would've used your left
instead of forcing your righty.
You don't let anything slide,
do you?
You want to be your best,
or you want to be
a Natalie Gunderson?
[CHUCKLES]
ALL:
Hey!
GIA:
What do you want?
'Cause there's...
They got sprinkles.
BUG:
I want five scoops.
[ON RADIO]
♪ Gonna be forever young ♪
♪ Yeah, we're dancing
On the ceiling ♪
♪ And we won't stop ♪
I am so proud of you, Reagan.
Thanks.
Although I could've had
two goals instead of one
if I'd shot with my left
instead of my right
there at the end.
So I know I'm new
to soccer and all,
but, uh, there are a few things
I do understand
about sports in general.
Check the league standings.
We got three points today
for the win, right?
Mm-hm.
Teams only have to finish in
the top four of their leagues
to qualify for Diamond Cup.
I'm just sayin'.
There's still time.
Diamond Cup. Us?
Us.
It was just one win.
No, it was just our first win.
I've always dreamed
of playing in the Diamond Cup.
The top four teams
in each league
are eligible.
Fourth place. I think
we can get there.
I know we can.
Do you know where
the Diamond Cup finals are?
Yeah, Harris Field.
Where the U.S. Women's
National Team trains
when they're in town.
I think the key
to making Diamond Cup
is practicing more
with the boys team.
Yeah. Definitely.
Boys? Gross.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
PENNY:
Bug's open. Bug's open!
JOE: There you go, Bug! Take it!
GIRL: Bug, I'm open!
JOE:
Take the next shot! Yeah!
GIRL:
Way to go, Reagan!
[GIRLS CHEERING]
♪ Independent ♪
[OBJECT THUDS]
♪ I never felt so free ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh
Hey! ♪
♪ And I'm feelin'
So independent ♪
REAGAN:
Are you the ref? Okay,
should I start from
my right foot or my left foot?
Okay. How was that?
I am using my left.
Fine. I'll do it again.
To another win!
[GIRLS CHEER]
I'm gonna go broke
buying ice cream.
Mirror me.
Mirror exactly what I'm doing.
Side-to-side.
♪ So free whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh
Hey! ♪
We moved up to 8th place!
♪ So independent ♪
♪ I'm just being me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
What are you looking at?
This is normal.
Haven't you ever, uh,
celebrated with air before?
♪ Hey, I'm kina sick... ♪
ALEX:
Good. Shield the ball.
Make sure you're between
the defender
and the ball at all times.
Good. Keep it up.
Now work with your right foot.
Your right foot.
Good, now your left.
♪ And they rock my world
Oh! ♪
♪ And I never felt better
Dancing on the bright side ♪
Stay balanced. Even if I'm
pushing you, stay balanced.
Great move.
♪ I'm feeling ♪
♪ Independent ♪
♪ I never felt so free ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey! ♪
♪ I'm feeling
So independent ♪
♪ Now I'm just being me ♪
♪ Just being me ♪
♪ I-N-D-E-P-E-N-D-E-N-T ♪
♪ I'm feeling... ♪
Does Coach know that buying
treats after a win
is very
9-year-old AYSO?
- I'm not gonna tell him.
- Me neither.
You got a problem with being 9?
JOE:
Okay, I need four chocolates,
two vanillas, a cotton candy...
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
♪ Just being me... ♪
We moved up another spot!
[ALL CHEERING]
♪ I'm feeling
So independent ♪
Where you think you're going,
squirt?
- Down the field.
- How you think
You're gonna do that?
JOE:
Yeah! way to go, Bug!
Way to go!
♪ So independent... ♪
[GIRLS CHEER]
Charlotte wanted me
to pass to her.
But her dad's not paying her.
Hi, Ben!
Ben! We're going
to Diamond Cup!
- Are you serious?
- Yeah!
- That's awesome!
- REAGAN: Thanks!
We're so excited. I can't even
tell you how excited we are.
Alex, I don't know if I'm ready.
We still need to improve.
I need to improve.
Everyone always needs
to improve.
I need to improve.
Diamond Cup is the best girls
soccer teams in the state.
I wanna talk to you!
BUG: Uh-oh.
I'll be with you the whole way.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Even if I wasn't here,
you're enough, Reagan.
Are you ignoring me?
Me? You can't be
talking about me.
Are you making fun of me?
Nobody ignores Claire Bishop.
Maybe you'll pay attention
when I tell my dad
to have his company
buy this lot.
[♪♪♪]
Hey!
Stop!
[GROANS]
JOE:
Reagan?
Honey, are you okay?
Sweetheart, are you okay?
[GROANS]
Reagan.
I'm okay.
Uh...
Alex?
[♪♪♪]
Alex!
What did you do
with Alex Morgan?
Have you seen Alex Morgan?
What did you do with Alex?
Wha...?
- Sweetheart...
- Oh, no.
Wha...? Alex!
Oh!
Come on, please,
please, please, Alex.
I can't do this without you.
Oh, come on.
Alex.
I'm here.
Ready. To practice
my left foot.
Alex?
Please. I need you.
[SIGHS]
Reagan, let's go!
Do I have to?
ANNE: Yes.
Come on.
[CROWD CHEERING]
LOGAN:
And I want to thank you all
for coming today.
I mean, this has been
a really hard decision for me.
But getting here to this point
has been hard
on my entire family.
My mom and dad both
have made so many sacrifices.
Between games
and practices, camps.
I mean, everything.
And then my sister...
Reagan.
[♪♪♪]
You know, I realized that
sometimes the spotlight on me
maybe left a little bit
of a shadow on her.
She's been one of my
big inspirations this season.
You know,
her newfound dedication
and practicing every morning
for her soccer,
it made me work harder.
She doesn't know this,
but I started putting these
'goal charts' in my room
just like she has in hers.
So thanks, sis.
Now, as for where I'm gonna
play football in college...
What, didn't believe me?
Thanks again. For today.
Come here.
Can I ask you something?
Shoot.
I got Diamond Cup starting this
weekend, and I'm really nervous.
Look, I still get
so nervous before games,
I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
No, you don't.
You do?
Yeah.
But you seem so calm.
Well then it's working.
What's working? Heh.
My secret.
Fake it 'til you make it.
That's it?
That's it.
So when do you
stop being nervous?
I'll let you know
when I make it.
[♪♪♪]
ALL [IN UNISON]:
Go, go, go, Bombers!
Okay, listen up.
You guys just go out there and
do your best and have fun.
And you remember:
you earned this.
- [CLAPS HANDS]
- Now, let's go!
- Come on! Let's go!
- Wait.
All these other teams have
these great pregame cheers
to get them pumped,
and we just walk out
onto the field.
She's got a point.
Any ideas, Bug?
Just one. Come on.
Soccer, soccer, that's our game!
Breakaways, Breakaways,
that's our name!
You can't beat us, no you can't!
Victory, victory, is our chant!
Hustle, hustle, we don't stop!
Breakaways, to the top!
Say it with me, say it proud!
Breakaways, say it loud!
ALL [IN UNISON]: Breakaways!
PENNY: Whoo! All right.
Who knew? Heh, heh.
JOE:
Let's go, girls!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
[♪♪♪]
Nice job, Penny!
Good steal!
- Okay, pass it!
- BUG: Penny! Penny!
Lateral it over and just do
the lateral thing over to Bug!
Come on, let's go! You got it,
take the shot! Take the shot!
Just like that!
Touchdown!
- [CROWD CHEERING]
- Go, go!
Good job.
Come on, Claire.
Come on. Come on.
- ALL: Yeah!
- Yes!
[CHEERING CONTINUES]
Penny, go!
Gia, watch 12!
Watch 'em. Penny! Shoot!
Shoot it right now! Yeah!
Yes!
Forty, 60, 80, one.
That's how you earn it.
Good job. Mm.
Good job, Crush.
Whoa. Nice shot.
GIRL: Way to go, Cindy.
Hmph. Be
home by dinner.
JOE:
Okay, Lexi, stand tall.
[ALL CHEERING]
BUG:
You go, Lexi! You go!
[GIRLS CHEERING]
JOE:
Hey, hey, hey. Listen. Listen.
You just made Diamond Cup final.
[GIRLS WHOOP]
You are going to Harris Stadium
to play on the same field
as the U.S. Women's
National team!
[ALL SQUEAL, CHEER]
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
LOGAN:
Hey.
You ready?
Heh. No...
Totally.
[CHUCKLES]
That's what I'm talking about.
[♪♪♪]
All right, girls. Let's work.
Knees up!
Winners always do knees up!
Yeah, let's go, number 9.
Let's go, 12.
Karaoke time.
You know what I'm singin'.
Winners always do sides.
Winners always stretch.
That's right.
JOE:
Good job, Bug.
Good job, lookin' ready.
Stay on your toes.
There you go.
All right, girls,
you got this, okay?
Just play your game.
All right?
I'm proud of you.
Just play hard.
Nice, Reagan.
Nice touches.
She's ready.
I know. And she stopped talking
to herself.
Claire's dad has been taking
some high-angle footage
of the Breakaway games.
Watch 13, watch 13,
watch 13, watch 13.
She's dangerous.
Take away her right.
Today, you girls
are gonna pull off
the greatest sporting upset
since Mike Eruzione, Jim Craig,
and the rest of the Americans
beat the Russians.
And as Herb Brooks said...
Who?
The 1980 U.S.
Olympic hockey team.
Lake Placid?
&quot;Do you believe in miracles?
Yes!&quot;
No?
We weren't born then.
My dad wasn't born then.
Right. Okay.
CLAIRE:
One! Two! Three!
ALL:
Crush! Kick! Destroy!
Say it with me, say it proud!
Breakaways, Breakaways,
- say it loud!
- ALL: Breakaways!
JOE:
Let's go, girls. Come on, girls.
OZ:
Crush soccer time!
No mercy, no loss.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
JOE:
Hey, Reg. Have fun!
[♪♪♪]
Oh, my dad's company is gonna
look into buying that lot
across from your house.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
TOM:
Come on, Claire.
You know what to do.
OZ:
All right, let's play our style.
Our style.
REAGAN:
Go, Penny, go!
JOE:
Pass it! Pass it! Come on!
OZ:
Teacup, what are you doing?
JOE:
That's good, Penny. That's good.
Get it in there. Get it up.
Get it up. Come on!
Steal! Steal!
TOM:
You go, girl!
GIRL:
All right, all right, all right.
Nice, Gia!
Come on, come on, Penny.
Back it up! Back it up!
TOM:
Go, Claire! Go, go!
OZ:
Here we go. Here we go!
- [ALL CHEERING]
- Whoo!
TOM:
Ha, ha! Thattagirl!
JOE:
Lexi, it's okay.
Hey! That's okay.
It's just one.
It's just one. That's okay.
Come on, teamwork!
That a baby, Claire!
Hey. Remember.
Still not getting my usual 25.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
[♪♪♪]
OZ:
Crush! You know what that means.
GIRL:
Get in there! Come on!
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
TOM:
Nice job!
- Oh!
JOE:
Okay, no bounce, no bounce,
no bounce!
Agh! Okay, no second bounce.
Good, good.
OZ:
All right, move it up,
move it up.
JOE:
On it! See, Penny? Get in there.
Nice job, Penny.
Come around, Gia. There you go.
GIRL:
Go, go, go!
JOE:
Looking good.
Good teamwork!
There you go, Penny!
Very good, Gia. There you go.
Gia, come down, help her out.
- OZ: Here we go! Here we go!
- JOE: Watch her!
Watch, don't let her kick!
OZ: Crush!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Boom! Yes!
That's how you do it.
That is a Bishop in the house.
TOM:
That a way, Claire. Whoo!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
OZ:
Jog off, jog off!
Winners always jog off.
Don't give up.
All right?
We've got a second half to play.
It's not over.
'Cause we have time.
And time is good,
because with time,
you have time, and time is...
Is... Is the opposite
of not time. Which would be...
You know who won
Diamond Cup last year?
GIA:
Crush.
Yeah, Crush.
You know who the runner up was?
Hm?
If we lose today, nobody will
remember what we did.
We'll just go back to being
known as the girls who got cut.
The players nobody wanted.
The ones Crush makes fun of.
And maybe that's who we are.
Or maybe not.
Because today is our chance to
force the Claire's of the world
and everybody else to call us
what we really are:
not Breakaways, but champions.
Now, let's get out there
and show 'em!
ALL:
Yeah!
Anything to add?
No, that was great.
That...? Was that
an Alex Morgan speech?
No. It was a Reagan speech.
[♪♪♪]
- [JOE CLAPPING]
- JOE: Have fun, girls.
Play hard. Okay?
Just play hard. Do your best.
Sweet mother of pearl.
Do...? Do they have
practice later?
Are they gonna watch us?
[HEART POUNDING]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
LOGAN:
Reagan!
Regs!
Fake it.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
OZ:
Okay, let's finish them off.
Finish them off.
JOE: Get in there, Penny!
Get in there!
Ooh!
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
OZ:
Steal! Steal, ladies.
Steal. Steal!
For crying out
loud, Logan. Heh.
OZ:
Come on, move! Move!
- GIA: Reagan, Reagan!
- OZ: Ladies, ladies.
JOE:
Nice job!
ALEX:
Pretty good.
Let's take it home, girls.
BUG:
Go, Reagan! Go, go!
JOE:
Go, Reagan! Go, Reagan!
- OZ: No. No!
- JOE: Go, Reagan!
There you go.
Go, Reagan!
GIRL:
Good job! Good job!
JOE:
There! You did it!
PENNY:
Way to go, Reagan!
[♪♪♪]
That's a foul!
OZ:
Wait, does anybody know
how to play defense?
Believe. Believe. Believe.
OZ:
Come on!
[♪♪♪]
GIA:
Go, Bug!
Bug, go!
Bug, cross!
Bug, cross to Penny!
No!
Claire!
What are you doing out there?
Sweetheart, you're gonna
have to get off the field
- if you're gonna play that way.
- Stop.
- Whoo!
- Yes!
Way to go, Breakaways!
Way to go!
Back, back, back, back!
JOE:
Time for one more push.
One more push, Reagan!
Stop her! Come on!
TOM:
Push her to her right.
She has no left!
OZ:
Hit it up! Come on!
Yeah! Yeah!
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[ALL SCREAMING AND CHEERING]
[♪♪♪]
Claire.
Let's go.
You've got game
footage to look at.
Both cameras. Let's go.
Aw, shoot.
[LAUGHS]
Forgot my backpack.
Go ahead. I'll meet you guys
in the parking lot.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey. I just wanted
to tell you: nice left.
Thank you.
Th-Thanks.
I... I couldn't have done it
without you, Alex.
What do you mean?
You just did.
You don't...?
Maybe it wasn't real.
What wasn't real?
You...
You inspired me
and helped me get here today.
Thanks. That means a lot.
Do I know you?
Feels like it, huh?
Yeah, it's...
You remind me of me.
Can I ask you something?
A favor?
It's kind of a big one?
Sure.
Good job.
But I think it's time
to move on to the next level.
Who's next?
ALL:
Me!
ALEX:
Okay, we're doing two-a-touch.
Are you ready?
ALL: Yeah!
ALEX: Perfect.
I scored a lot of goals
last season. Heh.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Thanks. Heh.
REAGAN:
Dad!
You're not gonna believe it.
Claire made a donation.
JOE:
Thank you, Claire.
Uh, can I get everyone's
attention, please?
Uh, first off, I want to say
a very special thank you
to Alex Morgan for being here
and donating her time today.
- Thank you, Alex.
- [ALL CLAPPING]
Thanks, guys.
JOE:
And to all of you
who have come here today
to help us save our field,
because we did it.
[ALL CHEERING]
[♪♪♪]
[CHEERING INDISTINCTLY]
♪ Sometimes the rain
Keeps pouring on me ♪
♪ And it's cold, cold ♪
♪ A gray sky parade
And it's so ugly ♪
♪ It gets old, old ♪
♪ It's bringing me down ♪
♪ It's holding me back ♪
♪ I don't know how
But it's not gonna last ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't let nothing
Crash my party ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Life is what
You make it ♪
♪ So let's make it great ♪
♪ You want it
Go take it ♪
♪ Jump in and celebrate ♪
♪ Live on the edge ♪
♪ Grab a guitar ♪
♪ Sing to the crowd
&quot;That you are who you are&quot; ♪
♪ Life is what
You make it ♪
♪ So let's make it great ♪
♪ High heels are killing ♪
♪ But I keep dancing ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I got one time around
No second chances ♪
♪ So dance, dance ♪
♪ It can't bring me down ♪
♪ It won't hold me back ♪
♪ I'll work it out
No matter how bad ♪
♪ When the lights turn off
I'm still flashing ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Life is what
You make it ♪
♪ So let's make it great ♪
♪ You want it
Go take it ♪
♪ Jump in and celebrate ♪
♪ Live on the edge ♪
♪ Grab a guitar ♪
♪ Sing to the crowd
&quot;That you are who you are&quot; ♪
♪ Life is what
You make it ♪
♪ So let's make it great ♪
♪ Here I go ♪
♪ Drinking from a cup ♪
♪ It's half full ♪
♪ Gonna see it all fill up ♪
♪ Life is what
You make it ♪
♪ So let's make it great ♪
♪ You want it
Go take it ♪
♪ Jump in and celebrate ♪
♪ Live on the edge ♪
♪ Grab a guitar ♪
♪ Sing to the crowd
&quot;That you are who you are&quot; ♪
♪ Life is what
You make it ♪
♪ So let's make it great ♪