What if I told you
fairy tales are real?
Imagine, endless realms
of terrible wonders.
Each and every reality
beyond our own is linked,
a vast multiverse
of grim forces
and sinister reflections.
Only the
thinnest barrier separates us
from all of the magic.
All the monsters.
Now imagine, once upon a time,
that barrier broke.
And when it did, all manner
of wicked fairy tale types
found a way from
their world to ours.
That was until
the princesses arrived
and showed us that
magic is real,
and a real threat.
So I founded Looking Glass,
and when death reared its
ugly head once more,
at least I was prepared.
Or so I thought.
Now it's Looking Glass
that protects the world
from any future
fairy tale threats,
though I fear,
with what I know,
that this time
I may need a little more help.
Hey, guy.
You okay?
She's beautiful.
Run!
I suppose it will do.
Looks like Prince Charming
has gotten cold feet.
Take the city! Find him!
Bring back my ring!
For the glory of Atlantis!
I've got a wedding to plan.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Tsk, tsk, such poor guests!
Of course, the squad's
away on holiday
when the bloody Sea People
start destroying my city.
Hatter!
Present.
Tell me we recognize our
new oceanic oppressors.
Uh, Princess Magdalena
of Atlantis
or "Magda the Mad."
Splendid.
I like her already.
And the handsome fellow?
Charles Charming III,
a Prince.
Of course.
Legendary hero, if
I remember correctly.
He was all set to be wed.
And then just up
and disappeared.
No doubt out to sea with
our little mermaid here.
Why is it always
a lover's quarrel
with these fairy tale types?
Well, that is not
the whole tale told.
Wait until you see
his bride-to-be.
Curiouser and curiouser.
I think it's time
we break the ice.
I'm supposed to be sending
these out of towners back home.
But we're about
to let this one out.
The last time she went
mucking about,
she nearly destroyed
the whole of reality.
Well, desperate times,
I suppose.
- Hatter?
- Yes?
If you would be so kind as to
prepare a batch of my medicine?
- Yes.
- I fear I'll require it soon.
Regular or extra strength?
Both.
Now, Hatter!
Snow White, I presume?
I think it's time we had
a chat about your fiancé.
Magda, baby!
Kill him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold your
sea horses there, fish sticks!
You kill me, how are you
gonna find your hubby?
I have the city surrounded.
My Mermen searching
block by block.
I'll find him.
Maybe, but I hate
to break it to you, sister.
You're not the only
game in town.
Charming's got options.
Sure, you might
find him eventually.
But someone else might
find him first.
Like Snow White.
What about her?
She's in town
and she's not alone.
And you know this how?
Identify yourself, stranger!
Pardon me, your highness.
Forgot my Ps and Qs.
It's been a while since
I've made a proper interaction
with real royalty.
Name's Rumpelstiltskin.
It's my job
to know these things.
I don't have my resume on me.
But my last gig was
Ruler of the Underworld.
That got boring real fast.
Turns out the dead,
they just love to talk.
"It's not my time!
Not yet!"
Then I started seeing
those BBQed people
that you were sending down.
And I thought, wow,
I have to see her for myself.
Rumpelstiltskin.
I've heard of you.
Ah, so.
You know my work?
I heard you killed Snow White.
Or that she killed you.
Yes.
Different Rumpelstiltskin.
It's a popular name
where I come from.
The enemy of my enemy.
Sure, yes.
Let's go with that.
All right.
If you're such a businessman,
what is it you are offering?
And what will it cost me?
Not only will I bring
Prince Charming to you
and lay him at your
flippered feet,
but I'll convince him
to tie the knot, too.
Hmm.
Well, that's how
it works, isn't it?
He has to marry you?
Yes.
According to my knowledge of
the Enchantment, all I need
is for him willingly place
the ring on my finger.
Well, that's doable.
And while I'm at it,
maybe I'll even take care
of Snow White.
All for the low,
low price of Atlantis.
I changed my mind.
Kill him!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Now listen here.
Hey, if I can spin
straw into gold,
surely I can get you hitched.
Plus, what do you need
Atlantis for anyway, huh?
Once you're leader of
all the land,
you'll be fine once we get
that ring on your finger.
Fair point.
I'll discuss terms
once Charles is
returned to me.
First, I'll need
a show of good faith.
How do you expect to
"lay him at my
flippered feet", was it?
That's the easy part.
You see, these valiant
heroic types,
the more honorable they are,
the easier it is
to manipulate.
And I know a surefire way to
get any hero to come running.
Magda.
Charles?
Oh, I thought he was dead.
He disappeared so long ago.
Where was he?
Atlantis, as it were.
Magda!
You know her, then?
From before all of this.
But what's she doing here?
Well, you may have
saved the city once before
but you certainly made a proper
mess of things in the process.
So far as I can tell,
when your mirror broke,
reality broke with it.
What was once a path to
a seemingly infinite number
of realms is all
messed up now.
Now there are bits and
fragments of
this mirror scattered all
over the bloody world, my world.
And each one is a gateway to
a different fairy tale realm,
including yours.
Should have known one
would have popped up
in the middle of the ocean.
This one is Neverland.
Quite fond of it myself.
Here, you'd never grow old.
It's wonderful for the skin,
if you can stomach the pirates.
And that one?
It's got flying monkeys,
of all absurdities.
And for each one apart
from its place,
it's me who puts them back,
including Magda.
Including you,
if I'm to be honest.
What does she want
and why is she here?
What she's always wanted:
To rule.
One might think
the ocean would suffice
for a girl with gills.
She wants the surface.
She needs Charles
to get it, his ring.
Whoever he marries
rules all the land.
So literal, you bunch.
Well, then, off we pop
to rescue the Prince,
stomp the evil sea people,
and send you packing.
Forgive the rather
rushed revival
but we're woefully
tight on time.
But I'll show you where to find
Sleeping Beauty and Red.
Oh!
Nighty-night.
Heh!
Sloppy and
stupid, Princess.
Thanks, Red.
Here, for when
the magic doesn't work.
Seems like they were
looking for something?
Or someone.
I wonder who got
all these guys?
Maybe Looking Glass?
There's plenty
to go around, Sleepy.
Kind of reminds me
of the good old days.
Nice to see some
familiar faces!
Looks like
you've been keeping busy.
Snow White?
I thought you were dead.
Just been on ice
for a little while.
Where are the others?
Well, if you haven't noticed,
there's been a lot of
heat around here lately.
Looking Glass has been
rounding people like us
and sending them
who knows where.
And now that
there's a whole army of
Atlanteans attacking the city,
they're nowhere to be found.
Well, that's why I'm here.
We have a mission.
- Finally!
- Oh, joy.
But you're not
gonna like it.
Do I ever?
How did you find us?
The mirror...
or what's left of it.
Then that means...
Oh, you're kidding.
Looking Glass.
- Nice.
- Let's go ask Alice.
So, let me get this straight.
This whole entire time, you've
been here literally chilling
and just, you've slept through
an entire enemy invasion!
It wasn't exactly my choice.
If someone would have
defrosted me sooner!
Oh, please!
Every time you royal types
go stomping around,
it's us little people
you step all over.
Well, that's enough!
Like it or not,
it's up to us to stop Magda.
She only wants one thing.
And she won't stop
until she gets him.
So it's up to us
to find Charles first.
Charles?
Charming?
Prince Charming?
Didn't you two have
a little...
That doesn't matter right now.
What matters is if
Magda marries Charles,
she could put the whole city
underwater if she wants.
Who would put that much
power in a wedding ring?
Charles is noble, valiant.
Every bit the hero.
He never wanted to rule.
That's what the people wanted.
And they gave him that power.
Power over all the land
in the form of a ring.
And he wanted
to share it with me.
"Fairest in all the land."
I get it!
All right! All right!
Let's all go back
and get your man!
How do we find him?
Well, that's a spot of luck.
The alley by the church!
Damn, Snow beats.
Shall I continue?
Oh, I think
that will do fine.
If I were the hero type,
I'd come running.
So what next then?
Kill hostages, destroy cities?
Threaten... threaten
to kill hostages.
Threaten to destroy cities.
If you kill anyone,
you have no leverage.
Hmm.
I see.
Well, maybe just one then.
So he knows I greatly mean it.
Magda!
Charles?
You made it!
The wedding's off, Magda.
You oughta know there are
plenty of fish in the sea.
Told you.
You've done enough damage!
I won't let you
harm anyone else!
Not on my account!
Then get down on one knee
and propose to me!
Maybe after
a few more dates first.
Bring him to me!
No!
It can't be! S...
Snowy!
Charles?
This guy's gonna
get himself killed.
Or worse... married.
Get away from him!
Hiya, Chuckie.
Come on, Chuckie.
You and me?
We're going through
the Looking Glass
Yeah.
Oh, no.
- Let's go!
- Okay. Okay!
Wait!
Where have you gone now,
my Charming?
- Again?
- Commitment issues.
Maybe that's our cue too!
Oh, he couldn't
have gotten far.
If there's anywhere I know
you're off fighting some battle.
Can we, can we...?
- Fall back!
- Yeah.
Was it a nice date?
Shame he doesn't seem
to have come up!
Well, Magda doesn't
have him either.
Not yet.
What happened?
We lost him!
Wait a minute.
What's that?
Where is this?
That's here.
Hello, beautifuls.
My darling!
It has been such a long time.
Snowy!
Yes, of course!
We sure showed those fish men
what for, didn't we?
Just like old times.
You and me.
Prince Charming!
Is this guy for real?
I don't see it.
So what happened out there?
Ah, yes.
Well, during the tussle,
I saw this creepy fellow
trying to sneak away
from the scrap.
Now, if you all follow me...
I've been playing around
with an idea.
And I figured I'd use
this little doohickey
here to send him back
where he came from.
Take the gag out.
I'd rather not.
I don't care what
you're plotting.
But I'm warning you,
I'll not have it!
Miss, I don't know
who you are.
But that man is an imposter.
I thought I killed you!
Different... Rumpel...
stiltskin!
Oh, God!
The Gateway!
Lady, untie me!
Snowy! The ring!
No!
I'm impressed.
Hmm, I knew you would be.
You've managed to capture
Charles, retrieve my ring,
and rid me of Snow White.
Where did you send them?
Where? When?
Who cares?
Let's just say I sent them back
to "Once upon a time..."
So save the date, sweetheart.
The wedding's back on.
So what do you say?
Do I get the gig?
He still needs to propose.
He'll come around.
You did... remove Snow White...
like you promised.
Just in case, take a dozen
Mermen into the Gateway.
Orders:
Seek and destroy.
Have it disabled afterwards.
I don't want them coming back.
From now on, no one
gets through this gate,
unless it's under my orders!
Now go!
Your sacrifice
will be celebrated.
You are two for two,
my friend.
Keep it up,
you'll have Atlantis yet.
Pick him up and put him
in something nice.
And kill anyone else inside!
Well, that's not right.
Wait a minute.
I know these woods.
The dwarves must be close by.
Back up.
This looks freshly carved.
I must have just
missed them.
How do I get back?
Where are the others?
All right.
How many of you guppies
do I gotta kill?
I'll ask them.
Old school, it is.
No.
No. No, no, no,
no, no, not again!
Don't freak out,
don't freak out!
Small spaces are no big deal!
Ow!
Just in case.
Thanks, Red.
Hey, hey!
Oh, not good.
No, no, no, very bad indeed.
Don't worry, Alice.
All is not yet lost.
We just need the power core
to bring them back
and we just need
to find them first.
Alice?
Hatter?
I've a present for you, Alice.
Alice, come along now!
Come along now!
Put it with
the other presents.
And wrap it!
Unhand me, you
amphibious abomination!
Now, Charles, is that any
way to treat the help?
You're a Prince, darling.
Soon you'll be a King.
Show some manners.
I swear it, if you've hurt
my beloved Snow, I will...
You'll do what?
Don't think about
her anymore, Charles.
She's in the past.
Impossible.
I think about her all the time.
Every waking moment.
No matter how dank the cell
you confine me to
or how unspeakable the
tortures you subject me to
or how long you confine me
to the darkest depths
of that abysmal abyssal
place you call Atlantis,
you will never touch my love for
her, you wretched water witch!
You fiendish fetid
fish-faced flounder
who will forever be remembered
as nothing more
than an up-jumped
usurping urchin.
You'll never know
a love like that, Magda.
Least of all, from me.
We'll see about that.
Take him away!
You... you said
you'd convince him!
Maybe you didn't see it
from your little hiding place,
but he did not look convinced!
He'll come around, trust me.
This will all work out.
What is it then?
Threaten the city again?
Torture him until he marries me?
No, no, nothing like that.
Look, you've just
seen the opening act.
But now, it's time
for the main event.
And what I have in mind
will take a
little more finesse.
And even you'll play a part.
That's weird.
They gotta be around
here somewhere.
Seven...
Oh, no.
No!
You were always there
to protect me.
I'm sorry I wasn't there
to protect you.
You deserved so much
better than this.
Magda will pay!
The Queen wants you dead!
Tell the Queen
to take a number.
Am I supposed to be impressed?
Well, the hard way, it is.
Five out of seven.
Thank you, boys.
How will you convince him?
Magda, it's what I do.
I'm beginning to wonder
exactly what you're up to.
Uh-uh.
I told you: I want Atlantis.
If I have to play matchmaker,
it's a small price to pay.
Hmm.
If I find out you're lying
to me, I'll skin you alive.
And feed you to the sharks.
Noted.
Now...
Oof!
Hey, flipper,
how's your acting?
One more try!
Aargh!
Unhand me!
I'll never talk... oh!
A little too method there, pal.
Enough, man!
Point taken.
Why not try that on me?
So, what are you in for?
Do I know you, friend?
Name's Rupert.
It's a long story, Rupert.
I've got time.
Once upon a time, I was
Prince Charles Charming III.
And together with my
beloved Snow White,
we had some adventures
together, Rupert.
There was no foe
we couldn't beat.
No spell we couldn't break.
There was nothing in all
the kingdom
that could rival
our combined might.
Our love for one another.
We were their heroes.
I was their hero.
But, alas,
our tale was not meant
for happily ever afters.
Though it was the realm
who wished for us to rule,
there were others whose
jealousy festered.
And none more than
Magda, the Mad.
Banished and confined
to the seas,
Atlantis long had a
tenuous truce with the land.
But the oceans weren't enough
to quell Magda's lust.
On the eve of my wedding,
it was her siren song
that lured me to the shores.
I never could resist
the call of adventure.
And what a wedding gift,
the seat of Atlantis
for my beloved Queen-to-be.
And, surely, I'd be back
for the cake.
But Magda's trap
was already sprung.
I was imprisoned in
Atlantis for so long!
Ages!
It felt like a lifetime.
Now I...
I don't know where or
when I am anymore, Rupert.
Or who I'm even supposed to be
in this strange foreign place.
It's not love for me
that motivates Magda.
No, it's power,
power of my ring.
The power I'm not even sure
I ever truly wanted
in the first place.
So, whoever you put
that ring on
has power over all the land?
Precisely.
We're talking everything?
All of it.
Like?
All the known land!
Pray, what about you, Rupert?
How is it that you've
come to share my fate?
Well...
It is your
lucky day, Charlie.
I'm here to help you.
I've been working
with a third party.
Magda found out.
So now I'm here.
What third party?
Alice.
Well, then I hope this Alice
is as clever as you suspect.
Or else you and I may
find ourselves old men
before this perilous
plot is through.
Thank goodness
you're all right.
Tell me, Hatter.
Have you had time
to prepare my medicine?
Oh, yeah, small dose.
Don't take too much
of that stuff.
You're liable
to stick that way.
Splendid.
You stay put a little
while longer, Hatter.
I think it's high time we got
these Mermen out of my building.
It's going to take
no small effort.
Okay, let's go.
All right, Alice.
Just like before.
Well, can't blame you
for overlooking
the small things, can we?
Uh, have we won yet?
I'm afraid not, Hatter.
It's as I suspected.
If we're going to find out
where and when Snow White
and the others wound up,
I'll need the Gateway
operational again.
I don't suppose you have
any expertise
in inter-dimensional
time travel, do you?
Um, only of
the hallucinogenic sort.
Of course.
Of course!
Hatter, that's it!
It's nearly tea time,
I'm afraid.
Oh, lovely.
Why don't you prepare a
pot of your special brew, hmm?
Do you think it might help
you in locating
our time-displaced defenders?
Um, it couldn't hurt.
Shall I make you a cuppa?
Oh, no, darling,
not right now. Thank you.
I'll need my wits about me
if I'm going to get
this little tumble down
the rabbit hole back
on proper footing.
You stay here. Focus on locating
our lost girls.
And bar the door behind me.
I've a sortie to sort out.
Off to see the Queen then?
Precisely, Hatter.
But let's hope
she doesn't see me.
You listening, pal?
Come on.
Just a little longer,
and this will all work out.
Forgive me, Rupert,
but what's the point?
I no longer care what
Magda does to me.
Snow White is dead.
And with her, my will to fight.
Let this play out just a
little longer and...
No, no, no!
Let go of him!
No! No!
Rupert!
Aargh!
Well?
Woo, boy!
Tough nut to crack.
Your boy is depressed.
It looks like your plan to get
rid of Snow White failed then!
He's lost his will to live.
And I need him pliable.
Back to Plan A then.
Sorry, deal's off!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down. Listen.
If he's lost his will to live,
we just have to give him
something to live for.
You better know
what you're doing.
No!
Rupert, you're alive.
Magda. She knows.
Knows I'm a double agent.
And she had questions.
And I gather she didn't
ask them very nicely.
I didn't answer any of them.
Well, good on you
then, Rupert.
I did gather
some information.
Snow White?
She's alive.
Wait for it...
50 degrees west.
Change by six
degrees for the wind.
Three targets all
lined up in a row.
Idiots.
Their average response time
is three minutes and 48 seconds.
It's an all you can eat
seafood buffet out here, Snow.
And there's gonna
be more coming up.
Soon as I kill one,
another school shows up.
I'm down to just with my arrows.
I ran into one too.
But this one was different.
He was ready for me.
Yeah. I'm pretty sure the last
time I was in these woods,
they weren't crawling
with Magda's Mermen.
Something's different.
It's really changed.
If Magda somehow
marries Charles,
she controls all the land.
Including the Gateway.
Red, I don't think
we were just sent back home.
I think we were sent back
in time or to another dimension.
We need to figure out
how to get back
and then we can fix all of this!
If Magda's using the Gateway
to send back all these Mermen...
Then we could
use it to get back!
Why else would she be sending
all these Mermen to get us
and anyone who would help us?
We need to get back
to before the wedding.
Then we could prevent all
of this from happening.
Do you know which way
the Mermen were coming from?
Yeah.
Somewhere back that way
where I came from.
- You know the way?
- Sure.
Just, you know,
follow the bread crumbs.
Let's see those gills
handle a full dose.
Come on.
That's right.
Breathe it in.
Now do as I say!
Come on.
Goodie!
I'm not so stupid, after all.
This'll do nicely.
Oh, that must be
Sleeping Beauty.
Good for her. I thought we'd
have to rescue her.
Well, that's not
very far from here.
Yeah. It looks like it's
where we're headed.
But it could be a trap.
- Can we afford to be careful?
- No. She could be in trouble.
We'd better hurry.
So what's the plan?
Where is Snow White?
Surely, you have a way
of getting us out then?
Better.
What if I told you there is a
way of getting you out of here
and to marry Snow White?
How, man?
Easy.
All you have to do is...
Oh.
No. No, no, no!
No!
Come on!
How? How?
Rupert, how?
How, Rupert!
Rupert!
Time's up, sweet talker!
Easy!
He bought it,
hook, line and sinker!
Just give it some time.
Let it marinate.
And you'll be the happy
couple before you know it.
I'm going to ask him myself.
No, no, no, no!
Look, the groom can't see
the bride before the wedding.
Why don't you go?
Get spruced up.
I'll bring him to the altar
when it's time.
It better be soon.
For all we know,
Snow White and her Avengers
could have found a way back!
I don't want any
uninvited guests.
I should have
killed them myself.
No. Trust me.
Give it time.
You'll be glad you did.
One hour!
Rumpelstiltskin!
Oh!
That's your trick!
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
When I last checked,
you were happily running
the Underworld with
the Queen of Hearts.
How is Gelda, by the way?
Good, I think.
You two don't still talk,
do you?
Oh, but we can.
And I'd be happy to inform her
of your current whereabouts
unless you tell me
exactly what's going on!
The wedding is in an hour.
But I have a plan.
Of course, you do.
And why should I trust you?
Look, okay, Alice.
Yes, did I help Magda
capture Prince Charming?
And get rid of the Avengers?
Yes.
But it was a con and
it didn't pan out.
I think she's catching
on to me.
She's crazy.
They don't call her Magda,
the Mad for nothing.
Anyway, it's good thing
that you're here.
I need a way out.
And how do I know this isn't
just part of your scheme?
You don't, but what if
I got you the power core
and showed you where
Price Charles is, huh?
We could call it a wash?
If I could free Charming
and reopen the Gateway,
then we'd rid ourselves
of this whole mess.
Oh, deal.
Now where is he?
Right this way.
Why is it every time I find
myself in a mess, I also find...
What is this?
Who is she?
You!
I found her running
around trying
to sneak off with your man.
Then I guess she... dies!
Oh!
Where is she?
After her!
I'll make sure you regret this,
Rumpelstiltskin!
Sorry, small stuff.
Oh!
All right, Alice,
time to crack on!
Oh, bugger!
Well, it looks like I can
trust you, after all.
Hmm. Magda, no one's gonna
crash your wedding.
I still don't understand.
In the present... or the
future,
if Magda marries
your boy Charming,
then she controls all of time?
Because we weren't
there to stop her.
All we have to do
is find a way back.
Then we can undo
all of this.
If we get back
to the right time.
Yeah.
I know it's confusing.
But all we have to focus
on right now
is getting out of here!
We're not gonna do anyone
any good if we're stuck
in the past or some
time-warp dimension!
We're gonna have to time
this really carefully.
First, we're gonna have
to find Sleeping Beauty.
Then we're gonna figure out
a way to lure the Mermen here.
Then we'll kill them.
Then, hopefully,
the Gateway will open up
and we'll just jump through it!
Or we can wing it.
Oh, hey.
Now's our chance!
Move it or lose it, Sleepy!
No, no, no, no, no!
Please tell me
this wasn't part of your plan.
No!
We must have gone too far.
I don't understand it!
Is this where the Mermen
are coming from?
You mean, is this when
the Mermen were coming from?
I guess Magda got what
she wanted after all.
Sure looks like she made
herself at home.
Without us here to stop her.
She must have found
a way to marry Charles.
He must be around
here somewhere.
So, right place, wrong time.
Exactly, and I'm willing
to bet there's a way outta here.
Looking Glass.
There again?
Think about it!
Where else are the Mermen
coming from if not here?
Magda's probably been sending
Mermen back for ages to kill us!
There's still a chance.
Yeah, if everyone
isn't already dead.
There's only one way
to find out.
Doesn't look exactly up
and running these days.
There has to be a way.
Magda might be crazy
but she wouldn't just destroy
the Gateway now, would she?
Wait!
Does that mean
we're stuck here?
I'd rather be back
in the coffin.
Long story.
Oh! How did this happen?
I gave up.
Charles...
Oh, my Charles.
My Charming.
I'm so sorry, Snowy.
I thought you died.
I lost my will to fight her.
I lost everything.
After she took control,
I... I...
My sweet, I just knew
I would see you again.
I'm so sorry things
turned out the way they did.
You've been gone for so long.
We all lost hope that
you'd ever make it back.
And now that you have,
it's too late.
She broke me, Snowy.
After we...
after she...
Hey, hey, it's okay.
After she got my ring,
she had no use
for me anymore.
And without my power,
well, I'm not the man
I used to be.
I'll fix this,
all of this, Charles.
We just have to get back
to the Gateway...
You can't!
I will.
Oh, my darling,
how long has it been?
Too long.
You just have to
tell me what's happened
in all this time.
I'll show you.
Once Magda gained control,
it still wasn't
enough for her.
She became paranoid, afraid
that one day you'd come back.
For years, she sent Mermen
through the Gateway
to find you, to kill you.
We know how that turned out.
Now she never leaves
that Throne Room.
We fought her for
as long as we could.
But she controls all the land.
I am the only one
she can't command.
And, well, am now an old man.
We?
We who, Charles?
Who am I?
That is a great puzzle.
Alice?
I think I once was.
But I must have changed
several times since then.
What happened to her?
I can't explain myself to you
because I'm not myself.
She's been this way since...
since Hatter died.
Feels like forever.
Sometimes forever
is just a second.
No kidding.
Alice?
If you're in there,
there's still hope.
We just need to get back
to before the wedding.
Before all this happened,
we could stop it.
Can you help us fix the Gateway?
Can you send us back?
I can't go back to yesterday.
I was a different person then.
God, she's bonkers!
The best people are.
You must be mad, too.
Else you wouldn't
have come here.
Okay, so Alice is nuts.
And Charming here is
an old geezer... no offense.
So what now?
We bring the fight
back to Magda?
No!
Our battle is in the past!
Uh, you mean present.
It's not here!
It's not now!
It doesn't do us or them
any good to fight her here!
We need to get back before
the wedding ever happened!
That's what started all of this!
But you're half right.
We're going to see Magda.
If she's been sending
the Mermen back all this time,
she has a way
to open the Gateway.
So we get in,
we figure out how
and we get out,
preferably unseen.
Stealth, I can do.
Darling, can you
show us the way?
No.
The place is filled with Mermen
and I fear I...
I fear I wouldn't be
any good in a fight.
Follow this path,
but be careful, Snowy.
If she hears you,
she knows you're there,
it will be too late.
My ring.
She commands anyone
who hears her.
Now go.
Go.
Why aren't you in your cell?
You know I don't like you
skulking around at night.
You already tried
to betray me once!
Did you forget?
No! No, my Queen! No.
I just thought that I could
be out if I were cleaning...
You thought... wrong.
I'm sorry.
It's just that...
Get back to your cell.
I'll just...
Please don't make me go!
I said get back
to your cell.
Y.. Yes, my Queen.
If only I could spin this straw
into something more useful.
You're back!
Shh!
But you're back...
Oh, we are not here
to rescue you.
This is all your fault.
You're lucky I don't kill you!
Oh, sweet death.
Wait.
Then why are you here?
We need to get
back to the past
and fix your mess.
And you're gonna help us.
How do we open the Gateway?
No, no, no, no.
The Queen won't like that.
Oh, I don't care!
No!
Shut him up, or
there's gonna be trouble!
Don't you wanna
undo all of this?
Take it back?
You don't understand.
The Queen, she's in my head.
She controls everything.
You just tell me,
is there a way?
Yes.
Yes, but she won't be happy.
No, no, you have to go.
You have to leave, or else!
Can you do something
about this?
Yes. I was hoping you'd ask.
Oh, thank you.
All this time,
what have I done?
You can shut up now.
Do you know
where the Gateway is?
Do you know how to open it?
You can speak now!
Yes. The power core.
Do you know how to get it?
Then go get it!
And don't get caught.
Go!
- Excuse me.
- Quickly, quietly.
Oh!
Go! Go!
Hatter!
Open this door at once!
How do I know you're you?
If I'm not me,
then who would I be?
Hatter, we don't
have time for riddles.
If you believe me,
I'll believe you.
Is that a bargain?
Fair enough.
Have a nice visit?
I'm afraid not.
Is it tea time yet?
The wedding's nearly upon us.
And I think it's time
I had a spot.
No.
Done.
Oh, gosh...
I had a cup of tea earlier,
and I didn't
get too far ahead.
The future then.
Fear not, Hatter.
Surely, we're not too late
to correct it.
I should hope not.
How does it work?
I need to find out where and
when the Avengers wound up.
You just take a sip
and you think of when you want
to be in there, you will go.
Splendid.
A cuppa then.
Oh, wait.
I got it. Please have a seat.
This is very strong stuff.
Well, let's hope so.
- Wish me luck.
- Yes.
The future, it is, then.
Ever forward, as they say.
Mm, mm.
I told you.
Oh, my!
It seems we've let
ourselves go, Alice.
What have they done to
my beautiful building?
Hello?
Alice?
Is that you?
My dear Prince Charming.
Forgive my saying so,
but you've aged terribly!
You're back, Alice.
Magda has my ring.
Then I've arrived too late.
That's just it.
You're right on time.
He's taking too long!
Time for Plan B?
My magic will wear off soon!
Oh, thank you.
What about him?
Leave him!
We could kill him.
Let him suffer here for
as long as here exists.
Rumpelstiltskin!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Come here at once!
Coming, my Queen!
Rupert, you're alive!
Are you here to set me free?
It's about that.
Sorry, Chuckie.
Magda's got Snow White.
The only way to get her outta
here is to get you to the altar.
Congrats, buddy.
You're getting hitched.
I don't understand.
If I marry Magda...
Oh, not Magda!
Snow White.
But how?
What about your friend, Alice?
Forget about Alice.
She's already played her part.
Trust me, you just need
to walk down the aisle.
It'll all fall into place.
Can you hang in there, buddy?
Of course, yes!
Anything!
Good.
Now I gotta go.
I got a part to play, too.
You're a good friend,
Rupert...
And a hero.
Anything for love.
Now it's show time.
Just gotta get into costume.
All right.
Coordinates are calibrated.
Everything is set
as far as I can surmise.
We just need the power core
and then we ought to be able
to send the girls back
just before the wedding.
Then fire it up.
Oh, that was careless!
I thought you were nuts.
Never proved any harm before.
In fact, I think it's quite
the asset more oft than not.
Well, what do you think?
Can you send us back?
Oh, yes, but with
hardly time to spare.
We just need to let it
warm up, as it were.
Ladies? Take your places.
- Snow...
- Charles?
I never thought
I'd see you again.
Now that you have
to leave so soon,
I...
I don't think I can bear it.
Charles, I promise you.
When we're finished, we'll
never have to live this life
because you'll have lived
a better one with me.
Give it a shot!
Oh!
Oh, did you not mean me?
Magda!
Stop right there!
When my little Rumpy here
told me what you made him do,
well, I thought I'd just
kill you, but...
Oh!
This is much more fun.
I told you we should
have killed him!
It's what I would have done.
In fact...
Oh!
But, my Queen, why?
I got bored.
And now I have new playthings.
Oh, the fun we could have.
Shall I make you
kill your friends here?
No. Too easy.
Perhaps I will let you
use the Gateway.
The Ice Age sounds nice.
I'm sure you would feel right at
home there, wouldn't you, Snow?
Listen to yourself.
Look around you!
Is this what you wanted?
A crumbling kingdom?
Nothing but brainwashed
subjects to do your bidding?
They don't follow
you out of love.
You didn't earn any of this!
Oh, but I did.
The sheer lengths I went through
in capturing your Charming.
The long and agonizing years
I spent twisting him
this way and that.
Oh, no, this... this has been
a long time coming.
And now, now I have
everything I've ever wanted.
But are you happy?
I'm about to be.
You had your chance
to be a hero
and you chose villainy.
Now you've got another chance.
I really can't believe it.
After all this time,
you show up now,
when you have no chance
of stopping me.
Oh, I wish Charles
were here to see this.
Be careful what you
wish for, Magda.
Charles?
Oh, Charles, how long has
it been since the wedding?
Too long.
Your reign of terror ends today.
I know I can't tell
you what to do.
But I would really rather
not kill an old man.
I'd rather die than
stomach another day with you.
If you say so.
Now, Rupert!
No!
Send... them... back!
Goodbye, Charles.
No!
Charles, you made it.
And you look so handsome.
What now?
We say our vows?
Something like that.
Be a good Prince,
and marry me...
Now.
Or I vow...
To kill her.
Oh, no!
Oh! Thank heavens!
Did you find them?
Yes and no.
What now, then?
Well, I've got
a wedding to crash.
Motivate him!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
If I marry you,
promise to let her live.
If you're a good boy.
Snowy!
Snowy.
Get your scaly ass
away from my man!
Kill them!
You don't deserve him!
"Fairest in all the land"!
He's marrying me!
Come on, Chuck, now!
Do it now!
Chuck? Snowy.
It's me, Charles!
We have to hurry!
Don't listen to her!
That's Rumpelstiltskin!
Oh, for the love of...
Snowy... Rupert?
Oh, now, Chuckie,
I can explain.
It's kind of funny.
I don't...
You're getting better at this!
Well, practice
makes perfect!
Snow?
Will you marry me?
It's about time.
Get away from him!
No!
If I can't have you,
no one can!
Stronger than you look!
Fight me or die!
I can't hit a woman!
I can.
Destroy the city!
Leave nothing standing!
Mermen are drying up,
fish face.
If I were you, I'd quit.
Now get the hell off my land!
You lied to me.
Magda...
You were trying to get him
to marry you all along.
You tried to trick him!
Magda, no, that's ridiculous.
You tried to trick me.
You ruined my wedding!
No! They ruined your wedding!
I was just here to help.
What was it you said
you wanted again?
Oh, you know what?
I'm good.
Let's just call it even.
That's right.
Atlantis.
I'll bring you to Atlantis,
but just be warned.
Once you see it,
you may never want to leave.
No!
Come along, men.
Time to go home.
No, no, no, please!
No, I beg you!
No! I can't swim!
No, Magda! No!
Please let me go!
Let me just stay here!
Please!
I hate the ocean!
You may kiss the bride.
Yeah, that's never
gonna happen.
I still don't see it.
Lovely ceremony.
But after battling
an army of Mermen,
chasing you through time
and living through
my own future death,
I've had just about
enough of the ocean.
I'll never eat seafood again.
So what now?
Are you gonna send us back?
Well, I don't suppose you have
to do anything I say, do you?
What with ruling all the land.
I know that's not
how it works here.
You don't have to worry about me
trying to take over the world.
Of course not.
It's already yours,
if I understand correctly.
Trust me.
We don't see it that way.
Splendid.
I think our adventure days
are over.
Oh, tsk.
Let's not be so certain
of that, Charles.
After all, the sea
isn't the only place
where hidden dangers lurk.
Believe you me, there's a
whole universe of wonder
waiting to seep through
the cracks of reality.
And no doubt we've got quite
a mess to clean up after
all that pesky time
travel business.
- We?
- Oh, yes!
Let's not forget who caused this
mess in the first place, hmm?
It would only be polite
to help clean it up.
If you're going
to stick around,
we'll need to make our little
alliance a tad more official.
So enjoy the honeymoon.
You certainly earned it.
But when you return,
I'll expect you
to report promptly to
Looking Glass, all of you.
If you call, we'll be there.
Splendid.
I've a number of matters
that I'm sure will require
the attention of
the Avengers Grimm.