Subtitles by explosiveskull
[birds chirping]
Okay.
[dog barking in distance]
[ominous string music]
[door closes]
[up-tempo synth bass music]
♪ People movin' out
People movin' in ♪
♪ Why? Because of
The color of the skin ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ But you sure can't hide ♪
♪ An eye for an eye
A tooth for a tooth ♪
♪ Vote for me and
I'll set you free ♪
♪ The only person talkin'
Bout love is the preacher ♪
♪ And it seems nobody's
Interested in learnin' ♪
♪ But the teacher ♪
♪ Segregation, determination,
Demonstration, integration ♪
♪ Aggravation, humiliation,
Obligation to our nation... ♪
The girl can sing.
I'll give her that.
Why don't you play a
little hard to get, Romeo?
Huh?
I'm off duty.
Not anymore.
Driscoll wants to meet.
- Tonight?
- Now.
♪ Ooh sweet Hallelujah ♪
♪ Can't you hear me
Talkin' to ya ♪
♪ Just a ball of confusion ♪
♪ That's what
The world is today ♪
♪ It's just a ball
Of confusion ♪
♪ Let me hear you, Let me hear
you, Let me hear you say ♪
♪ Ball of confusion ♪
[music fades]
This is Detective
Daniel Gallagher
with Detective
Charles Horvath
of the Vice and Narcotics Unit,
case number: 10-0-0-5-4-5-9,
meeting Langford "Lanny" Driscoll
for a first time felony weight buy.
Time is 21:13.
Date: August seven.
Multiple small buys of oxycontin, heroin,
cocaine have previously been purchased
from Michael "Studs" Driscoll,
brother of Lanny Driscoll.
Shakespeare.
[ominous string music]
[phone ringing]
[clears throat]
Hey, Casey, what's up?
I was just thinking
about tonight's game.
Give me some numbers.
Make them good.
[stammering] What are you talking
about, she got blown up?
Okay, Casey, listen, just...
Just settle down.
I'm really sorry this happened.
I am.
I don't know if
Pierce was involved!
I didn't even know she got blown
up till you just told me.
Casey, just calm down.
And I'm gonna get into it
for you right away, okay?
You all right?
I'll take the over
a hundred times.
Same thing on the parlay.
We'll talk tomorrow.
- [phone beeps]
- The fuck was that about?
That was my grandmother.
She misses you.
She says, "Hi."
Somebody got blown up?
Just something I'm working on
to pay the bills.
- How much you down?
- How much am I down?
[chuckles]
Ask me after
tonight's game, okay?
- You ready for this?
- Let's do it.
[sighs]
I was gonna get laid
tonight, asshole.
You can still get laid.
Okay.
So, we're two guys
with something they want.
They don't like
what we got...
we walk away.
A hundred says that fat fuck
tosses that cigarette
before we get to the boat.
Before we step on the boat?
Before we reach the boat.
- You want the bet or not?
- Yeah, fuck it. I'll take it.
Come on, you fat bastard,
toss the cigarette.
What's up, big fella?
How you guys doin'?
Studs, how ya doin'?
That must be
Charlie and Danny.
Thank you for coming.
Studs tells me great things
about you guys.
- I appreciate that.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Danny boy.
- Thanks for taking the time.
My brother likes you,
I like you.
Danny, why don't you stay
with Studs for a minute?
I need to talk to Charlie.
Charlie, come take
a look at this boat.
It's a great boat.
It's like a fuckin' hotel.
Picked it up from a retired
dentist in Florida.
Those fuckin' guys are loaded.
[Danny sighs]
[ominous string music]
You're lookin' good, Studs.
You, uh, lose a few?
What are you down to now?
Like, uh, whale weight?
Go fuck your hand.
I got a thyroid problem.
- Come on. I'm kidding.
- Don't kid.
[ominous music continues]
Who you lookin' at,
you fat fuck?
Who you starin' at?
I need a light.
Thanks.
Sure.
[gunshot]
[grunts]
Police! Don't you move!
You fuckin' prick!
[grunts]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[gunshots]
[music fades]
[grunts]
[shallow breathing]
[shallow breathing continues]
[ominous music continues]
- [gunshot]
- [grunts]
Whoa! Whoa!
Danny! It's me!
It's me!
What the fuck happened?
Driscoll! He made us!
- Are you good?
- Find Driscoll!
Oh, Jesus...
[Danny] Charlie!
He's wired, Charlie!
He's a cop!
- What?
- He's a cop!
[Charlie] Are you fucking
kidding me?
Charlie!
[boat engine revving]
[slow string music]
[sirens in distance]
[echoing] Drop your weapon!
[dramatic string music]
- [prison cell opening]
- [keys clattering]
[door slams]
[slow acoustic guitar music]
[prison siren buzzes]
[birds chirping in distance]
[music continues]
One time, believe it or not, there used
to be a whole amusement park here.
Your grandfather used to have
a cigar, cigarette, and tackle
shack over there by the pier.
It's where I met your old man.
I would say we were
about... 13 years old.
I used to have a little
business selling bait.
One day, these two hoods came by,
and they wanted to take my stand.
They kicked the shit
out of me.
They took everything.
And I wanted those guys dead.
I wanted that more than
anything in life.
I wanted to take my bait knife,
this one right here,
and I wanted to fillet
those sons of bitches.
But your father...
He saw what I was thinking,
and... and he made
me think it through.
He asked me,
"What do you want most in life?
I said I wanted them dead.
And he says no.
He fought me on that.
He said, "What you really want
is: You want your stand back."
So I took his advice,
and I moved my stand downriver.
I made more money
with that stand
than the first one.
You see what I'm saying?
If it wasn't for
your old man,
God knows where I end up.
Maybe dead.
Or maybe worse.
Maybe painted as a bent cop.
Hey, I gotta tell ya, Danny,
I don't think Charlie
was painted bent.
I think he was bent.
I think what Charlie loved
most in life was gambling.
And it put him
in Driscoll's pocket.
But fuck it.
Doesn't matter what I think.
Cause Driscoll sat
in a courtroom,
and he told the jury that he had
his hooks into you and Charlie,
and you got greedy, and you
pressed him for more money.
The next thing you know,
Charlie was dead,
there was a dead narc
that nobody knew about,
and you're in a fuckin' cell.
You really
believe that, Jimmy?
I believe what I see,
and what I hear,
and Driscoll had payments and dates in
his books from both you and Charlie.
I never took a nickel.
Well, Charlie did,
and he kept your end then.
The fuck he did!
You stuck your head
in the sand.
And if there's a crime
in that, you've done it,
and I've done the same.
When's Driscoll up for parole?
[laughs] That's not the move.
That is not the move.
The move is, go find Kate.
You know they took
her joint away?
They trumped up some bullshit,
took her license away,
and closed her down.
I didn't know that.
Of course you didn't know that!
Because you're thinking
about something else!
Let me explain
something to you.
Every cop in this city
hates you.
And they're gonna come after
the thing that you love.
What you need to do is:
You need to go find her.
She's working as a waitress.
As a fucking waitress
in some joint out in the sticks.
Go find her.
And make a life for yourselves.
Because she's the best thing
that ever happened to you.
Jimmy, I killed
Driscoll's brother.
He's not the kind
of guy to forget that.
What do you need from me?
When's he out?
- Sixth of April.
- Sixth of April?
- He gonna make it?
- Of course he's gonna.
He turned in two dirty cops.
The judge thanked him for it.
Sixth of April, he's out,
just like you are.
Now listen to me.
I know you're not bent
like Driscoll said you are,
but if you go out
and kill this guy,
that's exactly
what you're gonna be.
Charlie was good,
he fooled us both.
But, fuck, it's time to move on.
That's the call here.
Let it go.
Jimmy, if I don't
believe in Charlie,
I don't believe
in anything.
Welcome home, Danny.
Sorry about the stink.
Been hotter than a dog in heat,
and it ain't even summer yet.
[ominous music playing]
[gun cocks]
Anything else you need, Danny,
whatever, you let me know.
I owe ya.
Wheels?
Cleaned her up,
put a new battery in her.
Thanks, Jake.
[indistinct chatter]
[phone ringing]
[woman] Hello?
Sorry. One second. Hello?
[Danny] It's me.
Danny?
I got out.
Yeah, I know.
I've been thinking about you.
Yesterday was your birthday.
Christ, you didn't
remember your birthday?
I'm sorry they took
your place, Kate.
They shouldn't have
taken it out on you.
I moved on, Danny.
I'm doing all right.
Look, I have to go.
Wait, Kate.
You know what
hurts the most?
You cut me off.
Like I was the enemy.
Like I was one of them.
And I wasn't.
[sighs] I just
wanna know why.
I would've waited forever.
Don't call again, Danny.
I don't know what you need.
And I don't know
how to fix it.
But I hope you do.
[engine starts]
[sirens blare]
Where you at, Danny boy?
Good till about
a minute ago, Milty.
It's Milton.
Assume the position, shithead.
Spread them, motherfucker.
I do something wrong?
Jaywalking.
Jaywalking?
You lock jaywalkers up
these days?
Only the cop killers.
I'm gonna let you go
with a warning.
You ever call me
"Milty" again,
I'll put a bullet
in your fucking head.
- [thud]
- [grunts]
[door creaks]
[slow piano and string music]
[Danny echoing]
What the fuck happened?
[Charlie echoing]
Driscoll! He made us!
Charlie!
[Charlie echoing]
Hey, Casey, what's up?
I was just thinking
about tonight's game.
Give me some numbers,
make them good.
[phone beeps]
[dial tone]
Casey, this is Gallagher.
[up-tempo electronic music]
[indistinct cheering]
Charlie was into me
for a lot of money,
so he helped me out
with my sister.
She was having a problem
with her husband.
Found out he was
hiding money.
What kind of money?
The kind of money
you steal from somebody.
She thought that she could find
out who he was stealing it from,
she could use it against him,
try to save their marriage.
It's nuts.
But that's what
she wanted so...
I made a deal with Charlie
to square up the books,
if she could find out
what Pierce was up to.
That's her husband, Bill.
Bill Pierce.
So Charlie was tracking Pierce.
Yeah, cause I was worried
about my sister, all right?
What'd he find out?
Nothing as far as I know.
But that's why I called
Charlie that night.
It was Pierce's car, man.
It blew up.
Not Jen's.
Jennifer, that was her name.
What'd the cops say?
They bullshitted around,
made a lot of promises, like they were
gonna get who did it, then nothin'.
- You told them about Pierce?
- About a thousand times.
They thought since
it was Pierce's car,
he might've been
the intended target.
It's fuckin' horseshit.
It's an ongoing investigation.
[music swells]
Just wanna make sure
you have my pay ready tomorrow.
Yeah.
Hi.
You ever work with
Lenny Driscoll?
You know I'm a bookie.
Of course
I worked with him.
What about your sister
or Pierce?
Do they know
Lenny Driscoll?
Not that I'm aware of.
You think Pierce had
something to do with
what happened to you
that night?
Him or you.
Listen, man,
I don't know you well.
But I knew Charlie.
We were friends.
All right? I don't beat
people up unless I have to.
And I don't kill people.
Not friends like Charlie
and not scumbags
like my sister's husband.
What did you sister do?
For work? Nothing.
She painted in college.
She actually started taking art
classes again over at the academy
when she found out
about Pierce.
- What about Pierce?
- He's an accountant.
For the government.
He never said much about it.
Treasury Department, I think.
That's Jen.
You know, my sister,
she wasn't an important person,
but she was a good person.
And she deserved more
than what she got.
So if you find anything out,
I'd appreciate it
if you let me know about it.
[gunshot echoes]
[up-tempo tense music]
[woman] We're at the home of
government official, Bill Pierce.
This is where this morning his wife,
Jennifer Pierce, got into a car.
There was an explosion,
and she was killed.
Police are now investigating the
unknown cause of this explosion.
A shock for everyone here
in the neighborhood.
Needless to say, Bill Pierce
distraught by this turn of events.
As you can see, there are emergency
workers, and investigators,
explosives experts...
[tense music]
[elevator bell dings]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, buddy?
Yes? What can I do
for you?
Jack Bagby, from up on nine.
Listen, I'm a little bit
embarrassed. I'm new here.
I've forgotten the name
of the guy who's, uh,
talking to Bill Pierce
over there.
Oh, that's Mr. Loach.
He's a big shot. You don't
wanna forget his name.
Loach, huh? Right!
Treasury Department.
Nah, Treasury's
across the street.
You are new here,
aren't you? [laughs]
Yeah. Thanks, pal.
Sure thing.
[inaudible]
[elevator bell dings]
Aw, damn it!
I've done it again.
I forgot my card.
I got it.
Oh, thanks, pal.
Uh, ten, please.
[elevator bell dings]
[tense music]
Can I help you?
Oh, hey, hi! Uh...
Jack Bagby, I got an
appointment with Kim Masters.
There's no Kim here.
No Kim? 1114?
Department of Interior?
No, this is 1014.
Oh, God, no...
Oh, great! Now I'm late.
Terribly sorry.
You're gonna have to go
back down and see the guard.
You won't be able to get to
11 without an elevator pass.
Elevator pass.
Got it. Thank you.
[up-tempo tense music]
[music continues playing]
[engine shuts off]
[man over speaker] There is no
sin that cannot be forgiven.
Even when the weight
of his sins
has sunk the lost
deep into the lake of fire.
He may be born again.
So today...
I ask you this question:
Where will you
go from here?
Will you wade further
into the lake of fire,
thrash among the flames
waiting to be saved?
Or will you
save yourself,
depart from evil,
and do good?
For the wages of sin...
is death.
[soft church organ playing]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [indistinct pop music playing]
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
[pop music continues playing]
[inaudible]
- [indistinct shouting]
- [flirtatious laughter]
[slow acoustic guitar music]
[seagulls chirping]
[music fades]
So...
I guess I'll be going.
Last night was it
for me at Fatty's.
I'm going home.
Home's good.
You know what's strange?
Two years I've been here.
And you're the only person
I'm saying goodbye to.
I bet you got people.
Somebody to say goodbye to.
You'd lose.
[slow piano music]
[Kate echoing]
Don't call again, Danny.
[inaudible]
[scattered applause]
Thank you.
[Kate echoing]
I don't know what you need.
And I don't know
how to fix it.
[music fades]
[up-tempo dramatic music]
[computer pings]
[keys clicking]
[music continues playing]
[door creaks open]
Yeah?
I'm investigating
the death of Jennifer Pierce.
I'm glad someone's finally looking
into what happened to Jennifer.
You mind telling me about her?
She was good.
Little formal training,
but she had talent.
Did she have any
friends here,
anyone she might've had
a personal connection with?
Marcy Williams.
Marcy Williams, who's that?
I'll show you.
This was Jennifer's
portrait of Marcy.
Beautiful.
Jennifer was good,
but let's face it,
she had a great subject.
Would you mind showing me
Marcy's records?
Can't. Don't have any.
What do you mean?
When Jenn died,
I wanted to contact Marcy.
I checked the registrar.
She was never enrolled.
There's something that I
considered showing the police,
but they never
came by to ask.
I don't even know
if it's important,
but for some reason
I kept it.
That's Jennifer with Marcy.
[ominous music]
[music continues playing]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Stop.
Back it up.
[Danny] There. Stop.
[woman on phone] Okay, Marcy
Williams, Mercedes four-door, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Okay.
Here we go... Got it!
Not on file.
That's a red flag.
Usually means government issue.
What agency?
Your guess is as good as mine.
Anything else?
There are 14 licenses issued
under the name "Marcy Williams."
Forty-two under
"Marshell Williams."
If you give me an age,
I can crosscheck.
Tell you what:
I'll let you know.
Hey, G.
Yeah?
I'm glad you're out.
Yeah, me too.
[suspenseful music]
[tires screeching]
[music continues playing]
[door closes]
Hello, Marcy.
Actually, it's Rebecca.
- Gallagher.
- I know.
I know everything about you.
What do you know about me?
Well, I know you work for
some government agency:
CIA, FSB, FU2, one of them.
I know you had
the police investigation
into the death
of Jennifer Pierce shut down.
I know you were
sleeping with Jennifer,
but I bet there was no love lost
there when she was murdered.
Anything else?
I liked you better
as a blonde.
Give it time.
I don't think so.
Why are you tracking
Bill Pierce?
That's my business.
This is who I work for.
That should scare you.
It scares the hell
out of me.
What's it got to do
with Pierce?
You're interfering with
a major investigation
having to do with
national security.
You need to back off.
If you don't back off,
I will force you to back off.
You understand that, right?
Seems pretty clear enough.
My cell is on the card
if you have any questions.
I do have a question.
How much money do you think a
guy like Pierce makes a year?
- Why?
- He's got a young mistress.
He buys her gifts, expensive
jewelry, got a nice place
down on the waterfront
with her shacked up.
Be nice to know where he's
getting all that money from.
You sticking your nose into this is
only going to make things worse.
Well it couldn't get much worse
for Jennifer Pierce, could it?
By the way,
you sleeping with her,
was that for God
and country and all that
or was that for real?
- Eddie!
- Ugh.
You want it done right
or you want it done?
And put that cigarette out.
On second thought...
Give it here.
What do we got?
Professional.
- Only one?
- That I could find.
You piss somebody
off again?
It's a problem of mine.
[sirens blare]
Put your hands
where I can see them.
Problem, officer?
License and registration.
Okay if I reach
into my jacket?
Shut the fuck up
and get out the car!
Come on. Let's go.
You know, you two dick twins
are the second team
to stop me like this.
"Dick twins?"
Is that what you said,
"dick twins?"
Do you fuckin' think I look
like this fuckin' Uncle Tom?
You think I look like this trailer
trash, inbred motherfucker?
I didn't say that.
You going to jail,
scumbag.
I've been to jail.
I didn't like it.
You like your teeth?
'Cause you're about to
lose a couple of molars.
Tell me what
I did wrong.
Well for starters:
driving with a broken taillight.
Nope. No.
He just broke it.
Tonight, you've done nothin'.
But what you have done,
and what you are...
is scumbag motherfuckin'
cop killer.
You think just because
they let you out that
that somehow gets you
a free pass.
If that's what you think...
you very wrong.
That's a cute mustache.
Before you do anything stupid
have a look inside the car.
You see that?
That's a dashcam uploading
everything we say and do
directly to
my attorney's server.
That's right,
you dumb motherfuckers,
I own you.
So this is what's gonna happen.
You're gonna go back
to the precinct,
and you're gonna tell
your fuckhead buddies
to back off.
And you owe me for a taillight.
[suspenseful music]
[door creaks open]
- [lamp clicks]
- [grunting]
[Danny] Back off!
[grunting]
[thudding]
[glass shatters]
[grunting]
[choking]
[biting]
[screaming]
[sirens in distance]
All right.
We're just about done here.
Anything else
you could think of.
Like what?
Like maybe why someone
would wanna kill you.
Aside from half
the cops in this city?
Aside from them.
'Cause any of them
woulda done a better job
than what happened
here tonight.
Nobody I can think of.
All right. Thanks, doc.
Keep in mind what I got
from you is only
one side of the story.
The true side, Frank.
The side that used to count
for something in this city.
After we get the ballistics
in on the gun
and find out something about
this guy you say ran off,
we gonna be talkin' again.
Hey Frank, you get
a hit on that gun,
I'd appreciate knowin'
where it came from.
What are you a cop
or something?
Let me tell you something,
tough guy.
If I find even a smidge of
something I can arrest you for,
I will bury you.
I will fuckin' bury you
and enjoy doing in.
You think I say that
'cause you a bent cop?
Because your partner
killed a cop, a good cop?
Thought crossed my mind.
You'd be wrong.
I'll say that cause
you a scumbag.
Ask me why you a scumbag.
Why am I a scumbag?
Because I've been on the job 18
years, 9 months, and 22 days,
and I don't have
a gold shield.
Ask me why I don't have
Why don't you have
a gold shield?
'Cause the day you
and your partner got caught,
the bosses stopped all
promotions until
they completed an investigation
into police corruption.
I still don't have
my gold shield.
And that, my friend,
is why you are a scumbag.
We good?
Good as gold.
Have a nice evening.
Hey, Frank!
You, uh, got a card?
Just in case I have
any questions
or in the unlikely event
that you're not as lousy
at your job as
I think you are?
All out.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[dial tone]
[Rebecca] Hello?
You put a tracking device
underneath my car.
And you took it out which means
I'm gonna have to put it back.
Someone just tried
to kill me.
I don't know anything
about that.
I'm sure you don't,
but if it happens again,
I'll be sending your
little package to the media
with everything I know about
the Jennifer Pierce case.
Who the fuck...
[phone beeps]
[phone ringing]
[groaning]
[woman groaning]
Who's on the phone?
- [sighs]
- [phone beeps]
Who's this, and why you callin'
in the middle of the night?
[Danny] Jimmy?
Who is it, Jimmy?
Yeah, hold on a second.
Jimmy, who is it?
It's okay. I got this.
Go to bed.
Hey, you better be callin' me
cause you hit the lotto
because anything else...
is gonna be a real problem.
I need a favor.
What's up?
I may have a lead on what happened
that night with Driscoll.
I need files though.
Unsolved homicide, 3 years ago,
woman named Jennifer Pierce.
Uh, I'll see
what I can do.
Meet me at the Anaconda,
1 o'clock, you're buying.
Shame on you, Jimmy.
What am I supposed to do?
Turn my back on him?
Yes.
That's exactly what
you're supposed to do.
Just walk away from it.
Please.
Jimmy.
- What about us?
- [stammering] What ab...
What about all
the conversations?
Please.
I'm all he's got.
[birds chirping]
[Jimmy] Eh, this place
is all fished out.
So I know I haven't
lost my touch.
[sirens in distance]
What you wanted
on the car bombing.
It's an ongoing
investigation so, uh...
The material's highly
sensitive which means
don't ask any questions
which also means
get the fuck
out of my face.
The materials on the
forensics that was, uh...
That was more difficult.
Luckily I had a buddy
in forensics.
Somebody shut down access.
- Any idea who?
- Somebody high up.
[sighs]
What's it all about?
Charlie was working something
on a guy named "Pierce."
Husband of the woman
who got blown up.
I think that's why
Driscoll killed him.
Charlie found out
what they were into.
Whatever you're chasing
is a dead end.
You have any idea
what kind of money
Charlie was into the Shylocks
in this town for?
Forty-two five.
Forty-two five to three
different Shys in this town,
and that's the kinda money
that gets you bent.
April 6th.
- Still on?
- Still on.
You go after Driscoll,
I can't help you, Danny.
You understand that?
I don't want your help.
I don't give a fuck if you want
it or not, I still can't do it.
But I can go back
to my original advice
which is go find Kate,
go to, uh, Paraguay
or some godforsaken
country nobody can pronounce,
and make a life for yourself.
Phyllis, it's Gallagher.
Yes?
I need to get a court
transcript quickly.
- We know anybody?
- We do.
Who's transcript?
Mine.
[gun cocks]
Casey.
Was just checking in.
Wondering how it's goin'.
How'd you know
where I live?
Alexis.
She mentioned it when I dropped
her off at the airport.
She went home, you know?
Yeah.
So?
Well Pierce doesn't work
for the Treasury.
I don't know what the hell he
does, but he ain't no accountant.
I don't understand.
Where's your sister's car?
What?
The bomb blew up
Pierce's car.
Why wasn't your sister
driving her own?
It was in the shop.
- You know where it is now?
- No. I don't know.
Do you have any idea
why Pierce goes to a church
all the way over in Seidel?
Bill Pierce? He never went
to church in his life.
He's an atheist.
[priest] Pray my brothers and
sisters,
that our sacrifice may be
acceptable to God,
the Almighty Father.
May the Lord accept
this sacrifice at your hands,
for the praise
and glory of His name,
for our good,
and for the good
of all His church.
[all] Amen.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, buddy!
You got a minute?
I'm busy at the moment.
Great mass!
Eh, I remember you.
I remember everyone who
gives a nice donation.
Gotta tell ya, buddy,
I really enjoyed
listening to that priest
who was here the other day.
He was amazing!
Oh, Father Bailey's
the best.
He's a monsignor.
- Is he around?
- Nope. He's traveling again.
If it wasn't for
Father Bailey,
people of this parish
would have nowhere to pray,
nowhere to eat,
Oh, he's turnin'
it around.
- Where is he traveling?
- Middle East.
Father Bailey is
a missionary
for the United Nations'
World Food Program.
The man's a saint.
I don't know
how he does it.
Yeah, me neither.
- [bullets ricocheting]
- [all screaming]
[Danny] Stay down!
[Danny] Get down!
Get down!
[bullets ricocheting]
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music playing]
[register dings]
Thanks.
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
[Rebecca] Hello?
People keep trying to kill me.
It's getting annoying.
Now my car is gone.
It was ten years old,
had a busted taillight.
It was a piece of shit,
but it was mine, I liked it.
I can't help you.
Actually, you can.
Ask me why.
I learned this trick
from a piece-of-shit cop.
Go ahead; ask me why.
Why?
Because I followed Bill Pierce to a
church so far outside his parish
it might as well
have been in China.
He's delivering envelopes
to a priest who travels
to the Middle East
every couple of weeks.
Not on the phone.
I'll meet you.
Great idea.
Gas station. Exit 37.
- [thunder rumbles]
- [ominous music]
Get out.
It's raining.
Arms.
In the passenger seat.
What does Pierce do for the
Department of Fiscal Oversight,
which by the way
doesn't actually exist.
He's an analyst.
He's decoding transmissions
between certain countries
that might pose
a threat to us.
He's selling those
transmissions to the Iranians.
The monsignor is
passing them along.
But we're not after Pierce.
We're after who he's
working with,
someone higher up.
Who killed
Jennifer Pierce?
The Iranians.
How do you know that?
The bomb was made in Iran...
with materials from
the Ukraine and Russia.
If Pierce was working with
them, why would they kill him?
A very important Iranian
agent was recently lost.
"Lost?"
Eliminated.
The bombing was payback.
Pierce's wife had the
misfortune of driving his car
the morning she was killed.
Her name was Jennifer.
You slept with her.
Why can't you
say her name?
It was her idea.
Who tried to
kill me today?
The agency.
You?
No.
I have been reassigned.
Because I wouldn't do it.
Lose me?
- Yes.
- Why?
Because I think
it's wrong.
To lose you.
Why'd you agree
to meet today?
To convince you
to back off.
Was it the agency in my
loft the other night?
I told you.
It wasn't us.
[truck honks]
You're gonna have
to start trusting me.
Because if you don't...
You're a dead man.
Aren't you a little bit sorry
for what happened to her?
Yes.
Tell her brother
that his sister
died in an accident.
Make up a story that
he will believe.
[dramatic string music]
[dramatic thud echoes]
Here you go, man.
Eddie, it could get dirty.
This car?
Never seen it before.
Looks stolen to me.
- Let's go.
- All right, man.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [office phones ringing]
Hey, you.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Are you staying
out of trouble?
Absolutely.
Do you wanna
get in some?
I'm free tonight.
Now why would you wanna go
and do that to yourself?
Well, what can I say?
I'm a glutton for empty sex.
It's probably my
Catholic upbringing.
[indistinct news reporter]
What's goin' on?
Oh, there was
a fire at a church.
Monsignor Bailey, a beloved
figure in the parish,
was the only person
to die in the fire.
Apparently overtaken
by smoke inhalation.
That window there
was the monsignor's residence.
The struggling parish was facing
financial troubles of late.
A new monsignor was leading the
church back from the brink of...
[inaudible]
[man] It's Mr. Loach.
We can go.
[suspenseful music]
[crickets chirping]
[music fades]
[phone ringing]
[footsteps]
[tense music]
I tried calling you.
You didn't answer.
I don't trust you.
- Priest is gone.
- I know.
What happened?
I found out who Pierce was
working with at the agency.
Tom Loach.
His supervisor.
I turned in my report
to my superior.
Ten hours later,
the priest is dead.
What the hell did
you do that for?
I am not out here running
around unaccountable.
I'm supposed to be tracking down
terrorists and their money sources.
If I can't trust
my superiors,
then who can I trust?
Obviously it was
a mistake.
This goes higher
than I thought.
You think?
They're cleaning house.
Pierce is next, then you.
Me after.
Where is Pierce?
I don't know.
Gone? Lost?
More likely hiding,
but they're gonna find him.
I thought you should know.
Thanks.
[slow keyboard music]
[dogs barking in distance]
What's up, G?
Hey, Dougie,
how you doin'?
I was doin' better
a minute ago.
You're back on the job?
I got a private thing.
Here's a list of materials
was used in the car bombing.
I need to know where
they came from,
whether they're foreign
or domestic.
I don't do that
kinda thing no more.
I'm out. Been out.
And I'd like
to stay out.
I'm giving myself
a chance here.
I gave you a chance.
[woman] Dougie!
Everything all right?
Yeah!
G's an old friend.
G.
What I got here
ain't much.
But that kid?
He's mine.
I get it, Dougie.
I really do.
This is a one-time deal,
okay?
The battery, the wires,
the timer, even the C-4,
you get that
stuff anywhere.
You wanna know what?
Whether it's foreign
or domestic.
There's a guy,
Chuck Cumming,
mad genius with explosives.
Back in the day,
he was the go-to
for anything and anybody.
Will he talk to me?
Probably not. He's gonna
think you're a cop.
Tell him you're my friend,
- and, "I
- emember Bernadette."
"Bernadette?"
No cop will know
anything about that.
And if he's not around,
don't blame me.
[suspenseful music]
[birds caw]
[grunts]
[screaming]
[glass shatters]
Stranger!
Wait a goddamn minute!
[choking, gagging]
Dougie, I'm a friend
of Bernadette!
Bernadette!
What?
[gagging] Bernadette!
That ANFO could've
been made anywhere.
ANFO?
Ammonium Nitrate,
fertilizer, and oil,
common bullshit.
Device explodes, there are gonna
be elements that are released.
They're called taggants.
Same principle for tracing
ballistics on a bullet.
But it takes time.
I don't have time.
Hm.
You can try tracing
the pipe
back to the plumbing
supply source.
Same as the timer and the wire,
but that takes time too.
Ah, wait a minute.
Here's something.
[chuckles]
I'm so fucking good
at what I do.
Passion.
All about passion.
Check out the initiator.
The blasting caps.
What about them?
They're color-coated to
the manufacturer, right?
And these colors here,
what we're looking at,
come from one place
and one place only.
Well, where's that?
Atglen.
Atglen?
Atglen, Greece?
No. Atglen about
100 miles away.
Atglen.
You sure?
What?
Is there any way this bomb
could've been foreign-made?
You asking me
if I know my shit?
No.
Can I ask you
another question?
Why not?
Who's Bernadette?
You ever have something,
meant everything to you?
Yeah, I can see it
in your eyes.
Destroys you.
It's like taking
your gut and just...
spilling it
all over the floor.
Don't let it get away.
Ain't nothin' worth shit
without it.
I need something
else from you.
What's that?
A throwaway.
Something that
can't be traced.
And a silencer.
Give me a day.
- [birds chirping]
- [ominous music]
Tell me about this.
I'm sure you know
all about it.
I want to hear it
from you.
My partner and I were
trying to take down
a drug dealer
named Driscoll.
It went sour.
There was an
undercover narc from
another operation on the boat
that we didn't know about.
Charlie killed him.
Driscoll got caught.
Painted us as bent.
Were you bent?
No.
But I'm not so
sure about Charlie.
What they did to you,
they did to my last partner
in the field.
A good man
who gave them everything.
He hung himself before they
could beat him to the punch.
You lied about the bomb.
It wasn't foreign made.
I needed you
to walk away.
You knew Pierce
killed his wife.
It wasn't important to us.
So you buried the report.
We have secrets,
they have secrets.
In the end makes no
difference whatsoever.
Everyone is corrupt.
You're a cop.
You don't know that,
you don't know anything.
[Rebecca]
I am not a monster.
I liked Jennifer.
Why'd he kill her?
She was taping his
phone conversations.
She knew that whatever
he was doing, it was wrong.
"Something terrible,"
is what she said.
Where's his money?
I mean he's obviously
got a stash somewhere.
I doubt he'd trust the
bank, too easy to trace.
He didn't. I checked.
Okay, so, if I'm him,
I'm hiding, just waiting
for the right time,
grab the money,
and I'm running.
We find Pierce,
make this thing public.
It's our best shot.
[elevator bell dings]
Hey, buddy,
you got a light?
Thanks.
Say, do we know
each other?
Jack Bagby, up on nine.
Tom Loach.
- I don't think so.
- Huh.
Must've been just out
here stealing a smoke.
It's a great leveler.
Yeah.
[sharp inhale] Thanks, pal.
[phone ringing]
Yeah?
[Rebecca]
I found something.
I found a ticket
for long-term parking.
It was taped to the
underside of Pierce's desk.
Jennifer Pierce's car.
Has to be
where the money is.
Where is it?
The terminal
by the old pier.
I'll meet you there.
[suspenseful music]
[Casey] Hello?
Casey, Gallagher.
Need you to call a cop
named Schuhmann.
[horn blowing]
[gunshot, loud clang]
[suspenseful music]
[chain rattles]
[machinery whirs]
[grunts]
- Where is she?
- I don't know!
- I... Okay! Okay!
She's here somewhere! I don't know where!
I swear I don't!
Your supervisor, Tom Loach, isn't
feeding you any secrets, is he?
What?
You're stealing them on your own and
Rebecca's protecting you, right?
I don't know what
you're talking about!
- [gunshot]
- [screams]
I said hello
to Tom Loach.
He had no idea
what I looked like.
If he was trying to kill me,
he'd know what I look like.
He's investigating you
and probably her.
He found out about
the monsignor.
That's why you
killed him, right?
- Right?
- Yes! Yes!
She made me do it.
She's crazy!
The plan is to kill me
then take the car?
- Right!
- And then the car blows up.
- What? No! No!
- Yes! The car blows up!
Leaving everybody
dead, but her.
That's her plan!
- Who killed your wife?
- She did.
All I wanted
was the money!
I swear to Christ! I
didn't wanna hurt anyone!
[Danny] Rebecca!
It's over, Rebecca.
Loach knows. I know.
This was never about
your partner, was it?
Probably never
had a partner.
It's only about the money.
It's always about
the money, isn't it?
And there's a lot of it
inside the trunk of
Jennifer's car.
We can take it.
You and me.
- You fucking bitch.
- Shut the fuck up!
What do we do with him?
He doesn't count.
You fucking...
Drop it.
- I don't want to die.
- I don't wanna die either.
But if I'm gonna die,
I'm gonna die last.
Neither one of us
has to die.
He's gone.
It's only us.
Put the gun down.
You don't understand.
Nobody cares.
I tried giving them
everything I had.
And they spit it
right back in my face.
Don't you wanna...
make them pay for
what they did to you?
To your partner?
This is your chance.
All I want is to walk
away with all the money
that is inside that car.
And I want you to
walk away with me.
Tell me
that I can do this.
that we can do this.
Walk over to the trunk
and get the money.
If we don't get
blown to hell,
then we can go
before they get here.
Before who gets here?
[sirens in distance]
That's them now.
You're a fucking fool!
It's a problem of mine.
What makes you think they're
gonna believe you and not me?
Well, the bullet
that killed him
came from the gun
you're holding.
That oughta do it.
Go on.
Go get the money.
There's still time.
[sirens in distance]
[gun clatters]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[slow string music]
[phone ringing]
- [phone beeps]
- [Jimmy] Hello?
[Danny] Is he out?
He is.
Turns out Driscoll had nothing to do
with that woman getting blown up.
[ominous music]
Meet me at
the Anaconda.
Give me half an hour.
[woman sobbing]
It's a shame a man can't
make a living selling bait.
Forty-two five, Jimmy.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, I gave that up.
Must be getting old.
Wasn't quite
sure that you, uh,
picked up on that.
Charlie never
told anybody
how much he'd lost,
not even me.
I checked the
court transcripts,
that figure
never came up.
The only way you knew...
is cause Driscoll
told you.
You remember those two
hoods I told you about?
One day I ran into one
of them in the alley.
I made that prick pay.
I gave him a beating
he wouldn't forget.
But I went too far.
I cracked his head open on the
concrete, and he was dead.
I looked at the end
of the alley,
and I saw Driscoll,
he was watching me.
From that day on...
Driscoll owned me.
It don't matter what
made you bent, Jimmy.
You're either
one of them,
or you're one of us.
You told him.
You told him
we were cops.
[echoing]
He made us!
Find Driscoll!
I just told him to
turn down the buy.
But instead he tried
to turn Charlie.
He bought the 42.5
from the local Shys,
and he threatened to call it in
if Charlie didn't work for him.
Charlie turned him down.
He wasn't bent.
I need the address, Jimmy.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna give you
the address...
and then what, you're
gonna go kill Driscoll?
You think that's
gonna make it better?
Nothing gets better.
You're just gonna
get another day.
Just the next day.
That's it.
You understand
what I'm saying?
If I give you the address,
then I gotta go to Driscoll
and gotta tell him
you're coming.
I loved you, Jimmy.
You're the closest thing
I had to a father.
Ah fuck.
You gotta give up what you
most love in the world.
What you most want.
'Cause that's the thing
that's gonna kill ya.
Here's your goddamn address.
[dramatic string music]
[chuckles]
[doorbell rings]
[door opens]
Jimmy, Jimmy Murtha.
Welcome.
Yeah.
[engine turns off]
You're looking well.
Likewise.
- Is he coming?
- He's on his way.
[indistinct murmuring]
Oh, we barely
got time to eat.
Look at that!
Beautiful!
- Nice fish.
- Yeah.
You like fish, Jimmy?
Not so much.
This is wild salmon though.
You've never had it
the way I cook it.
I promise you, you're not
gonna leave here hungry.
Filet mignon of the ocean.
You know, Salmon...
swim upriver every year
against the current.
Look at that.
You got a beer?
In the fridge.
[door creaks open]
You know, up in Alaska,
they smoke this fish
on the beach.
You know that the Inuits...
make candy out of this.
They feed it to the kids.
[sharpening knife] I was
up in Alaska years ago.
I watched them.
They have a place called
The Salmon's Leap.
You know, Jimmy, you
gotta admire an animal,
a wild animal that
fights its way
against the current back
to where it came from.
[screaming]
[gurgling]
Fuck you!
[groaning]
[thunder rumbles]
[grunting]
[dial tone]
[phone ringing]
[Jimmy] Who the fuck is this?
You gave me
the wrong address.
I gave you another day!
Another day!
Where are you, Jimmy?
I...
[shallow breathing]
- [phone clatters]
- Jimmy?
Jimmy?
[slow string music]
[thunder cracks]
[acoustic guitar music]
♪ There's gonna be days ♪
♪ When you hate me ♪
♪ When I make you mad ♪
♪ There's gonna be days ♪
♪ When you don't
Know what to do ♪
♪ Maybe some days you'll wish ♪
♪ You could take it all back ♪
♪ There's gonna be days ♪
♪ When the love is so thin ♪
♪ The days are a game ♪
♪ That we just can't win ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
♪ There's gonna be days ♪
♪ You might wanna be free ♪
♪ When you hate me ♪
♪ But hold on strong ♪
♪ And don't let go ♪
♪ We'll carry on, I know ♪
♪ We can find a way ♪
♪ 'Cause you're still my girl ♪
♪ In the bad days ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ There's gonna be days ♪
♪ I haven't seen ya for months ♪
♪ Nights when my lover ♪
♪ Is a basement club ♪
♪ There's gonna be weeks ♪
♪ When you're all alone ♪
♪ Because of the days ♪
♪ I'm chained to
That open road ♪
♪ And I hope the years ♪
♪ That we come up short ♪
♪ Are swallowed by the years ♪
♪ That we make it work ♪
♪ And I pray the times ♪
♪ That our love is sweet ♪
♪ Outweigh the days ♪
♪ That you hated me ♪
♪ But hold on strong ♪
♪ And don't let go ♪
♪ We'll carry on ♪
♪ I know we can find a way ♪
♪ 'Cause you're still my girl ♪
♪ In the bad days ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ The bad days ♪
♪ Days ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ And hold on strong ♪
♪ And don't let go ♪
♪ We'll carry on ♪
♪ I know we can find a way ♪
♪ 'Cause you're still my girl ♪
♪ In the bad ♪
♪ Days ♪
[electric guitar chords]
[song fades]
[down-tempo blues song]
♪ We were oh ♪
♪ So desperate ♪
♪ That was all ♪
♪ We had at first ♪
♪ So we started ♪
♪ Huddlin' together ♪
♪ And everyone ♪
♪ Played its part ♪
♪ So much was forced ♪
♪ And the plan ♪
♪ Was not as clear ♪
♪ We were all ♪
♪ We ever had ♪
♪ To the last one
Standin' here ♪
♪ Woo, woo-oo ♪
[blues guitar solo]
♪ We were young ♪
♪ We thought we were in love ♪
♪ So it was ♪
♪ But that's not all ♪
♪ 'Cause we were brought up ♪
♪ Thinkin' life was endless ♪
♪ And everyone ♪
♪ Made its choice ♪
♪ So much was forced ♪
♪ And the plan ♪
♪ Was not as clear ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ We were all ♪
♪ We ever had ♪
♪ To the last one
Standin' here ♪
♪ But we were stuck ♪
♪ In this dance of power ♪
♪ We were all ♪
♪ We ever had ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ To the last one
Standin' here ♪
[song fades]