When you see this
You have the illusion of light
BEYOND REALITY
Friday, at 10 pm
People will spend the night in the casino
And that means, I'll be very sleepy tonight.
It's been three months working in this casino.
Everything is serious here
CCTV is everywhere
The security guards, the navy alumni
And I know everybody
Hi, Richie! How is your wife?
And everyone knows me
In a way, we're a big happy family
Richie is in charge of Blackjack
His back is not healthy
So I have to help set up a scrambler.
Diana
responsible betting table
He is my main problem
Because everyone knows I'm in love with her.
But you know what my mom told me?
If a woman ignores you
He might like you
I would deem silence - 'may'
But it seems he is not ready for a serious relationship.
Tn. Gold. The most demanding customers.
But I've learned all the complications.
And I am the one who is always told to serve him
Sometimes I hear something I should not hear.
But I do not interfere, and I will keep it a secret
So, in general. Everything is fine
But there is one thing
In the real world, my name is Michael
And I'm a con-artist
Rich's lower back made him feel pain
But it helps me. If not, I will not be able to approach the scrambler.
Con is also a game
I have prepared this moment for 3 months
The first step, Fireworks
Can I join?
The second step, Miracle Craps
According to Diana, I came to Crap's shirt to tease her
But I love money more
Much more loving money
Congratulations, sir
It's my lucky day, right?
The third step, VIP Card
I've been investigating
I have so many ideas that I want to do to him
But, I'm not a greedy person
After the mess I made
Card games will be accepted throughout the casino
We are having a technical annoyance. Please go to IT room.
While the explorers find out what happened
The richest customers are invited to the VIP room
That's what I need
Maybe this trick is very old
And the guards are now looking for who the Con Artist is
They will succeed. But this is part of my plan.
Fourth step, Elevator
- Where is the VIP hall? It's an elevator for the waiter, sir
Is it true?
How can I know which elevator is for the maid, and who is not for the maid
It's just a misunderstanding, do not worry, sir. I'll take you upstairs
Yes, it should be so
Okay, what happened?
- Sir, please be patient for a moment. Do not tell me to be patient, I will
God, this can not be trusted
- Gosh .... Be cool, sir
- You see? Everything is alright. - Fuck!
- The VIP hall is on ... Yeah, I know, you're stupid
The real chaos begins
Right after everyone thought it was over.
Please, the card
Bingo, all I need is the same desk
This is a place for high level affairs
The chips are very valuable
Thanks to Diana, I have enough capital to bet on
As long as I work here, I learn my opponents well
Nobody knows me, but they are like family to me.
Step Five, Modern Technology
God, this is amazing..I flew 3000 miles
just to get trapped inside the elevator
God, this can not be trusted
- Sir, please calm down ... No, you just calm down
The main thing is not to win every time
You have to be sure
You got a good chance
Then, add your bet
I see this is a serious game
Though I think this is a place to have fun.
Maybe we can consider
All in
I heard Dr. Ed has lost his license again
From my father, then my brothers, and now you!
Maybe you also want to give me advice?
If I can give you advice
When in doubt, do not do it!
Based on my experience
Especially if it's the last one you've got.
If I need your advice I will ask you.
Welcome
You should hear the advice of the wise.
What are you doing? - This father won.
Do not think too much, it's just money
Bring up. Thank you, ba pa k-ba pak
Why are you doing this to me? Where's my money?
Take this, just take it all
Where's my money? - I do not know.
No, not me. He!
No, no!
I'm the owner of this casino
My name is Victor
Where is the money?
I do not know
Have you tried looking in the bank?
Look, I'm one of your VIP clients
I'm on my way to victory
and then there was the con artist who thwarted my victory
What kind of operation do you run here?
God, your hand is so hard
Hear
A Con-man, take everything
He's what you should be looking for, not me
You make me rugilebih more than 5 million Euros.
I have to compensate the players, for their defeat.
You have to return all the money to me.
You have 1 week
APa7
One week?
It took 3 months to play this all
okay, okay, I got it
Okay
I have to say this, if I try to hide,
we will find you
You're an intelligent person, you know what I mean.
7 Day Countdown begins
Hello
A very good welcome
Mayki?
Mayki
- How are you? Nice to meet you again
What are you doing? You do not know him?
He is the best collector in history
They do not make people like this anymore.
Mayki, I think we will never meet again.
You should be on an island somewhere.
LEO!!
What does this symbol mean?
Wait here
Now, tell me! What's really going on?
I do not know, replaced the card in my hand
He changed your visual perception
Okay, psychic says
fortune teller, or magic practitioner
who are born with a talent for entering the subconscious,
It was like a room
Where you are allowed to perform any supernatural activity.
So, the con-man, has the ability
To change what everyone sees,
Leon, why do not you just tell me, where can I find him?
This is not a fairy tale
More precisely is the legend
We are all encompassed by the subconscious
And all the things that can not be explained,
And people with this ability can come out of the conscious realm,
leading to the collective unconscious
It's like an infinite universe
That will open unlimited possibilities.
And access to all unlimited human knowledge.
Normal people can also enter the subconscious
But they did not get out there without a special talisman.
A special kind of compass
Come on, Leon
Seriously
Is my 5 million money also there?
Here there is all information about the activities of Normal, and those with i1 capabilities
Just read it, dikantoranu
Now, I have a business
Alex, does everything go well?
As usual
It's your 5 million
Did he give you trouble? - He's as talented as me,
By the way, what is he doing?
I think he's trying to get rid of the problem now.
Who says - I'm pretty sure.
No problems in Las Vegasyang can not be solved.
This suitcase, skin quality is better
I have not seen a thing like that for a long time.
I circled half of this world to get it
Do you think you're the only one who can use this?
All right, do you agree to teach me?
You do not need to be too stiff
I offer this world to you
To save me
Shows the world you know
We work a lot together
And if you do not come back, who will I work for?
I'll be safe with this, right?
No
It's not safe enough
You need a partner
And I can not be me
Someone you can rely on someone you can trust.
Someone who really loves you
Do you have someone like that? - I will work on it.
Are you sure you want to do this?
When I was a kid
I have a two volume book
IHD Walls
The other one I always remember all my life
The story of a boy
a lonely dreamer
One day, he met someone
which entered from the right door
And then he realized that he was in magic.
In the world he lives in
He was amazed by what he saw
He loves to be there
How did he get back?
She looked up and found herself back
He's very lucky
Maybe
But when compared with your ability,
I feel he's nothing
That magic door
He wants to be a great kid
and I do not want to do the same thing
You understand?
Especially because now we have this
It's nothing
It will help you show direction in the unconscious world. But without a partner ....
You can never come back
It will be more challenging
6 DAYS
What are you doing?
I did it for you
You'll never know if someone is spying on you
Have you found your conman?
No, no, just
Just a few people I do not know
Are you sure this is real?
You're insulting me now!
All the goods here are lively
I saw everything with my own eyes.
And some of them. Some of these beautiful freaks
I see them myself
Directly
Luckily you said that to me. I saw them in your casino.
- What? Bella!
I'm stupid
Hey, what are you doing with my X-Files?
Okay, this is what I think
Being a host is an opportunity
but sometimes it takes time that I do not have.
I only have one week
But what if I can change the time to plan
With the capabilities it has
For example, can not this guy move things?
He can certainly make the dice move
I have no idea
Roulette Ball
Eric, rich kid
Son of a famous businessman
Father wants to promote his family's business
But Eric is a spoiled child
He does not want to work
He wants to have fun for the rest of his life.
You will not be able to bribe him with money
Why did not you go on with the party?
Who are you?
Let's just say I'm your good dewy mother,
who saved you from the glass tower
and who opened the world of adventure
Your talents will be needed
My mother was like a hormonal problem
If you want to listen to my dongs
Rather than having to hear the funny joke from your father
Okay, this guy, his name is Tony
He can control electronic devices.
So, he will not get caught on camera?
He's a bit coward
He was just brave with the little things
Make glass move faster
In order to break through the red light
Where are you going?
It would have been difficult for a supirtaksi to pay for his children's schooling
What do you want?
What is your ability name?
What is Bilocation?
Supertition?
You can control electronic devices remotely, right?
I do not understand what you mean
Are you from the police?
I did not do anything - not at all.
I have a quote for you
He can read people's minds
That would really help you playing poker, right?
Can he also control the minds of people?
For example, desire to raise a stick?
Her name is Tamara
But he works side by side for secret police, in whatever country
But he is very old
Are you sure you want to bring it to the casino?
You need it. Hypnotist
His name is Kevin
But he's crazy
She has autism, that sort of thing
Her parents locked her up
The doctors used it
Whatever program will be depressed.
This is a good business for you
They'll do anything for Kevin.
He is 50 years old
No, he's only 45 years old
She just drank too much
When he was drunk he would beat his wife
This is not the first time he has come to see you
But this time he came to see you
You plant the idea in his mind
So they do not drink
But it does not last long, right?
Can you get them to play?
Gambling will make their energy maximized in different ways
He will stop drinking, he will stop beating his wife
And everyone will be happy
let's play
TwoEnam
Add it
Kevin, come with me
Kevin, listen! We can be a good team, right?
- Yeah. You want me to take you away from here?
I want to, but they will not let me out.
- I'm supposed to help people. Nobody has the right to keep you here
You and I are going around the world
And help people play and win
Kevin, Kevin
I need help
Okay
Okay, let's go
Hey! Stop!
I said stop! Get him! - Come on!
They should give better food,
and cable TV
And let you go out into town
am I right? Say Yes!
The word ka n ya!
Come on, we gotta go!
Do not stop fighting! You have the right!
5 DAYS
Well, we'll start doing business
What we will do is not break the law
No one is sure that this is possible
But the risk will get smaller if we do it as a team.
Casino does not recognize the team
So we have to do it each
That's easy. Where will we start?
Craps, some players will turn, while others ...
put up bets, and everything is possible.
A good number to start
Okay, not bad for the initial experiment.
Okay, let's simulate the original casino.
Eric, if you play the dice, try not to attract too much attention.
If you see something unusual, raise your hand.
You two will help me at the poker table
No way, I have not done it for a long time.
Very good. Kevin
If you look like this in a casino,
Security will soon find out.
That's why we have Tony
Tony, did you see the camera on the side?
Can you divert it from us?
Okay
let's play
Where is the chip?
Give me 10, honey
Okay, here's the money
If it looks weird, I'll call for security
Okay Tony! Watch the camera
Kevin, distract
- Try to be more careful. - OK
I have a fullhouse
Shit!
Put your bets on!
This is mine
Leon!
Okay, you're great!
Now try to continue without me
Okay, let's play!
Put your bets on!
I bet six. Put your bet!
- Kevin, you screwed it up. Here, just wear this. It costs 200 Euro
- Give it to me! -I do not want your watch
My eyes, I can not see whatsoever
What are you doing?
We'll play once more, okay?
Shit! Tony! I can see it! Switch the camera
What are you doing to me?
I will kill you! give it to me!
What are you doing?
Shit!
I do not know, in their supervision somewhat orderly,
But somehow they can be stronger.
Makes me a little worried
What if we put a hearing aid in their ears.
Now this is not that much noticed anymore
Can he distract himself?
Tamara?
Where does he live?
4 DAYS
Veronica, you have to help me
You have to help me, Veronica!
- Tamara and I ... Do not bother me!
Whatever the price, I can pay
Come on Veronica. We do not have much time
Where is he? Where did he go?
I think you're missing something
I'm not their friend
Why are they chasing you?
Come on, I just want to help
And I have an offer for you
You can not even help yourself
The casino, your father
Go to hell!
Now I know why I have to chase you.
Why your grandma can live
He did it for the rest of his life, right?
And now no one is protecting you
I promise she'll be glad.
Please listen to me
You can earn money, and start a new life, away from here
Excuse me sir, I lost my passport. Can you help me? I need your help!
This must be fate
Have you considered my offer?
Come on! Believe me, okay?
No
3 DAYS
Thinking is karmabagi yourself.
Is the exhibit finished?
Yes, I'm sorry sir. We're closed
Too bad I'm late. Akudatang from afar and my plane delay
Sorry
The hypnotist will come to you
And will sendmuke the unconscious world.
Find a room under your subconscious for the person you need
And now, they are in your power
N0m0l` Satll
Number two
But remember
You only have a few minutes
Can you stand up, sir?
Can you stand up?
I am fine
Everything is alright
Hey, why did you go there?
Forgive me!
Yes, of course
Incredible, almost like the original copy.
I do not know how I made it
This is your unintentional masterpiece.
Extraordinary
I'll give you 500 Europads to buy this painting
Agree?
Agree
You are a wonderful friend
Can you shut up for a minute?
Can we talk?
Too many people are here
I have to go
All right, everybody
This is Veronica
I do not know how, but he can read and transmit thoughts.
He will come in our game
Before we enter the casino, we must make sure to dance in the same rhythm.
Veronica, you say there are too many people here?
I think I have an idea
Let's dance
Get Eric to hit the Konceng! - Eric, the bell!
Tell Kevin to make 2 people shout for help- Kevin tells 2 people to shout for help!
Please
Get Tony to make a short-circuit-Tony, shorted!
Veronica, we need an earthquake now everybody goes from this field.
Earthquake
Earthquake!
Not bad either
I'll treat you to a drink
All right, here's the plan
If we start by winning in small amounts.
It will take a long time
We can bi blakclist with ease, and it will harm us
That's why we're going to the biggest and richest kasinopaling in town.
They do not set limits on how many bets you can install
Which means ... One night one big advantage.
We'll all go in separately
They should not know when we are in a team.
Tony, you're going to be a transportation manager.
and security consultants
Kevin, you deserve to be the heir to the treasure.
Eric, you can be yourself
Spend your dad's money- That's easy.
And you ... will be my fiancee
Hug me, kiss me, very convincingly
You will support me even if I lose
Is that why you're taking me along? - That's just a small part.
You all ready?
2 DAYS
Tell Tony to switch the camera
Tony, the camera!
Okay, we need 10. Tell Eric-Eric, take out 10.
Okay
This must be my lucky day
Eric, it's your turn!
We seem to be good too, what do you think?
What do you mean?
You and me, we're both matchmaking
What do you think?
You forgot something
I hear all your thoughts
Look, we're like the ideal couple
We can understand each other whatsoever.
It will not be easy
But we will find a way
F, my friends. Some say if you are lucky to work, usually you are not lucky in loving |
This is for you
Eric, do not go anywhere We still have not won.
Good luck, gentlemen
Kevin, look at his eyes!
Tony, the camera!
Not bad!
Congratulations, sir
I'm back playing
Let's plug it in!
Very good!
Yes dear!
What does he do? He has to stop drinking
Do not worry, Michael. Everything will be fine
Just enjoy yourself
Everything is habist no bet again.
All right, Michael
Tony, stop it! Later we are caught!
I'll get the Jackpot! - Tony, no Jackpots!
- 34.Yes, baby!
Sir, come with me - What's wrong?
What is wrong?
Hey, I want to take my money!
Sir, please come with me- Wait a minute!
I said, please follow me!
What happened?
Are you guys crazy?
If you want your corpse found in an underground with an outlet,
just go ahead and do it
And soon you will be the security officer's month
But if you want to get out of here alive
Rich
Live, healthy, and rich
Follow what I say!
You understand?
Meet me at the tableCrabs, in five minutes
May I join?
Kevin, look at his eyes!
Tony, the camera
This is for you
Come on!
APa7
That is all?
I thought maybe we could do another job.
Something easy
It seems you like it
Then we can split up
There are many easy jobs waiting to be done.
What do you think?
We make a pretty good team
It will never end for you
Besides, I do not need money
No need money? That is interesting
No one needs money, but everyone wants it.
Why are you still here?
You can go anytime want from scratch
if you do not need money
Because it's not like you
You think you're a great professional
who knew the word took risks
You're just a selfish gambler who's stuck in their own bad habits.
You see yourself in a dark hole
play a role as a savior of yourself.
So now, no thanks
Maybe you're right
We should leave it like this
And you live in your cocoon
But nothing
Only you, your fear, your music, and nothing else
There was no hope
I want to save you You learn a lot.
But this is where our students have to stop.
You want to say I have a ball?
I can not let you go any further
Remember what I said about not taking part in this?
Yes. I'm working on it
It takes longer than I think
- How's he doing? - He made a lot of progress
Besides, she's not alone anymore. Not for long
He will not stay together for a long time.
Who was with him?
A professional person?
These people are involved in the same thing that we do
On your advice, of course
I hope he comes to me on his own free will
But we have to play it in a different way.
If a person can not have his own way
he has to give up
DAY 1
What do you want?
Come on
I try to get rid of them
Faster!
Sorry, Michael
You really are a champ
You surprised me
I have your money. Take it
I've taken it
But these people are more valuable to me
I will never work for you
What can you do?
Maybe turn that weapon into a banana.
Wow, really?
Really?
Not every time it works
Come on
Michael, I want to let you go
but I'm afraid they will not
the situation is quite serious
Sorry
No. Wait./No!
Michael!
Bastard
What? You?
What the hell?
Oh, I see. Now it makes sense
From the beginning is you! I can not believe it!
Everything is you!
I have not seen you for 10 years, and you showed up,
and you ruined my best operation!
I hope you come to see me
For your information, others do that
They went to Paris with their problems
And they do not have a team of psychic power
to rob a casino
That's why you do that?
You should realize I'll never come for you
Bring me back
Michael, you have not talked to me for 10 years!
I do not know what to do
OK
Maybe it's not the best idea, but what else can I do?
I have no idea. You can call
Somehow, I did not think about it
But I saved your life, did not I?
No. You set me up
Same as you didribuan times before.
What are you talking about?
That is your education
Do you remember what happened first?
You accept all this very negative.
Really?
OK. Maybe I'm a little overwhelmed
A little too much?
Michael. Michael!
Michael, do you remember how we dream
one day find the door on the wall?
I remember the story. Do you remember that?
Why did you say this to me?
Because I know where to find it.
You have 30 minutes for lunch
Drain
He needs to see something
Maybe he can drug at the hospital. She's getting worse
We should not take him to the clinic
We should do a lot of things differently
Tony?
Hello? / Hey, what's up?
The toilet was clogged
How can?
God, Michael! - I have nine lives
What the fuck? - Michael!
We're crazy. - What are you
Long story. Later
I'll get you out of here
And also the money
Where is Veronika?
He refused to work for Victor
He's been in a coma for a few days now.
He goes to his subconscious
Fuck it. I stopped
I also
Do whatever you want
Take them downstairs. I'll be down soon
and handle them on their own
Get rid of your hand
Keep an eye on the door
Come on
Please open the door
Extraordinary. Now what?
Now you open the safe. You have 5 minutes.
Where is he?
Above, in the hotel, room 209
Good luck!
I can not turn them off
but I can turn some off
What? Are you kidding?
Ka u ta kut?
I hate Twister
OK
Come on in action
Come on. How much longer?
Tell me // faster. - Let's hurry
Tell me how much longer. - Stop talking. Let me work!
What the hell, Jack ?! This is us!
Oh, shit./ Let's go to work!
Come on. Please
I love you, dear
Perfect
What next?
That is all
APa7
What do you mean, that's it?
We are confined in steel tombs
with a bunch of armed guards outside,
and you're gonna tell me you're over here?
This is a place in the entire casino
They can not catch us in here.
And now I have to pick up Veronika.
Shit! He tricked us
The game is over
I need you guys to help pick up Veronika,
wherever he is
You're normal. You're not like us
Continue?
We all have space
That's how I can pick her up, is not she?
Even though you got there
not sure you will get the ability
I do not need them
You're not ready for this
You will die
No one knows that for sure
But that was the only chance I had
that you have
All we have
I need you to help pick up Veronika.
- I do not know how. - Kevin, listen to me.
Get me into my subconscious
Let him try
Okay
When they come out, kill them all
Mom, why do you always have to go?
When you go home?
Nothing. Just you, your fear
your music, and nothing else
There was no hope
Raise your hands! You're under arrest!
Put your hand where I can see it.
You're just a selfish gambler who's stuck in their own bad habits.
Guilty. You were sentenced to six months in a juvenile prison.
Veronika. Where are you?
Veronika
Veronika, we have to go
What are you doing?
Veronika, can you hear me?
What are you doing, Veronika?
We have to go. Listen to me
We have no time. We must go!
Veronika!
Shit!
You can not hear me
I know how to hear me.
Veronika
Veronika, we have to go. Now
Can you feel that?
What are you talking about?
I do not know I can feel a world like this
Veronika, listen to meThe feeling is not real
You must come with me
Michael, you're dead
I'm real, and I'm alive. - Calm down
Stay with me
Veronika, listen to me. You have to believe me
I do not have much time
How about this?
I do not go
I do not have anything there
I do not go without you
Besides you, I do not have anything there
Trust me
Why did you do it?
APa7
You're risking your life for me
You know, in every human life
there are certain limits
you can not get past.
What is it because rasatakutut, or just because
he could not believe it was possible
Then I met you
And here I am
Beyond all the limits in my mind,
and all I can believe
I think to be with you forever, but that's impossible
It's the door. Let's go
For me the way it works is not like that. / What?
Why? - I have to find my own way out.
I'll come with you. - No
If you do not go now all this will be in vain.
When you wake up, I'll be there
waiting for you
You said you'd believe me, right? Yes, right?
Michael
These doors, each of them are
entrance to someone's house
someone's apartment. There are a lot of people who live there.
Some of them are very good, others are not so good.
You go in and give them a suitcase full of money
their lives will change
If you go in and take their savings
their lives will also change
But in a different way
I know. But these doors
They are closed to us We are ordinary people.
Each apartment has one door.
Everyone should live in his chance.
Michael, it will have all the knowledge
and the secrets of humanity
Everything that ever existed in everyone's mind, dead or alive
Now, can you imagine the possibilities?
We can learn anything we want.
We can get whatever we want
Please do not tell me how to think about a new business.
The business is our life. - Damn it
Are not we too old for this?
Maybe
And, there is one problem
Even all the great people who have been there have failed to return
8 minutes is how long you can survive there alone.
Then you start to forget your own existence.
In the end, your mind is gone
united with billions of previous thoughts.
You'll never get back to your senses
if someone does not remind you who you are
So, I need a partner
So you brought me here
just because you need me again
You always want to know what's behind a white door, do not you?
I thought about it, then I realized
the only person I can trust is you
You do not understand, huh?
Because of you, I involve some good people into trouble.
I still feel uncomfortable with the problem I caused
I want to help you, as your father
Now, there is one man. You know him
But this time, she will be on your side
And you have to share it with him. Take it.
This will be your compass
I think this is something you need for the rest of your life.
All my life I need a father, but yes,
this is also good. thank you
By the way, do not forget about my part.
This does not mean I'm going to be your partner
I am just kidding
No. I'm not kidding
I am just kidding. You're a good boy
Now you know who you are and what you can do.
We are in your memory. I pull you out.
Now finish yourself
How can I save them?
Look into it
and try to capture the essence
Sometimes there is more truth in the illusion,
than in reality
The key to the problem apapundi in one's mind
is stepping the right kind of downright.
No, no!
Wait!
No!
Sorry, I'm stuck
Michael./Michael
Take the money. We're leaving.
You lie to me again
Believe me, it will not happen again
Tony
Michael, are you crazy?
They will kill us
You gonna believe me?
Fraud is also a game
And the better you know your opponent
... the more money you can win
But let me tell you
ni?
This is only part of my plan
But the greatest art is to control your enemies
And the key to your victory is in his head.
What are the major weaknesses of the subconscious
like a bulletproof safe?
That is why
He's afraid of losing everything
And this?
This is the end of my plan
They descend from the other side. Everything is out, now
They escaped
All!
This is yours
Good work, everybody
I think your talent should be better utilized
rather than robbing the casino
I have a suggestion for all of you
3 MONTHS LATER
Do it. I paid 5 million for that
Wait. That's mine. - No. I hired you
No
Are you ready for the greatest robbery in the history of mankind?
Just one job then we split up.
That's what your mother told me first