It's okay,
you're gonna love it!
Happy first day of school.
Bye, sweetie.
Hi!
Hi.
Hey, I'm Sam.
Hi, I'm Julie.
- Bye!
- Bye, Mom!
I'm Hunter.
Sam's mine, right there.
The one with the glasses.
I'm Lisa.
That's my Julie.
I'm Mitchell.
Kayla's hero.
Oh. Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
You crying?
No, man.
It's a big day, that's all.
You know, can I have
a tissue, please?
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
It's a big day for all of us.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I think our daughters
are friends.
And I think that means
we're friends.
Should we go get a drink?
You okay? Yeah.
Yeah.
Do you guys wanna
go get a drink?
Ah, they made it.
You guys wanna go
grab a drink real quick?
Is he asking us if we wanna
go grab a drink?
I'm really hoping
it's coffee.
Shut the fuck up!
Happy Halloween!
Assalam!
I can see Russia
from my house!
That's right!
Right here! Whoo!
Hey, hey...
Put your seatbelts on!
Surprise!
Careful!
You're probably gonna miss these
mornings that we spend together, right?
Stop.
You're gonna make me cry, and I don't
wanna cry because it's prom night.
It's supposed to be like the
most magical night of your life,
and, you know, I'm just
so anxious aboutfl.
Well, call me
if you feel anxious.
Or maybe FaceTime me,
if it wasn't too loud.
If it was too loud, you could just...
We could wave or whatever.
That'd be funny.
And then, loan...
You know
what I was thinking?
You should send me photos
throughout the night.
Not like all night long, but if you
could do it every 30 minutes or so
then I can put together
one of those iBooks.
That would be so fun.
Yeah.
That would be a really... I don't
think you would regret that.
Hmm.
Mom?
Mmm-hmm.
Are you gonna be okay
when I go to college?
Who, me?
Yeah.
Me'?
What?
Please. Don't even
get me...
Don't even...
Please!
Okay, bye, Mom!
Okay, bye!
I love you!
Okay, I love you.
Oh, good,
you did the laundry.
Yeah, and got a totally
sleepy, happy baby.
Full-blown renaissance man.
Oh!
Beheveit
It's a good thing
she's asleep, too.
I was going
through the laundry.
Uh-huh.
Found these new thongs.
You know what I'm gonna
do with these?
"Paging Dr. Muff Diver.
Dr. Muff Diver,
"you're needed in the OR
immediately, emergency surgery."
Later on tonight, I'm tearing
these off with my teeth
like an old-school
cartoon billy goat.
Honey. Mitchell.
Those are your daughter's.
No way. Kayla wears
cleats and Bears jerseys,
not some dirty stripper
undenuean
You thought they were mine.
What am I, giving her
allowance in singles?
Go tell her
she can't wear these.
Tell her
they'll make her sterile,
like with the laptop
and my brother's balls.
We're not sure that's what
happened with your brother.
Honey, you're being
ridiculous.
Kayla's becoming a woman.
This isn't the time to tighten your grip.
It's the time to loosen it.
This? This means
we tighten the grip.
This isn't built for comfort,
it's built for speed.
We need to slow her
the fuck down.
The appliances go in
after the backsplash.
We've done it
the same way every time.
Uh-huh. All right,
put him on the phone.
I'm in the bathroom.
Thanks,
I was looking for that.
You mind telling me
what this is?
Uh, fuzz.
Yeah.
Yeah, fuzz.
It's what I thought it was and
then on further investigation,
it is clearly an unraveled
filter of a cigarette.
Kayla, are you a smoker?
What? No.
I'm not a smoker, Dad.
Hey, haven't you seen the billions of
ads that tell you not to do this stuff?
Dad! You can't teach someone
not to try things. Okay?
That's what trying things
is for. To teach you things.
It's a contradiction.
It's like telling me not to go for
a triple on a base hit to the gap
when I've made
a good turn around first
and I know that the right
fielder has a weak arm.
Damn it, you're smart.
Okay. Yeah. All right. Time
to get ready for school, Dad.
Okay, all right.
Julie! Sam!
Hey, girl!
Whoa!
I almost died.
Prom night!
I'm so, so excited!
Me, too.
Mmm. I love you.
I love you, too.
All right.
We're so gross.
I know.
People are looking at us.
I don't care.
We better get "Cutest
Couple" in the yearbook.
I'm having sex.
- That's great!
- I'm having soup.
No. Tonight.
With Austin.
Wait, you're finally gonna do it?
Yeah.
I mean, you know, we've been dating
for six months and we love each other
and I just awkwardly got my pediatrician
to put me on birth control.
But she gave me
a sticker.
Two because
I was good, so...
I know it's kind of corny or whatever
but it just seems like prom night,
it's kind of perfect,
you know?
We're gonna have,
like, dim lighting
and rose petals on the bed
and the scent from that candle
that gets me horny
every time I pass it
in Walgreens.
All candles get me horny.
I'm gonna
look into Austin's eyes
and then he's gonna
look into mine
and then we're gonna touch
each other's faces, you know?
For, like, a long time.
Like, a long time.
Just to, like, connect.
And then we're gonna...
Ka pow.
All right, fuck it, I'm in.
- What?
- I'm in.
I'm having sex tonight, too.
Uh...
Just like that?
Yeah. I mean, why not?
Because it's your first time
and your first time should be
special and perfect.
Yours can be special
and perfect.
Mine is gonna be tonight,
and with that dude.
They're just brownies,
they're not, like...
Connor Aldrich?
Your lab partner?
Yeah. What? You haven't
even hooked up with him.
You haven't even seen his thing yet.
What if he has a weird one?
They're all weird.
Penises are not for looking
at, they're for use.
They're like plungers. Listen,
my student athlete days
are over.
Tonight is the beginning
of my adult life
and for the first time
I can do whatever I want.
So I wanna go to prom, get drunk,
get potted up on weed
andlose
my goddamn virginity.
We're gonna have the same
first-time sex anniversary.
We can go to dinner every year
and commemorate it.
Olive Garden.
Yes! Olive Garden.
Breadsticks for life, bitch!
Oh, my God! It is gonna
be such a relief
to get this over and done
with before college.
Um...
No, I mean, like...
No, it's cool.
I just don't think
I'm there yet.
You know, maybe something might
happen tonight with me and Chad,
but I don't think sex
is gonna be that thing.
Sam?
But you never know
what could happen.
I mean, maybe my inner sexual
Smaug will emerge from its keep
and spread its mighty wings.
I never know
what you're talking about.
Yeah, me neither.
Oh...
Julie, is that you?
So realistic.
Ugh.
Come on, Sam,
we're waiting.
Be right there!
All right.
There she is.
Took me 20 minutes to figure out
how to do video on this thing
but I finally got it.
Nope.
I took a picture of myself.
Siri, video, please.
Wow! That Chad is going to rip
through his little tuxedo pants.
Mom!
What?
That's gross.
Why?
Because you're practically imagining
your daughter in sexual congress.
You sicko.
I was just trying to connect with you.
You never talk to us anymore.
Hey, I got this.
Okay.
Prom night, huh?
I got sad and reflective
on my prom night, too.
You were?
Yeah.
I was scared I wasn't
gonna stay friends
with the guys I had been
around most of my life.
But I was able to...
Hey, baby, I love you so much.
You just really freaked her out.
Sweetie, if you're worried about that
at all, just know you shouldn't be.
You never stay friends
with people from high school.
I mean, the oldest friend
I have is Jan from work
and I've known her
for three months.
Who's Jan?
You know Jan, babe. She
draws those silly cartoons.
Oh, racist Jan.
Yeah, that's the one.
Who you are today
is not who you're going to be.
And that's okay.
That's good therapy.
And who you become will be
so different that your friends
won't understand you anymore
and then you will wake up
and realize
these friendships are over. This
feels like a very painful divorce,
just like the one I had
with your father,
but then you'll find a Frank.
Uh, I appreciate that,
but that's not my deal.
I'm still cool with a lot of
my boys because on prom night,
me, Dennis, Matt, and Cory all convinced
our friend Steve to join the Army.
He fought
in the Persian Gulf War.
He died right away.
But once you go
through something like that,
you're bonded for life.
The bedrock of deep meaningful
friendships is shared experience.
I thought they were gonna
put him in the Reserves.
That is some horseshit.
Hmm.
Wow.
You look so beautiful!
Turn around.
Wow.
Oh, my goodness.
So what's the big plan
for after prom?
Uh, we're just
going to Austin's.
You really like him, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, I mean... Yeah, he's cool.
It's not like serious or anything.
His mom told me
he got into UCLA.
That's nice.
Yeah, I mean, it's good.
You remember that time when, like,
I thought about going to UCLA?
Yes.
That would've been crazy. That
would've been the worst mistake ever.
I don't think it would've been
that huge of a mistake.
Uh,yes,
it would have.
University of Chicago is perfect.
It's 45 minutes away.
So that way you're gone
but you're not gone, gone.
But I'm gone.
Right. But not, like, gone.
Right, but, like,
I'm going to college
and, like, I'm not gonna live at home.
So I'm, like, I'm gone.
Mmm-hmm.
Why are my boobs so big?
Ready, Kayla?
Yep.
And now, standing at 5' 7",
5' 9" if you count the heels,
straight out of Great Lakes High School,
the prettiest girl in all of prom,
Kayla Mannes.
Oh.
Just high-fives from now on.
Okay.
Oh, honey, I never thought
I'd see you in a dress!
Technically
it's not a full dress.
Some material is missing
from the middle there.
Okay.
You look great.
All right, yeah,
I think it's time to go.
Yes. Yeah. Honey,
we gotta go.
Honey?
Dad, are you okay?
It's like when
he watched Frozen.
Come on.
Hi, how are you?
Hi!
Hi! How are you?
Hi, Marcie.
Oh. Uh-huh.
Hey!
Hey, Mitchell.
Haven't seen you in a while.
Yeah.
You know, I was worried when I never
heard back from you about hot yoga.
Called you a bunch of times. I ended up
having to eat that two-for-one Groupon.
Oh, yeah, I don't really
do the hot-yoga thing.
We should catch up, though,
right?
Yeah.
Like a lunch, I don't know.
Yeah, maybe. Yeah.
Give me a call.
I've been calling you.
Mmm-hmm.
It doesn't work.
It's not effective.
I don't even know!
Wait, you guys.
Wait, this is, like, the best
lighting with the Valencia filter...
Oh, God. All right.
Here we go.
Yeah, okay. That's enough.
One more.
We're good.
Oh, my God, we need to
get this party started.
Ooh, okay, Julie.
Hmm.
I got you something.
It's coconut oil.
For lube.
I hear it works just as well and it
makes blowjobs taste like Almond Joy.
Thank God it doesn't
taste like Mounds.
I'd rather eat 10 dicks
than one Mound.
Thank you. That's so sweet!
Oh, my God, I'm so excited.
Me, too. You have to text me,
like, right away.
Oh, my God, we're gonna be
doing it at the same time.
Oh, my God. We have
to talk about it tomorrow.
Yeah. You're gonna know
every detail.
There's gonna be so much to talk...
Guys? Hey, guys!
I want in on this sex pact.
Are you sure? You don't have to
do this just because we are.
No, that's not why.
I want to have sex.
Yeah. That's something all
three of us have in common.
Mmm-hmm. Chad is gonna tap
that ass with his penis
and I doubt we'll have anal
the first time, but...
All right!
This is gonna make tonight
even more perfect.
Yeah.
It's gonna be the three of us!
Yes!
Prom night,
motherfuckers!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Rudy, it's coming up.
Turn left, bro.
Jesus, Rudy!
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
It's my fucking dad.
Yeah! Prom night,
bflchesl
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, God, it's him.
Arms up. Yo!
We gonna light
it up like it's prom night
Taio Cruz.
Like it's prom night
You got this, girl.
Don't mess this up because
that limo is totally awesome.
Sam!Sam!
Taio Cruz. Whoo.
Sorry.
30W. on!
Whoo.
You're so grown up!
Dad, what are you doing here?
You think I'm gonna miss the most
important night of your young lfie?
That's graduation.
No. Graduation's for losers.
I didn't even go
to my graduation.
But prom night,
that's a big one.
Prom was the best night
of my life.
I think about it every day
and I want you to have
the same experience.
Tonight you have fun,
you don't worry about any rules
that your mom or Frank laid down.
No one gives
a fuck about Frank.
All I know is this. You look amazing
and I would love to grab a quick pic.
No. Go stand with the other
parents and try to be normal.
Sam, I'm not a normal parent.
I don't even...
Holy shit,
you invited Hunter?
No, of course not.
I haven't talked to him since
he and Brenda got divorced.
You know he calls me all the time?
What?
He wants to play darts.
I don't play darts!
Darts?
You kidding me?
Anyway, I can't hang out with him.
I'll be guilty by association.
No. No, l will never forgive
that babysitter fucker.
Hey, Hunter!
Hey, man. Good to see you.
What up?
Ah...
Ah!
Did you have
another daughter?
I did. I did.
Thank you. It's been wonderful.
Yeah.
I'm thinking about doing that again.
You know, the whole second round?
I think a lot of dads kind of get
it right the second time around.
Or, you know, you could just
raise the one that you have.
Well, I did. Too late for that.
Raised, job done.
Hi, honey.
Actually, I heard
if you spend a significant amount
of time with your children
that you develop some kind of,
like, telekinetic bond with them.
Is that true?
I've heard. Mmm-hmm.
I hope it's not true because if it is, Sam
has been looking at a lot of Asian porn.
My wife's Asian.
Indian.
That's Asian.
This is more like, uh...
It looks like the typical Asian.
Yep, good seeing you, man.
Okay, good to see you, brother.
You know what I mean.
Who's this guy?
Who are you?
Dad, this is my date.
Hi.
Uh, it's great to meet you,
sir. I'm... I'm Connor.
Connor and I were in the same
science class. We're lab partners.
Yeah. We're working
on our chemistry.
Uh...
I'm gonna get a napkin,
if that's cool.
Okay.
Okay, so, uh...
With this, it's one shot
to the groin, stab, and drag.
I refuse to believe she couldn't
do better than that loser.
Oh, I think Chad seems nice.
Chad? No, Chad's amazing.
Look at that fedora.
I'm not talking about Chad, I'm
talking about fucking Frank.
What a dick.
Frank does not seem
like a dick to me.
He seems like a nice guy.
And you know what?
Don't blame Brenda.
It's really hard being alone.
Let's just agree
to disagree on Frank.
Here they come.
Okay, just be cool.
He's gonna talk about his
tow truck company instantly.
I guarantee you he's gonna
throw that shit in my face.
Be cool, be cool, be cool.
Brenda.
Hunter.
Frank.
Lisa.
What'd I do?
I'm sorry, I don't know why I just said
your name like that. This is so nice.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay.
No,no,no.
Leese,Leese,Leese.
I gotta go get
Julie's wrap.
Mmm.
Were you gonna let our daughter
take a fucking Lyft to prom?
What is this, Afghanistan?
How'd you pay
for that limo, Hunter?
'Cause I know your credit's
in the shitter.
It is.
Because I bought
your mom a wheelchair.
She's gonna pay you back.
With what money, Brenda?
Can she pay me back with crackers
that she steals from restaurants?
I don't wanna talk about your mom, I
don't wanna talk about her wheelohair.
All I care about is that my daughter
has the greatest night of her life.
If it was her greatest night,
you would not be here.
Oh, what a sick burn. All
right, all right, all right.
Good. Wait,yo,yo,yo,
we're all adults here.
Let's not make it
uncomfortable.
If you're gonna be around more,
let's have a beer sometime.
Okay, first of all, I don't wanna
go to have a beer with you.
I don't wanna hang out with you. I don't
like you, I don't like your wife.
I don't like your guys' deal. I
think it sucks and it's played out.
Hey, if you ever change
your mind, here's my card.
Ah, here we go.
"Tow with Frank." Where'd you
come up with that name?
It's very straightforward.
All right, I'll tell you this.
The design of that card
is pretty cool.
And my favorite part
is right fucking there.
Oh.
Wow, that is just...
No, that's us, Frank.
You've taken about 15 goddamn selfies.
I got it. I got it.
Yeah!
All right.
Bye, Mom.
- Have fun, honey. Okay.
- I will.
Bye,Dad.
Remember, stab, turn, drag.
I don't have the knife, Dad.
Yes, you do.
Check your clutch.
Ugh.
Hey, uh,
it's been a pleasure, sir.
I really, um...
I'm honored.
Oh!
Intense, professional grip.
Cheers!
Take it easy,
big guy. Hey, uh...
You guys have
a good night, too, you know.
Thank you.
See that smirk?
What was up with that smirk?
You are intense.
Sam.
Oh.
Hey! Mr. Lockwood.
Hey!
Pleasure to meet you.
Chad, yes.
Come on, man. Bring it in.
Yes. Good. Yeah.
My hat?
I wanna talk to Sam real quick.
Yeah, okay.
Let me get a picture
real quick.
Chad.
Oh.
Real quick photo. Just,
just so fast. Okay.
Don't even fuck with the filter.
Just plain.
Here we go.
There we go.
And then you wanna get a quick
one of me and Chad real quick?
That sounds cool. Yep.
Okay.
Sammy, here you go, baby. Real quick.
Just a couple fun ones.
Like this?
Bros.
Duck lips.
And then just kind of a...
Julie. Can I talk to you
a second?
We gotta go.
I love you.
I'd really like
to talk to you.
But I really gotta go.
Okay, fine. Just don't
forget your wrap.
It's okay. I don't think
lneedit
Are you sure?
Because we live in Chicago,
and it's chilly.
I don't know
about other places,
but it gets cold
in Illinois.
It's not that cold tonight, so
I don't think I need it, okay?
Okay, Julie, wait.
So you'll call me when you get
to Austin's after prom? Right?
Right.
Okay.
I love you.
Okay. I love you.
Okay!
Okay.
This is so cool!
on!
Blow it out!
Chad, I, um, I saw you
do Pippin last year.
That was really good.
Yeah, you're a really good singer, man.
What are you doing this year?
We're actually doing Arnold,
which is an all-male version of Annie.
Caught you drinking!
Just kidding, y'all.
I may look like a parent
but I assure you,
I am no narc.
Thank you, sir.
Not done yet.
Name's Rudy.
I did not go to my prom. No.
My leg was crushed by a cement
truck so I could not dance but...
So I've made it
my mission in life,
my whole career, to make sure
that little kids like you
have a wonderful night
to remember forever.
So just sit back, relax,
and enjoy your prom night.
Okay.
Oh, fuck,
that was the turn! Fuck!
Hey, Leese?
You got any S.O.S. pads?
I'm soaking those pans, but you burnt
the shit out of that mac: and cheese.
Sponge just isn't
gonna cut it.
Thanks for helping clean up.
Don't mention this one.
I mean, Marcie brought
the baby home early and...
I gotta keep busy. I gotta keep my
mind off of Kayla and "Connor."
That's not the right way
to use those.
'Cause his name
is actually Connor. So...
It's okay.
UCLA?
Uh-huh.
I didn't mean to snoop,
but I'm...
No, no. It's okay.
I mean, I don't think
it's a real thing.
She's not actually gonna go.
I think she just applied
for fun. She didn't...
Why, have you heard
differently?
I would assume it's to go, but she very
well could have applied ironically.
I mean,
you know millennials, right?
Hmm.
Wherever she goes...
You're gonna have a bunch
of time on your hands.
You oan figure out what you wanna
do for the back nine of your life.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
I think Julie
left her laptop open.
Julie's doing
a lot of texting.
Mmm-hmm.
ls everything okay?
Maybe we should
check to see?
Peace of mind.
Yeah.
What the hell is that?
I have no idea.
What are you
still doing here?
Hey, your, uh, mac: and
cheese is messed up.
Are you guys
snooping on your kids?
That is not cool.
No, it's not snooping
if the information shows up.
That's exactly
what snooping is.
No, it's like
the Patriot Act.
Well, it's not like
It's like snooping.
Okay. We don't know what
they're talking about, so...
What?
Okay.
Oh, is it like puzzles?
Ooh, I love puzzles.
Husk saw Inferno.
Yeah, great.
What are they saying?
Okay, so there's something
about an eggplant handshake.
Eggplant agreement.
Yeah. They got an agreement
to make eggplant Parmesan.
No, eggplants are dicks
in teenage emoji language.
What? LISA: You know
what, that's true.
Julie told me that the emojis have...
They all have secret meanings.
Mmm-hmm.
So, like, trees are weed
and snowflakes
are cocaine and
that thing is "yas queen."
'(as queer“!
What the hell is that? You've
never heard of "yas queen"?
No.
All right, grandpa.
Hold on. Julie is making some kind
of a dick-related agreement here.
Kayla is in on
the agreement.
No fucking way.
Okay, clown face.
What the fuck does that mean?
That means
she's down to clown.
- Okay.
- Three eggplants?
And look at the drool coming
out of that smiley face.
You wish that was drool.
That's cum, my man.
Stand down!
It is. Look, it's cum.
He's, like...
This is sex if I've ever seen
it illustrated in emoji form.
No, no, no. Maybe not. They're
best friends. They're just saying,
like, "You're okay with me.
"You're okay to me. You're okay to
me." You say that to your friends?
Whenever I see my friends, I go, "Hey!
You're okay with me."
I don't use these!
Hold on. Agreement hands,
agreement hands,
agreement hands. This is a...
It's a sex agreement.
They're making a sex pact.
They're gonna lose their
virginity on prom night.
That cannot be a sex pact.
That? That is friendship.
And that is the bond of friendship
that can never be broken.
I mean, maybe.
Yeah.
Oh! Just look, they wrote
"Sex Pact 2018."
I fucking knew it!
I love puzzles.
I told you guys.
Have you seen Inferno?
Call your kid. Leese,
have you seen Inferno?
Have you guys seen Inferno?
I figured it out in two seconds.
Did you see Inferno?
The guy jumps off the thing in the
beginning. He's got a virus.
Have you seen Inferno
with Tom Hanks?
Okay.
Okay, she's not answering her phone.
Yeah, Kayla isn't either.
Okay, what the heck
is happening?
She's always been
honest with me.
She's always
told me the truth,
and now I'm just swimming
in a pool of lies.
Okay. Here's what's
gonna happen.
She's gonna have sex
with that Austin kid
and then she's gonna think
that she has all these feelings,
which she does not
actually have,
and then she's gonna drive
across country
and follow him
and ruin her fucking life!
Okay, I think that's a pretty big leap
to make when you read a couple...
I have invested
every single piece of my being
into preparing Kayla
for success, and now this?
She is about to have sex with
some dipshit with a "man bun."
You're not using those
in the right way.
Hey, can we all come back
to "Planet Earth"?
'Cause this is not
a big deal.
They're teenage girls.
They have sex.
Do you freak out when you see
a bee fucking a flower?
I'm gonna stop her.
I'm in.
Let's cockblock
those motherfuckers.
Whoa...
No, sir. Uh-uh.
No, no, no, no. I promised Sam
the greatest night of her life
and if you guys fuck up
your daughters' night,
it's gonna fuck up my daughter's
night, and that shit is"not cool."
I don't give a fuck
what's cool with you.
Let's go, Mitchell.
I'll drive.
Hey! Hey, hey, wait!
No,no,no.
You wanna go?
You got to go through me.
Oh, Jesus. Okay,
you called my bluff. Wait.
Wait! Hey!
Get off! Get off of me!
Get off! HUNTER: Hey! Hey!
Not cool!
This is "not cool"!
Hey! What's the plan?
This is stupid.
Fuck off.
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
What the fuck are you doing?
I just need to talk to my
daughter for five minutes.
Get out of the car!
You get out.
You get out!
Stop saying what I'm saying!
Stop saying what I'm saying.
Stop! Okay. Listen, listen.
Hey!
Okay, everyone calm down,
calm down.
The window!
No, the window!
Hey! What the fuck! No!
Damn, these are new shorts!
Truce, truce!
Truce, truce, truce.
I'm so sorry!
Oh, my fucking God!
Uh...
I'm sorry, man.
It's not gonna work.
You're not Schwarzenegger!
How is that possible?
Oh, shit!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
My balls! My balls!
Your ass is so...
Hey! Hey! Not cool!
Ah! You're bullying me!
This is bullying!
What you're doing is wrong!
You know your daughter's
in this stupid sex pact, too.
Yeah, and she's not gonna
do anything about it, okay?
Like you would know
what your daughter's gonna do.
Okay, first of all, ouch!
Second of all, I know nothing is
gonna happen with Sam because...
Because she's gay.
Really? Did she come out
to you?
No, of course not.
She barely speaks to me.
Then how do you know?
Because, bro,
I'm her dad. And there's
just some things you know.
Chad is nothing.
He's like a beard.
Or whatever a lesbian beard is.
A merkin?
I don't know. The point is,
I guarantee you
they don't even kiss, okay?
I'm not worried about that.
I'm worried about you two
dicks fucking up her night.
Okay, well, what you don't
understand is that
sex can be very confusing
for young girls,
and make them say things and do
things that they might regret.
Like dropping out of college
to follow around
the Dave Matthews Band
with a guy they think they love who
then winds up getting them pregnant
and then leaving them
for the girl who makes grilled cheese
sandwiches with hash aioli on them.
Yeah, that is
a extremely specific scenario
and that won't happen
to Julie.
Dave's not even touring right now.
He's taking time off for fatherhood.
It was me, you idiot.
Me. That happened to me.
Yeah.
You weren't ready!
Okay, one more.
Smile.
I closed my eye.
Oh, my God!
You guys!
This is our song!
Do you remember when we
got snowed in at Sam's
and we played this like
over and over? Yes!
We have to dance!
This is our jam!
Hey!
Hey! I want a drink.
Okay, yeah, let's go get one.
No,no,no,no.
Like, a drink.
Oh, you want a drink-drink.
Yeah.
Okay, let me call my guy.
Hello, Mr. Drink Drink.
Let's go get fucked up!
Okay.
Kayla, Kayla! Ah.
Hey.Chad!
I'm gonna go
get, uh, some dessert.
Get me two!
Hey, Angelica,
it's a nice cape.
Uh, hey, Sam,
thank you.
Um, yeah, it's a Galadriel cape that I
made a couple months ago for LordCon.
Figured I could wear it again.
Not too much overlap
on the guest list.
Yeah. Totally.
Who'd you come here with?
Um... Just my friends.
Lauren and I broke up.
Oh!
No hard feelings though.
Um, she's still
a little confused.
How do you think one becomes
not confused?
It's probably different
for everyone.
But for me, when I kissed Brad
Markowski, I started to suspect it,
and then last year when I touched Dash
Lowenstein's dick, I was like,
"Fuck no." It was like
holding a dead snake.
Hmm.
But I guess you never know
until you try.
Uh, before I do
drink this, though,
I just wanna let you know
that I am fully planning
on having sex tonight.
With... With you.
Yeah, I mean, wherever
the wind blows us.
Well, the Wind's gonna
blow us there.
Wherever the night
takes us.
It's gonna take your penis
into my vagina.
Okay. Uh... You know,
if the universe wills it.
And the universe
will will it.
Thanks for letting me know.
I guess.
Uh,yeah.
Oh, my God!
I warned you.
This is what gin tastes like?
No, no.
I've heard that gin sucks and this sucks.
No, it's...
I made it. Um...
Oh.
This is so dumb. Okay?
Yeah, our kids are gonna hate us
because you're gonna humiliate them.
I'm not gonna humiliate Julie.
We're best friends.
I'm the cool mom.
Hunter, don't make me
sit on your balls again.
Stop, stop, stop it,
stop, stop!
This is how they're gonna
be remembered in high school,
as the weirdos whose parents
dragged them out of prom
because they were afraid
of their sexuality.
It's not something that should be
feared, it should be celebrated.
And... And we have to empower
these young women.
I mean, what year
is it, guys? It's 2018.
- Jesus Christ!
- Oh, gross.
Okay, you know what?
That's an unfortunate
coincidence.
Get a fucking room!
Let's take a picture!
Kayla! Let's take a picture
right now.
Okay, cool!
Cheese!
Oh, my God, my mom called
me, like, 15 times.
She's crazy!
Nope.
No. That's a no.
That's kind of funny.
Boom! Airplane mode.
No.
Yeah. We're flying
the friendly skies now.
Yeah, until she freaks out.
Look, can we please
get out of here?
No! We can't go right now.
They haven't even played
me and Austin's song yet.
How are we gonna
get in the mood?
I don't know,
light your Walgreens candle.
That's later.
Don't you want... Look, look.
Jake Donahue is just warming up.
Don't you wanna see him breakdance
and probably hurt himself?
- No. I don't.
- It's gonna be so good.
Do you remember
at the Sadie Hawkins Dance
when he tried to do the worm and he
fell and broke his two front teeth?
Yeah, he had to go to the hospital.
I have pictures.
It was great.
And this is gonna be better!
No,no,no.
So we're staying.
No! Julie, Julie. I promise
that you're gonna dance to your
song with your boyfriend tonight.
This place is dying, okay?
We gotta get out of here.
Okay, fine.
Okay, cool, let's go.
We're going
to the lake house!
I'm not sure
that this was worth $85.
Where's Chad?
What?
Oh, he's probably
out on the dance floor.
I'm gonna go find him
and meet you guys outside.
All right.
The fuck?
Smirking little piece of shit.
Top knot. Top knot.
Let's get him.
Yeah, you guys go do that.
I'm gonna get some punch.
All right, asshole, what'd
you do with my daughter?
Two of you guys have the same
shitty haircut? Hey!
Look at me.
My hair's too long.
Hey! You can't go around
assaulting children.
You have to blend in
if you want
some information, okay?
So just... Just be cool. God!
Okay.
Julie?
Prom night, huh?
What?
Just special night.
Gotta try.
Chad?
Yeah?
This is my moment.
You ruined my moment!
Fuck your moment.
What happened
back there?
What happened is that my daughter was
kissing Chad even though she hated it...
And I've been dragged in this
situation by you two fucking idiots!
Just ignore him.
Great idea.
We're gonna go
to Austin's house.
Julie said that's where the after-party
is and we'll get 'em there.
And that sounds
like a plan.
Hey, how dare you ignore me.
We are in this situation because
you two raised a couple of bigots
who have shamed my daughter into
losing her virginity to the wrong sex.
Shame!
My daughter is not a bigot.
We go to all of the marches.
We went to the Tax Day March
and nobody goes to that shit.
Nobody!
Ignore him.
It's hard.
Yeah, it is hard.
'Cause I don't quit.
And now I have
to go rescue Sam
because she is scared
and confused
and I know what it's like to be ostracized
by society for your sexual preferences.
Sleeping with women that aren't your
wife isn't a sexual preference.
No, it is! I prefer them.
How parents can let their kids
play music this loud?
We all share this planet.
This is how loud
I listen to my music, dawg.
Probably won't even be
able to hear us.
It's so dark in there.
They could be in the backyard playing
two-on-two hoops. I don't know.
Oh. I found a big window.
No, no, don't,
don't, don't.
Trust me. Do not look
in that window.
What? Look at me.
Do not look in this window.
Do not look
in this fucking window!
Julie's red dress!
Shit!
Shit! Oh, God.
I know this must be
tough for you.
I mean, if...
Hell, if that was Kayla
in there, I'd...
I'd kill myself.
Nope.
That's the wrong thing
to fucking say right now.
Stop them. Stop it!
I can't... Wait.
Hey! It's not Julie.
It's not Julie.
What?
Shit!
It's Austin's parents.
Good for them.
Really going at it.
Always wanted to do this. I've always
wanted to watch people have sex.
Oh, my God,
he's yanking her hair.
Ow. That looks like it hurts.
Yeah, we shouldn't
be looking, man. Come on.
She runs the risk
of, like, dislocating her hip.
Hey, Mitchell. You're being
a fucking perv, dude.
Don't look.
What happened?
We locked eyes
and then he finished.
That means his load
is on your soul for eternity.
Holy shit!
Oh, shit, he's coming.
I'll pretend I'm a plant.
Mitchell?
What are you doing?
Lisa?
Hey,Ron!
What are you guys
doing out here?
Hi!
Hey!
What a nice surprise!
We thought the kids were here. We
didn't realize you guys were here.
Oh, Cath and I were just having
a little prom night role-play.
You know, to keep the sex life alive.
Prom night!
Where are the kids? Um, do you
know where the kids are'?
The kids are at
Kyler Montero's lake house.
How do you know that?
Because Austin told us.
Yeah.
He's texted me, like,
19 times tonight.
Ugh. Oh, my God. Yeah, we
tell each other everything.
It's unbelievable.
He knows about prom night.
Well, you know.
I'm sorry, you...
You tell your son about your
sex games with your wife?
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Can't do that. There's a line.
Yeah, it's weird.
It's... It's weird.
We have a very
open family here.
Yes, we do.
We don't hide anything.
You know what,
what is Kyler's address?
Okay, listen, I feel like I
can't betray Austin's confidence in me
and frankly if Julie wanted to
tell you where the house was,
she would've told you.
Uh-uh.
I got...Hold on, hold on.
Buh,buh,buh.
Give us the address.
Or my giant friend's gonna tear
your husband's dick off.
Yeah.
No, I'm not.
Excuse me?
No, no, no. That's...
That's good.
And, uh, sorry to interrupt
your evening.
I hope you guys enjoy
the rest of your love-making.
- Ah, fuck!
- Come on, man.
- What was that about?
- What?
Hey, man, thank you for
killing my daughter's hymen.
I don't think so.
Kyler Montero's lake house?
Marcie did the bathroom.
She's gonna know the address.
So let's just go.
All right, dope.
Dope.
Oh, my eyes!
Yeah!
Okay, come on in now.
It's all fun and games
until there's a decapitation.
I don't need any more
dead girls on my conscience.
I'm sorry, Rudy!
We just had to check that off
the old prom bucket list.
Oh, my God! Sam!
Come here. Yeah!
Move, Chad!
Chad, you want a drink?
No.
What you got there?
This is a very, very special reduced
hash oil of my own invention.
It has rosemary essence
for blood flow,
a curcumin extract from turmeric
to reduce inflammation.
And it gets you super baked.
All right! Let's do it.
Do I just suck'?
Yeah, you press the button and
you take, like, a little puff.
Or a really, really
big one. Okay.
And then you just hold it
for, like, a beat.
You guys know that Tanner Dunn's
parents rented out a whole floor
of the Park West Hotel
for an after-party?
What?
Um... Yeah...
He, uh...
I guess they're super loaded and
they're still proud of him,
even though it took him, like,
six years to graduate.
I remember him. He got to miss
school when his kid was born.
Yeah, that guy.
You should definitely
let it go now.
Holy shit.
Oh, yeah. I can run a six-minute mile.
My lung capacity is legit.
No!
One more selfie.
And this time let's pose
like Kanye.
No!Boo!
Yes.
You take too many pictures.
They don't look like him.
It's just a bunch of
paint samples and swatches.
Hunter! Quiet!
Why do I have to be quiet?
Shit would not fly
if Marcie found out.
Who wears the pants
in this house, dawg?
- I do.
- Oh!
Mmm.
This is soy creamer, are you sure?
It's pretty freaking rich.
This is so messed up.
Who are you to get involved
in our daughter's sex life?
Honey, I was just trying...
No, don't "honey" me.
Did your dad try to stop you
when you lost your virginity?
That's totally different.
It is not different.
It's a double standard.
Oh, when a guy loses his virginity,
it's no big deal, it's celebrated,
but if a girl does, it's some
sort of big loss of innocence?
- Yes!
- But come on, you guys,
it's the same damn thing.
Marcie!
Stop talking.
Just give us the address.
Honestly, Lisa, I can't
believe you're on their side.
"Side"? This is not
some philosophical debate.
We're trying to stop our daughters
from some kind of sex pact
that they've planned and not
thought through all the way.
That is such bullshit.
How do you expect society
to treat women as if they're equal
when their own parents won't?
I don't know about that.
I'll deal with society tomorrow. Right
now I'm thinking about my daughter.
Well, that's convenient.
Yeah. You know what?
Go ahead
and be part of the group
that perceives women as little damsels
in distress that need saving.
Who cares about us
not getting paid as much
or not having control
of our own bodies?
Can you please not talk to me like I'm
someone who bombs abortion olinios?
I think we're a little off-topic.
We need the address.
I just can't believe
that you think Julie shouldn't
be free to explore her sexuality
in the same way
that boys are.
Girls and boys
are very different.
Guys will take
whatever's in front of them.
We have these
feelings and then
your parents won't
let you see the man.
And then he just writes
a lot of letters
but you don't get them because
your mom doesn't give them to you
and then it starts raining
really hard
because he built
a house for you.
And then, it's...
Mitchell, did you get
the address?
- Yup!
- What?
I'm really sorry.
I'll call you tomorrow.
I'm just really stressed out.
It was so good to see you.
Was that The Notebook?
Fucking fuck off, Hunter!
God damn it! Mitchell!
I love you, I'm doing this
for our daughter, I'll be home late!
Shit!
To the loss of our innocence.
Whoo!
Oh!
Come on!
You guys!
This is the best night!
lam so drunk, super high
and Connor has a little
something-something that I feel
I need to go check out.
All right.
It's fuck o'clock.
- No way. You, too?
- Yep.
These are macarons...
Ooh!
With a very special concoction
of mine that I call Wavy Davy.
So it's DMT that I get
from the dark web.
And then there's
a little tiny bit of Xanax
to just kind of take the edge
off, you know. It's pretty tight.
Sounds pretty tight.
And then I bake it
into a white chocolate macaron
andithas,Hke,
a raspberry filling
that's both light and fluffy but
also very flavorful and satisfying.
Are you ready?
Uh, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, let's do it.
Okay. Let's go.
Mmm.
It's yum.
So what do we do?
We just walk in
and flick the lights on and
off until the kids come?
Just act cool and young,
and maybe we'll just slip in.
Mitchell, untuck your shirt.
No, it's not that kind of shirt.
It looks stupid untucked.
Untuok your shirt. You look
like a youth minister.
Untuck your fucking shirt, man.
We're trying to look cool.
All right!
Whoa. Oh, Sorry, bro!
Sorry, guys.
Sorry. My friend's wasted.
Don't.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey! No
adults are getting into my house.
Not on prom night.
Okay, not on prom.
We were just down the street
at another party
and then we just decided
to come up here
and hang with you guys. Uh...
No parents here, right?
Ah, thank God!
No, not except
for you guys. No.
We're not... We don't...
Yeah, no.
Okay, so you're cops.
I got two DUls last year.
How could I be a cop?
The police?
Look at my untucked shirt.
You're literally the cop-lest
motherfucker I've ever seen.
You look like you got your hair
out in the baok of a squad oar.
- This is a regular men's haircut.
- Okay.
This is ridiculous.
All right, you're minors,
we're minors.
You're, like, 45 years old.
Fuck you. I was born in '77.
'87.
'94.
We're gonna drink
with you guys.
Would cops drink
with underage kids? No.
Okay. What about
a little chugging contest?
Um...
Yeah. Bring it.
Okay, wait.
I gotta get the room ready.
Oh, wow!
You're really going for it,
aren't ya?
I saw this in the romantic comedy,
American Beauty. So good.
You watched the whole thing?
You know what
this candle does to me.
Is that the one
that gives you hives?
No, it's the good one.
Oh, nice.
You look so hot right now.
Where are my chuggers at?
You ready?
Oh, right here. Let's go!
What, what!
KYLERI All right.
COOI.
Drop 'em.
Let's do it.
Wait, what?
Guys?
We're lust chugging, right?
Yeah, we're butt-chugging.
Yeah, you put the tube up your
butt and you funnel the beer in.
It fucks you up way more,
man, trust me.
Guys, butt-chugging?
You got this. You got it.
No, I'm tagging out.
You're in.
What? Why me?
You've had a baby. Everything's
looser down there.
I didn't have a baby out of my butt.
Even I know that.
Mitchell.
Okay, this isn't a common
occurrence with me,
but I have had things
up there before.
Hmm?
It's just all about breathing.
So just breathe through it,
and accept it in.
I can't do it.
Hey! She's up there right now
with that dick-bag, Connor,
with his man bun
and that stupid smirk.
Think about this.
Wait. Connor?
You know... You know
Connor Aldrich, The Chef?
Why do they call him
"The Chef"?
Oh. Maybe a big fan
of South Park?
"Hello, children."
No. No. He cooks drugs
into everything.
Everything! One time he made me
this, like, acid financier cake.
Oh! That shit
was to die for, man!
Like, literally,
I almost fucking died.
Yeah. Dude, if your daughter
had anything like that cake,
she might not remember
who you are tomorrow.
Give me the fucking tube.
Let's bone.
Wait, what?
Oh! Are you sure that this
is how you wanna do it?
Yes, Chad. This is always
how I've imagined it.
Oh, you know, I'd rather leave
my shirt on, if that's sexier.
I need another drink.
Wait, wait, uh...
Can you lube it up
with something first?
Yeah, I'll just spit on it.
No!
Why? Because I'm a man?
Get over yourself.
No, 'cause you're fucking gross
and your fucking saliva's gross.
I have lip gloss.
We got lip gloss.
Okay, fine. Shit.
I don't have lip gloss.
All right, guys,
let's get those tubes in.
All right, I got the lip
gloss on there. Okay.
Okay, okay. All right.
Okay, ready?
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
- It's not in yet.
- Okay.
Chill. LISA: It's just
gonna be on the count of three.
You got this, dawg.
This is for your kid.
On three, okay. All right.
On three.
Yeah.
- Okay, one...
- One.
Are you okay?
Okay, get your 40s.
They got a lager or an IPA.
It doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter.
Okay.
I don't know about this.
No,no,no,no.
It's too late.
It's already in.
Here you go. It's in you.
It's part of you now.
Ready?
Yeah.
Set...
Chug!
Butt chug! Butt chug!
Wait.
- Hey, hey!
- Loosen up!
It's not working, dude.
I can't!
You can hold my hand!
Okay.
- Ow!
- You're hurting her.
God! It really hurt!
I'm sorry!
Channel that energy
into your butt hole.
This changes
everything I know!
Dude, if your daughter could
see you now she'd be so proud of you.
Whoa...
lam...
lam tripping so hard.
It's not working.
It's not working, dude.
- Oh, it's terrible.
- It is.
Open up!
I'm sorry.
I can't do it, man.
Focus! For your daughter.
Fuck, Mitch. Focus.
You gotta breathe.
You gotta open up, dude.
Relax!
I'm relaxed! I'm dilated.
I'm staring at your asshole.
You're not dilating.
Mitchell, you're gonna
lose to this punk bitch?
Breathe. Take it in!
There we go.
Okay, good.
Oh!
It's working!
It's working! Holy shit!
Holy shit!
It's working!
We're almost halfway done.
Pos! Fucking run!
Cops?
What? Oh, no!
Ass beer!
Lisa, the foam went into my mouth!
I have to go to the hospital!
Hurry up!
Get out of here!
Shit!
We gotta go.
I got ass beer,
I should go to the hospital.
Shit!
The fucking cops?
The fucking cops are here?
Wait, wait, wait.
I can't get the tube out.
Pull the tube out.
Leese, pull it out.
No! I put it in!
I had to spit on it!
What? You spit on it?
No, it was my lip gloss.
What the fuck?
It was lip gloss.
Pull it out!
Hey, man, be gentle.
Be fucking gentle, all right?
I'm gonna be gentle,
all right? Ready?
All right, on three.
On three...
One.
Ow!
Come on.
Hey, guys!
Guys!
Wait, wait. Sam.
Sam!
Sam, Sam! We're over here.
No!
No. No.
The night is over.
No.
It's over. It's done.
The night is not over.
The night has just begun.
Jesus, Chad, use your legs.
I mean, I pretty much carried
her, like, the whole way there.
Hustle, hustle, hustle!
Come on, Sam.
Come with us!
I can't.
My car is here.
But all my friends
are going to the hotel party.
Maybe I'll see you later.
- Get in the car. Go, go, go, girl!
- Sam!
You'll see her later!
Seriously, hurry up!
What are you doing?
Whoo, this night is not over,
I swear to Christ!
Dukes of Hazzard!
Racist-ass show anyway.
I got the spins, man.
We gotta find
our daughter, dawg.
I'm gonna sit down
for a second.
Rudy! It's Rudy.
Rudy, Rudy,
wait, wait!
There he goes! Hit
the clicker, open the door!
L got mine.
Seatbelts!
You'll get a big ticket.
That's them
right there.
They're getting away.
You gotta go faster.
Okay.
Hey, you gotta be in it 110%.
You gotta be in it to win it!
How do you get more competitive
when you're drunk?
Hey, man. I'm more of a winner
when I'm drunk, all right?
And the question
that I have for you, Leese...
Are you a winner?
Are you in it to win it?
Winning is my bitch!
All right!
Strong.
Knock,knock!
Who's there?
Me winning.
It's not...
It's not that good.
Ow. Ow!
Lisa winning!
It's not that good!
Ow! Fuck! All right, it's good.
It's fine. I like it.
Hey, you're losing him.
Let's go.
Oh. Not on my watch.
Y'all think you gonna outrun Rudy
the main motherfucking man Glover?
Hell, no.
Are you all right?
No.
Come on.
Hey, guys.
Hey, I don't...
I don't feel so...
Oh, my God!
All right,
here's what we're gonna do.
Lisa, I have seen every single
Fast and the Furious movie, okay?
All of them, dozens of times.
Have you seen any of them?
I saw the Tokyo one, and I saw the one
where The Rock punches the torpedo.
Those are the best two to see.
Okay, in times like this,
I ask myself one question.
"W-W-V-D-D." You know
what that means?
"What would Vin Diesel do?"
Holy shit!
No one's ever fucking
gotten that before. Okay.
Oh, man, it smells like...
What we're gonna do,
we're gonna kiss the bumper.
You give it a little tap, and
then they're gonna spin and stop
and we're gonna spin
and stop the other way
and we're gonna look at each
other, and we're gonna go,
"lt's all about
the family."
Wait. I don't feel comfortable
running the kids off the road.
This slow and un-furious attitude is
not helping us. You have to believe!
Okay. I'm gonna kiss it.
Here we go!
What's that?
Did I do it?
No, you didn't even kiss it.
You gotta kiss it.
Kiss it for the family!
ls that Sam?
She barfed on us!
Oh, my God!
Okay.
Are we in heaven?
Okay. Listen, I know
how to do this.
Everyone lean backwards.
If we all lean backwards on three,
the car will roll back. Ready?
Okay.
One,
two, three.
Oh, fuck!
Ahhh!
Well, that's the last
of the ass beer.
Jesus! That's it.
Are you okay?
Are you bleeding?
You might have
internal blood injuries.
I'm all right, I'm all right.
Here's the problem.
The Fast and The Furious
movies are not realistic.
Where are we? Shit!
Fuck!
What are you doing?
I heard that in times of crisis,
parents have superhuman strength.
No offense, there's no scientific way
you're gonna flip that car over.
I couldn't even do that.
Yeah, I couldn't do it,
either.
Do not tell me what I can and can't do.
Kayla's not answering again.
God damn it!
We lost 'em, guys.
We are fucked! Or maybe not.
What are you doing?
Trying to telepathically
communicate with Kayla.
I'm with the X-Men of parents.
You know what
my secret power is?
I'm super fucking annoyed right
now and I hurt my love handle.
All right.
You guys think my new clothes
go with my fedora?
I'm just kidding, I know they do.
Hey.
Have you talked
to your mom?
No.
So my parents
were just texting me
and they were having sex and your
mom showed up looking for you.
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
It's okay. They have sex all the time.
Oh, my God,
she... The texts.
So many texts.
She's mad.
I need to handle this.
Good news.
A Lyft is on its way.
Oh, wait, no,
I know this guy. He sucks.
Oh, shit. It's Julie.
Be cool. Be cool.
Be quiet. Okay.
Hey, Mom!
I just got all your texts
and I just wanted to let you
know that we're all good.
Cool. Cool. Okay.
Um... Are you at the prom?
Yeah. Yeah, just nonstop
magical moments.
Huh. You are lying to me.
Where are you right now?
Where are you?
Why are you freaking out?
I'm freaking out because I
know what you're up to.
And I know that
you and your friends
are planning some kind of
little sex pact or whatever.
What did you say?
You heard me.
How could you possibly know?
Because I am your mother
and I know you.
And I know you
better than you know yourself.
And I also know that you're
planning on going to UCLA
and that
you're following Austin.
Yeah.
I know everything.
Oh, my God,
you know nothing!
Why do you even assume
that it's me following Austin?
Huh? You're not worried
about me, Mom.
You're worried about you.
You're afraid of losing me.
You're afraid of being alone.
lam not scared of being alone.
This is not about me.
I have not thought about
myself for the last 18 years.
This is about you.
And as a single mother,
lam trying to stop you from
making a life-ruining decision.
So I was
"a life-ruining decision"?
No. No!
No, that is not
what I meant.
You know what, Mom?
I'm not going to UCLA
because of some boy, okay?
I'm going to UCLA because it's
the furthest I can get from you.
Well...
Hello?
Nanaru is on his way.
Forty-six minutes.
Well...
So, she hates me.
She doesn't hate you.
Kayla's ignoring me. She's bringing
it to a whole new level of spite.
Yeah.
That's a new level of pain.
Yeah. I know.
It's just different for me
because I gave birth to her
and I just feel
very connected.
She was living in my body.
Kayla grew in me.
She grew in me. She did.
She grew from my balls
and I shot her into Marcie.
This is the same
for you and me.
Not exactly.
I mean, you have daily love
in your life
and I'm probably
gonna die alone
and won't be found
for a really long time.
Until one day, someone
will be walking by
with their golden retriever,
and the dog is just
gonna lose its shit.
And then they're gonna
call the police
and then they're gonna come in
and find me draped over the tub
with my feral cats
eating away at my hair.
'Cause cats do that.
The fuck is wrong with you?
That is some dark shit!
You're gonna die alone?
Whoa, whoa. My man! Come on! Where
the hell did you get that idea?
I call you all the time.
You ever return my calls? No.
Because we're not really
friends, you and me.
We're not friends?
I don't mean it at that...
You know what you are?
You are like the thing
that pops up on Facebook...
And then it's, like, this beautiful
picture of your grandma who's dead.
And you're, like, "Fuck you, Facebook,
for reminding me of my loss."
That's why you're avoiding me?
Because I remind you of loss?
Yes! I don't wanna be reminded of
sweet, young Julie and our kids
and that beautiful time
in our lives is over.
Oh, God! Boo-fucking-hoo
with you two!
You guys completely
ignore me. Always.
Yeah, no shit, cheater.
Oh, "Cheater"?
That's my designation?
That's what I am?
I'm the cheater?
Fuck that shit.
Did you guys ever once call me
when that went down
and ask me
my side of the story?
You didn't.
I would've told you the truth.
I would've told you that Brenda
had stopped talking to me
months before that happened.
Do you know she hooked up with her boss
at a company retreat in Wisconsin?
Do you know she beat me up?
She fucking beat me up at a
Romano's fucking Macaroni Grill!
She fucking slapped me in front
of the fucking maTtre'd!
I didn't know that.
I'm sorry, man.
And I fucking
embarrassed myself
and I embarrassed myself
in front of my daughter.
And I thought, "You know, I
should pull back a little bit,"
and fucking Frank showed up.
And I pulled back more
and I thought, "One day
I'm gonna fix it.
"One day I'm gonna
fucking fix it."
And then I thought if I gave her
something awesome like a great night...
I could get close with her
again, but I can't.
'Cause she's gone.
They're just...
The kids,
they just leave.
Oh, shit!
I know how we can find 'em.
Go to Cathy and Ron's.
Austin's been texting them
all night.
Did you hear
anything I said just now?
That's a great idea.
Fuck it. It's just
good to say it out loud.
Let's go flip that car.
Hell...
Jesus Christ!
Oh, my fucking God!
Shit!
My car just exploded.
Nanaru is 26 minutes away.
So that's good.
I thought I canceled him.
Thanks, Nanaru.
So Austin's parents aren't gonna
just tell us where they are.
So we need
to get Ron's phone,
read the texts,
and find our kids. Okay?
Hunter, it's not
gonna be you.
So, Mitchell, it's you.
No. That's breaking
and entering. That is...
I'm uncomfortable with that.
Are you a team player,
or aren't you?
Am I a team player?
I just chugged a 40 with my asshole.
I'm a team player.
Then get your head
in the game.
It's the bottom of the third.
We are down by one and there
is not a lot of game left.
There is a lot of game
left though.
Listen. You have one pass left.
One. One pass.
ls it rugby? ls it
Australian rules football? They
don't put a limit on passing.
If it was the third,
then I'd have the fourth.
You know what? You know
what's happening right now?
Let me tell you
what's happening right now,
is Kayla and Connor
are sliding into bed.
He's grabbing a condom
and then he's flicking it
to the side
with a smirk on his face.
That fucking smirk. No way.
We need a Hail Mary pass.
Are you up for that, son?
Yes, Coach.
Well, I can't hear you.
Yes, Coach. I'm in it!
I can't hear you.
I can fucking do this!
Let's go!
We gotta be quiet.
Careful.
All right, go.
Go.
Did you...
There's a person!
What? Fuck you.
Jesus Christ.
I'm gonna get you!
Not if I get you first.
Get away from here.
I'm fucking out!
Mitchell, in!
Get in.
Cam'?
Ron, no talking.
Come on, we had a deal.
We have to find each other
by sensing each other's musks.
Can't use our voices.
Here, kitty, kitty.
I can smell that musk.
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! I like
the sound of that!
Oh!
on! Hey!
You wanna touch first,
that works for Ronnie!
You want me to touch you?
Help yourself. Yes.
I'm gonna touch you. Hard.
Do it.
How about I touch you...
...with my nails, baby?
Let's have it!
Oh!
Your hair is so sexy, babe.
Oh, your grip is unbelievable.
L want you to touch me
where I like.
My balls. You know?
I want it bad. Do it, come on!
Really? How bad?
Let's go. Come on.
Come on, do it!
You there?
What, this isn't hard enough?
Let's go. Come on.
- Harder?
- Come on, do it.
Do it, I'm waiting.
Okeydoke.
Oh, yeah,
you like that?
Hey, man, I don't judge
people's sex shit.
But that was
ridiculous and stupid.
Way to take one
for the team, guys.
Hold on, hold on,
hold on. Here it is.
"The police came
to the lake house.
"Almost lost my flower
but didn't quite work out."
"Flower"?
He said that? He's a boy.
Buh, buh, buh... "Heading
to the Park West Hotel.
"We've got
the Grand Lux Suite.
"Looks like the little boy
is becoming a man."
Fucking dork.
Okay, so that was
10 minutes ago.
So they haven't had sex yet.
We can still catch them.
Okay, let's do this.
Hey.
How's she doing?
ls she okay?
No, she's not doing okay.
She's bummed.
She doesn't even wanna kiss.
And I love kissing.
Give me your room key.
What? Why?
Yeah.
Give me your room key and then
bring her up in, like, 15 minutes.
Uh, okay.
Yes. Thanks. You're the man.
Thank you for this.
How we supposed to find them in this place?
It's got, like, 20 rooms.
I'm sorry, what the
fuck are you talking about?
"Twenty"? It's got,
like, 200! What? Twenty?
Grand Lux Suite
is on the top floor.
Go, go, go! Move!
Hurry, Lisa!
What am I doing here?
on, my God!
Oh, my God, my favorite!
That's so sweet.
Oh, my God! This is a dream!
It's, like, perfect! That is so nice!
You're so sweet.
It actually wasn't me.
It was Kayla.
She wanted you to have
the perfect night.
That's why it looks so good.
Well,
why do you look
so good?
You're such a dork.
I know.
On, my God!
Not as smooth
as I could have.
Let me get my shoes.
Kayla?
Nobody move, where's Kayla?
Get that outta here.
Um, how's this work?
No, just leave it.
Okay, cool. Mmm-hmm.
It's difficult.
Play sports!
And that's that.
So, you sure
you wanna do this?
Yeah.
Yes! Fuck, yeah.
You're gonna penis me.
Yeah.
First I'm gonna...
I'm just gonna touch it.
You wanna touch it?
Yeah, you can touch it.
Yeah, yeah, go for it.
Okay, just, like...
Oh! Wow!
Okay. That is like the greatest feeling
I've ever had in my entire life.
Really?
It doesn't just feel like
a super-dry hand of a friend?
No. Nope.
Okay. So,
do you wanna
Put it in?
No.
Okay.
I can't. I'm sorry.
You know what?
Look, we don't...
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Holy shit!
Look at all of it.
Oh, my gosh!
I gotta get over.
Okay. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry,
I'm so sorry. I just...
It's okay.
I was thinking about it
and you, and then it just...
I'm sorry.
You're amazing.
I know we're still virgins,
but I feel different.
You know?
Yeah.
I know.
You ready to, uh, do this?
Wait.
Wait. Um...
Ah, Shit.
Shit.
Maybe Julie was right.
Like, maybe
losing your virginity doesn't
have to be perfect, but...
I feel like it should just be, like,
a little bit more special than this.
Yeah.
Like, not cheesy, but...
Like, if I was hard-pressed
right now,
I don't think I could
remember your last name.
It's Aldrich.
Aldrich!
I thought it was Ostrich.
I didn't realize that you're a virgin.
You know?
Yeah.
Um, but, like, I'd still
be down to do it
but maybe, like, you know,
when we get to know
each other a little more.
Like, maybe Monday
or something?
Yeah.
Not to, like,
plan it and be weird.
No, no, l can look at my
schedule and see if it's...
Okay.
Pencil it in.
Um, yeah, that's cool.
Okay, cool.
Let's just relax. We could do some
light journaling or something.
Yeah, yeah, we could do that.
Or we could do,
like, other stuff.
Yeah, like what?
Like...
Not sex, but...
I'm still down for pleasure.
You got this.
Hey, guys, what's up?
Anyone seen Sam?
Chad!
Oh, Jesus!
What the...
You again?
You?
What the fuck?
What's your beef
with me, dude?
I don't know
who the fuck you are!
I'm Jake
motherfucking Donahue!
That name means nothing to me!
Do you know what it's like to be
humiliated in front of everyone you know
and have to seek
redemption for that?
Actually, yes, I do!
Kayla?
Get the hell away from my daughter,
you little piece of shit!
Dad, what the...
Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
He didn't hurt you, did he?
What? No, he didn't hurt me.
Holy shit! Connor?
Oh, my God! Are you okay?
I'm actually totally fine.
Connor, I'm so sorry.
Are you okay, though?
Are you sure? Yeah.
Dad! What the...
What are you doing here?
I've been following you
around all night!
Are you set...
Oh, my Gem!
You've been following me?
Are you crazy?
You gave me no choice!
You're in over your head
with this kid.
lam not some pathetic damsel
in distress that needs saving.
I can handle myself.
No, you can't.
Yes, I can!
No, you can't!
Kayla,
you can't.
And that's why I'm here.
It's my job.
Oh.
Yeah, so you just don't think I can make
my own decisions and handle myself.
That really fucking sucks.
Kayla...
Kayla, I'm just trying
to figure this thing out.
God! Why is sex even bad?
I don't know. I don't know.
It's not... You know, it's...
I don't know.
I'm...
I'm just trying to be
the best dad I can be.
Well, you are.
You taught me everything.
You built me up.
Made me strong.
You made me into who I am.
Like, that's...
You did not have to save me
tonight, Dad.
You taught me how to do that
a long time ago.
And I love you for it.
You're the best coach ever.
Thank you.
Oh, Dad, come on.
Come on, toughen up.
It was just really nice,
what you said.
It's good. It's good.
I mean it.
Thanks, I feel like...
Like Phil Jackson when he
was coaching the Bulls...
And then
they were so good.
That's how I feel right now.
Yeah.
Uh, I should've taken
my socks off first.
I'm just warning you, I've practiced a few
times but this might not go that well.
That doesn't look right.
Yeah, all right. I think
you need another one.
I think we need
another one, too.
Wait, wait.
We have to do our dance.
We have to... Yeah, yeah.
What, now?
Naked?
No, get me one of
those, um, hotel robes.
I wanna feel fabulous.
Okay.
Coming right up, my lady.
We're gonna christen
every corner of this room.
And when we're done,
let's FaceTime my parents.
Okay, but right now, I
want you to stare into my eyes.
What?
Mmm-hmm. I just want,
like, a real connection.
So you just want me to
look straight into your eyes
for the next three minutes and 37 seconds?
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
Look at me.
Dad?
Where is he?
What are you doing here?
Chad?
Hey, Chad, you motherfucker.
Oh, my God,
are you kidding me?
Did he make you do something
you don't wanna do?
'Cause I don't care if he's the
fucking coolest kid in school.
I'm gonna shove his fedora so
far up his ass, it'll be a hat.
No, Dad, we didn't do it.
All right? And even if we did, it
would be none of your business.
It's just, I was worried about you.
Well, that's a first.
I deserve that.
Sam, I gotta tell you
something and I'm just gonna say it.
Sam, I have realized
over the last few years
that I've made
a big mistake in my life.
What, like cheating on my mom?
Well, no. Marrying your mom.
But, no, that wasn't
a mistake,
because then I wouldn't
have had you. Uh...
I've made lots of mistakes,
but the big mistake
is that I let what happened
between your mom and I
get in the way
of our relationship.
I'm sorry.
And I hope that
we can start over and
build up our relationship
again because
you're my only kid.
And I'm your only dad.
Well, Frank is...
Fuck Frank.
Frank's fine.
Dad,
can I tell you something now?
Yes. Yes, yes, yes, anything.
I'm a lesbian.
What does your mom think?
She doesn't know.
You told me before
you told your mom?
Yeah.
That's big news.
She doesn't know?
You didn't tell Frank?
No.
Ah.
Okay. Over. Crying is over.
What do
your girlfriends think?
No, I'm too nervous,
I can't tell them.
You're nervous
to tell Kayla and Julie?
I don't wanna lose
my two best friends.
This is the stuff you tell
the people you care about.
You think they're not gonna
support you because you're gay?
They would support you
if you were a vampire.
They would support you more. With
all the Twilight shit.
Do we Still like Twilight?
Definitely not.
No, no.
Oh, God.
Thanks for showing up.
Really. But you should
probably leave
because it's insane that you even
came here in the first place.
I'd love to get
a picture with you.
Yeah.
Great. Okay.
Just gonna stand on this.
Yeah, you know
the drill. Come on.
Come on. Here we go.
Gotta turn it around here.
Dad, you're not taking it.
What?
I'll remember this.
Come on.
Oh, my God!
What's up, dawg?
So, I just, uh, parented
the shit outta Sam.
And I feel, uh...
Oh, God, like, uh,
pride, I think?
That's it.
It's new.
Good for you, man.
Thanks.
Well done, my friend.
Thank you.
Well done.
How'd it go with Kayla?
Put Connor through a wall.
Are you serious?
Yeah. He's okay.
Yeah, he's lighter
than I thought.
Hey.
Hi.
So, Julie's, um...
Julie's having sex right now.
Okay. And sit down.
Wowee.
Yeah.
But it's good.
It's fine, right? I mean, you
have to do that eventually.
Right?
Are you good?
Yeah.
They seem like they really like each other
and that's nice. That's a good thing,
but it's just a little,
you know, scary,
because what if he doesn't know how
to do it right? You know, like,
what if he doesn't know
where to put it.
But he knows, right?
Should I go back up there?
No! No, no, no, no.
No, he'll figure it out.
It's one or the other.
Nope. Stay right here.
Do you wanna have
a drink right now?
Like, hang out?
Yeah.
Yes, I do.
I'm in. I'm definitely in.
Um, we will be having some
shots of alcohol, please.
Yes, we will.
This is crazy.
Well, I'm gonna, uh...
I'll let you guys have
your fun, and l will, uh...
I'm... I'm gonna
see you guys around.
Hey!
You, too.
Yeah.
Right!
Fuck,yeah!
Pifia colada.
Just get him a shot.
Cheers!
What a night, guys.
That's beautiful.
So, I don't think the kid at the lake
house was actually butt-chugging.
Definitely.
Yeah.
What?
And so he threw me
through a table...
- I'm so sorry.
- No, it was cool.
I kinda feel fine. It's cool.
All right, see you.
See you.
Hey, guys.
- Austin, uh, let's go get a drink, man.
- Yeah, sure.
Want a fry?
So badly.
Can I have a fry, too?
Yeah!
Yes.
So?
I couldn't
go through with it.
Yeah, l didn't. No.
Holy shit.
You're a woman amongst girls.
Julie!
Congratu-fuck-ulations.
Thank you.
How was it?
Honestly,
it was a little painful, kinda
fast, and kinda awkward...
But absolutely perfect.
AW!
You guys, so much
went down tonight.
I know.
Including...
Connor!
No!
Let's just say...
The Chef went out to eat my pussy.
It was good.
DJ Chad.
ls that Chad?
That's Chad.
Chad!
Scream
my name Yes, Chad!
Fuck yeah, Chad!
I love me
Gonna love myself No, I
don't need anybody else
Hey.
Gonna love myself
No, I don't need anybody else
I love me...
Guys, I gotta
tell you something.
Okay.
Really?
Yeah.
Wait, you are?
I love you. Forever.
And you, too.
Oh, my God!
I love you.
Sam!
Excuse me.
I can't believe
you didn't tell us!
Y I
ay"
Ta-da-da-da!
Aw.
Oh, hey!
Hey.
Hey!
Hi.
Oh.
Uh, Julie, I think we got
something over here.
Dope cape.
I'm not misreading things.
So you'll call me every day
till you get to L.A., right?
Yeah, and then, like,
every day after that.
Okay.
I'm gonna miss you so much.
You're gonna be okay, though.
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. It's the
weirdest thing because
I have been worried
about this day for 18 years.
And then
I wake up this morning
and... Nothing.
Like, I don't feel emotional at all.
I just feel like...
It's so bizarre.
What is that?
It's, like, splashing on me.
I know.
Isn't that so strange?
Yeah.
I love you, Mom.
I love you.
No, I have money. Like...
Lisa, tell him
I can afford... Mmm.
Sorry, sorry.
All right, come on.
Let's get this road trip started!
I love you.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me take a video.
- I love you.
Bye, Mom.
- I love you. Muah.
- Okay, bye.
See ya.
Drop Julie off in Cali
and then you and Kayla come right
back home, and text, please.
- That's a big maybe.
- Please.
Hey, take care of
my mom, you two. Okay?
- We will. All right.
- Later, big guy.
I'm going to college!
Drive careful, young man.
That's precious cargo.
I love you!
Aww.
Come on.
Guys.
- Come on. We did it.
- We did it.
We did it. We parented.
We did it.
Oop! It's Julie.
Oh, I must have been accidentally
added to the group conversation.
Oh, well,
should probably leave.
"Can't believe we're on
our own now."
Aw, that's sweet.
Yeah.
"We're gonna get lit af."
"Lit AF."
That's not great.
No, that's... They're gonna get literature.
African literature.
You think that's what "lit AF" means?
You think
they're talking to each other about...
Lit AF.
"Can The Chef get us..."
Trees?
What the hell's trees?
Trees mean weed, I told you that.
Mushrooms. Pills.
No, the pills are Kayla's allergy.
That's Claritin.
It's not Claritin. Look,
snowflakes. That's blow.
"Hashtag, no parents, no rules.
Hashtag, mad drugs.
"Hashtag, no condoms"?
Why would
they hashtag that?
Wait, is that a needle
and an eggplant?
What, are they gonna inject
heroin into some guy's dick'?
Let's go.
Let's get in the car.
I'll drive.
I'm sitting behind you.
Wait, wait, wait!
We're
just messing with you! Ha-ha!
"We love you guys,
don't worry."
You guys were so pranked!
I was in on it.
You didn't know.
No, no, I did. I didn't know
it was coming right now.
That's why I kinda
sold it so well.
But it doesn't matter.
You guys were like...
"Holy Shit!"
Yeah.
Damn it, Mitchell!
Marco?
Polo.
Mitchell, are you
getting a snack?
I'm so glad we can do stuff like
this now that Kayla's in college.
I have no idea
where you are.
I'm gonna do so much stuff
to you when I find you.
Oh. Oh.
Marco.
Polo.
Ah! Ah!
Polo!
I can't believe it,
it took you forever!
I spent so much time
on the stairs!
We're doing this. I know.
We're, like, totally doing it.
Let's just get crazy. I don't know!
It's hot. VVhoo!
I want you to grab my balls,
like Ron likes it, like hard.