Subtitles by explosiveskull
[RATTLING]
[WHIZZING]
[RIPPING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[CHIRPING]
[♪♪♪]
["CASTLES" PLAYING]
♪ You're all I'm not
You're all I see ♪
♪ You're the last thing
That breathe ♪
♪ Before I go to sleep ♪
♪ And I know you're simple
Underneath your skin ♪
♪ I pushed you out
I pulled you in ♪
♪ It's a catastrophe
So ♪
BOTH: ♪ Don't build
A castle for me ♪
♪ Because I can't be trusted
With anything ♪
♪ Don't make instructions
For me ♪
♪ Because I don't take
Lessons on anything ♪
ALL:
♪ Bada, da-da-da, da-da-da ♪
♪ Bada, da-da-da, da-da-da
Da-da ♪
♪ I give it back
But you want more ♪
♪ I call you up
To let you know ♪
♪ I'm face down
On the floor ♪
♪ Don't build a castle
For me ♪
BOTH: ♪ Because I can't be
trusted With anything ♪
♪ Don't make instructions
For me ♪
BOTH: ♪ Because I
don't take Lessons ♪
♪ On anything ♪
♪ Bada, da-da-da, da-da-da ♪
ALL: ♪ Bada, da-da-da
Da-da-da, da-da ♪
♪ Bada, da-da-da, da-da-da ♪
♪ Bada, da-da-da, da-da-da
Da-da ♪♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
I wanna start off
by making it very clear
that I didn't know
any of these girls.
Any of them. I mean, I...
I met them last night,
but I'd never met them
before that.
[CHUCKLES]
I read in a crime novel once
that the best way
to question someone
is just to let them
keep talking.
That's what you're doing,
isn't it?
It's totally
what you're doing.
You know what the murder rate is
in Palm Springs, Jackie?
Why would I know that?
Five.
Five per...?
Year.
Wow.
That's really good.
That's like a week in L.A.
Wait,
you think this was a murder?
Tell me about, um...
- Starfoxy.
- [SIGHS]
Okay, uh...
We met in college.
Well, Byron, Travis
and myself did.
About a year ago,
we found Kirk on Craigslist.
I guess our manager thought
we needed to "add keys."
I don't know,
he thought the whole Green Day,
power-guitar thing
was getting stale...
Jump ahead. I don't need
the whole discography.
[CHUCKLES]
Like when we got
to the house?
Start in the van.
Okay.
Um...
We left L.A. around 9 a.m.
We took the 74 because we knew
everyone else would take the 10.
[VIVALDI'S "FOUR SEASONS"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Okay. Seriously, Jackie,
what the fuck
are we listening to?
Vivaldi.
Thanks, but I was being
rhetorical, as to imply
why the fuck are we listening
to this shit?
Because it's my turn and this
is what I wanna listen to.
You had your turn,
and you made us sit
through Imagine Dragons.
Made you?
Imagine Dragons are awesome.
Imagine Dragons is awesome.
See, Byron agrees.
No,
just correcting your grammar.
Imagine Dragons is terrible.
I thought their first album
was pretty good, so...
Okay, well, this is calming.
We could all use a little calm
right now.
I'll be calm when I'm dead.
This weekend
is about partying, okay?
Shit,
we should be pre-gaming now.
I wanted to talk to you guys
about that.
Sounds like
we're in trouble.
I think we can all agree
that this weekend
is very important for us.
So let's skip
the festival today
and just go straight
to the house.
Heh. Fuck that.
We've got artists' passes,
- and we're gonna use 'em.
- I second that notion.
I third it.
Those badges cost 800 bucks.
That's more money than
I'm gonna spend on anything
in my entire life.
Okay, okay.
We go to the festival
for a couple of hours
and then we get to the house
before sundown.
Then we party.
No, and then we rehearse.
And call me crazy,
but maybe we actually
go to bed at a decent hour
and get some sleep.
Jackie,
if tomorrow goes well,
we're gonna blow up. Huh?
We're gonna have to get used
to playing to sold-out crowds
after all-night sex
and drug binges.
So we might as well start
to get used to it, huh?
See... I'm confused
because now you're both making
great arguments.
Kirk, it's one night.
Please? Just one night?
All right.
But only if you promise
to party twice as hard tomorrow.
Scout's honor.
[VIVALDI'S "FOUR SEASONS"
CONTINUES PLAYING, LOUDER]
[SONG ENDS;
ROCK MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
I'm gonna check out New
Pollution. What about you guys?
- Wax Battleship.
- Invasion 101.
Every man for himself, then.
So...
Meet back here at 5.
I'll get the door.
[BAMTONE'S "BLACKEST SHEEP"
PLAYING]
♪ Oh, yeah
I feel a surge ♪
♪ Rushing through
My veins ♪
♪ I wanna push
I wanna pull ♪
♪ I'm not giving in
I'm not giving in ♪
♪ I wanna push
I wanna pull ♪
♪ I'm not giving in ♪
♪ I'm the blackest sheep
In this earth ♪
♪ This blackest sheep is ♪
♪ Gonna get you, gonna get you
Gonna get you good ♪
♪ Oh, whoa-whoa, oh ♪
♪ Oh, whoa-whoa, oh ♪♪
TRAVIS: Heh. This place looks
like my grandma's house.
BYRON:
Where'd you find it?
Airbnb.
The couple who owns it
lives on the East Coast
- and only uses it in winter.
- What's up with these gnomes?
[KIRK CHUCKLES]
We are gonna trash the shit
out of this place.
[♪♪♪]
Okay, I was wrong.
My grandma's
definitely not this cool.
KIRK:
Dude, check it out.
One of these Chinese
pinball machines.
Japanese.
Whatever.
Oh.
[CHUCKLES]
Yes.
- Could use some jizz.
- Gross.
How are we picking rooms?
First come, first serve,
like on Real World?
JACKIE: Sure. But I found this
place, so I get the master.
[CHIRPING]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[DIRTY CHILDREN'S "I DID IT"
PLAYING]
♪ There is an inch ♪
♪ Around my waist ♪
♪ From chocolate ice cream ♪
I'm gonna hit the liquor store.
Want anything?
- Bourbon.
- Yes. Whiskey.
No. No booze.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Are you fucking kidding?
Do you not remember the
conversation we had in the van?
No partying.
Having a few beers
isn't "partying," Jackie.
It's a gateway.
[STRUMS GUITAR]
Oh, hey, grab a pizza.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
He's being such a dick
today.
Eh, give him a break.
He's just young and excited.
He's like a kid
on Christmas morning
that just wants
to have a couple beers.
Well...
we can't practice
without him, so...
♪ I've been waiting
For a year ♪
♪ Waiting for my head
To clear... ♪
That's a redo.
Because you hit the net.
- No, that's only on serves.
- No, it's a redo
- any time you hit the net.
- What?
It's only a redo on the serve.
That's the rule.
- In what rule book?
- All of them.
No.
KIRK:
We have arrived.
- Hey.
[KIRK SIGHS]
You didn't get pizza.
We'll order one.
[SIGHS]
Who are your friends, Kirk?
Uh... This is Maple,
Amber and Lucy.
- Lucy.
- [AMBER & LUCY LAUGH]
We met at the liquor store.
They're going
- to the festival too.
- No kidding.
Wow, 75,000 people in town
for the festival
and you bump
into three of them?
Heh. Right? Thank you so much
for inviting us to hang out.
We're staying in this sketchy
hotel in Cathedral City.
I'm pretty sure
there's a meth lab
- in the manager's office.
- MAPLE: Heh.
Oh, my God, what's the address?
I'll make a run.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Hey, Kirk says you guys
are playing tomorrow?
That's so cool.
It is so cool.
Kirk, why don't I help you
take these things
into the kitchen? Okay?
- [CHUCKLES]
- LUCY: Here you go.
- You guys have a hot tub?
- Yeah, I mean...
- It's very small. Over there.
- [WOMEN CHUCKLE]
KIRK: Look, Jackie,
I know you're mad.
They're all chicks.
But, look, calm down.
I'll have them call bros,
we'll get them here.
- We'll figure it all out.
- Huge, Kirk.
Tomorrow is huge for us.
Because "Castles" has had
so much airplay,
there are gonna be a ton
of A&R reps...
If we impress them,
we could get
a three-album deal worth,
what's the number,
half a million dollars, right?
Jackie, I know, okay?
You've told us
like a half a million times.
Listen, I know that you're new
to the whole band thing.
And being on tour
is still fun for you,
but if we don't pull this off
and get signed,
then that is it for me.
Do you understand that?
I'm not gonna spend
another 10 years
driving around
in that shitty van,
waiting for a shot.
This. This, right here,
is my shot.
Which is why
I want them gone.
[SCOFFS]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Look, Jackie.
If you wanna do this whole
Mary Poppins thing all weekend,
go for it.
But the thing is...
you're not my mom.
And I'm gonna chase it tonight,
whether you like it or not.
[RATTLING]
[♪♪♪]
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
Hi, how's it going?
Jackie, come pay for this!
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
Hi. How much?
Forty-two fifty.
Hey, anybody tell you you look
like the dude from American Pie?
Who?
Sherminator.
Oh, because I have red hair?
No.
Oh.
Can I get 10 back?
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
Surprised the Houlbrooks rented
this place out again.
After what happened last year.
Here you go.
Thank you very much for the tip.
Have a good night.
What the fuck happened
last year?
Ahem. So I said,
"Those aren't my pants."
[ALL LAUGHING]
That's why we're not allowed
in Modesto anymore.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
So which one of you guys
writes the songs?
We all do.
Well, we all have ideas
and we all contribute,
so we all get credit.
Yeah, but Jackie does
the heavy lifting.
Show 'em the book, Jackie.
Mm. That's so cute.
That reminds me of my journal.
I love to journal,
especially by hand.
It just makes you feel, like,
so much closer to the words.
That makes so much sense.
She's got, like, 200 songs
in this thing.
All of 'em genius.
- Can I see it?
- JACKIE: Sorry.
Mm. Industry secrets.
Yeah, how do we know
you're not spies for Phantogram?
Shit,
they found us out, girls.
We're secretly
sexy female bandits.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
Hey, a couple of my friends
are leaving the festival.
They're looking
for something to do.
Is it cool if I tell them
to just come?
Yeah, totally.
No.
[DOG BARKING]
The more the merrier.
How many friends?
Just a couple.
[FAWN'S "PENNIES" PLAYING]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- [WOMAN LAUGHING]
Totally! You too.
Know what you need?
You need sunglasses.
Oh.
Has anybody seen
my sunglasses?
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
♪ I know some things... ♪
We are gonna be
Internet famous.
♪ I do some things
You think I won't ♪
♪ Try to be, let me be ♪
Hey, would you like
some coconut water?
I have a whole case
in the fridge.
No, I'm good, thanks.
Okay, well,
remember to stay hydrated.
We are in the desert,
after all.
I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
Oh, my God.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- [MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
Ooh. Fire pit.
I made you a drink.
Thanks,
but I'm not drinking tonight.
Yeah. Ahem.
[GRATING]
[LUCY GROANS]
I just wanna say that...
I've been a fan of yours
for, like,
a while now.
I'm talking,
like, before this album
that you guys just released,
obviously.
I mean,
like, Section Five, okay?
I'm talking Paper Girl.
Like, I even really dug
that solo EP
- you put out a few years ago.
- Oh, let me guess.
You prefer
the early Starfoxy stuff.
I mean, not to be cliché,
but...
Don't apologize.
I do too.
Are you still writing,
like, solo stuff?
Yeah, actually. Um...
Okay, hold up.
Are you, like, writing
right now?
- Yes.
- Can I hear it?
Oh. It's just a verse
and a chorus.
Oh, no, that's perfect.
I have a short attention span.
Okay.
♪ Ice, maybe we can go
All night ♪
♪ Tell the sun to stay down
So we can do this right ♪
♪ I've got drugs for days ♪
♪ And you've got liquor
For weeks ♪
♪ I've got a house
With no heat ♪
♪ And a dance floor
On the street ♪
♪ There's a shout from the back
Of a sold-out crowd ♪
♪ We could turn the shit up
And play this song loud ♪
♪ There's a boy
Who's dying inside very night ♪
♪ Well, he don't look sad
But he don't look right ♪
♪ Yeah, you know
I ain't no killer ♪
♪ But this place
Makes me want to kill ♪
♪ Yeah, you know
I ain't no killer ♪
♪ But this place
Makes me want to kill ♪♪
[LUCY SCREAMS]
[LAUGHING]
Dude, that was awesome.
- [MAPLE CHUCKLES]
- [KIRK GROANS]
[KIRK INHALES DEEPLY]
Hey, look at me.
I'm Michael Phelps.
[MAPLE LAUGHING]
Where'd she get
that bathing suit?
Oh, her purse.
She carries a bathing suit
in her purse?
Yeah, for, like, occasions
such as this.
Come on, Jackie, get in.
The water's fine.
Yeah, come on, Jackie.
The water's fine. Heh.
I'm gonna call it a night.
You guys have fun.
[KIRK GROANS]
Yeah, that's right.
I forgot,
she'll melt if she gets wet.
Aah. Uh-oh.
Ding-dong, the witch is mad.
Heh.
[LINE RINGING]
[LINE CLICKS]
NOAH [OVER PHONE]:
Hey, babe.
Hi.
Thank you for the card.
[NOAH CHUCKLES]
No problem.
How is Operation
No One Parties Tonight going?
Yeah, it's going great.
We're just sitting around,
drinking kombucha,
playing Settlers of Catan.
[LAUGHS]
I bet you are.
- Getting nervous?
I've been nervous since the day
you got me to agree to this.
So you're gonna lie in bed
all night
just stressing about it
and not get any sleep,
right?
You know me too well.
Take one of your knockout pills,
get some sleep.
You'll thank yourself
in the morning
when you wake up
fresh as a daisy.
That's actually
not a bad idea.
Well, that's what I do.
I come up with good ideas.
Well, you deserve more
than your 15 percent.
- Well, I mean, that's...
- [CELL PHONE BEEPS]
Shit. Um...
Babe, I gotta take this call.
Um... I love you.
I love you too.
Okay, bye.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
- [KNOCKS ON DOOR]
- [SIGHS]
I'm coming.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
- [MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
- Mm.
Hey. Switch rooms with me.
What?
Why?
Because your bed is bigger.
Are you fucking kidding me
right now?
- [CHUCKLES]
- Oh, come on.
- Please?
- Yeah, please.
Come on, Jackie.
You owe me one.
Remember that night
after Bonnaroo?
♪ La, la, la, la
Let's just not... ♪
ALL:
Jug! Jug! Jug!
- [WHOOPING]
- [INDISTINCT YELLING]
[WOMAN SINGING INDISTINCTLY
OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Take your hands
Let it out ♪
[ALARM RINGING]
[♪♪♪]
[GROANS]
[SIGHS]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[SIGHS]
Top of our game, boys,
top of our game.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Hm.
[SIGHS]
Hmm.
Holy shit.
And Jackie Simms
was just standing over you?
Yes, sir.
And then what?
And then the police
showed up.
You called the police?
I mean, we didn't call them.
They showed up.
Why do you suppose that is?
I have no idea.
Huh.
Is this your handwriting?
Yeah.
Where did you get this?
Why don't you tell me what you
and your friends did yesterday.
First of all,
they're not really my friends.
I've only known them
like a year.
We don't hang out
outside the band.
They're more like coworkers
than anything.
Then tell me what you and your
coworkers did yesterday, Kirk.
Start with the van.
Phew.
We took off, like, 7 a.m.
The 10 was full of people
trying to get to the festival,
so we took Highway 74.
[VIVALDI'S "FOUR SEASONS"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
JACKIE: Oh, come on. What
the fuck is this shit?
It's Vivaldi.
I thought
Imagine Dragons was bad.
I like Imagine Dragons.
Who doesn't like
Imagine Dragons?
Well,
it's better than this shit.
- This shit's putting me to sleep.
- It's calming.
I figured we could use some calm
before the storm.
Fucking party storm.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [CHUCKLING]
Speaking of which,
I did bring a little surprise
for the hearty party
tonight.
- Oh, sweet.
- Presenting...
Oh, nice!
KIRK:
It's a 2009.
- I figured we deserve it.
- TRAVIS: Absolutely.
How much did that
set you back?
- Don't worry about it.
- Dude, pop it open.
- Yes! Pop it now.
- No. Hey, no.
No one's popping anything.
We are in a moving vehicle.
We don't want to get
arrested.
Good point.
- Hey, let me check that out.
- Sure.
JACKIE: So I decided we're
gonna go straight to the house
and skip the festival today.
I'm kidding.
Fuck.
Jesus Christ, lighten up.
Oh, my God,
you had me, though.
Oh, my God, I freaked out.
[♪♪♪]
Yeah. Yeah, this place
definitely looks
like my grandma's house.
I need to hang out
with your grandma.
KIRK:
Cool, a Pachinko machine.
TRAVIS:
Oh, fuck, yeah.
Yeah.
So how are we picking rooms?
First come, first serve,
Big Brother style?
Sure, whatever,
but I get the master.
Why do you get the master?
Because I said so.
[WATER SPLASHING]
TRAVIS: It's heated!
The pool is heated!
Oh, hey,
I just threw my bag up there.
Did you want the top bunk?
I don't know.
Byron, are you okay?
Yeah, it's just nerves.
The concert tomorrow
and everything.
Dude, don't worry about it.
We're gonna kill it. All right?
Yeah. Yeah, we'll kill it.
Hey, are you gonna
break that thing open or what?
Ah. No.
It's not even cold yet.
Let me know when you do,
all right?
I don't wanna miss it.
All right, I promise.
Scout's honor.
[EXHALES AUDIBLY]
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
[NOTE PLAYS]
You have an errand.
Go to the liquor store.
- Grab a couple cases of beer.
- And some whiskey.
- Why do I have to go?
- You're fresh meat.
[SIGHS]
Jackie, it's been like a year.
Still newer than us.
Okay, fine.
But I'm picking the whiskey.
Just make sure
it's not in a plastic bottle.
- Nothing Canadian.
- We're an American rock band,
we drink American whiskey.
And get some pizza!
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
[PA CHIMES]
Excuse me.
Do you have American whiskey
in glass bottles?
Bottom shelf.
[EXHALES AUDIBLY]
[LAUGHS]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- [MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
Am I doing something hilarious
that I'm not aware of?
[CHUCKLES]
Aren't you the keyboard player
from Starfoxy?
- I am. In the flesh.
- [CHUCKLES]
- I knew it!
We just saw your video
on YouTube.
- Yeah. We, like, love you guys.
- [CHUCKLES]
ALL: ♪ Don't build
a castle For me ♪
♪ Because I can't be trusted
With anything ♪
[ALL GIGGLING]
- That's our song.
- MAPLE: That's you.
- Yeah.
- [LAUGHS]
- Are you guys having a party?
- Yeah.
Oh, yeah, not really.
We play at noon tomorrow,
so I think we're just gonna grab
a drink, head to bed.
Oh, that's pretty fucking lame.
Heh.
I mean, come on,
it's festival weekend.
How about
we all have a party?
- Ooh. I second that notion.
- I third that.
Do you guys have a car?
My sweet ride
is right over there.
KIRK:
Do you guys, uh...
- [CLINKS]
- have a pen?
[MAPLE CHUCKLES]
Do we have a pen, girls?
I think we're 2-for-2.
- I've a pen.
- Look at that.
- [WOMEN CHUCKLING]
- We are staying...
here.
[CAR DOORS CLOSE]
Nice of you to show up.
- MAPLE: Oh, hi.
- LUCY: Hi.
- [LUCY LAUGHS]
- MAPLE: Okay, well...
- LUCY: Look at this place.
- Crazy.
- AMBER: Are you kidding me?
- Come on.
- LUCY: Dude, who owns this place?
- I have no idea.
- MAPLE: Oh, wait, look.
- He's got no idea.
- MAPLE: Gnomes.
- LUCY: You gonna get it for me?
- [CLACKING]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- It's a pool.
- What?
- Ooh. Very nice.
- LUCY: Crazy.
MAPLE: You didn't say
there was a pool.
Hey, guys, this is Amber,
Lucy and Maple.
I met them at the store.
They're fans of ours.
Oh, my God, no way.
So you guys coming
to the festival tomorrow?
Yeah, we're staying
in this super-dodgy motel
- in Palm Springs.
- Heh.
Yeah. I'm pretty sure
there's a meth lab
in the manager's office.
Heh.
Oh, jeez. That sucks.
Meth's, like, a total epidemic
right now.
- Yeah, man.
- Hey, man,
would you mind showing me
where your iPad is?
Yeah, yeah.
[CHUCKLING]
Hey, so Kirk says you guys are
playing the festival tomorrow.
That's so cool.
It sure is.
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
We should probably get
these inside, huh?
- Come on. Come on.
- Yeah, we should go.
- [LUCY CHUCKLES]
- [BOTTLES CLINK]
[LAUGHTER]
TRAVIS: That's why we can't
go to Modesto anymore.
- MAPLE: Well, that's fair.
- [ALL LAUGH]
So who writes the songs?
We all do.
Everyone has ideas.
We all contribute
and we all get credit.
Except for "Castles."
Only one of us
wrote "Castles," huh?
Oh.
Kirk, "Castles" was all you?
Yup. It was the first one
I presented
to the band and boom.
No way. That's so sick.
Yeah.
I actually have tons of songs.
I've been working on them
since I was, like, a teenager.
- This is so cute.
- Oh.
AMBER:
Let me see.
Oh, I wanna write my name
in a heart on the cover.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Damn, you guys have enough
in here
for, like, 30 more
Starfoxy albums.
Well, uh...
Actually,
tomorrow's gonna be my first
and my last festival appearance
with Starfoxy.
What? What does that mean?
I've decided
to go my own way.
Yeah,
but we're cool with it, though.
It was a group decision.
Wait, you guys are breaking up?
That's so sad.
No, we're not breaking up.
Starfoxy will live on.
It's just without Kirk.
[CHUCKLES]
But for now,
I say we celebrate.
- [ALL CHUCKLING]
- TRAVIS: Mm.
Hey, you guys got any friends
you can call?
[CHUCKLES]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[WOMAN WHOOPS]
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
♪ Oh, you got me going ♪
♪ You keep my heart
Safe... ♪
Enjoy.
Hi.
♪ You give me wings
You give me skies ♪
Bottoms up.
[AMBER LAUGHING]
You need to be wearing
sunglasses.
Hey, has anybody seen
my sunglasses?
You guys look thirsty.
What is this?
It's my world-famous
Old Fashioned.
It's rye whiskey, bitters,
sugar, and a slice of orange.
Oh, and some Rohypnol,
of course.
- [CHUCKLES]
Mm. Roofie goodness.
LUCY:
Yeah, enjoy.
[LAUGHS]
- [EXHALES AUDIBLY]
- So this is you singing?
Like, you did this whole thing
yourself?
- That's kind of awesome.
- Yeah.
I got like 50 demos
in there.
Hopefully somebody gets
to hear them soon.
But not with Starfoxy.
That's so sad.
Well, to be honest with you,
I met with this agent and...
Well, he told me
I don't need these guys.
Like, why should I slave away
trying to make Starfoxy relevant
when I can go solo
and just, you know,
take credit where credit's due?
I mean, this guy, he said
I could be their Peter Gabriel
- [CHUCKLES]
- or Chris Cornell.
Their Beyoncé.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [LAUGHS]
So, what, you're not gonna
play me a Kirk original live?
[CHUCKLES]
Like, right now?
Yeah, now.
Hey, Byron,
can you turn the music down?
- [CHUCKLES]
- [MUSIC CONTINUES QUIETLY]
[PLAYING "CASTLES"]
[UPBEAT ELECTRONIC
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
♪ Ice, baby
We can go all night ♪
♪ We'll tell the sun
To stay down ♪
♪ So we can do this right ♪
♪ I've got drugs for days ♪
♪ You got liquor for weeks ♪
♪ We got a house
With no heat ♪
♪ And a dance floor
On the street ♪
♪ There's a shout
From the back ♪
♪ Of a sold-out crowd ♪
♪ Turn that shit up
And play that song loud ♪
♪ There's a girl
Who's dying inside every night ♪
♪ Well, she don't look sad
And she don't look right ♪
♪ Yeah, you know
I ain't no killer ♪
♪ But this place
Makes me wanna kill ♪
♪ Yeah, you know
I ain't no killer ♪
♪ But this place
Makes me wanna kill ♪♪
[CLAPPING]
Who knew we had Stevie Wonder
in the house,
ladies and gentleman?
Wow.
And I thought
this was a fucking party
and you're killing my buzz
with your open-mic shit.
Jackie, can I talk to you
in the kitchen
about something real quick?
So serious.
- ♪ In the park on your skates ♪
- Okay.
♪ Everybody knows... ♪
KIRK: Can you guys
give us a second?
Thanks.
Seriously,
what is your problem?
I don't have a problem.
I'm having a great time
at your fucking
going-away party.
- That's what this is about.
- What else would it be about?
Jackie, you said
you were okay with this.
I lied, Kirk.
I fucking lied.
I mean,
what did you want me to say?
You used us
so that you could have a hit
and then you immediately told us
to go fuck ourselves.
You're unbelievable.
You think I used you?
- That's how this worked out?
- I didn't see anybody else
jumping to hire
some 22-year-old idiot
from fucking Bakersfield.
Yeah, and I didn't see
anyone else
jumping to join a mediocre
bar band called Starfoxy.
Thanks for the champagne.
Fuck you.
LUCY:
Oh, that one almost went in.
[SHRIEKS]
Send, like, three balls
at a time.
[LAUGHS]
Hey,
Maple's looking for you.
She went down there.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Maple?
- Maple?
- Kirk?
I was thinking
we could go for a swim.
[CHUCKLES]
Let me see if I brought
my bathing suit.
[AMBER CHUCKLING]
JACKIE:
So...
Where'd you get
the bathing suit from?
Heh. From my purse.
Well, I guess that shows us
what kind of girl you are.
Good night, Jackie.
JACKIE:
Good night.
Have fun.
So are you the type
to get in slow or just jump?
[LAUGHS]
[WHOOPS, SHRIEKS]
- Fuck it.
- [AMBER GASPING]
[CHUCKLES]
- [EXHALES AUDIBLY]
- [CHUCKLES]
[EXHALES AUDIBLY]
[♪♪♪]
God, this is so weird.
What?
Well...
I was just watching you
in a music video yesterday.
And now...
you are right in front of me,
inches from my face
and you're about to kiss me.
- Oh, am I?
- Yeah.
How can you be so sure?
Woman's intuition.
[CHUCKLES]
AMBER:
Maple!
We're leaving. Now.
- Everyone out.
- What are you doing?
These people
are fucking sleazebags.
Get out of the pool.
Let's go.
[CHUCKLES]
No, I'm having a good time.
- What happened?
- Lucy and I are leaving
and we're not gonna
leave you here alone. Come on.
I'll be back in two seconds.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
WOMAN: She just, like,
came in and kicked us out.
MAN:
I don't know what happened.
Dude,
what the fuck happened?
I don't know.
Seriously,
what the fuck did you do?
I didn't do anything. Amber and
Lucy were in Jackie's room
with Travis,
now they're pissed.
They came out
and told everyone to leave.
Why were they
in Jackie's room?
I don't know.
Well, where's Travis?
[SIGHS]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[SLIDING DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
They leave?
JACKIE:
Yep. They all left.
But I'm still here.
[♪♪♪]
You don't see nights like this
in L.A.
Sure don't.
Mm.
Kirk.
What the fuck happened?
Oh, God!
[♪♪♪]
Maple?
- You guys,
- KIRK: Come on.
you're not gonna believe
what happened last night.
Hey, Maple.
Oh, shit.
And that was the first time
you saw her that morning?
Yeah.
But, I mean, honestly,
I barely remember her
from the night before. Look...
Before we get any deeper
into this,
I feel like there's...
something I need to share
with you.
And I know it's gonna make me
look very, very bad,
but... I feel it's best
to mention it now,
for the good of this whole
overall thing and all.
I...
I am often very high.
No kidding.
Like, a lot.
To an unhealthy degree,
and I know that.
I've done
the research online.
They say
it's incredibly psychologically,
if not physically,
addictive.
And I have a prescription.
Why don't you tell me
about what you can remember?
Start with the van.
Um...
Well, I mean, I smoked
a breakfast bowl right...
That's marijuana.
- Got it.
- I was...
Uh... Jackie picked me up,
passed out ASAP.
And when I woke up,
we were already at the festival.
What about the champagne?
What champagne?
[VIVALDI'S "FOUR SEASONS"
PLAYING]
JACKIE:
We're gonna crash!
[CHUCKLES]
Wake up, dipshit.
Great, we're here.
Every man for himself.
Meet back here at 4.
- I hope they have dragons here.
- I love dragons.
JACKIE:
Who doesn't?
- [MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[♪♪♪]
♪ And there ain't no girl ♪
♪ With whom
I could be seen ♪
♪ And there ain't no girl ♪
♪ That knows
Just what to do ♪
♪ I don't know that bad things
Happen to me ♪
♪ They should happen
To you ♪
♪ Half of all bad things
Happen to me ♪
♪ Well, they should happen
To you ♪
♪ Half of all
The bad things happen to me ♪
♪ Well, they should happen
To you ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
Hey, where'd you find
this place?
JACKIE:
Your grandma.
[BLOWING RASPBERRY]
What's up with these gnomes?
[DOOR CLOSES]
[♪♪♪]
BYRON: Whoa, check it out.
It's a Plinko machine.
[KIRK SIGHS]
Well, first things first,
I'm headed
to the liquor store.
Also gonna see
if I can scrounge up some puss.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
- All right, this is awkward.
- I know.
Yeah, you said we were
gonna do this in the van.
Well, someone
was fucking sleeping.
Oh, hey, look what I'm doing.
I'm poking you with my finger.
Sure bet
that would wake someone up.
I still think we wait
till tomorrow after the show.
No, we tell him tonight
so he won't wanna play tomorrow,
and that way
we call Sweaty Jeff and boom,
new Starfoxy is born
on the festival stage.
But how do you know he's not
gonna wanna play one last show?
Man, he's a fucking baby,
okay?
The moment we tell him,
he's gone.
And it's, "Sayonara, Kirky."
I hope you're right.
Dude, trust me.
I'm always right.
Wanna see
if they have a Ping-Pong table?
JACKIE:
Yeah.
[♪♪♪]
It hit the net.
That's a redo.
No, it's only a redo
on the serve.
- No, it's a redo every time.
- It's only a redo on the serve.
In what rule book?
All of them.
[LAUGHING]
- Aren't they all?
- No.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- Hey. Girls.
[KIRK EXHALES AUDIBLY]
MAPLE: We're staying
in a motel in Indio.
- You guys got any meth?
- No.
Kirk says
you're playing tomorrow.
Weather's supposed to be
so cool.
Oh, come on, dude. I thought
we had a deal. No partying.
This isn't partying.
I think showing up with
a bottle of whiskey and groupies
kind of leads to partying,
don't you think?
Look, Jackie,
if you wanna do
this whole Mary Poppins thing,
go right ahead.
All right? I've got
some earplugs you can borrow.
But you're not my mom. I'm gonna
chase it tonight whether...
You're out of the band,
dude.
[CHUCKLING]
- What?
- Yeah, we thought
it was the best thing
for the group.
Best for the group.
Best for the group?
I've been a critical part of
this group for a fucking year.
We gave it a shot
and it didn't work out.
Heh. Look, there are plenty
of keyboard players out there,
especially ones
who don't treat people
that are supposed to be
their friends like assholes.
You two agree with this?
[♪♪♪]
So this is how you tell me?
In front of total strangers.
Hey, nobody asked you
to go scrounging for puss.
[SCOFFS]
Well, you know what?
Whether you want me
in this band or not,
I'm playing that show
tomorrow.
You can't deny me
that experience.
I fucking earned it.
He's right.
Fuck, yeah, I'm right.
And you know what else,
Jackie?
I'm gonna party tonight
like I've been waiting to
for months.
Call some friends.
Hot ones.
Travis,
order us some pizzas.
Later, dude.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
- Hey, man.
- Hey, how's it going?
All right.
Hey,
has anybody ever told you
you look like the dude
from American Pie?
Who?
The Sherminator.
[CHUCKLES]
Because I have red hair? No.
Forty-two fifty.
Here you go.
Keep the change.
Have a good night.
TRAVIS: All right, who wants pizza?
Excuse me.
Hey, man.
You want some coconut water?
I got a whole case
in the fridge.
No, thanks. I'm good.
All right.
Well, remember to stay hydrated.
We're in a desert,
after all.
- Cool. Cool.
- All right.
Oh, the Sazerac you requested,
sir.
- Oh, why, thank you, Miss Lucy.
- You're so welcome.
- AMBER: Hi.
- Hey.
So do you wanna go teach me
how to play your drums?
Mm. I would, because people love
when you turn the music off
at a party
to give a drum lesson.
There's just one problem.
I can't find my sunglasses.
Can't give a drum lesson
without sunglasses.
Okay, heh.
So do you wanna go
smoke this joint, then?
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
So was that awkward for you,
earlier
at the Ping-Pong table?
What,
you don't like Ping-Pong?
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, of course it was.
It wasn't supposed
to go down like that.
We were supposed to do it
in the van.
Well, at least he has Maple
to console him,
and knowing her, she's gonna
do it in a bathing suit.
- Hm.
- [CHUCKLES]
So Jackie's pretty intense,
huh?
I'm good.
I was watching
the "Castles" video,
and I was like,
"She seems intense,
but she's probably
really down-to-earth."
And then I met her
and I was like,
"No,
she's really that intense."
She's actually pretty chill.
I think this whole Kirk thing
has been pretty rough on her.
On all of us, really.
But she knows
what she's doing.
She's our fearless leader,
on-stage and off.
Sure, sometimes she can use
some unorthodox methods
to get things done,
but, you know, I trust her
to do what's best
for the band.
Can I ask you
a personal question?
Sure.
Where's the bathroom?
Whew. Oh, my... I don't...
It's right there.
[LAUGHS]
Thanks.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
- BYRON: Kirk!
- MAPLE: Seriously?
[KIRK LAUGHS]
- MAPLE: Come on.
- [KIRK LAUGHS]
- MAPLE: Stop.
- [KIRK LAUGHING]
- It's not even funny anymore.
- Come on.
Stop. No, no. Stop.
What a dick.
AMBER:
What did you say?
Oh, I wasn't talking
to you. Uh...
Allison?
Anne?
What the fuck?
MAPLE:
Okay. Wait.
Jennifer Perry?
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Come on. Come and look
at the stars with me.
[SIGHS]
Don't see nights like this
in L.A.
[♪♪♪]
Nope.
Look.
It's Orion's Belt.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, shit,
I forgot to call my mom.
Huh.
That's weird.
That you wanna call
your mom right now?
Yeah, it's a little weird.
No, my phone.
It was on the charger
right there.
I didn't notice.
Yeah, it was.
You sure you didn't
accidentally grab it?
It had a bright green case.
I'm pretty sure, yeah.
Would you mind checking?
Like, in your purse?
Okay.
[SCOFFS]
I mean...
I don't...
Oh.
Wait.
Here it is.
- Wait, what?
- Shh.
Hey. We have a problem.
Okay.
- So...
- Shut up.
- Are you...?
- Shut the fuck up.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
Nice discretion, Jen.
Douche went through my purse
while I was
in the bathroom, Erin.
What? No. I wasn't being creepy.
I was just...
I couldn't remember
her name.
Oh, well, thank God.
Next time,
take your purse with you.
Noted. Thanks.
What are we gonna do,
blow this place?
No. Have you seen
their equipment?
That's like 6, 7000 dollars'
worth of stuff right there.
And earlier I was scoping out
the bedrooms and I found...
You know, actually,
this might work out.
AMBER:
Move.
LUCY:
Go.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
Keep it cool, Cheech.
Take this.
Go ahead, drink.
Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
[SIGHS]
What's up, dude?
Switch rooms with me.
What?
Why?
Your bed is bigger.
Oh, come on, man.
Are you fucking kidding me
right now?
Oh, come on. Please?
Yeah, please.
You owe me one, Jackie.
Remember that night
after Kaaboo?
AMBER:
Good catch.
Didn't notice it
in my sweep earlier.
That's why they pay me
the big bucks.
So you guys are, like,
bandits or something?
Like, sexy female bandits?
Something like that.
That's pretty cool.
- What's the combination?
- To what?
To the fucking safe
I'm currently pointing at.
I don't know. I didn't even know
there was a safe there.
What? Kirk told us
you owned this house.
TRAVIS: That sounds like
something he'd say.
Was he trying to get
into your pants at the time?
- [SCOFFS]
- Shit.
LUCY:
Okay, we'll call Rita.
Rita's car is in the shop.
Then we'll go pick her up.
Is Rita,
like, your safecracker? Uh...
Oh.
I suddenly don't feel
so good.
I kind of feel like...
[♪♪♪]
It's probably the Rohypnol.
The date-rape drug?
Heh. It was in the Sazerac
I made for you.
It should be kicking in
pretty hardcore right about now.
Are you gonna date-rape me?
Heh. Guess you'll find out
in the morning, won't you?
[OBJECT THUMPS; MAN GRUNTS]
TRAVIS:
Ow.
Oh, God, what the fuck?
Am I in a closet?
[♪♪♪]
Yeah, I'm in a closet.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
JACKIE:
Kirk.
- What the fuck happened?
- KIRK: Oh, God!
- [WATER SPLASHING]
- KIRK: Maple?
TRAVIS: You guys aren't gonna believe
what happened last night. Oh...
- KIRK: Hey, Maple.
- TRAVIS: Oh, shit.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Palm Springs
Police Department.
You the owner
of the residence?
Um, no.
- Well, may I speak to the owner?
- They're not here.
- You know where they are?
- East Coast?
Look, we got a situation here.
There's a girl...
You recognize this vehicle?
Oh, shit.
Appears the driver mysteriously
lost control of the vehicle
and slammed
right into some rocks.
Neither was wearing
a seat belt.
It seems like there's something
on your mind there, Byron.
You ever hear
of the prisoner's dilemma?
Two suspects are arrested,
charged with committing
a crime together.
They're separated
and offered the same deal.
Whoever rats the other one out
first walks free,
while his co-conspirator goes
to jail forever.
But if your friend
rats you out first,
you go to jail forever
and he goes free.
So the question is this:
How much do you trust...?
I'll just tell you everything,
okay?
I'll tell you the truth.
I've heard a lot
of truth today, Byron.
No, you've heard the story
we were supposed to tell you.
We left around 9 a.m.
We took the 74
because we figured
there'd be less cops
than on the 10.
[VIVALDI PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
So, Kirk,
score any coke?
Ask and you shall receive.
All right. So we gonna dip
into that shit tonight
or are we gonna wait
till tomorrow after the show?
No night as good as the present.
I ain't waiting for shit.
Hey, as much as I love that
shit, we're in a motor vehicle.
Can you not go
waving it around?
Good point.
Hey. Let me see that.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
I'm gonna check out
New Pollution first.
What about you guys?
- KIRK: Wax Battleship.
- BYRON: Invasion 101.
JACKIE: Every man for himself.
Let's meet back here at 4.
We're good.
[LAUGHTER IN DISTANCE]
Come on. He's waiting.
[♪♪♪]
It's Jackie.
Jackie.
Nice to see you.
Have a seat, gentlemen.
You want coconut water?
I got a case in the fridge.
No, I'm good, thanks.
Okay, well, remember
to stay hydrated.
We are in the desert,
after all.
One moment.
Finishing something up,
and...
excellent.
Sorry. So how are you?
Good.
And Noah?
How'd he like that shit
I gave him for Vegas?
- Said it was A-plus.
- Excellent. Excellent.
We really care
about customer service here.
So let's get you set up.
So like I said
in my text, 800.
Yup.
It's all there.
I know. I trust you.
We're good.
So I gotta tell you,
I was a little surprised
when I got your order in.
This yearly gathering
of musicians flush with cash,
big boom for my business,
in terms of molly, shrooms,
coke,
and a shit-ton of weed.
But you, always coming up
with new, inventive ways
to keep me on my toes.
Ah.
Here it is.
Is it pure?
Pure?
That is grade-A organic
from-the-poppy-fields-
of-occupied-Afghanistan pure.
Do you guys want some needles?
I buy 'em in bulk.
[CHUCKLES]
That won't be necessary.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Okay.
So go out there,
be seen, take selfies,
do keg stands, whatever.
Just act normal.
[BAND PLAYING ROCK IN DISTANCE]
[WHISTLING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- [BAND PLAYING]
- [CHEERING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
Check it out.
They've got one
of these Chinese
pinball machines.
Oh, yes.
Go pick your rooms.
Byron, you're bunking with him.
I'm taking the master.
[KIRK SNORTS]
Daddy loves you.
[EXHALES AUDIBLY]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Whew.
[CHUCKLES]
You getting
that 3 o'clock feeling?
Little lump of sugar
in your coffee?
Uh... No, not right now, man.
I'm cool.
All right, suit yourself.
[SNORTS]
[EXHALES AUDIBLY]
[SNIFFLES]
[ROCK PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[STRUMMING]
Hey, I'm gonna hit
the liquor store.
JACKIE:
All right.
We really doing this?
We're really doing this.
We still cool?
♪ Are you ready
For what comes next? ♪
To face who you are? ♪
Let's go.
[♪♪♪]
Get the demos.
How much is he gonna have
to snort before...?
Not much.
He'll be on the floor
before he realizes
anything's wrong.
Are you sure about this?
This is the point of no return.
Don't give me
this bullshit right now.
I don't get why he can't play
the last concert.
- We can do this tomorrow night.
- No, we can't.
We talked about this endlessly.
It happens tonight.
I've got Jeff on standby.
He's learned Kirk's parts,
can be here in the morning.
- You told Jeff what we're doing?
- No, Byron.
Jesus, I'm not an idiot. I told
him we were gonna fire Kirk.
Hey, listen. I get it.
You're having second thoughts.
It's a man's life.
But look at the direction that
he's gone since "Castles" hit.
All the alcohol,
all the coke.
He's gonna be
shooting up soon anyway.
I mean, we're just beating fate
to the punch, right?
[SIGHS]
[STARRY SAINTS' "GHOST"
PLAYING]
♪ A ghost left
To its fate ♪
♪ Its fate ♪
♪ No fate ♪
♪ You're like a teardrop
In the rain ♪
♪ The rain ♪
♪ But it's too late ♪
♪ You're a ghost ♪
♪ Go, go, go, go... ♪
♪ Left to its fate ♪♪
This is done.
What are you gonna do
with the coke?
I don't know.
Save it for a rainy day?
I mean, Kirk,
he gets some good shit.
I'd hate for it
to go to waste.
Now, come on, let's figure out
what the fuck we've been doing.
♪ Catch me now ♪
♪ I can travel with you ♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
- MAPLE: ...this entire house.
- AMBER: A pool.
MAPLE:
And there's three bedrooms?
- KIRK: I think so.
- MAPLE: Very nice.
JACKIE:
Hey, Kirk.
Who are your new friends?
Uh... This is Maple,
Amber and Lucy.
We met at the liquor store.
MAPLE:
Yeah. Thanks for having us over.
We're staying in this motel
in Cathedral City
- that's honestly so sketchy.
- [KIRK CHUCKLES]
LUCY: I'm pretty sure
that there's a meth lab
- in the manager's office.
- [MAPLE CHUCKLES]
Would you show me
where your iPad is?
Yeah, man. Yeah.
Kirk says you are playing
the festival. That's so cool.
Byron, stay calm, man.
Stay calm?
What if he offers it to them?
We just have to make sure
that doesn't happen, don't we?
No, we have to get it
right now and flush it.
What will you say to Kirk
when he catches you?
How will you explain
his missing coke?
- I don't know...
- No, goddamn it.
Byron, if you try anything,
I swear to God...
We just need to get these chicks
out of here as soon as we can.
Don't let them
leave your sight.
Stay calm.
Point of no return.
This weekend's gonna be
my first and last festival show
with Starfoxy.
Your last festival show
with Starfoxy?
What does that mean?
I've decided
to go my own way.
Yeah, but we're cool with it.
It was a group decision.
But Starfoxy's breaking up?
That's so sad.
No.
No, we're not breaking up.
Starfoxy will live on, just...
without Kirk.
KIRK: But in honor of the eve
of our last show together,
I propose that we celebrate.
All right?
Yeah. I have some friends
I could call.
[CHUCKLES]
KIRK: ♪ There's a
shout From the back ♪
♪ Of a sold-out crowd ♪
♪ Turn that shit up
And play that song loud ♪
♪ There's a girl
Who's dying inside every night ♪
♪ Well, she don't look sad
And she don't look right ♪
♪ Yeah, you know
I ain't no killer ♪
♪ But this place
Makes me wanna kill ♪
♪ Yeah, you know
I ain't no killer ♪
♪ But this place
Makes me wanna kill ♪
[CLAPPING]
[HOWLS]
Stevie Wonder's
in the house!
I thought this was supposed
to be a party,
but you're killing my buzz, man.
Jackie, can I talk to you
in the kitchen for a second?
Sure.
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
Oh, hey, where you going?
I was gonna change
into my swimsuit.
Hey, I made you
my world-famous Old Fashioned.
- Oh, thanks.
- [CHUCKLES]
It's super tasty.
Do you want to...?
- You should try it.
- KIRK: Where's Maple?
LUCY: You know what?
Maple's looking for you.
She just went
down the hallway.
Okay.
Try it. It's so yummy.
I just made it.
- I'll be right back.
- Oh... Okay.
KIRK:
I don't know.
It's already turning
into kind of a weird night.
Then let's get weirder.
[CHUCKLES]
KIRK:
Okay. I'll, uh...
I'll try and find my suit.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- Here we go.
- [GASPS]
Crazy.
[CHUCKLES]
- Actually, uh...
- Hm.
Do you party?
- MAPLE: Do I party how?
- KIRK: Uh...
- with blow?
- [GASPS]
Oh.
As a matter of fact, I do.
But...
I'm okay for now.
Maybe later?
A little pick-me-up.
Okay.
All right. I'm gonna change
in here. Don't look.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LINE RINGING]
- NOAH [OVER PHONE]: What's up?
- I can't.
What?
Starfoxy will be just fine.
We don't have to do this.
Are you fucking kidding me?
What happens halfway
into recording the first record
when the label realizes
the three of you
can't write a hit song
to save your fucking lives?
They want you
because of "Castles,"
and that's it.
Songs are the key here,
Byron,
and his demos are worth
a fortune in the right hands.
Do the others share your...
newfound sense of morality?
No, they're on board.
Everything's going
according to your plan.
[SIGHS]
Man up, Byron.
Man the fuck up.
This is what's best
for you.
And most importantly,
it's what's best for us.
Now...
can you do this?
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
LUCY: We're leaving.
Now. Everyone out!
I gotta go. I love you.
I love you too.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- Why is everyone leaving?
- Ask your friend Travis.
- Come on.
- Where is he?
In hell, for all I care.
Come on!
AMBER:
Let's go!
- LUCY: Maple, hurry up!
- MAPLE: Just... No...
LUCY: No "wait," just
get out the door.
AMBER:
Let's go!
Oh, my God, I can...
- [DOOR SLAMS]
- Byron, what happened?
I don't know.
Seriously, dude,
what did you do?
I didn't do anything.
- Where's Travis?
- I don't know!
[CHUCKLES]
Bro, calm down.
Listen,
I know I'm gonna miss
nights like this.
You know, the four of us,
getting crazy,
getting shit-faced.
I mean, just promise me
that we'll still do this,
you know, like,
even after it's over, yeah?
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Good.
Oh, fuck this.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
Oh.
It's kicking in.
Good night.
And that's it.
I mean, that's everything.
I don't know how they died.
I don't know how anybody died.
I do.
See, I already had
the map key.
I just never had the map.
And now you and your friends
have drawn it for me.
Byron,
do you know who owns
3855 Guadalupe Way?
Donald and Mary Houlbrook.
Sweet couple,
live in Boston.
Own a chain
of greeting-card stores.
Spoke to them
this morning and...
well, they were very upset
to hear about what happened
in their home.
Apparently isn't
the first time, though.
Last year
during the festival,
someone was renting
their place
and smashed their mailbox
and pissed
all over the garage door.
Which is why
they installed security cameras.
Hm.
Hidden in the garden gnomes
by the front door.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
What's up
with these gnomes?
- Where'd you find this place?
- Airbnb.
I guess the couple lives
on the East Coast
and they only use it
in winter.
LUCY:
Who owns this house?
KIRK:
That would be Travis.
It's kind of our
weekend-getaway place
when our pad in the Hills
gets too stuffy.
- Yeah? That's nice.
- Cool.
- Hi.
- Hi. Forty-two fifty.
Hey, anybody ever tell you
you look...?
- I think she beat us here.
- Yeah, she always does.
- Awesome. I never do that.
- Yeah.
Let's go, what the hell
are we waiting for?
- Come on!
- Jesus Christ!
[LAUGHING]
Nice. I actually
like it when you yell.
AMBER:
Harsh, but I liked it.
- LUCY: It was out of love.
- AMBER: It was good.
Hey. Shh. Shut the fuck up.
Be quiet.
There go the witnesses
who saw the end of the party.
- Time to get to work.
- [ENGINE STARTS]
We're gonna get Rita,
help with the safe.
We'll take the canyon,
be back in a few.
I'll stay here,
hold things down.
Who cares about the safe?
AMBER:
We do. Call it a bonus.
The boys aren't
even out yet, so...
Hard to shoot heroin up
their veins if they're awake.
- Heh.
- We'll get the safe
- and it'll be fine.
- The safe isn't the priority.
The overdoses are.
If I wake up in the morning
and they're still alive,
we're all gonna be fucked.
The situation is gonna be
fucked. So we focus.
Focus?
[SCOFFS]
Last time I checked,
it was your husband
that was bankrolling
this tragic accident
to kick-start your solo career.
Wasn't you.
So why don't you
let us do our job?
You can go pop a bar,
get a little beauty sleep,
and let us handle it.
Understood?
Yeah.
Sure.
Go get Rita.
Do whatever it is
that you need to do.
MAPLE:
We will. Hey.
Where's the coke?
What?
The coke you switched
with Kirk's.
Where is it?
Noah said we could have it.
In my guitar case.
Fucking twat.
- Want some blow for the road?
- "Where's the coke?"
- [LAUGHING]
- See you in a second.
- I'll cut it up.
- We'll be in the car.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
- So, what happens now?
- FAIRBANKS: They'll be placed
under arrest and charged
with involuntary manslaughter
and attempted murder.
- What about me?
- FAIRBANKS: Well, I'm sure
we'll have some more questions
for you at some point.
But for now,
you're free to go.
Well, then...
I guess I've got a show
to get to.
[MAXIE DEAN'S "CASTLES"
PLAYING]
♪ You're all I'm not
You're all I see ♪
♪ You're the last thing
That I breathe ♪
♪ Before I go to sleep ♪
♪ And I know you're simple
Underneath the skin ♪
♪ I push you out
I pull you in ♪
♪ It's a catastrophe ♪
♪ So don't build a castle
For me ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't be trusted
With anything ♪
♪ Don't make instructions
For me ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't take lessons
On anything ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba
Ba-ba-da ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba, ba-ba-da
Da-da ♪
♪ I give it back
I want it more ♪
♪ I call you up
Just to let you know ♪
♪ That I'm face down
On the floor ♪
♪ Don't build a castle
For me ♪
♪ Ba, da, da, da, da ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't be trusted
With anything ♪
♪ Don't make instructions
For me ♪
♪ Ba, da, da, da ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't take lessons
On anything ♪
♪ Ho ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba
Ba-ba-da ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba, ba-ba-da
Da-da ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba
Ba-ba-da ♪
♪ Now I'm running
Out the store ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba, ba-ba-da
Da-da ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba
Ba-ba-da ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba, ba-ba-da
Da-da ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba
Ba-ba-da ♪
♪ Now I'm running
Out the store ♪
♪ Ba-ba, ba-da-ba, ba-ba-da
Da-da ♪♪
[YELLING]
MAN:
Boom!
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[KEYS JINGLING]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- [ENGINE STARTS]
Subtitles by explosiveskull