Little darc has been busy.
Mr. Tagawa says he's teaching me
a valuable trade.
Mr. Tagawa likes to sit on his fat ass.
As long as he doesn't have to work,
he'll tell you anything.
Hey, kid.
Reading that comic again?
"Darc."
You want to be a hero, huh?
- Been working hard?
- I fixed the bench.
You're a good boy, baby.
I got you something.
Open it.
Mom...
It's great.
Thank you!
I love you so much.
You will... do...
As...
I...
Say!
You little shit!
Mom!
Early release.
This was you?
Yeah.
The answer is still no.
Yeah, well, it's not the agency asking.
It's me, personally.
They got my daughter.
Kogakai.
Hear what I said?
- Got a bus to catch.
- They took my daughter.
Hey, do you hear me? Hey!
Fuck.
Been playing kachi-kachi?
What's this card?
Juu
the only card adopted from the west
and it is totally worthless
only until late in the game.
Then it can change everything.
You should spend more time working
and less time gambling.
Hey.
Could you stop a second?
My daughter's a nurse.
She got nothing to do with them.
All that shit, they got her holed up
three weeks now.
Can you imagine the hell
she's been put through?
'Cause I'm not going away, pal.
I'll stick in your head
like a fucking aneurysm.
It's kogakai.
What the hell do you think I can do?
Whatever the hell I can't.
You got a whole army of agents.
Ok.
So interpol gets involved now.
And they're looking for her.
Where the hell do you think
we're gonna find her? Tell me.
Sorry, can't help you.
You know I got you an early release.
I'll put you right the fuck back!
Shit. Darc.
You're... you're...
You're out?
Yeah, no shit.
What'd I tell you about being out here?
Guess I need to teach you another lesson.
Fuck!
You ain't the fucking cops, man.
Stay out of here, motherfucker.
Fuck.
I keep the deposit.
Comprende, big man?
You got to be fucking kidding me!
What are you looking at?
Excuse me?
Do you wanna bring your ass out here
and help me? Or...
Jeez, forget it.
Just bring 'em in here, maybe.
Just leave it, it's fine.
Do you want an award or something?
Hey, neighbor.
Thank you.
Daddy. Please. Please don't...
You want to keep her clean?
You know what to do.
Just beer, not a marriage proposal.
Thanks.
Oh, he speaks.
My name is...
Ivana mulligan.
My friends call me Ivy.
This is the part where you shake my hand.
Jake Walters.
People call me darc.
Darc. Ok.
Nice to meet you.
When she was five,
she fell off a swing.
She went into a coma.
A few days pass, she opens her eyes,
and she looks at me and she says,
"I'm sorry, daddy."
Sorry. You're fit.
You don't need this.
You don't need to do it for my daughter.
You should do it for your mother.
Mom!
Come on, baby.
Get them!
Get fucking both of them!
Move! Out of the way!
Mom!
Go!
She'll get the justice.
I want it stopped.
I want it stopped!
Nobody just walks into the yakuza.
Kageyama.
Toshio kageyama.
You recall that face?
Mom!
He's the one that ordered the kidnap.
He set it up.
It's his son, the oyabun.
Go, baby, go, go!
Fucking cunt!
Momma!
That's enough!
No!
Small world, huh?
Why'd they take her?
'Cause a bomb took my leg.
I went down, I came back.
They want to own me.
That's why they have her.
This ain't about me, man.
I don't give a shit
about what happens to me.
It's about my daughter.
Fucker!
Let go!
Get the police!
For fuck's sake.
Hi. Wow!
Almost didn't recognize you.
You really don't clean up half bad.
No.
I'm pretty handy with a hammer.
Do you think that this particular shelf
hung its fucking self?
I just... I could...
I could go for a coffee, maybe.
Bye, Ivy.
There's a biker named Bronson.
Toshio wants him dead.
But they got him holed up
in town somewhere.
There we go.
Shigeru kageyama
toshio's son.
Kind of a stain
on the family name.
The little shig's going to try
to redeem himself
in his old man's eyes.
Shigeru needs help.
You're up.
You know who the fuck I am?
Get off.
Yeah, the little asshole
just tried to rip us off.
I'll pay you what we agreed on.
No, the price just doubled.
Fuck you.
Wait, relax, all right.
Fuck.
Who the fuck are you? Hold him.
Who the fuck are you, asshole?
You have any idea who you're fucking with?
- Come on.
- Let's get him, guys.
Stupid motherfucker.
Where the fuck is Bronson?
Where the fuck is he?
Ah!
Who the fuck are you?
Hey, yo, wait.
Hey, that was fucking awesome.
Seriously, man, I owe you.
Let me buy you a drink.
Got somewhere to be.
Come on.
Just a drink.
A talk.
You don't like what I say, you walk away.
Keep the cash.
What were you in for?
Which time?
Seriously, what for?
I have a temper.
I don't like idiots.
Not a good combination.
You ever kill anyone? Not officially.
I'm working on something.
You could be helpful.
You know nothing about me.
You'll be checked out.
But I need someone now. Someone good.
And I know you are that, huh?
Yeah? All right.
- Give me your number.
- Don't have a phone.
Never had a need for one.
I'm taking your phone.
Here's my number.
And delete the rest.
- We haven't discussed payment.
- Don't worry about that.
Hi, am I interrupting anything?
No I... I exercise when I'm bored.
You must get bored a lot.
I am really busy tonight, so I thought,
sorry, that we could have an early dinner.
But, no funny business, we're just
neighbors. You fucking understand me?
- I fucking do.
- Ok.
So, I can tell that...
You're on the aloof end
of the social spectrum.
Which is not a problem for me,
I tend to talk enough for two.
But, the ex-con thing,
that may be an issue.
If you were put in
for abusing women or children then,
I gotta go.
And I'm gonna take my food with me.
Seriously, though, I think
that there's no lower form of life
than abusers of the innocent.
No arguments from me.
Ok.
Ok, great.
Let's eat.
Going to get some plates, and what else?
Silverware, probably.
No plates.
I guess a corkscrew
is out of the question.
Is out of the question, ok.
- Hmm.
- Ok, don't worry about it.
I shouldn't have wine, anyways.
If my students caught
that on my breath,
half of them would relapse
right there in class.
We just stick to the pizza.
Hi.
So, what do you do?
Keeps you so busy,
you can't even buy the basics.
Sorry.
Yeah?
I know where.
Yeah.
What I do, I gotta do it now.
- That's ok. Ok.
- I'm sorry.
We'll just share it later.
I'd like that.
Ok.
Well, I'll just...
Have fun doing whatever it is you do.
Four of them. Exit's on the other side.
These assholes killed three of my men.
You carrying?
You know how to use a semi, right?
All right.
I... I take the inside.
Come on, baby, daddy wants a queen.
Daddy is a queen.
Just fucking deal, Bronson.
I win this hand, I'm next.
Hey, girl, don't worry,
he won't even touch the sides.
What the fuck is this?
Go.
Bronson, it's a jap!
Come on, you motherfucker!
Die, chink.
Hey, I'm Japanese, asshole.
Same fucking difference.
Up there, that's where he is.
My father.
Emperor toshio kageyama.
An important man.
So very important.
Open your files.
As you can see from the chart...
Since coming to the U.S...
Gentlemen, please excuse the intrusion.
I have something you've been
desperately looking for.
Momma!
For this, your interrupt business?
I thought it was important.
You've been looking for him for weeks.
Finally, I found him.
Me...
And my new friend.
Jake Walters, my father.
The honorable toshio kageyama.
You brought a fucking gaijin?
Have you looked into him?
My father thinks you're a spy.
I killed three men in front of a witness.
You know any agency
that will condone that?
Wait outside.
Where did you find him?
He saved my ass.
And that's not suspicious to you?
He killed in front of me.
Besides, they would never try to get
a white guy inside.
Because we don't expect it
maybe that's exactly what they would do!
This guy is seriously good.
I've never seen anyone like him.
Trust me.
Just this once.
Remember this...
Don't speak about anything
important with him.
Of course.
I only hope he is
as good as you say he is.
I would stake my life on it.
Let's go.
Get me the dragons.
Fuck, yeah.
This is just the beginning.
Your brawn and my brain,
we're going to build am empire.
If you see anything you like,
she's on the house.
Kind of particular.
Hey, not me.
Have a look around,
I'm sure you'll find something.
Gaijin.
Is there a problem?
Yeah, you.
Shit. You ok, man?
You ok
- thanks for the help.
- I couldn't.
It was a test.
As a gaijin,
you'll never be yakuza.
I'm just here for the money.
Do your job,
and you'll be well rewarded.
I've already done one job.
Didn't you pay him?
Huh?
Wait.
You caused a great deal of damage
to my club.
Kanji will drive you home.
- I'll take a cab.
- No.
You work for us.
We'll get you home.
Find out everything you can.
This gaijin is hiding something.
Shigeru-San, sent me.
They're waiting to drive me back.
Please, if I don't stay...
I can be very good to you.
Do things that'll take your mind
off your injuries.
Come in. Please.
Have a seat.
Ah! No corkscrew.
Maybe I can help with that.
Wait.
Please.
That worked.
You wouldn't happened to have brought
any glasses with you.
Who needs a glass.
It's pretty bad.
Perfect with cold pizza.
Those things will kill you.
You're right.
Why are you here?
Why are you here, Lisa?
I'm not judging.
My mother was in the trade.
She had no choice.
My family borrowed money from toshio-San.
The business went bad...
- Until the debt's paid off...
- So if you disappear,
so does your family.
- Hmm!
- You need to get some rest.
Wait.
My mother never had any money of her own.
Buy something nice for yourself.
That's my fuckin' pizza.
So what?
- Need more information.
- Hey, I wanna know my daughter's alive.
That's the problem with today's cops.
No trust in the public.
Daddy?
Baby, listen to me. Listen to me!
Daddy!
Need to know who this is.
I'll text you a copy.
You better wrap your head around this.
'Cause if one thing happens to her,
I'm coming for you! You hear me?
So, she hit the spot.
The bitch I sent you?
I saw how you looked at her.
Seems all you white fuckers
like a bit of yellow.
But most of the girls
in the club were white.
Where do they come from?
All over the world, buddy.
Why do you think we got into
the shipping business?
You planning on starting out on your own?
What do you think?
I think you're smart enough to know
what would happen to you if you tried.
There. Pull over.
So, what do these guys owe you?
It's not a lot of money.
It's the disrespect.
You know, China people not
paying sets a bad example.
Do you what Japanese really like?
Sushi and golf.
Wait, wait, please!
We didn't have a choice. We didn't...
Everyone has a choice.
They make us, they make us!
Triple eight triad!
They said they would take it over.
And you believed them.
Fucking Chinese!
The register!
- Take it. Whatever we have is yours!
- Damn straight, old woman.
This will always be
kogakai territory, granny.
Remember that.
Apologies for the interruption, folks.
Enjoy your meals.
Looks like we got to go hunting.
Time to visit Lee at the triple eight.
Hey! Hey!
Fucking Chinese!
Help!
Please, I'm unarmed.
No witnesses.
Where is Lee?
Where the fuck is Lee?
Relax ladies.
I don't kill women.
Unless they deserve it.
No!
There you go then.
Let's go.
Grab everything you can.
Shigeru-San, back in a minute.
Shigeru.
Where's your new friend?
Somewhere around here...
He'll be back soon.
I see you again,
I'll drown you in your own fat.
Drown him in his own fat?
You ok?
Who are you?
What are you really doing here?
I'm looking for someone.
A girl.
Renee lafique.
She was here.
I took her food.
They moved her a few days ago.
To where?
I don't know.
They've got businesses everywhere.
Shipping yards, motels, private homes.
Think, Lisa.
Maybe someone mentioned something.
I have to find her. I'll try to find out.
- If she ends up back here, I can call you.
- Be careful.
You too.
They'd pay a lot for this information.
If Renee's taken back
to the brothel, she'll call me.
What do you mean
that's all you fuckin' got? Do you
understand the longer you're there,
the more of a chance
they find out who you are.
They're asking questions now
for Christ sakes.
Give them what they want.
Be a smart cop, leave out Japan.
Oh, come on, you're supposed to make shit
happen. That's why I got you out. Christ.
You gotta do something, goddamn it!
Do something?
Well, how much longer
do you think we've got?
Ok.
Wha... what does that mean? Ok.
Time to make shit happen.
That's everything.
What I could find anyway.
You gave me short notice, you know.
You're making excuses?
Well, that makes me suspicious.
No excuses. Hey, what
do you want me to say?
You want me to say he's bad fucking news?
All right.
He's bad fucking news.
Couldn't imagine the American
back line hold defense like that.
Vasquez! Yes, yes, he's through.
He's through.
He drops the ball
before he makes the edge.
He's out of the game, how unfortunate.
You motherfucker.
You are so dead.
Stay in here.
You!
I fucking knew it.
Get help!
You hear me, girl?
Do it and your family debt is clean!
Good offer.
If I were her, I'd take it.
Who the fuck are you?
Think back.
Japan.
Chiba.
An alley.
Whore.
Her throat,
slit.
I was eight years old.
Darc boy?
I'm gonna kill you toshio-San.
We both know that.
Unless,
tell me where Renee lafique is.
Where?
Ok. Ok.
She's...
Your momma had some good moves.
You fucking idiot!
We'd never hide her
in such a public place.
Jake.
You should've left.
I almost did.
They know I'm here.
You can't just leave me.
They'll torture me, I'll tell them
everything and they'll kill me.
Lisa. Do it.
Do it.
Please.
Come with us.
That's a big gun.
It's a big world.
They're just business associates.
Well, they're being loud.
I'd like them to go.
Oyabun is on his way from Japan.
Shigeru needs you.
Wait outside.
This gun is getting real heavy, boys.
It might just go off any minute.
You're a taciturn bastard.
The people you associate yourself with,
they speak volumes.
He'll be with us soon.
One more time.
Where'd you get these tattoos?
Do it.
Tell me who sent you, gaijin.
Did toshio
is that why you killed him?
Hit him!
Harder!
Do it again!
Get out.
He doesn't work for you
get out.
- Get out of or I'll fucking castrate you!
- Get out or I'll fucking castrate you!
Who brought him here?
Me.
Who put you in charge?
Look at his tattoos.
He is not who he says he is.
I knew about them!
It's one of the reasons I hired him!
What the fuck do you know?
You were born in America.
I was toshi's aide.
He was my friend.
He was my father!
And he regretted that every day.
You were my father's pet dog.
Just a translator. Nothing more.
The only reason I won't kill you...
My grandfather will want to know
where you were when my father died!
Taking you home.
And, Jake,
don't go too far.
You and I have a lot to discuss.
What about the whore?
It's strange she was the only one
left alive.
She was knocked out.
She called us as soon as she came round.
Why would she do that if she was involved?
- The gaijin is the...
- Not again.
He has done everything we've asked of him.
He has done everything
we have asked of him.
For money.
- What if someone offered him more?
- Like fucking who?
Enough.
If the gaijin is innocent
then the attack was carried out
by someone else.
Shigeru.
Find out who and clear his name.
Kanji.
When this is over,
I want to hear about how toshio died
while you were responsible
for his security.
And both of you,
remember this well.
We are yakuza.
No individual is more important
than the family.
I think
you owe me an explanation.
Oh, my god.
What happened to you?
I bruise easily.
You're such an asshole. Come on.
Let me talk to the cop.
This cop is mine. Get your own source.
This cop's mine. Get your own source.
Speak fuckin' english, asshole.
No individual is more important
than the family.
Tell me.
If you trust me, this isn't something
you want to know about.
I want to know.
They kidnapped someone.
I'm trying to find her.
'Cause it's a cop's daughter.
- He came to me.
- Oh!
- I gotta go. I gotta get out there.
- Ok. Ok.
I don't know if you're going to be
any help to anybody right now.
Don't be an idiot. Come on, ok.
Come this way.
Ivy, I...
I just wanted to tell you...
Sorry.
Wuss.
- Where's kanji?
- Fuck kanji.
- Get out!
- Calm down.
- Play fucking stupid with me. I dare you!
- I'm mot playing stupi...
Who did it?
I'm not going to ask you again. Who?
Lee.
From triple eight.
Never.
No, no. He can't be.
He doesn't have the balls.
And what if he shot up your place, huh?
What if he killed your men?
What the fuck would you have done?
Your job's to keep people
from fucking back.
You fuckhead.
If you're not doing that,
why the fuck do we need
your little bitch daughter?
You are certain it was him?
He admitted it.
His final words.
How did you find out?
I suspected from the beginning.
Our interpol dog confirmed it.
The same man who provided
the dossier on your partner?
That's right. He's been very useful.
So, your friend is cleared.
As I expected.
Shigeru, you've done well.
You're becoming the man
we always hoped you would.
Sorry for the interruption
but we have more information.
There were important details
omitted from the policeman's dossier.
Only until late in the game.
Then it can change everything.
Hey.
He's alive.
How did I get here?
You don't remember.
Those pills I gave you
really knocked you out.
Ivy, how long have I been out?
- Ah... sixteen hours.
- Damn it, I got to go.
Yeah, 'cause you seem fine.
Ivy, there's a girl's life on the line.
So, you're gonna risk yours to save hers.
I'm told, you're the last person
to see my son alive.
You'll tell us exactly what happened.
And before you begin,
you should know,
I have a man on the way
to your family's home.
Huh!
I brought your pain killers.
Supposed to take two.
They're really potent.
So...
Ok, or six.
- Ivy, you know...
- No, I'm sorry. I...
Peace offering.
Unless you were planning on hitching.
Just come back.
I promise.
Please, please, please.
All this for one woman?
Two, if you count his mother.
Bring me this woman.
And find kanji and shigeru.
Grandfather?
Yeah?
Hey, something went wrong.
Something really went fucking wrong.
They just told me to pick my daughter
up at the docks.
What the fuck does that mean?
Lafique...
- they know.
Where?
- Pier 9.
Wait outside. Do not go on your own.
Can you hear me lafique?
A cartload of shit.
Where's my daughter?
You were warned what would happen to her
if you ever lied to us.
So, where's my daughter?
Are you fucking insane?
Hey!
Baby! Baby!
Come on, listen to me.
Cut her down.
- I'll tell you everything.
- We already know everything.
Baby!
Cut her down! Cut her down!
Cut her down.
No!
Renee, your dad's with me.
Renee.
Renee? Lisa.
Lisa.
I'm sorry.
I got you.
I told them, they know. They know.
I know. That's all right.
Get away! Go!
He fucking lied to me!
All this time, he's been lying to me,
making a fool of me!
Faster, you fucking monkey! Faster!
Faster!
Where is he?
Where the fuck is he?
He's not fucking here!
Get off me!
Tell me!
Where the fuck is he?
Enough!
Don't!
- I fucking vouched for you!
- Drop the knife.
Those tattoos, the night we met,
it wasn't just chance, was it?
-Let her go, shigeru.
She's just my neighbor.
Shigeru.
Fuck you, and all your fucking lies!
Move! Secure him.
It's pointless.
It'll just be you and me.
You will never be oyabun.
You fucking...
Do it.
The last thing you're gonna see
will be the inside of her throat.
- No, no, no.
- On your fucking knees, you piece of shit.
Secure him!
Hands behind your back!
Ivy, it's ok.
It's ok.
Shigeru.
She's innocent.
Shigeru-San,
let her go.
Fuck it.
No!
Enough!
Put him in a chair
Leave us.
Shigeru, you too.
Oyabun, please.
Look at me.
There was a boy once, a lifetime ago,
with a whore for a mother.
That he was even allowed to live,
was a mistake.
I can't recall most
of the men I've killed,
but women,
there's something different about them.
You want to kill me, darc?
It's like you said,
it was a lifetime ago.
And yet, my son died in the present.
Get that little shit in here.
He's weak, he's ambitious,
perhaps, even he's a coward.
But it is his duty to avenge
his father's death.
Oyabun, I...
You will take him away and deal with him.
Leave it to me.
You will take Mr. Kimuro with you.
Wait a second, oya...
You'll do what I say!
I understand.
Jake.
Come on, Jake.
I fucking saved your life, Jake.
Fucking saved your life.
I have money.
You and I can start something.
It was just a fucking girl! Come on.
Jake, please.
Come on, Jake.
Jake, come on. Jake, please.
Jake, Jake, Jake!
Please, please don't.
Jake, please!
Prepare the men.
Get out! Move it, move!
Move, get out, move!
Juu...
The card that can change everything.
Are you here to save the girl?
Or avenge your mother?
You don't even know anymore.
Drop it.
You want to save her?
Or let her end up like your whore mother?
You're already dead.
So, end it now,
and I'll let her live.
Her life.
Or yours.
I'm sorry.
Do it, or else.
Of course,
where I'm going to send her,
she will be begging for death.
She will wish...
Mister.
Stay with me. Stay with me!
Breathe!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Come on, breathe!