(KNOCK AT DOOR)
NICK: Justin, let's go!
Justin. Hello, Justin.
Set an alarm for 11:00 p.m.
and set another alarm for 11:50 p.m.
Rhi, 6:30, hon.
- Rhi!
- I'm up!
Oh, my God.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Thanks, babe.
Hey, I need you to run
those errands today for me, please.
I don't really know about today.
Just try. Okay, Nick?
See you later.
Bye.
Jolene, breakfast. Come on.
- No.
- We're gonna be late.
God.
Um, I could also drive, if you want.
I mean, I could actually
use the practice.
Does that have spinach in it?
Yeah, Dad says spinach has antioxidants.
You know what else has antioxidants?
- Your balls. Yeah.
- My balls.
Well, Dad says it's important, so...
Hey!
What's going on up here, huh?
Dumbass.
Justin, my goon.
Yo, don't ignore me, bro.
Right, sorry. Hey, goon.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm good. All good.
(BELL RINGS)
I'm so tired.
I wanna drop Model UN,
but if I don't get into Stanford,
I will literally cry to death.
That campus is so beautiful.
And their mascot is,
not even joking, a tree.
- You're gonna apply with me, right?
- Yeah. For sure.
Where even is Justin?
I mean, what's up with him?
- He takes you totally for granted.
- I'll be right back.
Hey.
Look, I'm sorry for texting you so much.
I was gonna text you "Sorry"
again this morning
but I'd already texted you so much
and also, I know you don't like it
when I apologize
so I guess I'm sorry
for saying "I'm sorry."
Rhiannon.
- Yeah?
- Don't be sorry.
That was on me.
I should've written you back.
No, no, you don't have to text me
every time I text you.
I think I do.
Well, I can come watch your practice
if you want.
That doesn't sound that much fun
for you.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Like what?
What else do you have today?
Other than practice?
Nothing. No tests or anything.
Maybe it would be fun
if we just went somewhere?
Like, after school?
Or even now?
Is that something we do?
Well, couldn't it be?
MAN 1 ON RADIO:
He's an outstanding player.
He's young, he has an ERA of 1. 68.
MAN 2 ON RADIO:
He's not that young, 23. He's...
Twenty-three years old.
- This what you wanna listen to?
- Yeah.
MAN 2 ON RADIO: I mean, look at
his record. He got 18 wins...
How about you throw on some music?
MAN 1 ON RADIO: What are you talking
about? They're gonna dump him?
MAN 2 ON RADIO: Eighteen wins
against substandard teams...
("THIS IS THE DAY" BY THE THE PLAYING
ON RADIO)
(SINGING)
Couldn't buy back those days
You pull back
(SINGING)
And the sun burns into your eyes
You know this song?
How did I not know that?
You watch a plane flying
Across the clear blue sky
This is the day
Your life will surely change
When things fall into place
(BOTH VOCALIZING)
Saved your life. Saved your life.
All right, come on.
Hi.
"You have a nice smile."
Story checks out. Good job, cookie.
Bad job, cookie. It's not a fortune.
It's not?
No. A fortune would be,
"You will have a nice smile."
Because a fortune
is supposed to tell you the future.
Or something you don't already know.
Like that you have a nice smile.
Um, it's just Dad.
You don't talk about him.
Like, ever.
Um...
He had a manic episode a few years ago.
It's no big deal.
I had no idea.
Uh, yeah, I haven't really told anyone
about it.
Not even Rebecca.
You don't have to, obviously.
Sometimes I want to. It's just...
I don't know.
Well, what happened, exactly?
He came home one day
and told us he got a big promotion.
He took us out to some French restaurant
to celebrate.
And then we went to a movie.
And he paid the guy some crazy amount
so we could have
the whole theater to ourselves.
I'm guessing no promotion?
No. He had actually
just gotten laid off...
And snapped.
So, no new rich life.
And my mom had to take a second job
and we almost lost our house.
And now even if he could work,
I don't know who would hire him.
He just sits around
and makes paintings of faces.
Sometimes people need a break.
Life gets too much.
It sounds like you resent him
for checking out, though.
I want to talk to him
about that day and why...
But I can never seem to figure out
what to say.
I don't know why
I'm telling you all this.
I'm glad you did.
It feels good.
It's your turn. Go.
Uh...
Yeah, I mean, I hate French food, too.
Snails and croissants.
Snail-croissants.
I mean, what's that about?
- I meant, open your cookie.
- Oh...
See you tomorrow.
What's wrong?
You know every day
won't be like this, right?
I know.
But, maybe, it helps you remember
you like spending time with me?
Look, I just mean, today...
Today was the happiest day
I've had in a long time.
Tomorrow is tomorrow.
Let's end today on a nice note.
Okay.
That's the nice note.
Also, your mouth tastes so much better
when you don't smoke.
I'll try to remember that.
Set an alarm for 11:00 p.m.
and set another alarm for 11:50 p.m.
Hello, Amy.
Hey, what's going on?
Excuse me.
My family just moved here from D.C.
My mom told me to shadow someone
at the school today
but she didn't set anything up.
So embarrassing. Could I shadow you?
Um...
I don't know what that is, no.
What is that?
Yeah. Yeah. sure.
Rebecca, Alexander, this is Amy,
who might be coming here.
Hey, Amy. You've got a great person
to show you around.
Yeah, Alexander's a huge fan.
Okay, all I meant was Rhiannon
is super generous with her time.
Yeah, you wish.
Don't worry, we're friends.
He likes when I tease him.
How about we get back to the lab now?
Hey, Justin.
Justin.
Coach is pissed off at me
for blowing off practice.
- Amy, this is my boyfriend, Justin.
- Did we drink yesterday?
No, why?
We just left school
and went to Baltimore yesterday.
Like, just out of the blue.
It was amazing.
Yeah, I'll take your word for it
'cause I can't remember
a thing about it.
What part?
Pretty much the whole day.
It's, like, super foggy,
like I'm hungover or something.
Now I have to make up work
in three stupid classes by tomorrow
but I have a shift till 10:00 tonight.
So my life basically sucks right now.
Okay, so you had an amazing day
with your gorgeous,
incredible girlfriend.
And to you that sucks?
I'm sorry.
Who is this and what is her deal?
Who are you?
Why are you bitching and moaning
about the only good thing in your life?
Amy.
Chill, it's fine.
Okay, great talk. Gotta go.
Rhi, don't forget about
Steve's party on Saturday.
I'm sorry.
I'm just allergic to
unappreciative dicks.
That's not who he is.
You deserve better.
I'm sorry. It was in your face.
It's okay. I'm okay. You're very sweet.
Um...
But actually, I'm not feeling great.
Alexander, would you mind taking Amy
for the rest of the day?
Sure.
Thank you.
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- (POP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
I'm gonna need you
to ghostwrite some texts for me.
First, text Abby.
Just a bunch of tree emojis.
And then, second,
text Will something cute but mean.
Like, over-the-top mean,
but, like, still cute.
Can't it just wait until we get home?
No, why?
It's just stuff with Justin.
Is the stuff that he's a douchebag?
All right, look.
You have two options.
One, break up with him.
And, two, cheat, like, a lot.
Crazy amounts.
With crazy amounts of dudes.
You know, like how Lindsey does?
Mom doesn't cheat.
- I don't wanna talk about it anymore.
- All right. Great.
Set an alarm for 11:00 p.m.
and another alarm for 11:50 p.m.
Okay.
- You sure you don't mind?
- No, of course not.
Thanks, babe. I just need to get
super wasted tonight.
- Yup.
- Steve, my goon.
- My goon.
- What's up, man?
Hey, Stephanie.
Rhiannon.
Hey, guys. What's going on?
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
- Hey!
- Hi!
- Justin's over there.
- Thank you.
Bro...
That's so weak.
Shoot it.
BOY: Hey.
(MUSIC STOPS)
("THIS IS THE DAY" BY THE THE PLAYING)
Oh! Ooh...
Hey.
(SINGING) Well, you didn't wake up
this morning
'Cause you didn't go to bed
You were watching
the whites of your eyes turn red
The calendar on your wall
was ticking the days off
You've been reading some old letters
You smile and think
how much you've changed
All the money in the world
Couldn't buy back those days
You pull back the curtains
And the sun burns into your eyes
You watch a plane flying
across a clear blue sky
This is the day
Your life...
- When things fall...
- ...into place
I don't think I know you.
Do you go to Octavian?
No, I'm Nathan. Steve's cousin.
I'm Rhiannon.
That's a lovely name.
Oh, thank you.
I don't like it.
Why?
Well, everyone thinks it's Rihanna,
as in, Bitch Better Have My Money.
Also, no one can spell it.
That's their problem.
It's a beautiful name.
Thank you.
Yo. Hey. Who's this?
This is Nathan, Steve's cousin.
Hey.
Steve's gay cousin.
All right. Hey.
You got nothing to worry about, Galahad.
But, um, your girlfriend might.
JUSTIN: Er...
Thanks, I guess.
I'm gonna be upstairs.
Yo.
You wanna go someplace not upstairs?
Your boyfriend...
Not a dancer?
Um, not today, apparently.
So...
Why are you with him?
Um...
Uh, because we love each other.
Sometimes, it's really good with him.
I mean, he's my type.
Oh, okay.
And, um...
What's your type?
Um...
Tall, slim, nice shoulders.
(BOTH LAUGH)
What?
- What's wrong with nice shoulders?
- No, nothing.
I don't know, I guess I'm just more
of a butt guy myself.
But, you know, I get it.
- I guess when you've seen as many...
- Seen as many butts?
No, no.
STEVE: Real talk?
Not a fan of some dude
mackin' on my girlfriend.
Don't care if he's gay.
Real talk.
You gotta get
your cousin Nathan in line.
- He is gay, right?
- Bro, what cousin?
I just know that you can be attracted
to way more people than you think.
Me?
Anyone.
How do you know?
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
I'm sorry, I have to go.
We're not done here.
I'll call myself
so that I have your number.
You don't want this number.
I'm gonna get a new number tomorrow.
- You're getting a new number?
- JUSTIN: There he is.
Rhi. That's not Steve's cousin.
I don't even think he's gay.
- What?
- I'm sorry, I have to go.
- I'll explain later. Promise.
- What?
Where are you going?
Go, go, go.
Hell, no.
- Wait, you guys.
- JUSTIN: Come on, come on.
RHIANNON: Leave him alone.
STEVE: Don't creep on our women,
little dude.
Rhi, give me my keys.
- RHIANNON: No, Justin, you can't.
- (CAR STARTING)
- Justin.
- JUSTIN: My keys.
RHIANNON: No, you cannot
drive right now.
Who even was that?
Siri. Hey, Siri.
Do I have a phone?
FEMALE COMPUTERIZED VOICE:
It is 6:29 a.m.
FEMALE NEWS REPORTER: This teenager
missed curfew,
then said the Devil made him do it.
Monroeville's Nathan Daldry
was found asleep
around 1:00, Saturday morning
by the side of a highway
with a broken back windshield.
His explanation?
He had been possessed by Satan...
Your boy took down his social media.
- So, tell us what happened.
- Guess I gotta talk to him in person.
Justin, what are you thinking?
Leave him alone. He's disturbed.
Then why were you even
hanging out with him?
I don't know.
(BELL RINGS)
So, Friday night he was super weird.
And then, this morning,
I get a text from a random number.
(READING) "If you meet me in person,
somewhere public, I can explain.
"Please come alone."
Oh, my God. Are you going to?
I don't know, should I?
I think you have to.
This is the coolest, creepiest thing
that has ever happened.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Tell me you're alone.
You're alone, right?
I'm sorry, do I know you?
Nathan sent me.
Oh, um... Where is Nathan?
He's here.
In a way.
I mean, he's not, like, here, here,
but he also wasn't there on Friday
when you met him.
Or you thought that you met him.
You know, you actually didn't.
What?
Today, I'm Megan.
The day that you met Nathan,
I was Nathan. All right?
And the day that Amy shadowed you
at school, I was Amy.
And the day that
you went to the beach with Justin...
I was Justin.
Because I am someone who wakes up
in a different body every day.
Always someone my age.
Never too far from the last,
never the same person twice...
I have absolutely no control
over any of it.
Okay, did Rebecca tell you I'd be here?
She wasn't supposed to tell anyone.
I don't know why it happens,
I don't know how.
I mean, this is...
No one's ever tried to explain it to me.
And this is the first time
I've ever actually told anyone about it.
And I know I'm not doing a good job.
Okay. Well...
Thank you. This is all very good.
But I think I should go.
"You have a nice smile."
That was the fortune that you got.
The fortune that we both got.
You told me about the day
that your dad got laid off.
You told me about the French restaurant.
Okay, just stop.
I told Justin those things, not you.
He has nothing to do with this.
He's the only one who does.
I spent the day with him.
And now he and you and Nathan,
and God knows who else
are playing some stupid joke.
And, honestly,
I don't even want to know why.
- So just, please, stop.
- He doesn't talk to you like this.
He doesn't spend days with you
like the one that we had together, okay?
He doesn't see you.
You have to know that that wasn't him.
It's...
It's not possible.
It is.
Hey.
Hey. I'm all right.
I seem not all right to you? I'm fine.
Great.
Do you wanna study at my place
after school?
- "Study."
- Who's Megan?
I don't know any Megan.
Did you tell anyone about
what I told you
about what happened with my dad?
Um...
Honestly, I don't even remember
what you told me about your dad.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
What's wrong with you?
Are we hanging out or what?
JUSTIN: Whatever.
Hey. It's me, A.
Oh. Hi, um...
Wait, "A"?
He's James, but I'm A.
Like, just A, like the letter.
I'm still not convinced
that this is real.
Who named you A?
I did. I wanted a name that no one else
was likely to have, so...
Okay, the day you were Justin,
what was I wearing?
Peasant blouse, jean shorts.
What?
You know what a peasant blouse is?
Well, half the time I wake up as a girl.
Although, I will say, I think that James
could totally pull it off. I think...
Got the physique for it,
all that good stuff.
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
What was the last thing
I said to you that day?
"Your mouth tastes so much better
when you don't smoke."
And the name you called
Justin to his face
when you were Nathan?
What? Oh, uh, Galahad.
And when you were Amy,
who showed you around after I did?
Alexander.
You still could be a liar.
Just a ridiculously well-prepared liar.
Or I could be telling you the truth.
Or I could be going insane.
I mean, who are you?
Who are your parents?
Do they switch bodies every day?
Hey, do you mind if we go somewhere
a little more private?
Okay, maybe if you were
a petite cheerleader again.
But I'm not sure you fully realize this.
You're a big, threatening dude today,
so, absolutely not.
Right. (CLEARS THROAT) I get it.
I don't know if I have parents.
Um, I assume so,
but I have no one to ask.
So, every day of your life,
you've just woken up, and...
Just tried to live that day
for that person.
Not mess anything up for them,
make no mark, leave no trace.
And you're never that person again?
No. I might see them at school
a week or a month later.
If I'm in the same area.
So, like, when you're somebody,
are you them or still you?
I'm me.
You know, my consciousness, my memories.
But then I can also access
their history and their memories.
But not all at once.
The longer I'm in someone that day,
the more I know about them.
Who else have you told this?
I told you, no one else.
That sounds really lonely.
Can be.
And sad.
But it isn't.
Because I've seen so much.
I know what makes each person different.
And what makes everyone the same,
you know?
I've seen the same color blue
look 50 different ways
with 50 different pairs of eyes.
But you never get to stay with anything
long enough to watch it grow.
It's true.
But I'd like to, though.
If I show you something,
will you promise to show no one else?
Check out my Instagram.
I've posted pictures
any days that I could.
Of people I've been,
and the things that I've seen.
Of course, it's a risk.
I have to scrub the login information
every night before I go to bed
but it's good to have a record.
This still doesn't prove anything.
I mean, you could just be getting these
from other people or the Internet.
I could, but I'm not. Wait, wait, wait.
Can we please meet again?
I don't know. Yes, maybe.
Just let me process this
for a little while, okay?
Okay.
Bye, A.
Bye.
NICK: Did you need me?
No.
I'm good.
Hey.
It's me.
Remember?
Yet another person
has the unique idea to prank me
by pretending to be the Devil.
What?
No, no. I, um...
I'm hoping to write something
for my school newspaper.
Actually, I do recognize you.
You do?
I'll meet with anyone
interested in the truth.
Okay.
See, he did something to my memory
so the whole night's kind of hazy.
But...
I remember dancing.
Then...
I was in this unnaturally tiny house.
Then running for my life.
Apparently, that evening, I told my mom
that he needed to borrow a car
so I could go help some friends
write a musical about Jesus.
And this should go in your story.
When he was within me,
he used my phone
to access his Instagram account.
I was on Satan's social media.
It was intense.
It was a record of all the other
teenagers that he's taken over.
Can I see?
He kicked me off and
changed the password
before I could save any of the photos
but I recognize you.
- What do you mean?
- From one of the photos.
In the aquarium. That was you.
He possessed you, too, didn't he?
No.
No, I wasn't possessed.
When he was within you,
did he talk to you?
REVEREND POOLE:
I think that's enough for today.
Did you get a sense of what he was like?
Like, his personality?
I know his personality.
It's pure evil. He's Satan.
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
- Justin, you cannot threaten him.
- It's not a threat. It's not a threat.
I'm just gonna tell him, "Little dude,
next time you talk to my girlfriend
"I'mma help you out
by beating the Devil out of you."
How is that a threat?
Justin, that's the literal definition
of a threat. Rhiannon, tell him.
Rhiannon, tell her.
No. Are you a dictionary?
REBECCA: Are you a child?
I'm not a child.
RHIANNON: Hey.
How did you know it was me?
Just the way you looked at me.
Also, she doesn't go here.
He doesn't go here.
You're not very good
for his attendance record.
I'm not good for anyone's
attendance record.
(BELL RINGS)
Come on.
Look, I thought you said
you didn't wanna mess anyone's life up.
Speaking of which,
what happened to Nathan?
I had to see you.
I tried to get him home, put him to bed,
but at 11:59, I pulled over
and passed out,
except I screwed up
and forgot to erase my Instagram info.
He thinks you're the Devil.
If I'm the Devil,
humanity has nothing to worry about.
That's exactly what the Devil
would want humanity to think.
I can't win with you suspicious mortals,
can I?
Seriously, why are you doing this?
The day we met, I felt something
I've never felt before.
And I don't wanna let that go.
About that day,
how is it okay, what you did?
I let you kiss me
because I thought you were Justin.
I told you something incredibly personal
He never would've understood.
I was in his mind, Rhiannon. I know him.
Are you serious?
I know him better than you do.
He is my boyfriend.
You know you shouldn't be with him.
Oh, who should I be with, then? You?
I mean, off the top of my head,
that's an option.
This isn't funny, A.
This is so weird.
I mean, today, you're...
Not everyone's body
aligns with their mind.
But I'm not asking you
to give Vic a chance, Rhiannon,
I'm asking you to give me a chance.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
What do you remember
from that day at the beach?
Um, that it was super good?
I also remember this.
Can I ask you something else?
Yeah.
What do you like about us?
Us?
Yeah, like, our connection.
Uh...
Um...
We're so connected. Because we're...
We make a really great team.
Like, we've always
got each other's backs,
like, when you wouldn't let me
drive drunk the other night at Steve's.
That was super clutch.
And, I mean, that night
with that weird dude,
it reminded me that I would
fight like crazy not to lose you.
You know?
'Cause our connection
is really powerful.
JUSTIN: Steve was so wasted at the
party.
He's flirting with this girl from Monroe
and turns out that's
Stephanie's best friend.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Jolene, can I have the car
when we get home?
That's the shit I don't like.
I have to hit the library.
Nerd.
Hey. I hope we still have
some time to do stuff.
I basically had to steal
my sister's car.
You were easy to find, at least.
You're like the only person here my age.
Do I know you?
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
I mistook you for someone else.
I don't know what he looks like.
It's not a Tinder thing.
I'm kidding. It's me, A.
- Oh, my God. That was not funny.
- It was a joke.
- I can't believe you just did that.
- I never get to do this.
That was not funny.
(WOMAN SHUSHES)
- Maybe it was a little funny.
- No.
Nice shirt, by the way.
His mom buys his clothes.
- Actually, I kinda like it.
- Well, he hates it.
I've been in
homeschool situations before,
and some were great.
But this one's prison.
And the warden is a mom
who speaks really slowly.
But you got her to
take you to a library?
Yeah, well, for an hour.
And I have to have
50 new facts memorized
by the time she picks me up.
Okay, so let's get you some facts.
It can wait.
Tell me about your day.
It was just a day.
I was thinking about you.
- You were?
- (MAN SHUSHES)
Jeez.
You were?
Yeah, well, I mean, like, you know,
what was it like when you were younger
being you?
Um...
Best I could tell, I was born
somewhere in Phoenix, maybe.
But the family I was with, this one day,
they flew to Detroit for a wedding.
And I bounced around Michigan
for a while.
You couldn't get back to Arizona?
No. Like I told you,
I can't choose who I wake up in.
Right.
But I meant...
You know, what was it like for you?
Well...
I didn't figure out I was different
from other people until I was six or so.
What tipped me off was the way
people would talk about tomorrow.
You know, the things we'd do,
the places we'd go.
Tomorrow.
As though we'd all be together.
Which I knew we wouldn't.
But anytime I tried to say that,
the people, they wouldn't understand.
They'd think it was a joke or a game.
Or else they'd get worried.
After a while,
I just realized my tomorrows
are very different from everyone else's.
And you never found
anyone else like you?
No.
I mean, I search online,
message boards,
people talking about being taken over.
There's a subreddit that's interesting.
(MAN SHUSHES)
Should we get you some facts?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay.
RHIANNON: Forty-seven, chicken.
A: Chicken gestates for 22 days.
Forty-eight, goat.
Goat gestates for 136 to 160 days.
Forty-nine, groundhog.
Groundhog gestates for 31 to 32 days.
Fifty, kangaroo.
Kangaroo gestates for 32 to 39 days.
Wow. These are great.
They're really gonna unsettle his mom.
So, how'd I do?
- I don't know, I didn't check.
- You didn't check?
- I think I did all right.
- I think so, too.
Where's my reward?
GEORGE'S MOM: George.
What kind of a whore...
- She really does talk slow.
- Yeah.
- Seduces my son?
- Hey, just run.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, run.
- (KNOCK AT DOOR)
- Rhi, 6:30.
Holy shit.
What is it?
Nothing.
I will be cool about this.
I promise.
Nick, it's Walmart, not the Yukon.
I can't. Please?
Hey. Everything okay?
Yeah. Just, have a good day at work.
Hey, wait.
Come here.
I need to go to D.C. on Sunday
with my team for a pitch.
We could squeeze in
a little sightseeing,
little shopping, if you wanna come?
I wanna come.
Good.
Okay, have a good day. I love you.
Be cool, be cool, be cool.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to look.
Dude, were you gonna wake me up?
We're gonna be late.
Sorry.
What the shit are you doing?
Siri, set an alarm for 11:00 p.m.
Your makeup looks different.
It's good.
Breakfast?
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, I completely forgot.
It's okay, I hate that shit.
Everything okay with you?
You just look really pretty today.
So do your balls.
All right, keep your panties on.
Hey.
You're lookin' sexy today.
Oh.
I mean, you know, more than usual.
Well, thanks.
Thank you for lookin' so sexy.
So, do you wanna get out of here,
and go back to my place?
Maybe not today.
I thought you like when we do that.
You have no idea what I like, do you?
Excuse me?
I like leaving with you if you're
going to give me a special day.
If you're going to give me a day
of fooling around in your gross room
watching you play video games,
and maybe getting McDonald's for lunch,
that does not qualify as special.
Qualifies as awesome, though.
No, it doesn't.
We've had one awesome day
in, like, months.
I'm sick of hearing about this day.
Is that because you don't remember it,
because you weren't really there?
Do me a favor
and don't talk to me again today.
Are you on your period already?
It's been, like, a week and a half.
Well, then, congratulations,
you're not a father.
I'm sorry.
I lost control.
Please, please don't be mad
at me tomorrow.
NICK: Everything okay?
Mmm-hmm.
Thanks.
Dad, why do you paint?
You never ask about my work.
Uh...
I think when I started doing insurance
and gave up on painting
that maybe I bottled up things
that I shouldn't have.
All those years, doing something
that wasn't me.
Took its toll?
Yeah.
So, why faces?
Well...
I suppose it's like,
"Write what you know."
Paint what you see.
In my mind's eye...
This is what I see.
Some face of someone I don't know.
They're just there.
I wanna give 'em
the space to exist, live...
Be.
I could use a fresh face.
Wanna sit for me?
Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay.
A: So, I was you yesterday.
And I tried to leave you every memory.
I tried to change things for you
as little as possible.
Although, I did do
a week of your homework.
And I'm amazing at homework.
No need to thank me.
Okay, fine, you're welcome.
I need you to know
that I didn't choose to be you.
I wouldn't choose that, even if I could.
And in all of my years,
I've never woken up in the body
of someone I care so much about.
It was the best and most terrifying day
of my life so far.
You are the only reason why.
Yours, A.
- Hey.
- Hey, babe, what are you doing here?
I think we need to take a break.
But this stuff between us is great,
our connection.
It's really not.
You don't see me.
- MAN: I can see you.
- You have no idea who I am.
Have a nice life.
Hey.
Are you kidding?
I woke up feeling clearer
than I ever have in my entire life.
Where are you today?
I wanna see you.
- A: What?
- Nothing.
What?
Your hand feels different.
Yours feels the same.
Thanks for not breaking up with Justin.
- Honestly, it was not easy.
- (RHIANNON LAUGHS)
RHIANNON: My uncle's
in California right now.
He barely uses this place, anyway.
But I have to be home by
Sunday afternoon to hang with my mom.
A: Oh, yeah. Right.
So, this is our weekend?
This is our weekend.
Was that just because I look like this?
It's because you're you.
And 10% because you look like that.
So, you actually remember everything?
Well, it was like I went to bed Thursday
and woke up today,
wearing a really strange bra,
thank you very much.
But with all these memories, somehow,
with you in them.
A: That must be really weird.
No, it's amazing.
A, I think you should let people
remember you.
I think you should leave more memories
behind for more people
and make more of a mark.
You're such a bright,
beautiful, kind, funny...
- Thing.
- Person.
You're not freaked out anymore
that the first time that we met
I let you kiss me, and
tell me all this personal stuff,
without knowing that I was there?
Well, you must kiss a lot of people.
And hear a lot of personal stuff.
Yeah, I...
I've been a lot of boyfriends
and a lot of girlfriends.
How does that not sound terrible to you?
A, it sounds incredible.
RHIANNON: So why midnight?
A: As far as I can tell,
I get 24 hours in each house.
After that, I get pushed out.
RHIANNON: "Pushed out"?
A: By the person whose place I'm taking.
When they return, I don't know,
it's just what it feels like.
What happens when you push back?
I don't. When it's time to go,
it's not my body.
Look, we just haven't gotten that far
in AP paranormal biology, yet.
But I think it's being covered
in the spring.
RHIANNON: Come on.
So, do you consider yourself
a boy or a girl?
A: Yes.
RHIANNON: See you tomorrow.
A: I promise.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
LINDSEY: You wanna
up and disappear, fine.
You do it on a day when we're supposed
to go to D.C. together? Rude.
I didn't forget. I just...
You can't expect me to drop everything
that I'm doing for this family
to drive for three hours
to pick you up from a vacation you just
up and decided to give yourself.
Apparently this family's not
the only thing
keeping you busy after work.
Excuse me?
Rhiannon, what the hell
is going on with you?
I just...
You just what?
I...
Nothing. Nothing's wrong.
Michael. I thought you were already up
and showered.
Oh, my goodness.
We are gonna miss our flight.
Hustle your ass, Michael.
Hey. Can you pick me up today?
Mikey. God damn it, Michael.
My family's supposed to
fly to Honolulu today.
If I go, tomorrow, I wake up as a kid
who's not flying back here.
Silver Springs.
There's a Target down the highway.
Meet me in the parking lot.
Oh, my God. This kid does not exercise.
- MICHAEL'S MOM: Michael.
- Shit.
- Hey. Over here.
- Michael. Michael, get...
Get back here.
Okay. Slow down but don't stop.
I can't hear you.
- Shit. Do stop.
- What?
- Stop. Stop.
- Shit. Shit.
Michael!
- MICHAEL: Got it.
- Oh, God. Jolene's gonna kill me.
MICHAEL'S MOM: Michael!
- Get back here.
- Go. Go. Go.
Okay, okay, okay.
What are you doing with my son?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
I'm sorry.
Well, had to be done.
Couldn't lose you to Hawaii.
- But where were you?
- I couldn't come.
Well, I was alone, and cold,
and freaked out.
And if my mom hadn't come,
I don't know what would've happened.
Not to mention that she's pissed at me,
and I can't even begin to explain why.
- I'm sorry.
- Where were you, A?
- Getting a lung transplant.
- Shut up.
I woke up in the evening.
I had no way to call you.
I couldn't contact you.
They wouldn't even give me a phone.
You're serious?
Yes.
RHIANNON: Well, was it successful?
A: I think so.
RHIANNON: Oh, God.
A: I feel awful about abandoning you.
No. No, it was my fault.
The weekend was my terrible idea.
You think it was a terrible idea?
What? No.
I mean, it was amazing, too.
I just...
I think we need to be more careful.
Yeah.
RHIANNON: You know,
I thought you'd "left" left.
A: I'd never leave.
RHIANNON: Other than every day.
A: Do you think we can keep doing this?
I mean, not knowing who I'm gonna be
or where I'm gonna show up next?
A: I guess I should probably go clean up
whatever chaos we caused for this kid.
RHIANNON: We'll figure this out.
I promise.
Weird hands?
Less than you'd think.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
Jo, I'm really sorry about the car.
I feel horrible.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Can I tell you what's happening?
I'm in love with someone who wakes up
in a different body every day.
Always the same age,
never the same person twice.
Yesterday it was a kid
I needed to save from his family.
Saturday, it was the guy in the pickup.
And Sunday, it was someone
who couldn't make it to the cabin.
So, that's what this is.
Look, whatever weird,
fake, role-playing,
polyamorous-type shit you're into
nowadays, just don't involve me.
- Jolene, it's real.
- And don't involve my goddamn car.
TEACHER: Because I'm stupidly nice,
I'll excuse yesterday's absence.
(BELL RINGING)
- Can't happen again, Rhiannon.
- It won't.
Hey, where'd you go yesterday?
I just didn't feel like being at school.
Rhiannon, why are you not telling me
anything anymore?
And who is that rando you hooked up with
over the weekend?
What rando? What are you talking about?
Jolene told her friends
that some guy abandoned you
in the middle of the woods with no car.
That's, like, the ultimate rando move.
Why is this everyone's business?
It's not. But I figured it's mine
because I'm your friend.
At least I used to be.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
- A: Hello?
- Is it you?
Yeah.
I got your message.
Wow.
Yeah. I knew she had some dark thoughts.
Maybe an hour ago I decided to draw
something cheerful
in one of her notebooks.
Make her feel better.
That's where she had it written down.
A: She's got it all planned out.
If her dad finds her pills, she's gonna
drive into the side of an overpass.
RHIANNON: When does her dad come home?
He doesn't leave the hospital
until 5:00 a.m.
He's in surgery until then.
You've got to stop her.
There's nothing I can do.
You don't believe that.
Call her father. Call a counselor.
It's Kelsea's life, not mine.
So, if she were gonna kill someone,
what would you do then?
- I'd turn her in.
- Right.
So how is this different?
It's not fair of me to do something
that makes up her mind for her.
So you never, ever get involved
in the lives of the people
you're inhabiting?
I can't.
What about Justin?
What made that so different?
You.
If you leave her at midnight,
she's going to go through with it.
So, you're just gonna have to
try and stay.
I believe you can do it.
And I need you to believe it, too.
How?
Push back.
Stay with me?
Honey?
You need to get me help, Dad.
I've been thinking about it
for a long time.
(DOOR OPENS)
- (KNOCK AT DOOR)
- I'm up, Mom. Jeez.
Sweetie?
You feeling okay?
Jo said you told her something
kinda strange.
About meeting someone
who's in a different body every day?
It was a joke.
All right.
Hey.
I love you, Rhi.
If you ever need to talk,
I'm always here.
Dad?
Do you still love Mom?
Of course, I do, sweetheart.
I don't think we can know what it's like
when you're in love with someone...
And they change.
Hey, what's up, slut?
Hey, don't shame the slut.
Rhi, I'm proud of you.
Stay slutty.
Shut up, dumbass.
- Hi.
I really missed you yesterday.
I'm sorry about those guys.
It's my fault.
It's nothing. So tell me everything.
She's got more appointments tomorrow.
Doctors, maybe an overnight stay.
Probably she goes on medication.
I hope it turns out okay.
I mean, I think it could...
But it's her life, so...
It is. And you saved it.
You stayed.
I stayed.
So that means you can
stay in someone else, maybe?
Maybe I could.
What are you doing tonight?
Date.
Not with you.
With her boyfriend.
It's their anniversary.
I probably shouldn't miss it.
Well, maybe tomorrow then.
Can I kiss you?
Yeah.
Hi.
What are you doing up so late?
I thought you had a test tomorrow.
Mom, I know you and Dad
are trying to make it work.
But every day you can grow
a little bit closer to each other
or you can grow
a little bit farther apart.
Okay.
Um...
Look, I know Dad is not who he was.
But you're not who you were, either.
Because we all change.
And you've changed, too.
So...
Please, just grow closer.
He's amazing, Rhiannon.
He's curious and kind, and handsome.
It's funny, I've known him for so long,
but I don't know much about him.
He's so shy at school.
Yeah, he's not the kinda kid
that's built for high school.
He's built for what comes next.
He remembers
beautiful things beautifully.
He reads and he sees.
And he listens
with every part of himself.
He sees what's funny in people
without ever being cruel.
Excuse me, I'll take this guy
if you don't want him. Who is he?
Oh, he's talking about himself.
Oh.
Hi.
(BELL RINGS)
So, do you have plans after school?
Um, it is after school.
RHIANNON: What is happening?
Where are we going?
Do you think you could stay in Alexander
for one more day?
I'm not sure.
You did it with Kelsea.
With Kelsea it was easier,
I think, 'cause...
I guess she didn't wanna
be here anymore.
It's fine.
I get it. It's all good.
Would make things easier, though,
wouldn't it?
- (KNOCK AT DOOR)
- Rhi?
Hey.
(BELL RINGS)
Oh, my God. You stayed.
That's so exciting.
I knew exactly what it was.
Date night again tonight?
Tomorrow? I have to study for a test.
Tomorrow.
Okay.
Hi. Someone's excited for learning.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I better get home,
or my mom will kill me.
Should we call it a night, then?
Actually, I guess I could come in
for, like, a minute.
- I think I should go now.
- Yeah.
Who forgets their own birthday?
Is that the new girl's fault?
Mom, I said I was sorry.
Past few days,
I don't even recognize you.
I don't know if this is some
teenage angst bullshit,
but I won't have it.
- Mom, please don't be mad.
- I'm not mad.
Your aunts and I cooked literally
all day preparing that dinner,
which was at your request.
All of your favorites.
I'm just disappointed.
That was a shitty, selfish thing
you did.
I'll make it up to them somehow.
You have a family that loves you.
Don't take that for granted.
- Hey.
Where have you been?
You weren't in class.
- Rhiannon...
- Did you get in trouble?
Not as much as you might think.
- Rhiannon.
- Hey, are we still on for tonight?
His parents went out of town.
So, my place at 8:00?
Yeah, great. I'll see you then.
Hey, Rebecca.
REBECCA: TGI Friday.
I've been a bad friend.
I'm sorry. I'll tell you everything.
I don't need an explanation.
Well, good, because I'm not really sure
I would give you one
that would make any sense.
Are you and Alexander a thing now?
Uh, yeah.
I always thought you should be together.
You did?
Yeah.
I'm glad you're happy, Rhi.
I got practice, so, gotta go.
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
Wow.
What is this, the Last Supper?
More like a first date.
Turns out, he's a really great cook.
He's a really great guy.
Okay. I know.
So are you.
I mean, really great. I've never had
your cooking, so I can't speak to that.
Rhiannon, he's got a family
that loves him, and that he loves.
It's everything I've ever wanted.
Yeah. It's been nice.
But it's not mine.
I'm forcing Alexander
out of his own life, and it's wrong.
And the longer I stay,
the more I'm damaging him.
We'll go back to how it was.
Do you know Flynn in my algebra class?
You cannot, under any circumstance,
be him.
If that's who you wake up in,
then don't even call me.
I mean, it can be Flynn.
It's not a deal-breaker.
I can't do it to anybody.
Not to Alexander, not to Flynn.
- Not to you.
- What are you saying?
I've been thinking about this over
and over and over.
I'm always going to be blocking you
from being with someone
who's perfect for you.
How could you say that?
Because Alexander's perfect for you.
- He's your type.
- You're my type.
Do you think I wanna live without you?
Do you think I'll ever be happy
in a place you're not?
Go back to a life that you're not in,
back to seeing only faces
that aren't yours?
Hearing only voices that aren't yours?
You should be with him.
He's tall, slim, nice shoulders.
He's really smart.
He's incredibly kind, he's interesting,
and thoughtful on so many levels.
No. We can make it work, A.
I wanna believe that.
You know I wanna believe that.
Think about what happens
if you and I stay together.
I mean, really, truly, imagine it.
What does that look like in a year?
In 10 years?
What will happen to your life
if I'm the person in the world
that you're closest to?
How alone will it make you...
If the one that you love is me?
And the one that you're with is me.
And you can't tell anyone about me.
How much is that gonna cut you off
from your family?
from everyone you know?
And what happens when I start waking up
as someone in a marriage?
Someone with kids?
What if we want a kid?
How will it feel for you to raise
that kid almost entirely alone
and not be able to explain to anyone
why that's what you chose?
Whose kid is that gonna be?
Is that gonna be my kid?
Or will she be the kid of some guy
that you'll never see again
while my kid leaves you
the day after she's born?
Will my kid ever know her parents?
Or is she gonna have a life like mine
and always wonder...
Stop.
Most people know that their first love
won't be their only love.
But for me, you're both.
Say something.
We have three hours until midnight.
Let's not waste it.
RHIANNON: What else?
A: In some minds, everything feels muted
and dim.
And in others, it's like everything
is supercharged and unfocused.
Like a radio flipping
from station to station.
Hard to get control of.
What else?
Um...
I'm thinking.
Am I going to see you again?
I have to believe that we will.
But you have to believe that we won't.
RHIANNON: Where are you going to go?
A: Far away.
New York.
Chicago, if I can get there.
Just some big, dense city
where there's lots of people to be.
There's still some things
I need to figure out about myself.
Make marks, okay? Leave traces.
Yeah.
It's time.
Will you remember this tomorrow?
I'll remember everything.
So will I.
This is the nice note.
Good night.
(ALARM BEEPING)
KATIE'S MOM: Katie.
Katie, you up?
Katie.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
Hi.
Has anyone ever told you,
you have a nice smile?
Just being honest.