(RUSTLING)
- GIRL: Don't touch my shit!
- (R&B MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
I said, don't touch my shit!
- Get your trash out of my house!
- GIRL: Yo.
Anything break, I'm gonna
Ronda Rousey your fat ass!
(SIREN WAILING)
- Nobody scared of you, Mo.
- Shut the fuck up.
All the shit I do for your ass.
Miss Jones, mind your business.
Thank you, Miss Jones.
WOMAN: You wonder why you keep
getting thrown out of foster homes.
- Whatever.
- Fucking with a man twice your age.
MO: I ain't touched your fat boyfriend.
You grown, right? You a woman?
Goddamn it, be one.
Stop throwing my shit out the window.
I ain't playing with you.
- WOMAN: Your ass 'bout to learn.
- Whatever.
Don't want to hear you crying,
coming back around.
Ain't nobody coming back nowhere!
Fuck your house!
WOMAN: Slut ass.
MO: Dumb bitch.
("CONFLICTED" PLAYING)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
♪ Always been conflicted ♪
♪ I strained to obtain
So I could give more ♪
♪ Most dangerous
When there was nothin' to live for ♪
♪ For that fetti bag
Ready to let the six pour ♪
♪ Was on nothin' long enough... ♪
(SONG CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY NEARBY)
(BED CREAKING)
Social worker pressed me so hard
to rat on you.
MAN: What you tell her?
MO: Ain't nothing to tell.
You don't have to buy me stuff.
But you're like... my step-daddy, right?
Nadège done ruined half my shit.
I could use some new stuff.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Yeah, you should do it.
GIRL: I don't have no money to go out.
Think it's cute
ringing everybody's bells this late?
- WOMAN: Yes, she's sorry.
- (BABY CRYING)
Fuck that bitch.
I'd use the belt on that one, Lucila.
You gotta teach these kids respect
if they gonna live here.
(LUCILA IN SPANISH) Here one day
and you're already causing trouble.
(IN ENGLISH) You wake the baby.
(BABY CRYING)
LUCILA: Monique.
Monique.
Monique, you no sleep all day.
(IN SPANISH) I have to get to work.
Time to go to school!
(IN ENGLISH) Come on.
Ándale.
Ay...
(MUTTERS) Imposible.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(BOY YELLS)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
("GETCHA TEAM" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Omari.
(BOY GRUNTING)
- BOY: That's all you got? Come on.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
COACH: All right, let's go.
BOY: Where you going?
♪ It's nothin' to crush 'em
'Cause truthfully I'm better than y'all ♪
Omari.
(GRUNTS)
- BOY: You're like a little girl.
- OMARI: Hold up.
♪ No, this ain't the clash
Of the average Joe's ♪
- What's up?
- Nadège kicked me out.
♪ Warrior spirit
I'm playin', but I ain't playin' ♪
- When?
- Yesterday.
Help me get my stuff
before she steals something.
Omari. You got something better to do?
I'll be done at five.
- Gotta go now.
- COACH: Hey.
Five.
- You here to wrestle?
- MO: Please.
All you ever practice is doubles.
Shit's mad predictable.
(BOYS LAUGHING)
MO: Your coach is wack, yo.
Your problem ain't even in the lift.
You're not getting your shoulder in
close enough. You gotta go deep.
(DOG BARKING)
(HIP-HOP PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Tell me how he rock that much bling
and not be locked up.
- What'd Nadège throw you out for?
- She a crazy bitch.
She's jealous 'cause Hassan
paid for my nails.
Ain't my fault she ain't learned
how to please her man.
- You got a new foster family yet?
- Whatever.
Soon as my dad get out,
I'll stay with him.
Wait, give me that.
What are you doing?
- NADÈGE: Who that?
- Omari.
NADÈGE: Get out of here.
Mo don't live here no more.
- I left my math book in her room.
- NADÈGE: Is she with you?
No.
("REMIND ME" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
I... I need it to do my homework.
(LOCK CLICKING)
- Hurry the hell up.
- MO: The fuck out of the way!
NADÈGE: Oh, you fucking bitch!
Your punk ass through!
Okay, Mo.
- You wanna play?
- OMARI: Mo, hurry up.
♪ In love with you, darling ♪
- HASSAN: What the fuck?
- (MUSIC STOPS)
NADÈGE: Uh-huh.
Trespassing.
Tilden...
- Who you calling?
- NADÈGE: The police, that's who.
HASSAN: Why you wanna do that?
NADÈGE: This slut done broke
in my house, Hassan.
Hang up that phone before I smack you.
("ONE FOR GHOST" PLAYING)
♪ Take me across her lap ♪
♪ She used to hit me with a strap ♪
♪ When I was bad ♪
OMARI: Yo.
Mad people be trying for the Powerball.
Don't they know black people
don't never win real money?
Shit, if I won...
I'd buy me one of them big-ass TVs.
Surround sound and all that shit.
Imagine Halo on that.
- A TV?
- Yeah.
I get that much money, I'm getting
a house and getting the fuck out.
Where you gonna go?
Everyone you know is here.
That much money, you can get a house,
move to Miami and be on the beach.
- Eating oranges all day and shit.
- Oh, yeah, oranges.
You'll be a millionaire
and you gonna be peeling oranges.
- Please, you gonna be peeling for me.
- Yeah, all right. (SCOFFS)
BOY: Yo.
Can I get a lick?
I don't know. Can I?
BOY: How about you give me your number?
1800-fine-ass-ho. What's up?
Yo, Omari, where you going?
Don't make me go back
to that Spanish lady house.
Chill with me. Omari!
(MO GRUNTS, THEN CHUCKLES)
- OMARI: Gotta be up early for a run.
- MO: You said we chilling at your place.
- You owe me a rematch.
- MAN: Watch where you going!
(MAN MUTTERS) Shit.
Fine, one rematch, but I'm not...
- What up, O?
- OMARI: What's up, Darrel?
DARREL: You the big man now, huh?
How's your mom?
OMARI: She good.
DARREL: Yeah? She still dancing?
OMARI: Yeah.
She don't tell us where, though.
DARREL: It's better that way.
I'm gonna go.
I got practice in the morning.
Yeah? What for?
Wrestling, actually.
- No shit. What you weigh, 130?
- OMARI: Yeah.
But I'ma drop to 120.
I'ma dominate at 120.
- Best correct your footwork.
- Whatever.
How you gonna say whatever
when you be tripping on your feet?
Think 'cause your mom buy you
new sneakers, you gonna make varsity?
Take out all of the glass?
- DARREL: Yeah.
- Good.
You no want if we get fined.
You got a job? You work here?
Better get your asses home.
Ya'll looking for trouble out this late.
- Let me get your number.
- Ain't got one yet.
Let me give you mine.
All right, I'll see you.
OMARI: When he get out?
Mind your damn business.
- What'd I say?
- "I'm gonna dominate at 120."
You wouldn't even be on a team
if it wasn't for me.
Why you mad for?
You supposed to be happy your pops is out.
Mo?
(MO BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MAN RECITING ADHAN)
(GASPING)
You don't see me working?
- Why didn't you come find me?
- I been busy.
Can I come live with you?
You lost your mind?
I can get a job.
- No.
- I can help pay for the rent.
No. I said no!
Shit.
What you need me for anyway?
Look at you. You a grown woman now.
You do your thing, I'll do mine.
We see each other round the way.
(BABY CRYING)
I talked to him. He got a job now.
- Like, a real job.
- Have a seat.
You can find out where he live, right?
First we need to discuss
what happened at Nadège's.
- I had to get the rest of my shit.
- We had an agreement, Mo.
You'd let me know if anything was missing,
and I'd send someone.
I don't trust that bitch.
And as your social worker,
if I can't trust you, I can't help you.
Not gonna need your help
when I move in with my dad.
We talked about this, Mo.
He's not your legal guardian anymore.
Well...
he said he wanted to adopt me, so...
I know the last few homes
have been difficult.
But I do think Lucila...
could be a really good family...
No, she's not my fucking family!
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
You lucky you skipped algebra.
Ms. Nestor gave us a quiz,
and I swear that shit wasn't even math.
What, you not talking to me now?
What'd I do?
Watch it.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
- Say that shit to my face!
- OMARI: Mo.
- (SCREAMS)
- OMARI: Watch out!
Mo, chill!
Get off of me!
Bitch, if you don't get off of me...
- OMARI: Mo!
- Fuck you!
(ALL YELLING)
- Calm down.
- BOY: She started it!
Get the fuck off me!
This is the third fight this month.
As I've explained to Monique,
she'll be suspended for three days.
She needs a positive outlet
to channel that anger.
PRINCIPAL: I'd love to see her
reach her potential.
She's been given many opportunities,
but I cannot allow this kind of behavior.
- (SIRENS WAILING)
- (FIRE ENGINE HONKING)
(HORN HONKING)
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(MAN CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: What's going on? What's going on...
with the door and the trash?
We gotta go. Come on.
Here we go.
(NO AUDIO)
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
- (GUNFIRE ON VIDEO GAME)
- (DOOR CLOSES)
(GAME GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
MO: Give me that.
("THE MASQUERADE IS OVER"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
♪ You're a lot the same ♪
(BABY CRYING)
♪ But my heart says no ♪
♪ No, you're not ♪
♪ You're not the same ♪
♪ I'm afraid ♪
Remember when your pops used to make us
wrestle for stupid shit, like...
Happy Meal toys?
You cried like a baby over that tow truck.
Hey, Mater was the shit.
Besides, you only won 'cause you cheated.
♪ And so is love ♪
WOMAN: Hurry up.
You gonna be late.
- I told you about coming round here.
- Please. Like you own this block.
I'm coming from wrestling practice,
if you so nosey.
Coach say I'm gonna be
his best lightweight.
They got a girls' wrestling team?
Nah, I'ma wrestle boys.
Never heard of no girls wrestling
on no boys' team.
Yeah, well... I'm better than you.
That right?
Come see for yourself.
Cut them nails before you hit the mat.
(BOYS CHATTERING)
'Sup, troublemaker?
Still letting people on the team?
Practice starts at three.
Gives you exactly four minutes
to stop wasting my time.
- You ain't hear me?
- Coach, you need anything?
I said, you still letting people
on the team?
It's a boys' team.
Could've fooled me.
Besides, I need a positive outlet
for my anger.
Right, Coach?
No one here's interested in your games.
- You see me talking to you?
- COACH: Hey.
You wanna try out?
- BOY: Coach, you ain't serious.
- Take a knee. Now.
- You seen what she did to my girl?
- A knee.
COACH: How many of you
missed this morning's run?
Fifty push-ups, now.
- One.
- Damn! They all get punished?
What you waiting on?
BOYS: ...three, four...
- COACH: You like your earlobes?
- ...five, six...
Don't even think about
getting on my mat in those things.
- ...nine, ten...
- ("THE ANTHEM" PLAYING)
What are you doing?
- What it look like?
- COACH: Pick it up. Pick it up.
♪ It's time ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Hut, hut, hut ♪
♪ Who is it? ♪
COACH: Do those rolls. Come on, Monique.
♪ From the block to the bar
For the rimmy on the rocks ♪
♪ DIP, VIP
Straight to the back ♪
Step deep, stay low.
♪ Shake up the stacks ♪
♪ I place with the kick
With a case to the black ♪
COACH: Keep your center low. Elbows in.
♪ Left pass and around
To my mansion there ♪
♪ We drink up
Drinks up off gans and Rémy, uh ♪
♪ Get the hand, get the gin ♪
♪ Get the crisp served ♪
♪ Get the pin, get the yens
Get the picture ♪
♪ One to the two
Gun to the shoot ♪
♪ Take boys in the club... ♪
One knee, keep the head up.
Quick transfer to the double.
Keep your head up.
Drive through with the ear
and your left leg.
- (THUD)
- All right.
Good, good, good. Okay, partner up.
One, two.
MO: Omari.
Practice with me.
- Me and Jorge usually partner.
- So?
Let him practice with somebody else.
- COACH: Switch.
- (CHUCKLES)
(STAMMERS) It don't look right.
COACH: Get your head out fast. Come on.
How you gonna say that when I been
showing you shit for years?
Your pops' the one who been showing us.
- He only showing me now.
- OMARI: What?
- MO: Who you think training me?
- Get your girl in line.
Go eat some more tacos, fat-ass.
- Shut the fuck up.
- COACH: Hey.
Anyone planning to stay on this team
better be drilling now.
Tyson.
Pair up with Mo.
- BOY 1: Yeah, Ty!
- BOY 2: Tyson.
(CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
What? You ain't never touched a girl?
Today's your lucky day.
Hey! Opa! (LAUGHS)
My bad. Come on, let's wrestle.
Ah!
Damn! Now you a perv,
trying to feel some titty?
BOY: Tyson.
Switch with me.
Fucking pussy, yo.
(COACH SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
BOY 1: Yo.
BOY 2: Oh, shit.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
COACH: Other man, switch. Malik.
Stick to the drill.
DARREL: Ain't nothing in it for a dude.
You beat a girl, you look like
a motherfucking roughneck,
don't know how to treat a female.
Get beat, you a straight bitch.
So how's that my fault?
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(MUTTERS SOFTLY)
Remember that one time
I took you to get your hair braided?
You were small,
you were walking around all proud,
like you some type of queen.
The girl across the hall
from your grandma called you ugly.
Gave her a bloody nose, too.
Ain't never talk to me like that again.
When I came home and told you,
you slapped me upside the head.
Remember why?
'Cause I ain't raise you...
to give a shit what nobody else think.
("MO'S THEME" PLAYING)
♪ Yo, yo, yo ♪
♪ Hey, yo, now check the skill
It's very versatile ♪
♪ I'm fresh up from the shadows
Barrels burstin' in the air ♪
♪ From Pitkin to Livonia
Saratoga to The Hill ♪
♪ The Ville
In 2017 it's still real ♪
♪ I'm from the corner
Where the sun don't shine ♪
♪ Babies hit in their strollers
Shootouts in daytime over profit ♪
♪ In search of mad loot
It gets toxic ♪
♪ To fight and overcome
You gots... ♪
COACH:
Got our first match in two weeks.
♪ 'Cause ain't shit in this world
Gonna break me ♪
COACH: Don't know how any of you
expect to make weight
if you can't even get your asses up
for morning run.
I'll be watching to see
who's ready for varsity.
♪ Now follow with me
As this world rotates ♪
♪ They tried to take me out the game
I had to plan my escape ♪
♪ Keep focused, be humble
Stay away from the fake ♪
♪ And keep shining, keep shining
What? ♪
♪ Sometimes it feels as if
The world gonna end ♪
♪ Had my back against the wall
And now I'm back for revenge ♪
♪ More focused, more hunger
Never falling again ♪
♪ I keep shining, keep shining
What? ♪
♪ Now, one's for my projects
And two is for my set ♪
LUCILA: Monique. Monique.
(SONG CONTINUES OVER HEADPHONES)
What?
Think you cute dressing your baby
all bougie for church?
(IN SPANISH) Have you seen my pearls?
English, lady.
I'll pray for you.
(DOOR CLOSES)
COACH: Ten more seconds. Finish strong.
- BOY: Let's go, champ.
- COACH: Come on, wrestle hard.
- Oh, shit.
- Come on. Come on, yo.
- Ooh.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- Chad, nine. Chris, four.
- Yeah!
(BOY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
All right, next up.
- Next up.
- JORGE: Come on, O.
BOY: Go ahead, O.
- Let's get it, kid.
- COACH: That's enough.
That's enough. Omari.
You wresting off of 120,
or you busy wetting your pants?
(BOYS LAUGHING)
BOY: Put her in her place, man.
BOY 2: Drop her ass.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
- There it go.
- Yeah.
- Let's get that.
- There you go.
Duck under, man.
Don't tie up. Wrestle hard. Let's go, O.
COACH: Enough dancing,
somebody take a shot.
- See what I mean?
- Oh, damn!
- Sweep.
- Let's go, O. Get up.
Come on, O. Get out of that shit.
Here we go.
Come on, bro. She mad scrawny.
I would end this shit in 30 seconds.
Get her down, O.
No, no, no.
Ooh!
Damn. You gonna let a girl dominate?
Get up, O. Get up.
- Oh! Shit.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
Damn, O.
COACH:
We got ourselves a new starter.
(BOYS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Get that signed before Saturday's match.
BOY: Thought we was gonna
have to call the ambulance.
OMARI: Yeah, okay, okay.
You couldn't beat a girl.
What are you doing?
You so shook, you ain't even give me
a chance to take you
- and your big titties down.
- BOY: Oh!
Yo, you like it rough, huh?
- I'm down with that.
- Nigga, please.
Y'all too busy jerking each other off
at McDonald's to make morning run?
- Oh, shit.
- She's right.
All ya'll fucking lazy.
Yo, Mo, is it true your dad trains you?
Yeah. So?
Omari said he won states.
He gonna come to the match?
He'll be there.
By a hundred-pound girl.
She was on your ass.
I let her win. You heard her.
She said, "My dad trained me."
(SIREN WAILING NEARBY)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: You ain't gonna tell me
you were getting out?
I gotta find out in the streets.
DARREL: Still need to lay low.
Yo, what up, shorty?
You remember Monique?
Yeah, I seen her round the way.
Growing up real nice,
just like her mommy.
DARREL: What you need?
Nothing. Just came to let you know
I made varsity.
No shit?
What type of team you make, baby girl?
They got girls wrestling now.
You believe that shit?
(MAN LAUGHS) Yeah, I can believe that.
I seen some bitches get nastier
than my pits.
DARREL: She got her pops' fighting genes,
I guess.
We got our first match on Saturday.
I'd like to see that.
All right, that it?
Starts at four. Hedgeman.
All right, then.
- MAN: So she's staying by you again?
- DARREL: Nah.
MAN: You know I got a living situation
set up for you.
- DARREL: Gotta think about it.
- MAN: What you mean, think about it?
I'm trying to give you a better situation.
You gotta think about that?
WOMAN: You don't answer her calls.
- You come home beat up.
- The fuck's she talking about?
(IN SPANISH)
Look. Covered in bruises.
MO: Ain't like she think.
WOMAN: She's also missing some jewelry.
I told her I ain't steal
her ugly-ass earrings.
There's a group home in the Bronx
that has a spot open.
The Bronx? You know how far that is
from my school?
- WOMAN: There's a school near the home.
- No, look.
That wrestling coach she met,
he gonna teach me, like...
discipline and all that.
See?
- WOMAN: Wrestling?
- Yeah.
(IN SPANISH)
What's she saying? What's wrestling?
Uh...
(IN SPANISH) I think... she joined
the wrestling team at her school.
Wrestling?
Like with costumes?
No, like in high school. The sport.
But that's not for girls.
Ask him, he gonna keep me
out of trouble. I swear.
(PEOPLE CLAPPING, CHEERING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- REFEREE: Easy.
BOY: On the inside.
Foot on the inside, man!
COACH: Let's go.
Jamal, get your legs back.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(PEOPLE CLAPPING)
BOY: What?
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- COACH: Let's go.
You know you gotta go beast
on their asses, right?
COACH: Come on, ref, make 'em wrestle.
COACH: Get to your base.
Get to your base.
MALIK: They fit all right?
Yeah. Thanks.
Gotta loosen up.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
You'll be all right.
Plus, the kid you're wrestling,
he's a freshman.
Besides, he ain't seen your magic weapon.
Mo. You're up.
Remember, keep him in front of you,
and don't tie up.
Look for the shot.
Hey, hey, where's your head at?
All right? Okay.
Seriously?
- How's this even allowed?
- How are you even allowed?
- 'Cause I'm a dude.
- Why you crying like a bitch?
Mo, cool it!
Knock that off.
You're here to wrestle.
In the middle.
(DOOR OPENS)
Shake hands.
Let's go. Shake hands.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- (BOYS CHEERING)
COACH: Let's go, Mo! Let's go!
Stop him.
Keep him in front of you.
- (TEAMMATES CHATTERING)
- BOY: Make it quick, Santo.
COACH: Don't tie up!
MAN: Work the score.
COACH: Take a shot. Take a shot.
- REFEREE: Two.
- That's it!
That's it! That's it!
(BOYS CHANTING) Santo! Santo! Santo!
COACH: Off your back! Off your back!
REFEREE: Two.
COACH: Come on.
- REFEREE: Three.
- COACH: Bridge!
REFEREE: Four.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Okay, it's Red's choice.
Red chose top. Green, set up.
Red, get set.
COACH: Up and out, Mo. Up and out.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
REFEREE: Easy.
COACH: Come on, Mo.
REFEREE: Watch the fingers.
BOY 1: Come on, Mo.
BOY 2: Let's go, Mo! Let's go, Mo!
- Come on, Mo!
- REFEREE: One, green.
One.
(MUFFLED CHATTERING)
Two.
Three.
- COACH: Get off your back!
- REFEREE: Four.
- Get up! Off your back.
- REFEREE: Five.
- COACH: Get to your base.
- REFEREE: That's three near falls.
Red.
COACH: Come on, Mo! Break the hand.
REFEREE: One escape. Green.
COACH: Good! Good!
REFEREE: Two! Takedown, green. One.
Keep him down.
REFEREE: Two.
- Three.
- DARREL: Lift the head.
- REFEREE: Four.
- Lift the head.
REFEREE: Five.
COACH: That's it! That's it! Right there!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(PEOPLE CLAPPING)
REFEREE: Winner is green.
DARREL: Let me get a shrimp-fried rice.
(SOFT ROCK PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
WOMAN: What size you want?
Let me get a... small.
Gotta watch that weight, right?
Tell you what,
you don't appreciate your own room
until you share a cell with a mental case.
This one foster home,
I had to share a room with six kids.
- Place smelled like shit.
- Yeah, well...
Juan know he owe me, so...
You working for him again?
You stupid? Nah.
Working for him?
This is just like payback.
Know what I mean? Back pay.
I'm gonna save up a little bit...
then I'm out.
- Where you going?
- North Carolina.
- Aunt Keisha's?
- You remember her?
She still got that crazy dog?
- Russell? Russell wasn't crazy.
- That dog was definitely crazy.
He tried to bite my arm.
I still got the marks.
'Cause you and your cousins
used to try to ride his ass.
Remember that one time
we pinned his ears back?
And you wonder why he bit you. Shit.
Even a dog got some pride.
We should've never came back here.
(SCOFFS)
Shit don't always work out
the way it's supposed to.
My boy Jay get out,
we gonna open this car wash...
down in Greensboro.
- For real?
- Yeah.
Jay know the owner.
Car wash been sitting empty
at the dude's gas station.
We gonna go 50-50
on the whole thing.
We ain't gonna be nobody's bitch.
I don't really…
I don't really see it.
Where's my counter gonna be at again?
(CHUCKLES)
Come on, man.
You know I know how to upsell.
Watch me double your take.
("BUGGIN' OUT" PLAYING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
♪ Yo, microphone check one, two
What is this? ♪
♪ The five-foot assassin
With the roughneck business ♪
♪ I float like gravity ♪
♪ Never had a cavity ♪
♪ Got more rhymes
Than the Winans got family ♪
♪ No need to sweat Arsenio
To gain some type of fame ♪
♪ No shame in my game ♪
♪ 'Cause I'll always be the same ♪
♪ Styles upon styles upon styles
Is what I have ♪
(COACH CHANTING) Mini Mo! Mini Mo!
COACH: When's the last time
Hedgeman made playoffs?
- BOYS: Never.
- COACH: How'd you like to change that?
- ALL: Yeah!
- COACH: Come on, now!
Chop, highlight! Chop, highlight!
Highlight!
(PEOPLE CLAPPING)
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- There we go!
(ALL CHEERING)
(ALL WOOFING)
MO: You see his face
when I hit the reverse? I'm like a snake.
Just when you think you got me...
- Watch me go all the way to cities.
- First time I went to cities,
I had a clean record.
Not one loss.
Damn.
Go in there head all big. Get on the mat.
Dude half my size come at me
frothing at the mouth
like he got rabies.
I'm like,
"Who the hell is this little bulldog?"
Man, that kid had bite.
- He beat you?
- You stupid?
Nah.
They match the best with
the worst records in the first round.
This kid come in knowing he got one shot.
It's sink or swim, and this motherfucker
did not want to drown.
Sometimes wanting it that bad is enough.
Unfortunately, not when you messing
with the king.
(MO LAUGHS)
WOMAN: As soon as she's mobile,
you'll wanna get those cabinet locks.
- Especially in the kitchen.
- LUCILA: Yes, yes. I make good.
WOMAN: I don't wanna
promise anything, but...
I think there's a very good chance
you'll be able to adopt her.
LUCILA: There is Monique.
The one in the other room.
Hi, Monique.
I'm June, Nyasa's social worker.
I understand you moved in
not too long ago.
How do you like living here?
I ain't gonna be here long.
She can have my room soon enough.
♪ I'm a real nigga taking real hits
You just another Horowitz ♪
♪ When I shoot, I take you down ♪
♪ You a clown ♪
♪ I'm Ghostface, you Action Bronson ♪
(ALL CHATTERING AND CLAPPING)
JAMAL: Yo, listen, listen, listen!
♪ Niggas just be fertile
When I sit on the money ♪
♪ They gonna feel like they dead
And we going to finals ♪
♪ This shit is viral ♪
♪ Nobody can rival ♪
♪ No, I ain't gonna rhyme that ♪
♪ Bust it! Bust it! Bust it! ♪
(MO AND MALIK SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(BOYS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SIREN WAILING)
(INDIAN MUSIC PLAYING OVER CAR SPEAKERS)
(LOCK RATTLING)
You coming in or not?
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
Thought you said you was done with Juan.
You want me cleaning up rat shit
and picking up trash?
Ain't no punk-ass boss stealing from me.
So my girl going to playoffs.
Go in there and get my smokes.
I don't see none in here.
(DARREL CHUCKLING)
You practicing that bear hug?
Yeah.
So, what you waiting for?
(CHUCKLES)
What?
Nothing.
Go ahead, set up.
Uh-uh. Nah, nah, nah, look.
You can't do nothing.
Pin this arm. Let me see.
Grab me.
Pop the arm.
Gonna pin his down...
and drive through.
You feel me?
(CAR APPROACHING)
Go ahead.
Sit down.
(GATE RATTLING)
They better have wrestling teams
in Greensboro.
Let's try again.
Come on.
DARREL: In a minute.
We gotta paint that car wash
something fresh.
Think people getting their car washed
somewhere 'cause of a color?
Hell, yeah.
Think people getting their car washed
in some boring joint?
You gotta get niggas
with the fly-ass rims,
dope-ass set of seats. Detailing?
That's where the money at, yo.
All right.
All right, what color you think
get the most business?
That's easy. Gold.
(LAUGHING)
- What?
- Where the fuck you get this from?
MO: It's called vision, man.
- Ain't my fault you ain't got none.
- Watch out.
Oh, now you the one with the ideas?
Hey!
(MO SQUEALS)
DARREL: I got the arm.
I got the arm.
- I got the head. Just giving me every...
- Oh!
(PEOPLE CLAPPING)
Mo, on his back.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
- COACH: Let's go.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- BOY 1: Cover.
- BOY 2: Come on, Mo.
BOY 3: Take him down, Mo.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(ALL CHANTING) Mini Mo! Mini Mo! Mini Mo!
(CHEERING)
OMARI: Yo, you heard?
Jorge's brother's bringing his dirt bike
after Coach's thing.
- Word?
- He gonna let me ride.
I'm gonna pop a wheelie and everything.
What?
It's easy. I seen it on YouTube.
Just let go of the clutch and pop.
Yeah, all right.
- You down?
- No, I got plans.
Juan got you walking his dogs again?
Hell, no.
"You better bring their asses back clean.
Don't want no shit on my Persians."
Yo, shut up.
I heard he brushes his dogs' teeth
with an electronic toothbrush.
(MAKES BUZZING SOUND)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- DARREL: Yo, you ready?
- Give me a sec.
What you sulking for, string bean?
Keep on drinking them protein shakes,
you'll get your glory soon enough.
COACH: It's Darrel, right?
I hear she takes after you.
It's in the blood, I guess.
(COACH CHUCKLES)
Well, you're a stronger man than me.
If my daughter wanted to wrestle,
I'd... (CHUCKLES)
Where'd you wrestle at?
Five-six-nine.
I was at collegiate.
Probably before your time.
- Oh, yeah, probably.
- MO: All right.
We gotta bounce.
I'm taking the team out for a bite
if you'd like to join us.
Unless, uh...
there's somewhere else you gotta be.
- Yeah, at work.
- I thought we was hanging out?
DARREL: Maybe later.
- But you said we was...
- Plans change... Mo.
Besides, team gotta bond and all that.
Ain't that right, Coach?
Yeah.
You got it.
DARREL: Call me later.
MALIK: You gotta slow down.
You gonna crash.
- I got this.
- You gonna crash.
- MO: Oh!
- I told you.
- Game cheated, yo.
The problem is your driving's worse
than your wrestling. That's what's...
That's the real deal.
- Now what?
- You all in my ear.
- Get your stink breath out my face.
- MALIK: Then do something.
We about to do a pull-up contest.
You coming?
Yo. I thought you was
gonna pop a wheelie.
Yeah, what happened?
We came for the show.
I told you my brother had a race.
I said that.
Whatever. Mo, you coming?
- No, I'ma chill here.
- Whatever.
JAMAL: Ooh!
(LAUGHING)
For real, though, we make it to finals...
it's like a whole bunch of recruiters
that come.
JAMAL: Mm-hm.
- Bet you get a scholarship.
- Yeah!
Our little prince right here
is gonna get a free ride to college.
Whatever, man. Whatever, man.
You gonna be coming by my place
every weekend
trying to holla at some college hos.
I will be prying them off my dick, bro.
'Sup, shorty?
You want a ride? Look... Oh.
(MO LAUGHS)
My bad, he ain't take his meds.
Why you trying to fuck up my game for?
What game? What game?
Exactly.
Anyway... there's mad women's teams
in college now.
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- You know?
What's up, beautiful?
No, no, we just chilling.
- (LOW BARK)
- MO: Where we going?
- DARREL: Just... Just wait. Just wait.
- This where Juan do them dog fights?
Nah.
Nah, this the real shit.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(BABY CRYING)
(DRUM 'N' BASS MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
MC: All right, y'all. Tonight, we got
three-time Brownsville champ...
It's the real fight right here.
MC: ...Keisha the Killer.
Make some noise for Keisha!
(CROWD CHEERING)
But don't be fooled,
'cause Miss Lala, she may look skinny,
but she ain't come all the way
from Flatbush to eat shit.
Give it up for Miss Lala.
- Where's the money at?
- They boxers?
- MC: Show your bets.
- Nah, kid, they fiercer than that.
MC: All right, ladies,
center of the ring.
No biting, no scratching, no hair pulling,
no weapons. Got it?
(BELL RINGS)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
MC: Hey, hey! No hair pulling.
No hair pulling.
(THUD)
(YELLS)
Ya'll give it up for Keisha the Killer!
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
DARREL: Go ahead, eat.
That's cool, I can't eat.
We got another match on Saturday.
Malik said there might be
college recruiters.
Oh! Well, if Malik say...
Stop playing. (CHUCKLES)
They got women's teams now.
College cool...
and all that, until you get hit
with real responsibilities.
When your mom passed…
I did what I had to do.
I didn't have no choice.
Can't wait till I make my own money,
get my own place.
Well, if I could, I'd be in the ring
like them girls tonight.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Them girls on some other shit.
I think that one girl got her jaw broke.
But you know how much money they make?
Shit.
You said the money was good with Juan.
You said you was saving up
for the car wash.
Yeah, well, Jay didn't make parole.
So, unless I can come up with his half...
and quick, ain't gonna be no car wash.
Fuck, Monique!
Shit. The minute I get out,
you in my grill to take care of you.
- I told you it ain't like that.
- Did you make varsity or not?
- Yeah.
- Ain't none of them girls
training on no boys' wrestling team.
You already had an advantage.
You working out with dudes,
and you training with me.
One fight, you can make as much
as I make in a week working the lot.
Fact is...
if I don't come up with ten Gs
in the next two weeks, owner gonna sell
the wash to somebody else. I'm...
I'm doing my part.
We both know what happen
if I keep working for Juan.
Fuck it!
Fuck it. Fuck it.
Fuck it. It's stupid. I'm stupid.
I'm stupid.
- I ain't say...
- I shouldn't have took your ass there.
- I'm saying the money...
- Eat if you gonna eat. Shit. I gotta...
I gotta get back to the lot.
(SIGHS)
(COACH SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Damn! No wonder you ain't make varsity.
You wouldn't be starting
if I hadn't let you win.
How come everybody saw me
take your ass down?
COACH: Watch his down.
Chest to back, and spin.
OMARI: Oh, Juan buy you those kicks, too?
At least my dad comes to my matches.
Your mom's too busy taking her clothes off
for random niggas.
(COACH SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(NYASA CRYING)
WOMAN: What?
What's wrong? What? What, what, what?
LUCILA: She probably hungry.
Nyasa mom here.
WOMAN: What's wrong?
You not happy to see Mommy?
Just...
Here. I gotta use the toilet.
- (DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
- (LUCILA SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
You should be happy for her.
She should be with her real mom.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
(PEOPLE CLAPPING AND CHATTERING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
MAN: Come on, Nicholas.
Come on, let's go.
Nice and easy.
Let's get this done.
Lower your anklets.
COACH: All right, Mo.
Shake hands.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
COACH: Take a shot.
Get to your bridge! Build up! Build up!
That's it. Get in there, Mo.
Where's that fire? Get in there.
Build up! Build up! Build up!
Build up!
(MO PANTING)
Get up! Get off your back! Off your back!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
REFEREE: Shake hands.
Shake hands. Shake the coaches' hands.
COACH: Hey!
What the hell happened out there?
(BOYS CHANTING) Let's go, Huskies!
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
Let's go, Hedgeman!
Let's go, Huskies!
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
(BOY LAUGHING)
Everybody allowed to lose a match.
What's that corny shit Coach say?
There's no such thing as losing,
it's just...
It's just winning and learning.
(BOY CLAPPING)
You know how many times
my father seen me wrestle?
You get used to it.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(DRUM 'N' BASS MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
MC: All right, y'all, show your bets.
Where the money at?
You got money on the fat girl?
That girl can do damage.
Trust.
MC: Where the money at? Come on.
Don't be cheap.
What, y'all sleeping?
How much we need for the car wash?
You and me dump Juan
and get the fuck out of here.
MC: The rules: no biting, no scratching,
no weapons, no hair pulling. Y'all got it?
Couple of fights...
we'll be good.
MC: All right, ladies,
center of the ring.
(BELL RINGS)
Jab. Jab, jab.
("#1 SOUND" PLAYING)
That's your combination. Jab straight up.
Just when they think they got you,
mix it up.
Why do that when I can just do this?
This ain't wrestling.
Shoot on somebody like that,
you gonna get your grill knocked out.
- COACH: Mo!
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
Straight. Jab, jab, straight.
- Come on.
- Jab, jab, straight. Jab, jab, straight.
One, two. Uppercut, uppercut.
Get in there. Grab my fucking neck.
Grab. Grab the neck.
All right, come on. One, two.
(MO GRUNTS)
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- COACH: Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
It's all right, I got it, Coach.
Guys, have a seat.
♪ Price of freedom getting higher
Future on consignment ♪
♪ Niggas want Obama
Be the first to co-sign it ♪
♪ So, God bless the child
That makes its own luck ♪
♪ Choked up intense hunger to come up ♪
BOY: Let's go, Mo!
(CHANTING) Mini Mo! Mini Mo!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(CHEERING)
COACH: Let's go, let's go!
(WOOFING)
♪ We goin' to finals
We goin' to finals ♪
♪ We goin' to finals ♪
(BOY 1 SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Where the fuck you been?
I been calling and texting all night.
MO: What? My ringer was off.
I told you to keep your phone on vibrate.
You about to miss the fight.
- What?
- Hurry up, let's go.
- Tonight?
- Yes, tonight. Goddamn. Shit.
You lucky Juan kept your spot.
BOY 2: Only had 20 pounds on me, too.
BOY 3: What you talking about?
I had double unders.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
MC: All right, y'all.
So, tonight, we got a few virgin fighters
in the building.
So, I'ma need y'all
to put y'all hands together,
'cause we 'bout to turn up. Let's do it.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Who the girl?
Juan cousin.
Don't worry, she ain't got nothing on you.
- MC: All right, ladies.
- Show her who the queen.
MC: To the middle.
Y'all know what time it is, right?
Gonna need y'all to try to make this
as clean as possible.
All right, got it? So, dap it up.
And on my whistle,
turn up.
(WHISTLES)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
What you running for? Get back in there.
Come on, Naya.
Come on, Naya. Quit playing with her.
- There it is.
- Get up, get up, get up.
What you running for?
- (MO GRUNTS)
- (DARREL YELLS)
Yeah!
Mo. Mo.
You lost your fucking mind?
What, you stalking me now?
- What's wrong with you?
- With me?
The hell you doing in there, Mo?
We're one match away from finals.
What's Coach gonna say
when he sees your face?
MO: Coach not gonna say shit.
'Cause Coach not gonna know shit.
I swear, O,
- you open your mouth...
- DARREL: What'd I tell you?
Them girls ain't got nothing on you.
What up, O?
You see your girl get real in there?
Yeah.
She did good.
Anyways, I gotta go.
DARREL: You be safe.
What'd I tell you?
I didn't say shit.
He came here by hisself.
Besides, he's not gonna say nothing.
Where's the money?
(SCOFFS)
Go ahead, feel that.
Five hundred?
- You said winner take a G.
- What you want it for?
You lucky he even let you have a fight.
It was just a warm-up.
I'll tell you when you ready
for the big leagues.
- ("I GOT IT MADE" PLAYS OVER HEADPHONES)
- DARREL: Black Moon.
Das EFX.
Special Ed? This shit is old as me, yo.
Who you think put me onto it?
You're a little mini-me, you know that?
Malik call me Mini Mo.
(MOCKINGLY) "Malik call me Mini Mo.
- Malik say I'm fine."
- Ain't even like that.
"Malik say I'm fine."
(DARREL LAUGHS)
Whatever. He got a girl anyway.
Hey, listen.
Fuck Malik.
You gonna be a legend.
And not just in some...
high school yearbook.
Make a name out here,
ain't nobody gonna fuck with you.
Come here.
Gotta teach you how to duck.
(LATIN MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
You can leave now.
Ay... ¿Que te pasó?
Get the fuck out!
COACH: Lucila wants you off the team.
You and I both know you didn't
get punched in the face wrestling.
Now, tell me what's going on
with your father,
or I'll pull you off this team myself.
Ain't got nothing to do with him.
I got beef with some girl.
My dad runs one of Juan's parking lots.
I chill with him sometimes.
He got no place to live,
so he sleeps there.
This girl called him homeless, and...
I lost my shit.
Just 'cause I messed up,
it ain't the team's fault.
I'm gonna win. We going to finals.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(SIGHS)
- (BOYS CHATTERING)
- (FIGHT BELL RINGS ON TV)
BOY: He's stalling.
He's gonna spank him, bro.
- We can bet money, bro.
- (WHISPERING)
JAMAL: He got taken down.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
JAMAL: This is why
I don't watch white porn.
BOY: You are not watching
half the fight, Mo.
We can put money on the fight.
BOY 2: Chris been watching
the whole thing.
What's up with you?
That time of the month?
Why you all...?
Come on. Come on.
How long you been wrestling for?
MALIK: Since I was ten.
Uncle wanted me to start boxing, actually.
I got punched in the mouth one time,
and I was like...
"No, thank you."
("LET YOUR LIGHT SHINE" PLAYING)
My nickname was Wrong Way,
because every time a fight broke out,
all my friends running towards the shit,
I'm running the other way.
They got a medical term for that.
It's called no balls-itis.
Yeah, well...
when my dad came back around...
I almost got thrown off the team.
Tried to work the corners with him
and be tough...
You, dealing? I'd have loved to see that.
If it wasn't for Coach riding my ass,
showing up to my house,
I would've dropped out.
- Coach pay you to tell me that?
- What?
(SCOFFS) Fuck, no.
You sound like one of them guest speakers.
- "Stay in school, kids. Don't do drugs."
- (MALIK LAUGHS)
Yeah, well...
would've been one corny ass gangster.
Damn, what do all these schools
want you for?
- These the good schools.
- 'Cause I put in the work.
Not like you. Look at yo ass.
You just faking.
You think you a real wrestler.
- MO: Whatever.
- You think you're a wrestler.
Now who the king?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
♪ Even when the sky is gray ♪
♪ And you feel like ♪
♪ There's no way, no, no ♪
♪ All you gotta do is ♪
♪ Look inside yourself and see ♪
♪ See the light, yeah ♪
♪ See the light within yourself and be ♪
♪ Be the light, yeah ♪
♪ Be the light and come away with me ♪
♪ Go and let your light shine through ♪
(MUFFLED VOICES)
- (DOOR OPENS)
- GIRL: Please...
(GASPS)
- I thought you had more class.
- MALIK: Ain't what you think. Nathalie.
It ain't what you think.
- How about what I see?
- It ain't mean nothing.
- NATHALIE: What are you talking about?
- MALIK: We don't mean nothing.
Nathalie, just...
(NATHALIE YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
- OMARI: You fucked him?
- Move out the way.
You know she's pregnant?
- I'm not playing.
- She was right.
You'll let anybody fuck you.
(DRUM 'N' BASS MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
I'm ready for the real shit.
Gotta get the fuck out of here.
Watch these girls and learn.
COACH: The underhook.
Fake and set single. Snap down.
Good. Shuck. Release that forearm.
Circle. Good, do it again.
Good.
All right. One, two.
(ALL CLAP)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
That's not an underhook.
You holding hands with him, Tyson.
Who taught you to shuck? Do it again.
Actually, Coach...
I'm kinda having some... female issues.
You worried about weight?
Nah, I'll be good if I don't eat.
I just...
- (INDISTINCT CHATTERING ON TV)
- (CELL PHONE CHIMES, BUZZES)
- (LUCILA SINGS SOFTLY IN SPANISH)
- (NYASA CRYING)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES, BUZZES)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
What color do you like?
I'm not allowed to have nails
'cause of wrestling.
I make nice for you.
(IN SPANISH) Good luck for tomorrow.
How come you never had your own babies?
(IN ENGLISH) God no...
(IN SPANISH) God wouldn't let me.
COACH: Okay, listen up. Remember...
there's no such thing as losing.
There's only winning...
and learning.
I want you to take pride
in how far you've come,
and have faith in how far you can go.
All right? Bring it in.
Give me some love.
- Winners never quit.
- ALL: Quitters never win.
- COACH: One, two, three!
- ALL: Hedgeman!
- COACH: Three, two, one!
- ALL: Huskies!
(ALL WOOFING)
(ANNOUNCER OVER PA) Hedgeman High
is happy to welcome Garner
for the last match of the season.
I know you're all excited.
We'll be getting started in a few minutes.
How you feeling today?
- I'm good.
- Good.
- I'm counting on you.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
(ALL CHEERING)
COACH: Get the hand-off! Look away!
REFEREE: We've got a takedown. One. Two.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
WOMAN: You got it! You got this!
You got this! You got this!
REFEREE: Okay, let's go.
Top man, work something.
I know shit got messed up the other night.
I crossed the line. Big time.
We family now.
I got a family.
Really?
What kind of father does that
to his daughter's face?
What kind of father
ditches his kid for college?
COACH: Look away. Rip 'em off.
There you go.
REFEREE: That's a warning.
Better work something, top man.
That's one.
Two.
Three.
Four.
That's two near falls.
Continue to work.
COACH: Come on, ref, make 'em wrestle!
REFEREE: One.
Two.
Three.
Two near falls.
Go, bottom man. Try to work something.
COACH: Don't give nothing away.
No, go to your base. Control his hands.
Get off your back!
- Off your back!
- REFEREE: One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Hold on three, top man.
You lose your match,
we ain't going to finals.
Then you'd better win.
- DARREL: What you need all that for?
- I can't go back there now.
MC: All right, let's go!
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
- DARREL: Go ahead, warm up.
- What about my shit?
What? It's fine.
- Somebody gonna steal it.
- DARREL: It's fine.
Go ahead, warm up.
Go ahead. Get in there.
MC: We got some fresh talent
in the house.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
We about to get started.
- Settle down. Settle down.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Tonight, we gonna see
if King D's fresh talent
can face one of Brownsville's toughest:
- Ms. Cheryl!
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- MAN: Real champ right here.
- MC: Show me your bets.
Kill her, Mama.
MC: Show me your bets.
Listen up. Tonight's your night.
There's five Gs with your name on it.
But you gotta win.
All right, now, show your bets.
Show your bets. Let's go.
So, listen.
No biting,
no scratching, no hair pulling,
no weapons. Y'all got it?
All right, dap it up.
("BLOCKBUSTER NIGHT PART 1" PLAYING)
- All right, y'all.
- (BELL RINGS)
♪ You punks is pussy
Proverbial pansy panty holders ♪
Come on, Mo.
You gotta fight back! Go!
♪ Macabre massacres
Killing cunts in my colosseum ♪
Put your damn fists up!
♪ I'd fall back if the casting calls
Are ending in semen ♪
- (MO GRUNTS)
- (CROWD ROARS)
(GRUNTING)
(BELL RINGS)
Break it up. Break it up.
We got a fight tonight!
- Mo, what the fuck you doing out there?
- She's all over me.
You said you wanted to fight. This is it.
Now, you gonna sink or swim?
(BELL RINGS)
♪ Well, pardon me, I guess I'm just
As sane as you explain'ed ♪
Come on, Mo, you gotta fight back!
Move your feet!
(MO YELLING)
Come on, Mo!
MC: No grabbing hair!
♪ The gates of hell
Are pugnaciously pacin', waitin' ♪
♪ I give a fuck if I'm late
Tell Satan be patient ♪
♪ But I ain't here for durations ♪
Stop the fucking round!
♪ And tell 'em fuck 'em
I never loved 'em and salutations ♪
(BELL RINGS)
MC: All right. All right. Break it up.
Break it up. Hey, you okay?
Go to the corner.
You go to your corner.
Mo, next time she hit you,
just go down and stay down.
- What?
- You ain't ready for this.
- I ain't no quitter.
- Mo!
- (BELL RINGS)
- Monique!
♪ Proved that we was fuckin' brutal ♪
♪ I'm talking crazy
Half past the clock is cuckoo ♪
♪ You rappers doo-doo
Baby shit, just basic boo-boo ♪
(MUFFLED CHEERING)
(MO WHIMPERING)
(DARREL WHISPERS)
Stay down, stay down, stay down.
(WOOFING)
Go!
Beat her ass, Mo! Beat her ass, Mo!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
- That's it! That's it! We got it!
- (SIREN WAILING)
MAN: Yo, it's the police! Let's go!
Come on!
- MO: I won. You seen it, right?
- We gotta split up.
- Where the fuck you want me to go?
- I don't know.
- Go back to the Spanish lady house.
- Like this?
See seen me leaving the match.
She'll know.
If I get caught,
you know where I'ma wind up.
- You get the money?
- You don't listen!
I'll call you when we clear, all right?
You the queen.
Mo. All right? You gonna be a legend.
Don't worry about all that.
You the queen!
What about my stuff?
(DOOR OPENS)
COP: Yeah, right over here.
(COP SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
We got the perimeter surrounded.
Wow, look at this.
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
Jesus.
("THE MASQUERADE IS OVER"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(SNIFFLING)
(CRYING)
(SOBBING)
♪ The masquerade is over ♪
(BOYS CHATTERING)
What?
What y'all looking at?
One stupid motherfucking wrestler.
MO: You win?
I taught you good.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
COACH: Hey.
Keep icing.
You understand I'm legally obligated
to report him?
When I was a kid,
I used to think I was mad lucky.
Most of my friends didn't know their dad,
maybe for like...
five minutes on their birthday
or something, but...
I was living with mine.
I wanted one of those
Razor scooters so bad.
Wouldn't shut up about it.
(CHUCKLES, SNIFFS)
One day, D brought one home for me.
Told me... to make sure
I only rode them in Tilden Projects.
But I was mad proud.
Rode that shit everywhere.
One day, this kid at Marcus Garvey...
seen me with it and said it was his.
Said he carved his initials in the handle.
Seen 'em, too.
I told him my dad bought it new
and would fuck him up.
Kid started stalking me.
One day, he seen me with D, and...
ratted him out to the cops.
They found out he'd been
robbing people for Juan.
You were a kid, Mo.
You're not responsible for your father.
(SNIFFLES)
(EXHALES)
I'm gonna do right.
I swear, just...
don't make my dad do no more time
'cause of me.
My mom says you can stay in Tanya's room
as long as you want.
She sleeps in my mom's bed anyway.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
COACH: I know. I know.
I'm very sorry for everything I've done.
And...
you're the only foster mom
never kicked me out.
And...
You be a good girl now.
(NYASA CRYING)
WOMAN: Quit crying. Come on.
Why you always crying?
Come on, stop crying. Stop crying.
Stop crying.
Shh, shh, shh.
I know. I know. It's all right.
Okay.
(NYASA CONTINUES CRYING)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
COACH: She not only let herself down,
she let the whole team down.
So, I put it to the group to decide.
Should she be suspended from finals
or not?
Omari had't won for her,
we wouldn't even be going to finals.
BOY 1: Yeah, that's true.
BOY 2: Yeah.
Everybody has a right to make a mistake.
That was a big one.
But we gotta think about
what's best for the team.
It's our first year going to finals.
And all respect to Omari
for stepping up, but...
Mo's been killing it all season.
Mo...
you have anything to add?
I'm gonna do whatever's best for the team.
Whatever y'all think that is.
Let's put it to a vote.
All in favor of Mo starting on Friday.
OMARI: Mo.
- (BOYS CHATTERING)
- Mo.
Monique.
- You got my bag?
- Why would I?
'Cause you stupid. Check yours.
Mine is missing.
Yeah. You lucky I asked.
Would've had to save your ass. Again.
You lucky you got big feet,
or I would've worn 'em anyway. Now move.
- Hey, where you going?
- I forgot my bag inside.
Mo.
Nice hair.
Thanks.
- (BOY 1 WHISTLES)
- BOY 2: Whoo!
(BOYS CHATTERING)
BOY 3: Get it, girl!
Girl, this ain't a runway.
Get out of here. Hurry up.
(MARCHING BAND MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
DARREL: Monique.
You got a match?
Now you the one hard to reach.
Fame getting to you?
Look, I know shit got fucked up.
I felt bad leaving after the fight.
For real.
But you...
You know I couldn't get caught
near all that. Mo. Mo, I...
I tried to double our earnings.
I was up for a little while, too.
Mo. Monique.
(STAMMERS) I just... I just got excited.
That's all.
Seeing you in the ring, on that mat...
it reminded me of me.
All that flying.
You could do something with that.
I know.
How about we start our own thing?
Dude I know, he got a gym, and we...
Mo.
Monique.
Oh, it's like that now?
Too good for your own pops now?
(BOYS CHATTERING)
COACH: Jamal here?
All right. Chad? Where's Chad?
- BOY: Yo, we gonna hook in.
- COACH: All right, so...
we got one, two, three, four, five, six,
- seven, eight, nine. Where's Tyson?
- (BUS ENGINE STARTS)
Somebody call and see if he's coming
on his own.
I'm not waiting more than five minutes.
MO: Dad.
DARREL: All right, don't...
Don't go soft on me now.
(MO CRYING)
How long you had my notebook?
- COACH: Y'all ready to go to finals?
- BOY: We're going to finals!
ALL: Yeah!
(BOY WOOFING)
(ALL CHANTING) Let's go, Hedgeman!
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
Let's go, Hedgeman!
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
Let's go, Huskies!
Let's go, Hedgeman!
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
Let's go, Huskies!
Let's go, Hedgeman!
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
(YELLING) Let's go, Huskies!
- Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
- (LAUGHS)
("EXHIBIT C" PLAYING)
♪ Lord ♪
♪ Please send her to me ♪
♪ It's coming, it's coming, it's coming ♪
♪ Lord ♪
♪ Please send her to me ♪
♪ Ladies and gentlemen, this time around
The revolution will not be televised ♪
- ♪ Whoo! ♪
- ♪ Cross my heart that I love her ♪
♪ As we proceed ♪
♪ To give you what you need ♪
♪ '09, mother... ♪
♪ Get live, mother... ♪
♪ Ladies and gentlemen of the court ♪
♪ In the hearing against ♪
♪ The State of Hip-Hop
Vs. Jay Electronica ♪
♪ I present Exhibit C ♪
♪ When I was sleepin' on the train ♪
♪ Sleepin' on Meserole Ave
Out in the rain ♪
♪ Without even a single slice of pizza
To my name ♪
♪ Too proud to beg for change
Mastering the pain ♪
♪ When New York niggas
Was calling southern rappers lame ♪
♪ But then jacking our slang ♪
♪ I used to get dizzy spells
Hear a little ring ♪
♪ The voice of an angel
Telling me my name ♪
♪ Telling me that one day
I'ma be a great mane ♪
♪ Transforming with the Megatron Don
Spittin' out flames ♪
♪ Eating wack rappers alive
Shittin' out chains ♪
♪ I ain't believe it then
Nigga, I was homeless ♪
♪ Fightin', shootin' dice
Smokin' weed on the corners ♪
♪ Trying to find the meaning of life
In a Corona ♪
♪ 'Til the Five Percenters rolled up
On a nigga and informed him ♪
♪ "You either build or destroy.
Where you come from?" ♪
♪ "The Magnolia projects
In the 3rd ward slum" ♪
♪ "Hm, it's quite amazing
That you rhyme how you do ♪
♪ And that you shine like you grew up
In a shrine in Peru" ♪
♪ Question 14
Muslim Lesson Two ♪
♪ Dip diver, civilize a 85er ♪
♪ I make the devil hit his knees
And say the "Our Father" ♪
♪ Abracadabra ♪
♪ You rocking with the true and living ♪
♪ Shout out to Lights Out
Joseph I, Chewy Bivens ♪
♪ Shout out to Baltimore, Baton Rouge
My crew in Richmond ♪
♪ While y'all debated who the truth was
Like Jews and Christians ♪
♪ I was on Cecil B, Broad Street, Master ♪
♪ North Philly, South Philly
23rd, Tasker ♪
♪ Six Mile, Seven Mile
Hartwell, Gratiot ♪
♪ Where niggas really would pack
A U-haul truck up ♪
♪ Put the high beams on ♪
♪ Drive up on the curb at a barbecue ♪
♪ And hop up out the back
Like, "What's up?" ♪
♪ Kill a nigga, rob a nigga
Take a nigga, bust up ♪
♪ That's why when you talk that tough talk
I never feel ya ♪
♪ You sound real good
And you play the part well ♪
♪ But the energy you givin' off
Is so unfamiliar ♪
♪ I don't feel ya ♪
♪ We need somethin' realer ♪
♪ Nas hit me up on the phone
Said, "What you waitin' on?" ♪
♪ Tip hit me up with a tweet
♪ Diddy send a text every hour
On the dot sayin' ♪
♪ "When you gonna drop that verse?
Nigga, you taking long" ♪
♪ So, now I'm back spittin'
That "he could pass a polygraph" ♪
♪ That Reverend Run
Rockin' Adidas out on Hollis Ave ♪
♪ That FOI, Marcus Garvey, Niki Tesla ♪
♪ I shock you like an eel
Electric feel, Jay Electra ♪
♪ Oh my God! Keep going! ♪
♪ They call me Jay Electronica ♪
♪ Fuck that ♪
♪ Call me Jay ElecHanukkah
Jay ElecYarmulke ♪
♪ Jay ElecRamadaan
Muhammad A'salaamaleikum ♪
♪ RasoulAllah Subhanahu wa ta'ala
Through your monitor ♪
♪ My Uzi still weigh a ton
Check the barometer ♪
♪ I'm hotter than the motherfuckin' sun
Check the thermometer ♪
♪ I'm bringing ancient mathematics
Back to modern man ♪
♪ My mama told me never throw the stone
And hide your hand ♪
♪ I got a lot of family
You got a lot of fans ♪
♪ That's why the people got my back
Like the Verizon man ♪
♪ I play the back and fade to black
And then devise a plan ♪
♪ Out in London, smokin', vibin'
While I ride the tram ♪
♪ Giving out that raw food
To lions disguised as lambs ♪
♪ And by the time
They get they seats hot ♪
♪ And deploy all they henchmen
To come at me from the treetops ♪
♪ I'm chillin' out at Tweetstock
Building by the millions ♪
♪ My light is brilliant ♪
♪ Lord, hear me ♪
♪ I rest my case ♪
♪ '09, Act 3 ♪
♪ First chapter of the end ♪
♪ The last chapter of a new beginning ♪
♪ If it's so? ♪
♪ The things we do without even tryin' ♪
♪ Be better than a lot of y'all records
Don't get mad ♪
♪ Morning after ♪
♪ World premier ♪
♪ Me? ♪
♪ For real though ♪
♪ I ain't even gonna say nothing ♪
♪ Matter of fact, I ain't sayin'... ♪
♪ I don't even why I'm sayin' this ♪
♪ Jay, you should get Puff
To do this over ♪
♪ We moving out ♪
♪ Onto the next record ♪
♪ And, uh, I'ma let this just ride ♪
♪ Ride, ride ♪
♪ Ride, ride, ride, ride ♪
(JUST BLAZE LAUGHS)
♪ Love her ♪
♪ Cross my heart that I love her ♪
♪ Lord, hear me ♪
("MO'S THEME" PLAYING)
♪ Yo, yo, yo, yo ♪
♪ Hey, yo, now check the skill
It's very versatile ♪
♪ I'm fresh up from the shadows
Barrels burstin' in the air ♪
♪ From Pitkin to Livonia
Saratoga to The Hill ♪
♪ The Ville
In 2017 it's still real ♪
♪ I'm from the corner
Where the sun don't shine ♪
♪ Babies hit in their strollers
Shootouts in daytime over profit ♪
♪ In search of mad loot
It gets toxic ♪
♪ To fight and overcome
You gots to keep the proper mindset ♪
♪ 'Cause ain't shit in this world
Gonna break me ♪
♪ Might've knocked me off my square
But they'll never deflate me ♪
♪ They all think I'm crazy ♪
♪ So what?
That won't shake me ♪
♪ Out this idea that I'm striving
Steady climbing for greatness ♪
♪ My aspirations
Kill my trials and tribulations ♪
♪ The past is in my brain
I use my pain to erase it ♪
♪ It's written in the stars
Like Orion's constellation ♪
♪ I'll reach my destination
We'll make it, uh ♪
♪ Now follow with me
As this world rotates ♪
♪ They tried to take me out the game
I had to plan my escape ♪
♪ Keep focused, be humble
Stay away from the fake ♪
♪ And keep shining, keep shining
What? ♪
♪ Represent this to the fullest, y'all ♪
♪ Go, go, go ♪
♪ I represent this to the fullest ♪
♪ I represent this to the fullest, y'all ♪
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪