Tess.
Your air mattress is deflating again.
Okay.
Have you seen my other shoe?
It's hiding from you.
Wants you to come back to bed.
As tempting as that sounds,
I have to go somewhere where
there's air conditioning before I melt.
You know, we can solve this really easily
if we just moved in together.
It's been six months, Tess.
I'm ready for a bigger commitment.
Rodney, you can't even find
time to name your goldfish.
Found it. All right. One more
kiss for the road. Come on.
Get over here!
No...
I can't!
I hato go. No, look,
I'm letting you go.
Look, this is me letting you go.
Come here.
Oh, my God.
What?
Morning breath!
Ohh!
That's your cue.
Yeah.
Why don't you put it in
the same spot every time?
Got it.
That is for...
Job.
Job interview.
Holy shit. I can do this.
Okay, help me up. Help me up.
♪ It's a hard time
living on the wrong side ♪
♪ Walking on a thin line
Thumbing for a long ride ♪
♪ Anywhere would be fine
long as it ain't too shy ♪
♪ Anything is so fine
Look at what you got ♪
♪ But it's a washout
when you really find out ♪
♪ Thought you got
the good stuff ♪
♪ But you got the potty mouth ♪
♪ Everybody knows now
every little know-how ♪
♪ 'Cause she's got you so down
Looking for a spot ♪
♪ Now it's in my hands
Now it's in my head ♪
Oh! Hey, little man. Sorry about that.
It's no trouble.
But I do need an update
about the rent.
We need one of those three
back-payments pronto.
One more week, I promise.
Please... lock the door.
Oh!
Sorry about that.
Thanks, Charlie.
And I don't know if a week
is going to cut it.
Mom was using all sorts
of colorful language
this morning to describe you,
and none of it was good.
Five days, then. I'm on my
way to a job interview now.
Even if you get a job, you
probably won't get your paycheck
until two weeks from now.
Good point.
We'll figure it out.
I'll talk to her.
It'd be a shame to lose you.
Yes. Say that, plus other
nice things about me.
I don't care if they're lies.
Just make 'em nice.
Very odd that you're always
working in that little bunker.
Good luck!
Thank you!
Open, door.
Oh, got to get you fixed.
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Phil brought in steak fajitas
for casual Friday,
so I wanted to get in there
before the interns ravaged them.
They smell delicious.
I'm Rodney.
Susan.
So, according to this résumé,
the longest job you've held
is six weeks.
Well, technically
it was nine weeks,
but they were two-day weeks
for, like, five hours a day.
And the one before that?
A week?
It was a 60-hour week.
Look, before we get into...
office politics,
can we talk...
salary
or s... I don't think
we're there yet.
No, no. I don't mean
to just zoom into that,
but, you know, obviously
I was thinking 60. Thou?
Thou?
..sand.
Sand.
Like, thousand?
Like, thousand.
No, I'm a reasonable guy. I'm
willing to negotiate by a few.
"A few"?
Few. I don't
want to undersell myself.
Wait.
Did Danny set you up for this?
Who's Danny?
You don't have a college degree,
and you don't have any experience,
and this is an assistant position.
I was shocked that you guys
called me in, too, a little bit.
I mean, an "assistant CEO"
sounds really important.
Assistant to the CEO. "To."
No, no, I'm pretty sure the guy on
the phone said "assistant CEO."
Okay, that would be my current
assistant, right there.
Oh. We got eye contact.
Just ignore him. Hmm?
Look at me. Don't look back Don't look...
You need somethin'?
Hello?
Just look at me. Don't look back.
Okay.
If we stay still long
enough, he will go away.
Can you hear me?
Susan?
Susan!
Susan, can you hear me?
Every day.
Susan!
Harry, don't you have
work to do?
No.
What else would be the point
of casual Fridays?
Fuck this job.
Is that who
I'm competing against?
Essentially.
I am...
liking my chances.
Well, I don't intend on replacing
one idiot with another.
Right, right.
Oh, Jesus, he's back.
Hey, I spilled coffee
on the copier.
It's busted.
That's on me.
Is now a good time
to talk salary, or...
Do you have any
bartending experience?
Personally, I have a lot more
bar-attending experience.
Oh, come on.
That was funny.
Okay, let's try this again.
How do you make a, uh, mojito?
Tequi... Gin.
Rum.
And... other stuff.
I'm more of
a whiskey fan myself.
All right, so, uh, how do
you make a whiskey sour?
Whiskey, whiskey, and a jealous ex-lover.
Am I right?
'Cause it's sour?
Okay, I'm going to get going.
I got a, uh, massage
in 15 minutes.
It's one of those...
you know.
Ugh. That kind where they walk
on your back with bare feet?
I'll be in touch.
Hey, hey!
Hey.
How'd that one go?
Did you get it?
Practically gave it
to me on the spot.
What?
Congratulations!
I am so proud of you!
Oh, it wasn't anything.
Oh, it's so good!
I'm so impressed!
So, what's... what's this?
Are we celebrating?
Oh, it's just a little
this and that.
Here.
Oh, yeah.
Cheers.
Oh, I can get you...
a glass.
Oh, God, that's good.
Slow down, slow down.
It's really good.
There you go.
All right, put the money
in the bag!
Oh, shit. Don't shoot.
Yeah, hurry up, or I'll
blow your brains out! No.
Look, do as I say,
and no one gets hu...
Holy shit, you're huge.
Billy Coburn?
Is that you?
No. Just step
the hell back.
Hell, hell, hell.
I'd recognize
that voice anywhere.
This boy used to be
the best soprano
St. Matt's choir
ever had.
Till he hit puberty,
and then down he went.
Now he's with the tenors.
Damn it, June.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry. Mrs. Fleming.
I'm sorry.
That's better.
Your poor mother
would be puking in her grave
if she knew what you were up to.
Explain yourself.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Fleming.
It's just, you know Claudia?
She's pregnant again,
and it's twins this time.
Aren't you the stud.
Thank you.
But it's just,
how am I supposed to feed
my entire family on a
kindergarten teacher's salary?
You know? And then my dad's
disability ran out...
This is not the way, Billy.
I know.
Damn straight you know.
Okay, now, you just get
your kiester home.
You're... You're not
gonna call the...
No, Chad's not going to call the cops.
Are you, Chad?
Yes, the hell I am.
Let's try that again.
You're not going to
call the cops on this
downtrodden, very loyal
husband and father.
Chad?
No.
Louder.
Thank you.
Don't you ever let me hear
that you're involved in
this sort of shit again, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
'Cause if I do,
my hand is going to go
so far up your ass,
I'm going to be able to
pull out your teeth
one by one.
Got it?
Yes, ma'am.
All right. Now get.
You know I could've
taken him, right?
You can get the next one.
Good morning, my working man.
You'd better get up and get going.
You're going to be late.
Late for what?
Uh, your new job.
Oh. Right.
Yeah, yeah.
Late on my first day?
That'd be bad.
Listen...
I, uh, I got to get going.
I'm going to be late.
You good?
Yeah.
Okay. Lock the door
on your way out.
Yeah.
Hey, neighbor.
How you been?
It's great to see you
out and about this morning.
Listen, I never got
your response back
regarding reinstating
neighborhood watch.
I sent a few letters out
but never heard back. Oh.
It probably got lost in the mail.
It doesn't matter.
I got another form for you.
Right. Uh,
I'll file that.
Fantastic.
Oh, and I couldn't help
but notice your yard.
I got to be honest, June,
it's seen better days...
Even months.
Is that all, Woody?
I mean, curb appeal
is important, you know?
And we don't want
the property values
in this neighborhood going down.
I mean, look,
the-the bushes
out there in front,
they're growing so tall.
Those should just be trimmed.
Uh-huh.
So that, you know, you want
people to see your house.
Like right over here,
this is all so dry.
Used to be all lilies, and now
it looks like Afghanistan.
And the geraniums are...
desperately trying
to stay alive.
And, I don't know,
my heart just breaks for 'em.
Your heart breaks for them?
And...
your bougainvilleas on this wall are dead.
That needs to be...
What is the matter with you? Do
you have Asperger's or some shit?
I mean, can you not read
the writing on my face?
Get the fuck away from me.
You don't care about me,
I don't care about you,
so you have a great day,
and I won't.
Well, I hope...
Thanks for the paper.
I hope you do have a great day.
And, you know,
remember, if you see
something, say something.
Woody.
I see something.
I see a jackass.
You don't have to be
such a twat, June.
You're a twat.
A delight, as always, Woody.
Jun you've reached the Flemings,
Jim and June,
and we're not here right now.
Leave a message.
We'll get back to ya.
Not a long one though.
Bye.
Mom, are you there
and just not picking up?
Damn straight.
Mom, I'm...
I'm worried about you.
You haven't returned
my call in... in weeks,
and I have no idea
what's going on.
Call me, okay?
I love you.
Hey, dude.
Either buy something or get out.
I'll take a regular
cup of coffee.
Our medium is a grande.
Did you want to do a grande?
That's fine.
Uh, what else?
That's it.
Uh, we have a $10 minimum here.
The free Wi-Fi.
That doesn't make sense. I'll
have a brownie. Good choice.
Oh, you made it. 12.50.
12.50?
Mm-hmm.
For a medium cup of coffee
and a brownie? Exactly.
That one got declined.
Hmm.
Let's try this one.
Also declined.
Third time's a charm.
No.
This is fun.
We could do this all day.
Can you guys taper this off?
I got to teach a spin class
down the street.
You need to wait your turn, sir.
And are we done here,
or you got anything else?
How about a...
free refill?
You didn't pay for that.
Fuck you.
Hey, bud, you forgot your laptop.
Hey, you forgot your laptop!
You forgot your computer!
Fuck you... I don't even care. I'm
going to steal that computer.
How's the bread?
Mm. Good. You want?
No. I had a big breakfast.
Then why invite me to lunch?
Well, because there's a few
things we have to talk about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Wait, wait.
Let me guess.
You're worried about me.
Well, yes.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, you think I'm not taking care
of myself since your dad died.
Am I right?
And the house, it's in a
complete disarray... Oh, Ollie.
Your dad was the neat freak.
To tell you the truth,
he was a little OCD.
I'm, uh, more, uh, CGS.
"Could give a shit."
I am sorry I have not been over
as much as I used to,
but I am putting in 60 hours
a week in the hospital.
It's too much, Ollie.
Take care of yourself, huh? I
mean, even God took a day off.
God didn't have you as a mother.
Just let someone help you.
I'll think about it.
Okay? Promise.
Son of a...
I feel like I'm just
floating by, you know?
One day I want to do this.
Next day it's something else.
I guess I just need
some guidance.
Go with your gut.
Right now, all my gut's
saying is "feed me."
Maybe you should get
a job at a restaurant.
So, what do you want to do
when you grow up?
Eh, in this economy,
hard to say right now.
Got to see how it plays out.
That makes sense.
With that being said, I ran
the numbers with my mom,
and we can't swing it, Rodney.
It's time to move out, ASAP.
I appreciate you
going to bat for me.
No problem.
By the way, you need
a new carburetor.
May have to downgrade
to Rollerblades.
Hello.
Tessie?
Shh! Tess?
Your new roommate's here.
♪ Your roommate is here ♪
♪ Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
Where is my Tessie? ♪
Tess?
Jeez, Rodney, what... what
the hell are you doing?
To what do I owe this...
pleasure?
What's going on? Why-Why is
your stuff here? What...
I thought me and this little guy
could come over for a talk.
Maybe a fresh start.
Is the pizza already here? Oh, man,
you are one fast delivery guy.
Wait. Where's... Where's the pizza?
Who's this guy?
Rodney... No! Eh,
eh, eh, eh-eh, eh!
Who the hell are you?
Who the hell are you?!
I'm Keith.
I'm sorry, but...
is this some sort of
a sick joke?
Just shut up!
God, you give me
such a headache sometimes!
So you're really not the pizza guy?
Look.
Maybe this is
some sort of a weird...
speed bump in our relationship
that soon will pass.
No, Rodney. It's not
a speed bump.
Think of it as a
permanent road closure.
What?
Sorry, dude.
How long has this... fling
been going on?
Five months. We have only
been dating for six months.
What do you want me to say?
Look, Rodney, I...
I can't keep taking care of you.
I need to be provided for,
and Keith is responsible.
He's a pilot.
She breached the cockpit.
He literally takes care of
hundreds of lives
every single day,
and you can't even take care
of an unnamed goldfish.
Sushi.
What?
The fish.
I named him Sushi.
You said if I named him, you'd
think about moving in with me.
I wasn't serious.
You're breaking my heart.
I'm sorry.
No. No.
Whoa! Sushi!
Sushi needs water!
Where-Where is he?
I don't know.
Sushi! Where'd he go?
Oh, God. I don't even know
how that happened.
How what happened?
Can I have a moment
alone here, please?
Take all the time
you need, brother.
I appreciate that, Keith.
Right.
How can we just let him
stay in the bathroom like that?
What if he tries
to kill himself?
He's going through
a rough time right now.
It's a fish!
His fish.
No.
I'll do it.
I'll check on him.
Give it, like, a minute. If I
hear weird sounds...
Oh!
Shit!
Arrrr!
Uhh!
Mm-hmm.
Okay, buddy.
I'm parched too.
You too, baby.
Happy.
What in the...
devil stick is this?
Where the hell does this go?
Jimmy Buffett.
Hey. You know, it's rude to just
snatch something away from somebody,
especially
while they're napping.
Rude?
Right.
This from that punk
who outright stole
my electricity.
You know, you'd better get your ass
out of here before I get my gun.
You have a gun?
Uh-huh. Three.
Lola... Ooh,
she's my favorite.
Small problem.
My car appears to be broken.
Then I tried calling for help
before my phone died,
which prompted me to borrow...
Steal.
Steal your power just long
enough to charge my phone.
You entitled punk!
You know, we all got problems, kid.
Take 'em someplace else.
I'm sick of looking at
that old hunk of shit.
I could say the same thing
about you.
Oh.
Oh, that is good.
That is so good.
I'm calling the cops.
Okay, that's really unnecessary. I'm
sure we could work something out.
Don't test me. Not testing.
Not testing.
Is everything okay, June?
Fuck off, Woody.
Yow!
Okay, look, look, look, look.
I have a proposition.
You have grass.
Everybody's grass needs cut.
So how about in exchange
for your, uh,
borrowed power, I...
Stolen power,
I'd be more than willing
to lend my labor.
Okay.
Okay, but you've got to do
some other shit too.
Speaking of shit...
like clean my toilets.
I don't do toilets.
And I don't do you.
Look, Liz?
Jer. Is that you?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
You win.
Jerry, hold on.
Say that again.
You win.
Jer, I'll call you back.
Hey.
Don't cut your toes off,
asshole.
♪ Burst in the morning, baby
Sing out that tune ♪
♪ Power into burning
in the bright afternoon ♪
♪ Sugar and caffeine's
gonna fuel my day ♪
♪ Till the evening breeze
will seal me away ♪
♪ I can't help but wonder
what I'm doing ♪
♪ I can't seem to
figure it out ♪
♪ I'm heading down
the road to ruin, baby ♪
♪ Am I just fooling myself? ♪
Ahem.
Hello.
Hmph.
When am I allowed to take my
state-mandated 30-minute break?
God, I hate you.
Mm.
Tuna salad sandwich.
Yummy.
Is this tuna of the can?
No. I caught it.
Impressive.
Is there... anything else
on the menu?
Nada.
Well, I don't really let
processed bullshit into my body.
Watch your goddamn mouth.
You watch your goddamn mouth.
Hmm.
This smells like a dead corpse.
You really are an ungrateful
little bitch, aren't you?
Well, you're
an old-ass bitch.
I'll just eat the chips.
Five-letter word for "spoon."
Ladle?
That's it, bud.
Wrap it up.
That's enough for today.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Get that.
That.
Thanks for the laughs.
Have a nice life, huh?
You too.
I'm Rodney, by the way.
Really?
I thought your name was Asshole.
I'm June.
Dumpster's that way.
Okay.
Uh...
Set the winners aside
just for you.
Now, if you win, I want my cut.
Fair enough.
All set.
Thanks, Chad.
Have a good night, June.
Yep. I'll see you
tomorrow.
Get home safe.
Why are you still here?
I think I, uh, left my
wallet inside your house.
Thought you didn't have
any money.
Oh, I don't.
So why do you need
an empty wallet?
I guess I don't.
Guess I'll just hit
the sidewalk.
You can have, um,
three of these.
Domestic or import?
Don't push it.
She'd been
cheating on me for months.
Months.
And if that wasn't bad enough,
then Sushi died.
What, your dog?
No, my goldfish.
May she float in peace.
Hey!
Sushi and I had
a swimmingly good time together.
So, would you take her back?
Sushi?
No, the bitch.
Aren't we not supposed to call
women bitches anymore?
Like, feminism
or something like...
No. You are not supposed
to call women bitches.
But me?
A cunt is a cunt.
Hoo!
You didn't answer my question.
You asked a question?
I did. Would...
Would you take her back?
Yep.
Mm-hmm.
No.
Maybe.
That's a yes.
She was just really, really,
really... hot.
Men are so stupid.
What about your husband?
Dead.
Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
Uh-huh.
When did he pass?
God!
I hate that word.
"Pass." I mean,
like death is as easy
as-as-as passing gas.
I mean, stupid assholes,
you know?
They... They...
They use another word
to make it seem like it's okay,
but, you know, he's dead.
D-E-A-D.
Dead.
So, what's your story, huh?
I grew up in
the foster care system.
Hmm. That must've
been tough.
Eh.
Ah.
So,
you want to watch
an Antiques Roadshow?
I'm gonna need
another one of those.
Me too.
Come on. Now, just like
I showed you. Okay.
Uhh.
I'll need an initial here, here,
and sign and date here.
Still the 28th, right?
Yes.
Great. Well, let me know
if anything changes.
Good seeing you.
You too.
Um, hi?
Hello there,
uh, strange person.
Hey there.
What are you doing?
Just, uh, putting some
finishing touches on my place.
This is your place?
Well, it's, uh,
more of an investment property.
It's a foreclosure.
Probably gonna flip it.
I'm Rodney, by the way.
Hey, where are you going?
Who's this?
That's the help.
Really?
I'm gonna take this personally
here in a second. A word?
Unh.
So nice to see you, sweetheart.
I love these sweatpants.
What is this, the 20th day in a row?
Mom, these are all full.
Have you even taken
a single pill?
Mom, this is your life.
If you read, you will
see that it says,
"Do not mix the pills
with the booze."
So I'm just following
directions.
Oh, then lay off the booze, Mom.
It's simple.
Honey,
if I cold-turkey quit,
that will kill me.
Just let me have
whatever I need, okay,
to enjoy the rest of my life.
God. That's crazy.
Here I was actually thinking
you were listening
to what I was saying
at lunch the other day.
I was listening.
You said, "Get somebody
to help out around the house,"
so I did, look.
Helping himself to lunch!
Is he actually homeless?
Hey! Zip it. You
are homeless, remember?
Is there any garlic sauce?
That is for her, not you.
This is actually pretty good.
Out.
This is your life.
Hello again.
Please don't yell at me.
I think we got off
on the wrong foot here.
Look, I'm not here
to steal your mom's shit
or take advantage of her
or anything like that, okay?
I promise. Can you
do me a small favor?
Sure.
Do you think you can try
and get my mom to take her meds?
Yeah, no problem.
Seems easy, but it's not.
Are you saying that
June is stubborn? Gasp.
Trick her like a dog.
Seriously?
Doctor's orders.
Hey, Olivia.
Hey, Floyd.
See you in Pilates.
Oh, yeah.
How many dead cats are in here?
You think darkness is your ally,
but you merely adopted it.
I was born into it.
Molded by it.
I didn't see the light
until I was already a man.
But by then it was nothing
to me but blinding!
How long have you been
standing there?
You're a weird little man.
There's a ton
of cool shit in here.
Really? Who the hell
do you think put it here?
Check this out.
This is how Jim and I met.
Really?
I see this handsome guy ride by.
I whistled.
He stopped.
I got on.
And never got off.
♪ Supper's almost ready ♪
♪ Supper's
almost ready ♪
♪ Rodney ♪
♪ Supper made that Rodney ♪
♪ Rodney made the supper ♪
Well, supper's almost ready.
Hmm.
What's on the menu?
Doesn't smell half bad.
Mmm!
Well, the old bitch can be
nice when she wants to be.
I like to call it...
Rodney Surprise.
Ah.
It's pasta with...
Uh, uh, uh!
Don't spoil the surprise.
So, why don't you invite
a friend for dinner?
I mean, that is
if you've got any.
Yeah, sure.
I think I know someone
who can make it.
♪ Supper's almost ready ♪
Oh, June, drink up!
You are in the liquor penalty box
right now. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ew! That did not
look good.
Okay. Boy, we are running
low on the old hooch.
Oh, can't you pussies keep up?
What does that mean?
That means we're her friends.
Uh-huh.
Okay, I think I saw a bottle
of something in the garage.
All right.
Be right back.
You'd better.
So,
shark attack, shark attack,
shark attack, shark attack!
Shark attack!
Booze attack.
Booze attack. Booze attack. Oh, yummy,
yummy, yummy. Look at what he brought.
Look at what he brought. Here.
Arm-wrestle me. Arm-wrestle me.
Come on. Ready?
Here we go.
Oh, no!
Got ya.
He's a strong man.
Okay.
All right, guys.
Who's up? Your turn.
It's all yours, big guy.
Your turn, buddy.
All right, but I can't
drink much more juice.
It gives me the runs.
Oh, God.
Well, shit.
I think, then,
it's time for you
to have your first beer.
All right, I came
as fast as I could.
Oh! With burritos!
Okay!
'Cause I made dinner,
so, not sure why we have that.
Yummy, yummy,
yummy, yummy. Yum!
What's that?
Uh, special occasion.
Company. Company.
About that dinner?
Let me get some plates.
Yeah, and we're all going to eat.
You too, Charlie, okay?
You like burritos?
Yep.
Mmm. Me too.
How's that look to you, huh?
Here we go.
So you met my mom when you
were stealing her power?
Borrowing.
Stealing.
Stealing. Yeah.
Who does that?
You would've done
the exact same thing.
No.
No, you wouldn't have.
So you actually like
living here.
Yeah, I do.
I mean, there's this...
There's, like, one thing
that's... mm.
What?
Sometimes June makes me
rub her feet.
Ew! What?
No, I'm kidding.
That only happened, like, twice.
You are a freak.
So you got a man?
Whoa. Don't even.
What?
Well, the... the first
question you asked me...
The very first question...
Isn't about my work,
which I do way too much of,
or-or about my hobbies
or my interests or...
No.
No, the very first question
you ask me is if I've got a man?
So you're single.
Go to hell.
I'm going through a, uh,
pretty rough breakup myself.
She dumped me,
but I guess you could say
I returned the favor.
I'm s... What?
What are you laughing at?
You don't want to know.
Okay, now you have to tell me.
You can't judge me.
I make no promises.
I upper-decked her.
You what?
You know the top part
of the toilet
where there's the lid, and then you
got the clean water up there, right?
Mm-hmm.
So...
Yeah, I don't like
where this is going.
Yeah, so I went
number two in there,
and then I sealed that bad boy
up like an Egyptian coffin.
How old are you?
No.
I misread that.
Mm-hmm.
Look at this.
Go.
Whoa-ho-ho-ho!
Brought you a little
movie snack.
You son of a bitch.
Ollie put you up to this?
I plead the Fifth.
Mm.
I'll eat the banana,
but that's it.
You're a good kid.
Hello.
All right, I would like
a pack of reds,
a fifth of gin,
and six scratchers, but please
pull every other scratch off.
Hello.
Yeah.
June said there was
some asshole coming by
to get some stuff for her.
Okay. I will take
a pack of reds,
a fifth of gin,
and six scratch-offs,
but please pull
every other scratcher.
Hey, how is she, by the way?
She's fine.
Yeah, she hasn't been
coming in here lately,
and she didn't look too good
the last time...
You know what? Never mind.
I'm rambling.
Uh, just costs $10, for June.
Tell her I said hi.
Will do.
Good.
♪ Her father was
a concrete man ♪
♪ And her mother
was a painter ♪
♪ Born with good hands ♪
♪ She was born a creator ♪
Aren't you, uh, hungry?
No, I guess not.
Huh. Well,
that's a first.
Well, there's more for me.
What are those pills for?
My business, Rodney.
I'm serious.
So am I.
Mind your business.
It's just, uh,
Olivia seemed pretty intent
on getting you to take them.
Now there goes my appetite.
And earlier today
at the convenience store...
What'd he tell you? He just
asked if you were okay.
What are you hiding?
You know what?
I'm going for a drive.
You're not allowed to drive.
Then you go for a goddamn drive.
I don't have a car.
Take mine.
How sick are you?
I'm fine.
Don't lie to me.
"Don't lie to me"?
What are you, my father?
Huh? What do you care?
Because I care about you,
you idiot.
Don't talk to me like that,
you son of a bitch.
Who the hell do
you think you are?
Look, um,
I'm just worried, that's all.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Right, you're worried. Yeah, I
know what you're worried about.
You're worried about
losing your free ride.
You know what?
This is not working for me.
Uh-uh. I, uh...
I think you have
overstayed your welcome.
Pack up your stuff.
Tonight.
I want you to pack up
your stuff and go.
You don't mean that, June.
Oh, don't I?
Don't I?
You know, I, uh,
I gave you a roof,
I gave you a place to stay,
I put food in your stomach,
but that is not enough for you.
No, no. You just
have to keep prying,
don't you, kid? Huh?
Look, if I want to...
if I want to kill myself,
that is my business.
June, you're blowing this
way out of proportion!
And you get out of here.
Go on. Go on. Get out.
Leave. Get out. Yeah? No
wonder you're all alone.
Fuck you. Fuck you.
Stop, stop, please.
You're gonna talk shit, huh?
Hey! Hey! Stop!
You're gonna talk such shit stuff?
Man up. I'm sorry!
Man up, huh? Pussy! Pussy!
I am not gonna fight you!
June! June! Get the fuck
out of my house! Get out!
And you're gonna die
in this house all Al...
Well, thanks for coming, Rudy.
We need someone who could
start right this second.
We are clogged with work.
It's actually Rodney.
Huh?
Ah, that's right.
I apologize.
Well, we've been having
a shitter of a day.
So, do you have
any plumbing experience?
We need someone who can lay
a lot of pipe, and quick!
Hey! Hey!
This work is no laughing matter.
You'd be amazed at some of
the house calls we get.
The things some kids do
to toilets!
You ever heard
of an upper-deck?
Excuse me.
Talk to me.
Well, just do it!
You'll be saving someone's day,
and frankly, we can use the cash.
You'll be a hero. Little Tommy
will forever salute you.
So, back to you.
You said you guys need the cash?
Yeah, but don't worry.
I'll make sure you get paid.
Really?
Of course.
When a poor person's toilet
gets clogged,
they grab a plunger
and fix it themselves.
When a rich person's toilet
gets clogged,
they grab a Valium, Xanax,
Klonopin, Ativan, whatever,
and they call us.
They're willing to pay us
hundreds of dollars
to fish their shit
out of the toilet.
I'm sorry. I thought you were
making a joke about the shit.
Kid, don't curse.
If you can't take
this job interview seriously,
you probably don't belong here.
Well, I appreciate
the consideration.
Yeah. You didn't get
the job, idiot.
That's not my résumé.
It's not?
Oh, this guy's good though.
Rudy, we are clogged with work.
Okay.
So he just up and left,
just like that?
Just like that.
It was like...
Flash Man.
Right, and you're sure
you had nothing to do with it.
Absolutely.
Nothing.
Mom.
He was an asshole.
So are you.
Good point.
Are you going to apologize?
What for?
And besides, I don't
even know where he is.
You call him.
I don't have his number.
What? Seriously?
He lived here.
Why would I have
a need to call him?
He really didn't have any money.
I got this.
Check and mate, mate.
I call a re-do. I'm gonna
quit while I'm still on top.
Come on!
Fine.
Yes!
You all right?
What? I'm fine.
You should go talk to her.
You keep saying that.
Because, duh, it's true.
How about this?
If I win, then you have to.
You've been playing me
this whole time. Yes.
No, I mean, you've been waiting for this
moment, and now you're gonna whoop my ass.
Also yes.
Well, what if I quit?
Then you'll have lost
because you resigned.
You're going to be
president someday.
Nah, that's for chumps.
Party on the top floor.
Slap it, boss.
Little slap to make her happy.
What?
Weirdo.
Hey. Um,
so I know this is
kind of awkward,
and you probably didn't
expect to see me again
after the whole incident,
but, um,
is there any chance
I could crash,
just for tonight?
You are more than welcome
here, buddy.
It's great to see you.
You too.
You too, my man.
Like I said,
it'll just be one or two...
One or two or a few.
Yeah.
Let's make it...
Wanna call it three or 14?
Just a handshake on five?
Can you just promise me,
like, a week?
Five...
Do you have pizza?
Well...
Fuck it.
Did you take your pills?
Yes.
I promise.
How are you feeling?
Like shit.
I could use a drink.
I'm sorry I haven't been around
as much as I should be.
You work your ass off.
And you love it.
And I love that you love it.
Never say you're sorry.
You take good care of me, hon.
Better than anybody
could ever do.
It's not your fault you got a...
stubborn old bitch of a mom.
I am so proud of you.
And your dad... oh...
He would have been
real proud of you too.
You did good, baby.
You did good.
Mom? Are you okay?
And your actions
put me in a slightly
more hurtful position.
You're basically the reason
I'm in this entire situation.
Do you know what
your problem is?
I'm just lost.
You escalate things.
You need to
un-escalate things.
You need to de-escalate.
You're going up.
You need to go down
and un-escalate it
instead of escalate.
That's your problem.
Okay.
Excuse me.
But I see what you're saying.
Hello, people I don't know.
Tough crowd.
Is this some sort of a...
party, or what are...
Either way, I'm gonna guess my invitation
was probably lost in the mail.
And I don't really have a mailbox right
now, you know what I'm sayin'? Hey!
What, did somebody die
or something?
Um, I just personally
wanted to thank all of you
for being here today.
I know you all hold a special
place in my mom's heart.
I'd like to say a few words myself.
Uh, uh, uh, uh.
Mm.
Allow me.
Okay.
You've come to fight
as free men,
and free men you are.
But what will you do
with that freedom?
Will you run?
Or will you fight?
Is that from Braveheart?
June fought.
June was a fighter.
I didn't know her...
that well,
but I knew that much.
She took a chance on me
when no one else wouldn't.
"Would."
Thank you.
I guess now's
the part in the speech
where people say all those
stupid cliché things like,
"She lived life her way"
or "danced to the beat
of her own drum,"
but I think
June would hate that.
She would.
I had the, uh,
worst day of my life.
Everything that could
go wrong did go wrong,
and then I met June,
and she rubbed it in my face.
But then she gave me
a place to stay,
and she gave me tuna sandwiches,
and they were fuckin' terrible.
But she made me, me again.
I, uh, guess that's
all I have to say.
Shit, fuckin' allergies or...
Who wants to get laid?
Wake up! Yo! Hey, wake up!
I decided to have a funeral
for my old self.
It passed.
And me?
I am headed to Hawaii.
How old are you?
Oh, I got you good!
You monster.
Come on, let's get you up.
Come on. Get up!
Let's help her.
After we get me up.
Ooh! Yeah.
Yep.
I'm up, I'm up, I'm up.
All right, well, hey,
I just wanted to let you know,
all that stuff that I said
over there, I was just joking.
I didn't mean any of that,
so don't get weird.
Well, some people grow up,
and others, like you, yeah...
born a little bitch,
always a little bitch.
So, Hawaii?
Mm-hmm.
The ocean air
will be good for her.
Uh,
speaking of it,
uh, want to give me
a minute, a little tick
with Rodney?
Yeah.
Oh, hey, Rodney?
Yeah?
Thank you for taking care
of her when I couldn't.
So, listen.
Against my better judgment
and the advice of my lawyer,
I decided I wanted to
leave you a little something.
You shouldn't have.
What is it?
Now I really know
I shouldn't have.
Corner convenience store?
I actually own it.
Hmm?
And I'm leaving it to you.
What?
Mm-hmm.
Why would you do that?
'Cause I don't scare you.
And, uh, you make me laugh.
I appreciate the faith.
I almost forgot.
Meet me in the garage.
The garage?
Easy. This is very
scary, Rodney.
Easy.
Stop.
Here?
Keep 'em closed.
Okay. All right.
Don't cheat.
I'm not gonna cheat.
Could ruin the whole thing if you cheat.
I'm not a cheater.
All right.
I'm many things,
but I'm not a cheater.
And... t...
Hang on.
Can I open 'em?
No.
♪ Ta-da! ♪
Can I open?
Yes.
New set of wheels to get around.
Rodney, I don't know...
I don't know what to say.
Ah, ya...
jerk!
I love you too.
Yeah.
Ah!
You might need this.
Oh, yeah.
Probably not, but...
It's not empty.
"Noice!"
Back pay.
Ah.
Come here.
Come here. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
You like it. Love it.
Come on. No. No.
Yeah?
Come on.
Are you crying?
No!
Oh, I...
couldn't see.
I'm, you know, remembering.
You know, they say
you never forget.
Let's hope to hell
they're right.
Pray for me.
June.
Woody.
Let me just cut to the chase.
I heard that you were leaving,
and I want to wish you farewell.
It was truly
a pleasure knowing you.
You don't mean any of that.
No, I do not.
You know, Woody,
you... weren't
the worst neighbor.
I think in a way,
I'm gonna miss you.
Wow.
Just kiddin'.
Take care, Woody.
Wh-Where's your helmet?
Twat!
♪ I'm gonna find
some other place ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Find some other way ♪
♪ I miss you ♪
All right, guys, I'm out.
Bro, you just got here, man.
Hey, that's what happens
when you're the boss.
And, Chad, make sure none
of that candy's expired.
Yes, boss.
And that is not an excuse for you to just
eat the candy and then say it was expired.
You got me?
I got you.
Same goes to you, Billy.
Yes, sir.
Do these chips taste
expired to you?
Do you guys have, like,
flavored condoms here?
I'm going on a date tonight.
What?
♪ Oh, it's a hell of a thing ♪
♪ What did you expect
from me? ♪
♪ Darling, I'm a hypocrite ♪
♪ And maybe a liar ♪
♪ Oh, but maybe you like it ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Well, it ain't a secret
Everybody can tell ♪
♪ I'm a hot-headed fool
Should be with anyone else ♪
♪ But I'm Four Roses in, and I don't
like the way he looks at you ♪
♪ But your kiss is like
a razor blade ♪
♪ It's like salt
on an open wound ♪
♪ Oh, we tell each other
we can change ♪
♪ Or we'll kill each other
trying to ♪
♪ Oh, its a hell of a thing ♪
♪ What did you expect
from me? ♪
♪ Darling, I'm a hypocrite ♪
♪ And maybe a liar ♪
♪ Oh, but maybe you like it ♪
♪ Oh, your tears
are like a hurricane ♪
♪ First you pull me close
and go away ♪
♪ Then you smile and tell me
I should stay ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the only one
that can love ♪
♪ That kind of crazy ♪
♪ Oh, its a hell of a thing ♪
♪ What did you expect
from me? ♪
♪ Darling, I'm a hypocrite ♪
♪ And maybe a liar ♪
♪ Oh, its a hell of a thing ♪
♪ Makes me weak
in the knees ♪
♪ Baby, I'm a hypocrite ♪
♪ And I know
that you're lying ♪
♪ Oh, but maybe you like it ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Maybe we like it ♪
♪ Burst in the morning, baby
Sing out that tune ♪
♪ Power into burning
in the bright afternoon ♪
♪ Sugar and caffeine's
gonna fuel my day ♪
♪ Till the evening breeze
will seal me away ♪
♪ I can't help but wonder
what I'm doing ♪
♪ I can't seem to
figure it out ♪
♪ I'm heading down
the road to ruin, baby ♪
♪ Am I just fooling myself? ♪
♪ You gotta check your brain
You gotta check your brain ♪
♪ Yo, yo, son,
you gotta check your brain ♪
♪ Check your brain
You gotta check your brain ♪
♪ You're insane
♪ Walkin' down the street
with a mic in your hand ♪
♪ A wack DJ Not a playa, not a man ♪
♪ You keep rappin'
like the Treacherous Three ♪
♪ But without us,
where would you be? ♪