(film reels ticking)
(alarm buzzing)
(door clanking)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
^.^.^.^.COLORED by.^.^.^.^
® Sud_Arun collections ®
A member of Psagmeno.com
(indistinct chatter)
Come on, step up.
Ladies,
right up to the door.
Let's see those
pretty mugs.
(instrumental music)
♪ Nineteen hundred
and sixty-three ♪
♪ They came inside
for armed robbery ♪
♪ Now one night late
I made my break ♪
One.
♪ I say it's
too late to quit ♪
♪ I can't stand oh no ♪
♪ In the old barn ♪
♪ Let me tell you
what I want now ♪
♪ I want love
and affection ♪
♪ Not the house
of correction ♪
♪ I want love ♪
Two.
♪ Not the house ♪
♪ Of correction ♪
♪ I can't stand oh no ♪
♪ In the old barn ♪
♪ I gotta say it
one more time ♪
♪ I want love
and affection ♪
Three.
♪ House of correction ♪
♪ I want love
and affection ♪
♪ Not the house
of correction ♪
♪ I can't stand oh no ♪
♪ in the old barn ♪
Four.
♪ I want to go home ♪
(music continues)
(alarm buzzing)
♪ Let me say
what I want ♪
♪ I want love
and affection ♪
♪ Not the house
of correction ♪
♪ I want love
and affection.. ♪
Five.
♪ I can't stand oh no ♪
♪ In the old barn ♪
♪ I want to go home ♪
♪ I want to go home.. ♪♪
(alarm buzzing)
(indistinct chatter on TV)
- Nicole.
- What?
How long are you gonna
frost that thing for?
I just want to make sure
that the icing is perfect
so the canvas
on which to paint...
It's a sheet cake.
Sheet cakes
are not supposed to..
Have you been
to a church bake off?
Listen, at least you can
eat this cake, okay?
I like the cake I made.
- You are a diabetic.
- And?
And it was full of sugar.
You remember
to take your pills?
- I don't think I did.
- I don't think you did either.
- No.
- Go on.
(cell phone ringing)
Hello.
Oh, no. Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Alright, thank you.
What's the matter?
That's work.
I gotta go in
early today.
- Today?
- Yeah.
But it's my birthday.
(indistinct chatter)
Alrighty.
Come on. Fork it over.
Come on.
Anderson!
You going
to your meeting?
- Oh, yeah. On my way.
- Alright. Okay.
(Carmen laughing)
- One step at a time.
- Have a good night!
(instrumental music)
(laughing)
There's two cakes
back there.
Excelente.
And you like the food?
Yeah. This is good, mom.
Well, there you go.
There you go.
- Hey, y'all.
- Hey!
I have to go.
I don't know
how you do it.
Being a part
of the brutal mass
incarceration system.
Imagine how much more
brutal it would be
if I wasn't working in it?
I know I couldn't do it.
Don't eat off his plate.
Momma,
I don't have a plate.
I'll make you a plate,
do you want a plate?
Ma, she's getting ready
to go.
Love you, sis.
Love you too.
- Love you, Junior. Bye.
- Bye.
We'll save you some cake.
Okay.
Save me a piece of both.
You gonna win
that karaoke contest.
Aahh hoo-ah hoo-aah!
Hoo-ha oh!
♪ Bh-bube bh-bube
bh-bube-e ♪♪
(knock on door)
(humming)
♪ Do re mi fa
so la ti do ♪
♪ Do re mi fa so la ti.. ♪
Stevens!
Oh, uh, you wanted
to see me, warden?
Come here, sit down.
Stevens, how would you
like the opportunity
to prove yourself?
Sir?
Listen, Stevens,
first thing tomorrow
I need you to escort
a prisoner on a death bed
visit downstate.
I appreciate it, sir,
but I don't think
that I can get away
on such short notice
I'm sorry.
I recall you saying
you were trying to get
a full time position here.
Yeah, I did.
Well, let's use this as an
opportunity to prove it.
Uh, yeah. Okay.
Yes! Excellent!
Stevens, I knew
you'd come through for me.
First thing tomorrow.
Get out of here.
See you tomorrow.
(instrumental music)
Come here
and lie beside me.
(music continues)
(door buzzing)
Anderson,
warden wants to see you.
Why? What's going on?
How the heck do I know?
You can ask him yourself.
Get up.
Uh, Anderson, there's no,
oh, easy way to say this
but your mother is dying.
Oh, man. That's too bad.
Well, she only
has a short time left
and she requested
to see you.
I don't know,
I... kinda stuck here.
Well, we sometimes
grant emergency furlough
in situations like this.
Oh, you mean like
a deathbed visit?
More like a supervised
36 hour release.
Thirty-six hours?
(instrumental music)
Nicole,
what are you doing up?
Why are you here?
Shouldn't you be at work?
I got a special detail.
I have to escort
a prisoner downstate.
I will be gone
for 36 hours.
I'm gonna be here
by myself for 36 hours?
I already laid out
all your medication.
You know, I have things
I have to do
at the library.
Okay, well, maybe you can
ask Brandy to take you.
Brandy's not gonna..
She's a terrible driver..
- I don't understand...
- Mom.
The warden says
that if I do a good job
he might get me
a permanent position
which I have been trying
to get, without any luck.
You're going
with somebody dangerous.
You putting
yourself in danger.
I mean, t... technically,
she is a prisoner, momma.
But no, and besides
she's gonna be
all chained up.
Well, what are you
doing exactly?
I am taking her
on a deathbed visit.
- A deathbed visit?
- Mm-hmm.
To see her mother.
Oh.
- Her momma's dyin'?
- Mm-hmm.
And you're
taking her down?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thirty-six hours?
- What if I die?
I could.
I don't wanna
scare you but..
(wheezes)
Momma..
- Please be careful.
- I will.
Go back to sleep, momma.
(wheezes)
(laughs)
Okay. Stay up
and write your will.
I'm not feedin'
that damn fish.
You better feed that fish.
(indistinct chatter)
- Stevens.
- Oh.
Oh, God. It's heavy.
What is she in for again?
- Armed robbery.
- Right.
(coughs)
The judge sentenced her
to a mandatory eight.
She's getting off early
on good time served.
God, she's got
a lot of priors.
Look, don't you worry
about that.
Just do your job.
She's in the program,
she's clean.
Yeah.
Yeah, she seems it.
There you go.
Do I get a weapon, sir?
Oh, yes.
You do get a weapon.
A service revolver.
- You get that.
- Oh, Taser. Wow.
- Some of this.
- Oh, pepper spray.
I have got that.
Good for you.
Is that all?
What, you want a tank,
Stevens?
It's not
the zombie apocalypse.
Right. Uh, any advice?
Oh. Yes.
Don't turn your back
on the prisoner.
Don't let the prisoner
out of your sight.
And whatever she says,
don't believe it.
Right, okay.
Thank you.
You're gonna do fine,
Stevens.
Yeah.
(instrumental music)
Right down here.
(music continues)
There we go.
Inmate, turn around.
I am CO Stevens
and I will be
your emergency
furlough escort.
Give me your hands.
You are in my custody
and you'll follow
my orders
without question.
Alright?
Whatever you say,
Officer Stevens.
To the bench.
No, no,
don't sit on the bench
just turn around
and face the wall.
Alright.
Away from the wall.
I have the authority,
at my discretion
to terminate this leave
at any time.
- Is that clear, Anderson?
- Very clear, CO Stevens.
For the next 36 hours..
...I own you.
Let me see your eyes
so I know you understand.
I just wanna go
see my mother. Hm?
Anything you say goes.
Good.
Can we go now?
No, you don't tell me
when to go.
I tell you when to go,
that's the orders thing
you follow them,
I have to give them first.
Okay?
Okay, let's go.
(knock on door)
This way.
Alright. Go.
Stop here.
Here.
(alarm buzzing)
Alright.
(instrumental music)
Alrighty. No, I got it.
Here I come.
I'm okay, I can get out.
- I... I can get that.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Wait a minute!
- Alright.
Aw, man. It's beautiful.
- Thank you!
- Alright.
(chuckles)
Hey! Hi, boy!
That lady has handcuffs!
Aw, don't be afraid,
don't be worried
there's nothing
to be worried about.
Come on.
No funny business.
Not from me.
Okay.
- Whoa! No, no.
- Okay.
What's... what's
going on here?
I... I don't, I really don't
want any trouble on my bus.
Well, there's not
gonna be any.
- Um..
- Here you go.
I see handcuffs, leg
shackles, prison uniforms..
Kinda
smells like trouble to me.
Yeah,
I'm a corrections officer
and she's in my custody.
Look, uh, Nicole Stevens
I'm the captain
of this ship, okay?
I'm the captain.
That means my only
priority is the safety
of my passengers
and of myself.
Okay, captain, but there's
nothing to be afraid of.
I'm not afraid of nothin', I just don't
like the looks of your passenger.
Oh, come on. Don't judge a
book by its cover, mister.
- What?
- I'm not, it's not...
Okay, that's it.
You're not boarding!
Oh, God.
(sighs)
Well, it's the law.
You have to let us board.
The law? On this ship
I'm the law.
We are on official New
York State business, sir.
We're on a deathbed
visit here.
- Time is of the essence.
- Who's dying?
- My mother.
- Oh, your mother?
Where does she live,
'cause I could go
pick her up
and bring her back to you.
Listen, this is no time
for jokes
this is serious business.
I have no desire
to cause trouble.
I... I... I just
wanna go see my mother.
Look, mister,
you got a mother, right?
Yes, I have a mother.
So I got a mother too.
She's asked to see me.
You gonna stop me
from seeing her?
Please, mister, please,
let me on your bus.
(sighs)
Alright, listen. You stay
on your best behavior.
You keep her locked up
the entire time...
I mean that's part
of the thing.
- Get on the bus.
- Okay.
Thank you so much.
That was so good of you.
- So, so good of you.
- Get on the bus.
- Very thoughtful.
- You know, okay. Alright.
I don't think
I can get on that step.
Like, maybe push..
That's it, Got..
Jesus Christ.
Next time I'll do
the talking, okay?
- Oh, you got it.
- But thanks.
- You did a good job.
- Yeah, okay.
Why do we have
to take this shitty bus?
'Cause the limousine
wasn't available.
Where do you wanna sit,
huh?
- Where, here?
- Yeah.
- This one's good.
- Alright.
- We'll take this one, alright?
- Yeah, that's fine.
(engine sputtering)
(chuckles)
Hot damn!
We're gonna have
a good time.
(instrumental music)
Welcome aboard,
passengers.
A few, uh,
quick announcements
and safety procedures.
This is a
no smoking ride.
Turn your
cell phones off.
Please don't move around
the cabin.
Don't bother me,
I'm the driver.
You don't want me
to be distracted.
Just general manners are
appreciated. Thank you.
That's crazy.
(cell phone ringing)
No phone calls
on the bus, ma'am.
I'll answer it.
- Hello, Nicole?
- Hi, I'm working.
- You okay?
- Honey.
Where are the
Multi-Grain Waffles?
- The frozen ones?
- Yeah.
Yeah. In the freezer,
where else, mom?
No, they're not
in the freezer
I'm looking
I... I don't see them.
You sure, they're
in the yellow box
remember, they switched
the box colors?
- It's yellow now.
- I remember that.
I remember that,
they're not in here.
No. No, no, no. There were
some right when I left.
Well, they're not
in here now, Nicole.
Now, I... I need them
to keep regular.
Well, what about
the bran cereal.
You can try that.
I don't like bran cereal,
where are the waffles!
Well, why don't you have Brandy
go and pick you up some then?
Brandy is not here.
Listen,
I had a whole plan.
I was gonna get
the waffles
I was gonna make 'em
I was gonna put syrup on 'em
and some butter, and just
have a pleasant day.
Okay, I understand
but I'm working here,
I gotta go, moms.
Love you, okay? Bye.
Who's paying
for this trip?
My understanding is that
the inmate pays for it.
So, you.
(chuckles)
That's a great rule
but I don't know
how I'm gonna do that
at 22 cents an hour.
Well, your mom
must really wanna see you.
(instrumental music)
(cell phone ringing)
Hi, Brandy.
Who the hell do you think
you are running off
and dumping moms in my lap
without even
saying a word!
Okay, well,
I had an emergency
come up at work,
so I didn't really
have a choice.
And you didn't even
have the courtesy
to pick up the telephone
and give me
a goddamn call?
I didn't wanna
wake you up.
When are you coming back?
- Sunday night.
- Sunday night?
Yeah.
So who's gonna take her
to her volunteer thing
at the library?
I guess you will
just have to take her.
You know what, Nicole?
Don't you dare ever
try to pull a stunt on me
like this again!
You hear me?
- Uh, okay.
- Ever.
Bye, Brandy.
Who's Brandy?
She is my sister.
- You got sisters?
- No, I'm an only child.
You're lucky.
(scoffs)
I wish I had a sister.
You kidding me?
Yeah.
(instrumental music)
Excuse me.
Ugh! Jesus.
- I gotta go.
- Yeah, sure.
No, no, no, no.
I gotta go.
Like, number one
or number two?
I'm just asking.
How urgent is it?
I gotta go.
I can't wait.
Why didn't you go
before we left?
I did, they served
mystery meat for breakfast
and it comes out
when it wants to.
Can I please just..
...permission
to go to the bathroom?
- Yeah. Okay.
- Please?
Well, I gotta take you.
So. Come on.
Jesus. Okay.
Alright, here I come.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much, you're
not gonna regret this.
Excuse me! Thank you so much.
Sorry. Comin' through.
- Okay. You gotta undo the cuffs.
- What?
I gotta get
the jumpsuit down.
- Just, just undo one of 'em.
- No. He'll kick us off.
- I am prairie doggin' it.
- You're what-ing it?
You know when a prairie dog
sticks his head out of a hole?
Oh, God! Alright, yep.
Alright. Thank you.
Alright. Wa.. Wha... wha..
Alright, where're we goin'?
We're going back to the seat.
Thank you. I'm so sorry.
Alright, yes, ma'am.
Right away, ma'am.
- Captain, we have a situation.
- What? What is it?
My prisoner is having an emergency
of the number two variety
she needs
to relieve herself.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah, number two.
Is there a way
that I can release her
restraints so that she can
get her jumpsuit down?
- Just one of 'em.
- No way you're unlocking her.
- No way.
- Your choice.
In a minute you're gonna
have a real stinky mess
on your hands, okay?
So, ball's in your court.
- Please, please, please. Please..
- She's gotta go.
Uh..
Attention passengers, uh, we are
gonna have to make a very quick
unscheduled rest stop.
You're gonna have exactly ten
minutes to do your business
and if you don't
make it, uh, tough shit.
- Thank you, thank you, sir.
- Thank you so much.
She's prairie dogging.
They call it, they call it a
turtle head where I come from.
(cell phone beeps)
(beeps)
- I got it.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Ah! What a relief.
Hey, soldier boy.
Seen any action lately?
Well, I'm always
lookin' for action.
But, honey, like you look
tied up right now.
- I'm free in six months.
- Six months? It's a date.
(laughing)
You see that?
I still got it. Yeah!
- Uh-huh!
- Six months!
(horn honks)
- Thank you so much.
- Goodbye.
- Good riddance.
- Thank you so so much.
And I hope one day,
when you find yourself
in trouble, you find
someone to be as kind
to you
as you've been to me.
- Okay.
- Anderson!
Now, give my best
to your mother.
(chuckles)
Alright.
Ah, I'm ready.
Feels good to be out
in the street, you know.
Well, the train is coming
in ten minutes.
Don't get used to it.
(indistinct chatter on PA)
There's track trouble
so your train's gonna be
delayed two hours.
Okay, thank you.
That's too bad.
Listen, anything happens
to either one of us
I'll meet you
right back here.
Funny.
No, really.
Are you hungry?
We got some time.
Yeah, I haven't eaten
since yesterday.
I know a place nearby.
Alright..
Oh, goddammit,
these hurt.
- What?
- Ow!
Please, I need you
to stay closer, okay.
I'm right here,
I'm right here..
Wait, give me
a minute. Please.
Give me a minute.
I just think that we're...
I don't know.
(grunting)
You goddamn bastard,
try that again!
What happened?
Tried to run off
with my lady's bag.
- Oh!
- It's alright.
- Thank you.
- Don't you worry.
Alright,
just stay close, okay?
Train station's
right down here, darlin'.
It's a good thing
I'm here. Ow!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
No, I'm good.
It's just..
Ow! Goddammit. Ah!
- I must've caught some skin under that.
- Alright.
- Come on.
- Really?
Yeah. But you better not
make me regret this, okay?
I'm not gonna make
you regret anything.
We're gonna have
a great time.
You got that one?
Oh, fantastic.
Thank you so much!
Alright, okay, okay.
No, no, I... I'll be good,
I promise. I promise.
- It was a high kick.
- That's all I got.
(instrumental music)
Come to momma.
Thank you!
(laughs)
So, Stevens,
what do you think?
Ah?
It's kinda messy,
Anderson.
Oh, thank you.
You can call me Joan.
Huh.
But how's it taste?
- Not bad, Anderson.
- Can't do it, can you?
I'd rather not.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
It's dripping down
my sleeves here.
Would you just maybe,
help me loosen one.
I got six months.
I'm not going anywhere.
- Yeah.
- Alrighty.
So sweet, thank you.
Oh, fantastic.
That's great.
- There we are.
- That's great.
Yeah, alright.
- Come on, give me the other one.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my gosh.
You're too good to me.
I know you're not
going anywhere.
- I get to see my mom, right?
- Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
Alright hold on.
Here.
They're going
right back on, okay?
Absolutely!
Now, I can eat
like a lady.
(instrumental music)
(chuckling)
Jesus!
My mom's gonna freak
when she sees this crap.
Oh, no, you look good.
Yeah, well.
You don't know my mother.
She's the reason
I ended up like this.
(cell phone ringing)
Sorry-ass, loser inmate.
On my way to see her on
her deathbed with my CO.
You think this is the way I
wanted my life to turn out?
No. Probably not.
But you can't really
blame your mom, can you?
Oh, yes, I can,
she's a ballbuster.
(cell phone ringing)
(laughing)
You know what
I'm talking about.
Hi, mom.
I'm working now, okay?
I can't talk.
I will call you later.
My mother was so out of it
she had me stuck
in a loony bin.
But you were
a drug addict, no?
Yeah, that's probably what
made a drug addict out of me.
You know my mom actually used
to work in a mental hospital.
I know those places
can be rough
but I'm sure she thought she was
doing it for your own good.
(cell phone ringing)
It's over now, you know?
You learn a lot
about dysfunction
co-dependency... you know.
You gotta, you gotta
stand up for yourself.
It's..
- It's important.
- Yeah.
Give me a minute.
Moms, I am working.
What do you want?
- Your sister is out of her mind.
- Ma..
She won't help me,
I can't find anything
I don't know
where anything is
and she's just,
she's workin' me!
Pull yourself together,
okay?
I need you to lay down,
and calm down, alright?
Goddammit, I will be
home when I am home.
Wh..
Ma, what'd she say?
She said give her regards
to the sweetest
and best sister
she's ever had.
Sure.
You gotta eat.
Nicely executed, officer.
Here's to.
- Yeah.
- Feels good, right?
(chuckling)
Yeah.
This is not
the last impression
I want my mother
to have of me.
Alrighty, come on.
No, you don't tell me
when to go
I tell you when to go,
and we got plenty of time
we don't have to go.
- Oh, we do?
- Yeah.
Uh, hey, what do you say
we go get a super-quick
shampoo and blowout, huh?
(chuckles)
No, we don't have
that much time.
Yeah, but it's just
around the corner.
Twelve bucks,
can't beat that.
It's a hairdressing school
and I used to go there
all the time
before I got locked up.
Fine, but it's not
on the schedule, so, no.
Well, the train's not
on schedule either, man.
We got time,
let's go do it.
This is gonna
kill my mother.
Please.
Anderson,
the answer is no.
(speaking in foreign language)
You're makin' me
nervous back there
you wanna cop a squat?
Only because my feet hurt.
(speaking in foreign language)
(Anderson laughing)
You married? Officer?
I'd rather not say,
thank you.
Oh, you are so not,
I can tell.
You got a boyfriend?
Not now.
Come on.
Why not, look at you.
I am.. I'm busy.
I work a lot,
I take care of my mom
I don't really have
a lot of time to go out
and meet people.
Too busy for nookie?
(sighs)
Yeah.
I can't believe you still
live with your mother.
Unbelievable.
(chuckles)
Yeah, well, she raised me
and my sister on her own.
And, uh, we're
all she has left. So..
So, your sister
helps out, huh?
I wouldn't exactly
put it like that.
She, uh,
she helps herself out.
You know, one thing
I learned in this world?
You gotta help yourself
'cause no one else will.
I think the problem
is too many people
think like that.
(hair dryer whirring)
You have gorgeous hair!
Well, you girls
did a fantastic job.
Do I have time
to go to the bathroom?
Where's your bathroom?
- Over there.
- Alright.
Save us some bother
a bit later, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Just save you
the trouble later..
Yeah, that's all
I'm talking about.
I mean, you know
what happens when you..
- Ah!
- Oh, I'm sorry. Sorry.
- Me first.
- Mm-hmm, of course.
Alright.
- Make it quick.
- Thank you so much.
Mm-hmm.
Hm.
Yeah, yeah. I'm comin'.
Just a minute.
I gotta finish
my business.
Oh, baby, real make-up.
(indistinct chatter)
(toilet flushing)
Here I come, here I come.
Alrighty. Ready to go?
Someone got a new face.
Oh, come on.
Let's go catch our train.
- Great job, ladies.
- Okay, wait.
Not so fast, please.
Alright.
Oh, I'm right here,
I'm not goin' anywhere.
- Where am I gonna go? Come on.
- Hey.
- This is so much fun.
- Okay, I need you to..
It's amazing!
I'm right here!
I need you
to restrain yourself.
- And just stay a little..
- I'm restraining myself.
- Thank you.
- Absolutely.
It's all good,
don't worry.
We don't have far to go,
but we better hurry.
- Hold on, please.
- Whoa! Whoa!
- Oh, what? Oh, your mom again?
- Shut up.
Whatever.
No, the train is delayed
another hour.
Oh, God.
Are we even gonna make it to
my mom before she's dead? Huh?
Maybe I can find us
another way.
One train out there,
that's all there is.
You know, um,
I'm beginning to feel
a little anxious
about all this
it's a lot of excitement
for me today.
- Hey, how you doin'?
- Good, how're you doing?
- I'm doing alright.
- Lookin' good, baby.
- Yeah, thank you, baby.
- Oh, God.
But, uh, I think there's
a meeting right up here
I could pop right in.
Oh, they help me
and calm me right down.
- You ever been to a meeting?
- No, I haven't.
Oh, no. You should try it.
Ten minutes in a church.
It's a beautiful thing.
All kind of a blur.
I met a guy online.
I think we met for brunch.
I, uh, drank three bottles
of rose, uh
but then later on, at
spinning class I blacked out.
Thank you so much. I feel
so much better already.
- Yeah. Okay. Just..
- I think I hit my neighbor's bike.
And then also, I guess
rock bottom. So, uh..
I know it's only been
since yesterday, I think
but taking it one day
at a time is really
helping me, so..
- Thanks.
- Thanks for sharing, Karen.
(applauding)
Thanks.
Remember, we're all vulnerable
to our feelings and our desires.
The question,
do our emotions drive us
or do we drive our
emotions?
(cell phone ringing)
- Hi, warden. Yes, uh...
- E... excuse me.
- One second.
- You can't do that in here.
We need an atmosphere
of recovery. Please.
Of course. Yep.
Ah, no, we're just
at the train station.
Sorry,
it's a little noisy.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Alright. Uh-huh.
Okay. Yeah.
Oh, God! Ah, no, no.
Everything is going great.
Yes. Thank you so much.
Uh-huh, okay.
(cell phone ringing)
Oh, God.
Yeah, hi, moms.
Would you like to share,
young lady?
Uh, me? No, I, uh..
I gotta go with my CO.
I gotta go, moms.
(instrumental music)
And despite these
noble intentions
I was ruining my life.
I violated
the veterinarian's oath
I was taking advantage
of all those female
pet owners who were
distraught over their
sick and injured puppies
and kitty cats.
I lost my family,
and most of my friends
because they were
basically afraid that
I would offer
rescue and shelter
to their wives
and, and girlfriends
and, and sometimes
their, their mothers.
Um, excuse me, miss,
but we have a strict rule.
There's no
sitting together
if you could just sit
one seat over.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
- When you're ready.
- Yeah. Thanks.
And I was suspended
from the board
of animal medicine.
But now, you are sexually
sober, is that right?
- How long has that been?
- Um... three months.
(applauding)
Whoo! Way to go!
And have you been able to
abstain from masturbation?
Well, that's not easy.
We all know
that our hands
can be our worst enemies
sometimes.
Right? Yeah.
- Right?
- Well, Yes. Yes.
Um, well, keep it up!
Uh, I mean..
I mean, the good work.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you.
(applauding)
Um, Kevin said
that it's not easy
and that is so true.
Because we have
to remember that
our habit makes true
intimacy impossible.
Lust kills love..
Would anybody else like
to come up and share?
(instrumental music)
Ah! Ha ha! I forgot
how good this feels.
Oh, me too.
It's been three very
long months.
- Three months?
- Yeah, three months.
Baby, it's been years
since I've been
with somebody.
- Really?
- Yes.
Oh, my God!
You must be famished.
I'm starving!
- Oh, yeah.
- I am so ready..
You think you can
handle me?
Yes, this is going to be
so awesome.
(laughing)
Wait, will you come
to my place?
- What?
- Come across town to my place.
To my shelter,
come to my shelter.
- To your place?
- Yeah, I do.
- Yeah, you wanna come?
- Oh, yeah.
- You wanna come?
Let me see what my
friend is up to. Huh?
(music continues)
♪ Uno ♪
♪ Dos ♪
♪ Tres ♪
♪ Uno dos.. ♪♪
- Oh, no!
- There you are.
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
We got a train to catch.
Yeah, I had to take
a call.
Come on.
The train station is like,
two minutes away from here.
- You feel better now?
- I am so much better.
Thank you so much.
Ugh, ugh..
- Wh... what..
- Ugh! Ugh!
I..
(choking)
Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
Help! Somebody help!
I'm... I'm a doctor,
I'm a doctor.
Hold her legs,
she's having a seizure.
Is she going to be okay?
- Yeah, if you do what I say..
- Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh, she's
swallowing her tongue.
And she has
a very big tongue.
Okay. Hold her legs, now!
- And spread them.
- Spread them, what?
There's a pharmacy
across the street.
Okay, go and get her
this medicine, alright?
- No I can't go, you gotta go.
- Right away.
No, you gotta go,
I'll stay with her.
I'm... I'm a doctor.
Go, go, officer, go!
Okay! Listen, make sure
she doesn't go anywhere.
No, no, she couldn't
even if she wanted to.
- Go. Please go.
- Alright. B-R-B.
You're gonna be just fine.
Hi. This is
for an emergency!
I need you to hurry,
come on!
Is this some kind of joke?
Joke? No. What?
It's from
a veterinarian.
It's worm medicine
for a dog.
- A dog?
- Mm-hmm.
(instrumental music)
Bitch.
Not you, sorry.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
(instrumental music)
(knocking)
No! Oh, my..
(gasping)
No!
You've reached the voice
mail of Doctor Kevin Rivera.
I'm probably busy at the
office or at the kennel..
So please leave a message
after the bark.
Okay, I don't know
if you are aware
but you have
an escapee with you
so you call me back
as soon as you can! Okay?
Oh, God!
Good evening,
Dr. Rivera.
Good evening, Dennis.
Glad to see you're
back to your old self.
Thank you.
Alright, six..
...D
(knocking)
Anderson! I know
you're in there. Open up!
(panting)
Are you in there?
Anderson!
(coughing)
- May I assist you?
- Ah, yes.
I, I don't know.
Who are you?
Miss, I'm Michael Evans
I'm the building
manager here.
This door you keep
beating on, it's empty.
- Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
Yeah. The doc moved out
a few months ago.
Damn.
Do you know where to?
I have no clue.
I will tell you though,
you're not the first woman
to come beating
on that door.
He must be a hell
of a veterinarian, huh?
- Shit!
- Yeah.
Oh, shit.
You know, I'm,
you know, I'm being nosy.
Just do me a favor,
you can stand in front
of that door
as long as you can
maybe he'll come out,
I doubt it
but just don't bang
on my door, alright?
- Yeah, alright. I got it.
- Alright. Thank you.
- Yeah, thanks.
- Yeah.
Yep.
God, that looks easier
in movies.
Okay, Kevin Rivera.
You better beware,
I will find you
where you live.
(cell phone ringing)
No. Not now, mom.
Oh, no.
Not now. Come on!
Hey, hey, sir?
(instrumental music)
(sighs)
(chuckles)
I never dreamt
I'd get so lucky
as to play footsie with
a sexaholic veterinarian.
(chuckles) That's not
the only thing I play.
- Oh, no?
- Mm-hmm.
Nice.
(knock on door)
Mr. Evans?
Yeah, uh, come in.
Hey, uh,
can I help you, miss..
Stevens.
Stevens, Nicole. Stevens.
Uh, my phone died
I was wondering if maybe
I could charge it in here.
Oh.. I was literally about
to walk out the door.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
You know, it's king of..
It's kind of urgent.
You a cop?
- I'm a corrections officer.
- Fair enough.
It's my civic duty
to assist you,
Officer Stevens.
Nicole is fine,
thank you.
Outlet is right
over there.
Thank you so, so much.
Charge.
What,
are you here a case?
- I'm tracking a prisoner.
- Oh.
- That I lost.
- You lost a prisoner?
It's a long story,
I'd rather not talk
about it now, thanks.
Would you like
a cup of coffee?
Yeah. Yeah, I would,
thank you.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thank you.
(clears throat)
So where do you think
your prisoner is
right this moment?
God, I don't know.
Guess she's off havin'
a little party.
Oh, right,
with the old super-vet.
Yeah.
Yeah, he parties
a certain type of way.
Oh, God, please.
I don't wanna know.
Yeah.
You got a tough job
ahead of you, Nicole.
Yeah, I'm afraid
I'm not gonna have
a job after this.
No, don't say that.
You're good
at what you do.
- I can tell.
- Mm..
Fair enough. You're not
the best at what you do.
But... you look good in
that corrections uniform.
You look like a badass.
What you should do
is think like a criminal.
You need to get into
the mind of the criminal.
It will lead you
to your criminal.
Develop a perp's
perspective.
A perp-spective.
Exactly.
You think you could
do me a favor?
- Yeah, what's up?
- That office upstairs, can you unlock it?
You're thinkin' like a criminal.
Come on, let's go.
Thank you.
We'll probably
both lose our jobs.
Thank you,
thank you so much.
Let's make this one fast. I
wanna get you in here quick.
Go ahead.
Can I help?
Oh, well, try not to..
(indistinct chatter)
Alright, well,
I'm tryin' to keep my job.
- They're all empty.
- Ooh.
- Thank you.
- Sorry.
It's okay.
Bingo.
I told you she was badass,
look at this!
Yeah! Hell, yeah!
Okay. Oh, shit.
Yeah.
- Uh.
- Perp-spective.
(instrumental music)
(laughing)
Ahh!
(moaning)
(whining)
- Can I see you again?
- Um..
I'd like to,
I mean, I'd like you to
you know, yes. Sure.
Great, I would love to,
I mean, under
different circumstances
it would be great.
- Okay.
- Well, I know you live upstate.
I do. I live with
my... self. Upstate. So..
But I... I... I come to the
city, you know, often. So..
Look, oh,
this is my card.
- Oh, yeah.
- Got my number on there.
I'll call you now
so that...
Right! So that I have..
Yeah, we call each other.
- You can call me if you want to.
- Right.
- Okay.
(cell phone ringing)
- Hello.
- Hey. Who this?
- Is, is this building, uh, manager Michael Evans?
Is this Officer Stevens?
No, this is Nicole.
You sound great
over the phone.
You do, you sound..
You got a nice voice.
You sound, you sound
really good..
Uh, well,
I, I got your number.
- I'm gonna hang up now.
Okay. Alright, well..
We should... we should
do this some other time.
We should get together,
alright?
Yeah. Thank you
for the... electricity.
- Of course.
- I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
- But thank you.
- Alright.
- We'll talk soon.
Absolutely. Call..
You got my number.
- I.. You have mine too. So..
- Alright.
Okay.
Whoopie! Ha-ha.
- Have a nice time, miss?
- Oh, you bet, best time ever.
Anderson.
Miss Stevens!
Where have you been, huh?
I'm taking you upstate.
And you're gonna be there
for a long time
so I really hope that your little
trip to the vet was worth it.
Oh, it was worth it.
Oh, sister,
you don't know.
Yeah, good.
I hope he de-flea'd you.
Go!
Bye, Dennis.
Goodbye, Dennis.
If we hurry,
we can catch...
Oh, you are certifiable
if you think
I am getting on a train
with you right now.
I... I... I am getting on a
train, but you are going
back upstate where you belong.
You are in...
No, we gotta go out to the island.
We gotta go see my mother.
- I'm in trouble?
- Yeah.
- What about you?
- What about me?
What happened. You wanna make warden...
warden look bad
for God's sake? I know.
I'll tell you what we do, I'll
tell you what we do, alright?
Here I am,
I'm in your custody.
We go out,
say goodbye to mom
and get me back in time
for Sunday lock-up.
And now, it looks like you know
what you're doin' for once.
Won't you just, shh?
Just shut your mouth
and stop talking, okay?
I don't wanna hear
you speak!
I'm not speakin',
I'm not sayin' a word.
I hear sound's comin' out
of your mouth.
Ticket, please.
Would you mind
taking your leg off
of my belongings, please?
Thank you.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Shut up.
(instrumental music)
(music continues)
This is where
you grew up?
Home sweet home.
(music continues)
Just give me a second,
alright?
You're ringin' in five, four,
three, two, one, or I do.
Haven't you had a good time today?
I've had a great time.
...three..
(doorbell dinging)
Hmm?
Well, guarantee ya
that's about to end.
You look good.
Thanks.
Get in here, Joan!
Oh, my goodness.
Let me look at you!
Oh, my goodness!
Oh, God.
Let me look at you.
This is Nicole, Paula.
It's Officer Stevens,
if you don't mind, ma'am.
No, Officer Stevens.
Sorry.
Oh, it's so good
to see you.
If you'll excuse me.
- Give me the right.
- What is she doing?
She's just
doin' her job.
- Alright, down. Other one.
- Yup.
Don't, don't watch it.
Do you have to do this
in here?
If you knew what it took
to get us here, ma'am
you'd be shacklin'
her yourself, so, yep.
Yep, I do.
Alright, come on.
(instrumental music)
Mother?
I'm here.
Figures..
You didn't really wanna
see me, did you?
But I thank you
for the lovely holiday.
Oh, my God,
you're still with us.
Hello.
It's Joan, your daughter.
Joan?
Ah! I'm glad you came.
- You are?
- Yes, I'm glad you came.
Oh, hello, mother.
I need you
to sign some papers.
Sign what papers?
To give you some money.
Well, you don't need
my signature
to put me back
in your will.
Not the will.
It's, it's an agreement.
What kind of agreement?
For you
to live your life
any way it pleases you.
Oh, mother.
Oh! What's the catch?
I want you to stay away
from my granddaughter.
You mean my daughter?
I can't do that.
I'm clean and sober now.
I get out in six months.
I'm gonna find her
I'm gonna make
that right.
She is nothing like you.
She's a lovely,
sweet, young woman.
I don't want you
to disrupt her life.
I don't doubt
she's lovely.
I would like to meet her
some day, alright?
You must never,
ever see her.
Promise me!
You are a cold bitch.
You'll get
a $100,000 a year
in monthly payments
but as estate executor,
I will stop the checks
the minute I find out
you've breached your contract
and made contact with her.
Joan..
You're 50-something-year-old
convict.
You have no skills.
Take the money.
What does she
actually know about me?
Nothing.
The adoption papers say
that you died
in childbirth.
Was that really necessary?
Let's go.
(coughing)
Paula.
What's her name?
Do you know
my daughter's name?
Lily Benson.
Thank you.
Go.
- Love you.
- Love you too.
Anderson, you okay?
You wanted
to keep the baby?
I don't know
what I wanted.
No one ever gave me
any choice.
Now, all these years later
she wants to pay me off
to not see my kid.
I got a daughter
out there.
She thinks I'm dead.
It's not right.
No, it isn't.
(snoring)
(laptop keys clacking)
(sighs)
Okay, next.
(cell phone ringing)
Alright, thank you.
Your car's ready now.
- Thanks.
- No, wait!
- Your license and your credit card.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Yeah. Thanks.
(snoring)
(instrumental music)
(music continues)
- Hey. Hey! Hi.
- Hi.
I had a spot of
car trouble this morning
and I was wondering
if I could
trouble you for a lift?
Mm. Insurance issues.
Sorry, I can't.
- Yeah, insurance, it's a bitch.
- Yeah.
I, um..
Look, I, I... I
don't usually
do this sort of thing
but, uh, it's been
a totally hectic morning
and, um,
if you would kindly
see your way
to giving me a ride
I'd be willing
to give you a blow job.
Mm, hop on board.
Fantastic!
Awesome!
(groaning)
I can't believe you!
You are going away
for a long time. Up!
Put 'em behind
your back.
We'll have that little
ride another time, huh?
- That's it. Up!
- Alright.
Whoa!
- Come on.
- Everything cool?
Yeah. Everything's cool.
(instrumental music)
You know, I'm gonna report
you for this, right?
It's gonna mean years.
What were you thinking?
You think I was thinkin'?
Assholes don't think.
Nope, they don't and you
are an asshole, alright?
You had six months
left and now
you're goin' away
for a long time.
Asshole.
You, you know what?
You are the most
exhausting
self-destructive person
I have ever met.
You got that right.
(cell phone ringing)
Oh, Jesus.
Hi, mommy!
What do you want me
to do for you now, mommy?
Hello.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah, okay.
Mm-hmm.
That was your
mother's lawyer.
She passed.
You heard me?
Loud and clear.
Get me back to my cell.
Yup. Gladly.
You okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm great.
Just great.
(engine revving)
(instrumental music)
(sniffles)
Do you need me
to pull over, Anderson?
I'm fine.
What's the matter?
(music continues)
(engine revving)
Where are we?
We're at the home
of Lily Benson.
- Wait, what?
- You heard me.
Nicole! Wait a minute,
where are you going?
Wait, whoa, whoa,
whoa, shit.
I didn't ask you
to bring me here.
Yeah.
Get out.
What are trying to pull?
You have exactly
15 minutes, okay?
And don't even think about
thinking about doin' anything.
I want you to stand close
to that door
where I can see you
from here.
I don't,
I... I can't do this.
Yeah. No, no. Not now.
- Not like this.
- Anderson, you're goin' away for a while.
So I think
now is the time.
Go on.
(doorbell rings)
Hello.
Oh, hi.
Oh, my God, um..
I'm... I'm
looking for Lily.
I'm her.
Can I help you?
Um..
...I'm, I... I knew
her mother.
- You know Norma?
- Uh, her birth mother.
- My birth mother?
- Oh, God.
You, you knew that..
Yeah, my parents told me
when I was 12.
And... did they tell you
anything
about your... mother?
Excuse me, but why
did you come here?
She would have
wanted me to.
Would you like
to step inside?
Yeah, thanks.
(instrumental music)
How did you know her?
I, um, uh..
We were best friends
when, uh, we were young.
Why didn't you contact me
before?
Oh, I just, I just
found out about you, um..
I'm her only child?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Are you, are you married?
Yeah. Um, Brad's helping
a friend with an addition.
- Beautiful, beautiful home.
- Oh.
Do you have children?
Just Johnny, he's seven.
Hey, hon,
come downstairs.
Do you work?
I'm a graphic designer.
I work from the house.
It's, um,
it's kind of slow.
Can I get you something
to drink?
Some coffee
or juice or water?
Water would be fantastic.
Have a seat.
Hello, lady.
Oh, hello, boy.
What are you doin'?
I'm coloring a truck.
Ooh, a truck.
Ah, thank you.
Ma, this lady's
watching me color a truck.
And I hope it's okay.
He loves his trucks.
Yeah, I see that.
How do you think my mother would
feel about being a grandmother?
Once she got over
the shock..
I know she'd dig it.
If I could talk
to my mother..
...I'd tell her that..
...I didn't care what
she did in the past.
She'd be welcome
to visit anytime.
I... I... I gotta
get goin'.
You could stay for dinner?
Uh, maybe another time.
Yeah, okay.
Bye.
(instrumental music)
Yeah.
Don't worry, I got it.
I'll take care of that.
I'll get
the other one too.
All locked up.
(instrumental music)
Alright, lift up.
Stevens!
What in the hell
is goin' on?
You know, your phone was
goin' straight to voicemail?
And I hear
you rented a car?
That's not in the budget!
Please tell me
what is happening?
Alright, sir, there is a
very good explanation.
Oh, she's got a very good
explanation she says.
Please tell me
your goddamn explanation.
There was a problem
this morning.
What? With the prisoner?
With the train.
There was a three hour delay
and I didn't wanna risk it
so I thought it'd best
just to rent a car.
As for my phone,
there were some issues
with my provider,
but I'm resolving them.
Warden, warden if I might
have permission to speak.
Speak, Anderson.
Uh, well, I would
just like to say
that in spite of all the unbelievable
travel snafus we came upon
it was, in fact, Officer Stevens'
single-minded determination
that got me to my mother's
bedside before she passed.
And I know her gratitude
was absolutely expressed
to her very good friend,
the governor.
Oh. Huh... alright.
Stevens, you did good.
I want you to come in to fill out some
paperwork for a full time position.
I'm going to put you
on staff.
Thank you so much, sir.
Alright, I gotta get down
to The Jackknife.
It's karaoke night.
So, ladies, good evenin'!
- Sing well, sir.
- Always do.
(instrumental music)
You did me right in there.
I owe you a thank you
and an apology.
Yeah, you do, several.
Hey, I think it's best if we forget
about this weekend, alright?
Our little secret.
You got it,
Officer Stevens.
See you around, Joan.
(music continues)
I don't understand why you
don't know where my pills are!
You know, any time
I ask Nicole for my pills
she has put them in a strategic
place for me to find them.
- Nicole, Nicole, Nicole!
- Where is my book?
You got somethin'
to say to me, sis?
I do.
Where the hell
have you been?
Working my ass off.
Where else, Brandy?
I have a life.
I have my own family.
So how dare you run off and
leave me holdin' the bag?
Well, you don't think
I'd like those things
particularly
in that order?
I would, okay?
But how am I supposed
to get those things
if all I do is work
and take care of moms?
- Hi, Nicole.
- Hi, moms.
Did you save me
that piece of cake?
I forgot.
See? See?
Okay, from now on, I'm
gonna get my fair share.
I will help out with moms with
you, but not instead of you
because what I will not do
is I will not give up
my life.
I know you don't think that
I have a life, but I do.
And I will not give it up, so
that you can live yours. Okay?
- Moms, sit down.
- Okay.
I will help out
as best as I can.
- But I am a grown woman.
- I know.
Which means, I have to live
my life for myself, okay?
- Okay. Okay.
- Not just for you.
That was easier than I
thought it was gonna be.
This is non-negotiable.
Okay.
I got it, thank you.
I can't believe
she ate my cake.
- That's so wrong.
- Sorry
That's okay.
Hello?
I've got an all-points
bulletin out
on a super-cute,
Taser-packin', badass.
Would you happen to have a
20 on her current location?
Is there a badass here?
- Ma.
What?
Why are you on my phone?
- Because it rang and you were talking.
- Mom.
Why would you
answer her phone?
Because it was under
my butt cheek.
Uh, where's
Nicole Stevens?
Uh, yes. Is this, uh, building
manager, Michael Evans?
I think I ate the cake.
(laughs)
I love you, mom.
I love you too.
I like that phone
feeling though.
(laughs)
Well, the twenty on
Nicole Stevens
is that she is currently
walkin' into her bedroom
and takin' off her uniform
in preparation for a nice,
hot bubble bath.
So you tell me. Who's
thinking like a criminal now?
So you ready for me to
kick your ass in checkers?
Wanna try Candyland?
You did your hair?
Yeah, you like it?
It's not bad
for an old lady.
You know I'm a grandma?
- No, shit!
- Uh-huh. You got kids?
Uh-huh.
Oh, my God.
They twins?
(indistinct chatter)
♪ In the old barn ♪
♪ Okay I wanna go home ♪
♪ Go home ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
^.^.^.^.COLORED by.^.^.^.^
® Sud_Arun collections ®
A member of Psagmeno.com
(instrumental music)
♪ Standin' on the corner ♪
♪ Doin' no harm ♪
♪ Along came the man ♪
♪ A real one ♪
♪ Before he finished he
grabbed me in the chest ♪
♪ I said
wait a minute man ♪
♪ Let the jazz
be the rest ♪
♪ But still.. ♪
♪ In the old barn ♪
♪ Let me tell you
what I want ♪
♪ I want love
and affection ♪
♪ Not the house
of correction ♪
♪ I want love ♪
♪ And affection ♪
♪ Not the house
of correction ♪
♪ I can't sing oh no
in the old barn ♪
♪ I wanna go home ♪
♪ Go home ♪
♪ I wanna go home ♪♪
(instrumental music)
(music continues)