AmericasCardroom.com brings poker back
Million Dollar Sunday Tournament every Sunday
HOWARD PHILLIPS LOVECRAFT
AUGUST 20, 1890 -
MARCH 15, 1937
"Terror writer
super amazing.
By far, the best of all. "
ELIZABETH KELLER
Patrick had a
vague foreboding.
Something was about to happen.
How could you tell your parents,
that the evil things
They were everywhere?
In the ether and in each
particle of dust.
Patrick always saw them.
And it always seemed to him that
only he knew about them.
And then ...
On the night of the seventh day,
he could feel his
imminent arrival.
Something whispered in the
twilight breeze.
"It's going to happen tonight."
The next day,
when his mother opened the door,
there was nothing further.
The urine track of
Patrick William Wards ...
I was driving to an empty closet.
Bathed in darkness
of his last night.
The end.
OMG!
Here we go.
It is one of your best.
- Mom, you always say it.
- Yes
But this time I'm serious.
Really?
I was fascinated, captivated ...
scared.
It looked like...
Lovecraft.
- Already. It seems too much, right?
- Do not.
I did not find totally
my own voice yet.
Yes. That's it!
- Vera!
- Mom, my sister is a phenomenon.
- Tell me something new, please.
- Do not!
Beth, honestly,
I do not understand how you can spend days,
writing that shit that
ends with urine on the carpet.
You do not understand.
What the hell you want
Say with your stories?
- They're supposed to be terrifying.
- Terrifying.
Terrifying is having you as a sister,
good luck to find a boyfriend.
Calma, Vera.
I do not speak French!
Keep writing, Beth.
And if I'm not what
good enough?
You're good enough, Beth.
You only say that for
What are you, my mom?
What is that?
But what the fuck?
Okay friend.
Come on, Vera, have manners.
No French, mom!
Do not.
Yes, it's fine. Yes.
A classic car they have.
My mom and I love old things.
- Are they just passing through?
- Do not.
We are moving here.
For Aunt Clarice's house.
Aunt Clarice? Does she live around here?
I'm not sure exactly.
I mean, he died.
She was the sister-in-law of the
My mom's cousin or something like that.
Clarice Giordan!
The French lady,
who lives in that house ...
Dammit!
For the love of God! It's going to smell
to enamel here for a week!
Watch the store for me,
Miss Giordan.
My last name is Keller.
HORROR BOOKS
KILLER OF FAMILIES
ATTACK FOR FIFTH TIME!
What are you doing?
What is that?
A story that you would not like.
As you know?
There is nobody here?
My God, it stinks.
She is coming back.
Oh my God!
I look horrendous.
Agree,
what is the story about?
A guy is entering
the houses of the people.
Killing parents
and saving the daughters.
All about your age.
Y...?
He stays at home with them.
Along with the corpses
parental.
- You are inventing it.
- Girls!
Let's move on!
Jesus Christ.
It's Rob Zombi's house.
She'll like it here.
It's not so bad.
It is an extension of your brain.
They have to be kidding.
The rooms are upstairs.
Mom, it smells like old people here.
It has a moldy smell, Vera.
Yes, that's what I said.
- Look at all those dolls.
- Yes
Clarice never
I let them play with them.
What was the problem
of Aunt Clarice?
Is working?
Do not!
Now, yes!
When are you going to leave?
that fucking machine?
And only use a laptop!
Never.
God,
It's like the Flea Market here.
She bought everything
this for herself?
The old women love
this kind of shit.
A Chinese puzzle box.
What?
It is more than a mirror.
It's really a box.
I read about this.
There must be a button
secret somewhere.
Jesus!
So, do you like it here?
Do not!
Vera, be careful with that.
Who will buy something like that?
Love?
Baby?
Beth?
I'm fine.
Oh honey.
Of course it's fine.
That's why you looked so pale.
What happened to her?
Nothing.
She is like you now.
Great.
You know that you choose the best moment.
Vera!
She is fine?
Now you ask.
You could have stayed and helped.
Why bother?
You ran to rescue her
anyway.
I do not know why he writes
these stories...
and it crumbles with
a little blood
Mom, she ...
She is afraid of flying.
He is afraid of the boys.
He is afraid of his own
damn shadow.
When I packed the other day,
I found something...
what you would not believe
I'm not in the mood, Vera.
An interview.
With her, mom.
Several written pages
as if it were in a magazine.
She invented everything.
At the interview,
she is a famous writer ...
and they are asking you
about his books.
I should check your reality, mom.
It's good to know what you want to
your sister, after all.
I know you're angry
for leaving your boyfriend.
Whatever, mom.
And stop using makeup.
Fuck you!
Piece of shit.
I know you love her more!
Beth. Beth. Beth.
Damn Beth.
Shit.
Shit!
Mom!
Where is your antique lamp?
Down there.
Who is your favorite writer?
Already.
Your old lamp!
Where do I put it?
In the room.
Can you hear me?
Yes!
Hears! Calm with the door.
Are you enjoying my bed?
This is yours.
And this is also yours.
Your shits are not going to
stay in my room.
Take them.
Would it kill you to be more
kind to your sister?
Maybe yes.
It was what I thought.
It is not mine.
It is an old house.
Mom! It's my room!
Go help Lovecraft's daughter.
Jesus!
Lower!
Shit.
Jane? What?
Hello?
Jane? I can not hear you.
Mom?
Did you hear that? Mom ?!
No!
No. No!
Stop!
Fuck!
Help!
Help...
He just wants to play with the dolls.
Do not look at me.
Do not!
Mom.
Listen to me, Beth.
You have to go, please.
Go away. Escape!
Escape
Do not!
Damned.
Mom!
Do not.
Mom! Mom, no!
Mom...
Do not!
- Do not!
- Beth!
Look here, Beth!
Honey, honey, come here.
Hey hey. It's okay, Beth.
It's okay.
You're good.
Hears.
Oh my God!
- I was in the basement.
- I know.
I know.
With Vera.
It's over now. Agree?
It was so real.
It was a long time ago, Beth.
Hears.
It's a beautiful morning at CO1.
Relax and enjoy the station
of classical music of Chicago.
Hello?
Give me a second.
Yes?
It's Jerry.
Hey, Jerry.
I'm not sorry,
she can not answer now.
We have to talk.
I'm going to ask you to call soon.
It's about sales.
Sorry?
Five times more, my friend.
Are you writing?
Yes, of course he is writing.
Yes.
I do not know, Jerry.
I am going to tell you. It is right here.
I'm going to tell you right now,
agree?
It's okay. Great. Thank you.
All the personnel of the
Editorial will be in the show.
Your sales skyrocketed.
They adore you
They love sales.
You want to know?
I hate the numbers.
Good...
They are gigantic.
And they love you.
Yes, hello. Do not.
I just told you
It's okay. I know...
Today's guest was
called the teacher of horror.
His latest book,
is "Incident in
Land of Ghosts ".
It just came out two weeks ago,
and it's already on top of the
lists of the best sellers.
We are very lucky
in having it here.
And rarely makes appearances
on television.
Elizabeth Keller
It's a pleasure to meet you, Elizabeth.
The pleasure is all mine, Eve.
"Incident in the Land of Ghosts" ...
It's your most book
personal until now.
And a kind of
tribute to your family.
If true.
What happened to you and your sister
when were they teenagers?
Are you asking if the
Book is an autobiography?
What I mean, Elizabeth,
it feels so real
The details are so intense.
I guess the question is,
"Why write this book?"
To avoid going crazy.
Really?
I mean,
is there any better reason to write?
No.
She did not stop
Talk about Vera and me.
I got defensive.
Everyone must have noticed.
It's not that bad.
When you are mysterious,
you are the one who commands
You only say that for being
my greatest admirer
Shit.
You're right.
I'm going to take the Harlequin to bed.
are you sure you want?
see this again?
Take it from him and go
how much does it matter?
He will not go to bed using this,
true?
Why not?
He loves this disguise.
I told you, they love you.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Beth!
Please, you have to come back!
- Vera?
- Returns! Please!
- Mom is there with you?
- They're in the house!
Vera, listen to me.
You're not listening to me, Beth!
I'm hearing you!
Do not leave me alone, Beth!
Mom is there?
Vera?
Your mom is obviously with her,
true?
It has to be.
Answer, answer
Its busy.
Okay, try again.
Are you sure about this?
I do not know.
It could be nothing.
Only a delirium from Vera, but ...
Mom does not answer her phone.
And I'm having
those dreams again.
Something is not right.
I understand, but ...
They should never have
to stay in that house.
It does not help Vera.
She should be a hospital.
It's fine.
Call us when you get there.
I'll do it.
Be careful.
Here? Are you sure?
Yes.
Mom?
Beth?
My girl!
What are you doing here?
Why did not you say you would come?
Vera called me last night.
She was screaming and the
phone connection was cut.
I tried calling back,
but I did not get it.
And I did not know what was happening.
I had no idea
who used the phone
Everything is alright?
Yes. She is resting.
I missed you so much.
You are very pretty.
You have not changed anything.
The house follows exactly
same, mom.
Good...
After so many years,
You still have your crazy style.
It's fair.
I sold most of the things.
Yes?
You will not believe how much I won
for the old toys.
Really?
Y,
I will be able to rebuild the whole house.
Do not you receive the
Money that I send?
Of course.
Oh, Beth.
I did not mean that.
Mom,
If it's not enough, just tell me.
I do not know why I said that.
You are spoiling me
I am your daughter and I can do it.
I'm not spoiling you. I...
Sweetie.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I exaggerated.
Beth ...
Are not you angry with me?
Why should I be?
Why did I leave you?
here alone with Vera?
Beth, look at me.
You did not abandon me.
You left why you had
and to your own life.
That is perfectly natural.
It is understood?
Dont be like that.
That is my girl.
We are going to give
Since when do you drink?
Caipira beer?
Shit.
On the edge of the door.
You locked her?
Unloved, she locks herself up.
Hide the key down there.
I made a copy.
Vera?
Sweetie?
Are you hidden?
Vera?
The first aid kit, Beth.
In the closet on the left.
Vera? Where are you?
Sweetie?
The first aid kit, Beth.
Vera?
Help me!
Vera!
Mom!
Hold your legs.
Do not!
Beth, move!
Hold your legs.
It's okay.
Do not...
It's okay. Enter the room.
Help me!
Calm down, Vera!
It's okay. Take it easy.
Help me!
Take it easy.
Bring the kit, Beth.
Look at me.
It's over, baby. It's over.
How did you do it?
They hurt me
Nobody is going to hurt you.
My sister.
Beth?
I'm here, Vera.
She is watching you.
- Vera.
- She is watching you.
Please tell me how you had
inspiration for this book.
Of course, it started when
I was doing my Master's Degree.
At The Sorbonne.
And I ...
I went to the galleries in Paris,
and there was a gallery that was
with an art exhibit ...
Do not worry about it.
Come here.
It is difficult right?
I know.
Active time of year, so that
the artists meet and believe.
How do you do it, mom?
Last week the
I found in my room.
Attached to the heater.
She was screaming like ...
I had to turn around to
see that there was nobody
What I can do?
There's nothing you can do, Beth.
She continues to revive
that night, again and again.
Come here.
It's okay.
Where are you?
Help ...
Help me!
HELP ME!
Vera?
Are you going to let me die alone?
Do not.
Not alone?
You will not die, Vera.
They are making me pay.
And you are not there.
I move...
and they burn me.
I scream and they ...
Please.
I am begging you.
Please, tell them.
Tell them I'm not a bad girl.
Vera?
Vera, listen to me, okay?
I'm sorry, if I offended them.
Tell them to stop punishing me.
You did not do anything wrong.
Tell them.
It's not your fault.
It's not your fault, okay?
Are here.
- Vera? It's just mom.
- Vera?
Vera?
The truck.
Oh my God!
Mom?
Get lost.
Have you already woken up, honey?
Yes.
Eugene came?
So much crap in this house.
Did he leave the account?
I did not even see it.
What a great day for a field day?
You still smell Beth.
That smell drives me crazy.
What are you talking about?
I should have eaten you
while you lived here.
Then, you would never leave me.
And no boy
I would bring my girls closer.
Stop drinking, mom.
The flesh of my daughters.
You have no sense
Are you okay, mom?
God, I look like shit.
I do not know where your talent comes from,
Dear.
Your ability to create
your own worlds
It still hurts?
Nothing hurts more truth.
You're still cute, mom.
What I am trying
to say is that ...
"Incident in the Land of Ghosts" ...
It's your best novel so far.
Did you read it?
Of course.
It was so good that it did not
I wanted to stop reading.
I did not say anything about the book,
why I did not want to bother you.
I'm very proud.
Beth.
Beth, I miss you.
You left me...
All alone
HELP ME!
Vera!
Vera, it's fine!
It's okay.
Vera
Vera, it's fine.
It's okay.
Vera
What did you do?
Vera, look at me.
Vera, there is no one here!
There is nobody, Vera!
Where is the key?
Do not!
Do not! Do not! Do not!
Vera!
Listen to me!
Open the door please!
Stop! Vera!
Vera!
Open the door!
Vera! Please!
By...
Vera?
Mom!
Help me, Beth.
Mom.
Mom, where is the key?
Vera is having an attack.
He locked himself in the room.
Where is the key?
The key to the room.
Where is?
There is no key, dear.
Vera?
Vera!
Do not!
Leave me, you son of a bitch!
Moron!
Vera
Help me ...
Mom! Call an ambulance.
Vera!
Stay still, okay?
It's okay. It's okay.
Here you have. Here you have.
The ambulance is on the way.
I know why you did that.
I know what you want from your sister.
I'll wait for
them on the road.
Otherwise
They will not see the entrance.
Mom!
Stay with her.
And wait for me.
Mom.
What did you want to say before?
Do not listen to her, Beth.
Vera?
Vera!
Stay...
Stay with me, Vera.
Vera?
Stay with me.
Vera
Vera?
I can hear you.
Vera, I can hear you.
Please, please stay with me.
Please, Vera.
Vera
We broke your sister.
And now ...
It's your turn.
Mom?
Mom...
Mom!
Mom.
Vera?
What did you do to me?
Do you understand now, Beth?
Vera!
What did you do to me?
They broke me.
And now they are playing with you.
Vera!
He chose you, Beth.
You are a psychopath!
Stop!
Tell me what you did.
It's not me!
- Tell me!
- Stop, Beth!
Wake up, Beth!
For the first time in your life,
stop running!
Try to accept reality!
Came back!
Beth.
You're still here.
Listen to me.
Accept what happened.
You just have to face the truth.
Mom.
She could not do anything.
No no no no!
Do not!
Mom died, Beth.
- Do not.
- If he did.
She died.
Do not!
They killed her, Beth.
Died.
I am so sorry.
Mommy.
- Mommy.
- I know.
She died, Beth.
You have to let her go.
Beth ...
Beth.
We are just the two of us, Beth.
Beth ...
Only two now.
You come back?
Beth?
You were talking about them
as if they were real.
And from mom.
You looked at me as if
I was crazy.
You could not hear me.
You had gone.
I did not know how to bring you back.
I hate you, Vera!
I hate you.
CHICAGO, ILLINOIS
MY TYPE OF CITY
"I serve her and she serves me" ...
Up up. Now! Now!
You need to hide.
Here.
It's a game, okay?
She wants people to hide.
Listen to me.
If it takes you up there ...
Do not move.
And do not cry, okay?
Does not matter...
It does not matter what he does to you.
He will go slowly, okay?
The last time I ran,
It was much worse.
Do not do it.
Listen to me.
If it takes you up there ...
It does not matter what I do.
Do not move.
And do not cry.
Do you want to be my friend?
Do you want us to be friends?
I like you.
Do you want to be my friend?
Do not!
Do not...
I love you.
You're crazy.
Nobody loves you.
You're ugly.
You're a shitty pig.
I'll kill you.
Pig.
Nobody loves you.
- You're a pig.
- Nobody loves you.
Do not!
Do not...
Come here.
Do not!
Do not...
Do not.
Vera
Vera!
Come.
The door...
The door.
Come on, Beth.
Wait ...
Do not!
Wait!
Wait ...
Do not.
STATE POLICE
Hold on, okay?
We came to help.
Calm Calm.
Do not touch it, fuck!
Do not come closer.
Behind! Behind!
Back, fuck!
It's okay.
They're fine, girls.
- No, do not you dare ...
- I promise.
Patrol calling Central.
I have a situation here.
Tell me who did this to you.
A witch.
And an ogre.
They came for us.
In Aunt Clarice's house.
Between 14 and 15.
Thin.
One is blonde.
The other brunette.
Change.
Two damn subjects.
In a candy truck.
A candy truck?
Can you hear me?
I welcome you, John.
I'm at the gas station, Janet said
who saw the girls you describe.
Just kidding?
I swear to god.
Wait, can you tell me
Where does Aunt Clarice live?
Janet said they were going ...
to Clarice Giordan's house, in the
Corner of Holy Flowers and Jackson.
I know the place.
They were with mom.
Janice spoke with one of the girls.
She is safe.
By God, John.
Send to the team
We're going to take them to the hospital.
And direct to there.
Understood. Change and out.
Cooper?
I got information.
We have to go.
I know where the girls come from.
Do not!
Do not...
Beth?
Beth!
Look at me!
Came back!
Beth!
Do not!
Do not...
Do not! Do not!
Do not.
Do not!
Do you mind putting them over there?
- Yeah right.
- Thank you.
You look wonderful as always.
Thank you very much.
- Thanks for coming.
- I appreciate the invitation.
- Of course. Enjoy
- I will do it.
Finishing it.
You are beautiful.
You too.
You're always perfect, honey.
The most beautiful dream in
the most beautiful world.
- Hello.
James, this is my mother.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Do you think I can
steal it for a minute?
Yes!
Here we go.
Thank you.
Say hello to mom
It's not your thing, is it?
Not quite. Do not.
I already imagined it.
It is even less when
I finished reading it.
Oh my God!
What?
I waited all my life
At this moment.
And now it finally arrived and ...
And I would prefer to die to
hear you tell me ...
Your novel ...
It is a masterpiece.
What?
You listened to me perfectly.
If you change just one
word in this book ...
I will never talk to you again.
Thank you.
That is to say...
Thank you very much, Mr. Lovecraft.
Howard
Beth ...
Vera
Beth!
Do not listen to her, Beth.
There is nothing else for you there.
She is my sister, mom.
The world is a horrible place,
Dear.
But she is still my sister.
Beth!
Are you sure of
What do you want to do?
Beth.
Yes.
Go, baby.
Beth ...
Go.
Beth!
Die die!
Do not!
Do not move!
Backwards!
Hands up.
Little by little.
Do it now.
Hands up!
Do not move, fuck.
Do not do it!
I love you
Okay, Beth.
We are about 30 or 40
minutes from the hospital.
I'm afraid that until then ...
You're stuck with me
You are very strong, did you know?
And very brave.
I bet you like sports.
Do you like sports, Beth?
Do not.
Do not?
Well, I would have lost that bet.
I like to write stories ...
Incident in a Ghost Land (2018)
NESTED proudly presents
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org