(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(faucet trickling)
- Shit!
(laughing)
- You scared me.
(man moaning)
- Where's your mom?
- She's at the store.
She'll be back in like an hour.
- You like staying here?
This is a nice place, right?
- Yeah.
- I'm a good guy, huh?
You like me?
- I guess.
- Anything I could help you with?
Anything I can do for you?
I just wanna be there for you, that's all.
Maybe you need a little extra cash.
(chuckling)
I know you done this before.
- A hundred bucks?
Really?
I'm a little more expensive than my mom.
Ow!
Shit.
- You got just as bad
of a fucking attitude!
- What the fuck are you doing?!
Get the fuck away from her!
- Fucking join in, bitch!
(woman yelling)
Teach your bitch kid some fucking manners!
(glass shattering)
(screaming)
Do it, bitch!
(dramatic music)
(mother yelling)
(whimpering)
(dramatic music)
- Hey.
This has got to stop.
Get your shit together.
We're getting out of here.
Come on, let's go.
Come on!
- Okay.
(city commotion)
- Christ.
Throw me my phone.
Thanks.
Shit.
Thank God we've got a guy
coming here in 10 minutes
who can pay for this shit.
Fuck, where's my makeup?
Can you see it?
- Sorta.
But it's pretty dark in here.
He probably won't notice.
- You wanna wait in the
bathroom or the car?
- Bathroom.
- Actually, wait in the car.
You're getting too big
to hide in the shower.
- Okay.
Got my vaporizer in there?
Thanks.
- Hey.
You forgetting something?
Give it 45 minutes, Max.
- Okay.
(door closing)
(men chatting)
- [Man] What's up, Nina?
- What's up, girl?
(distant police siren)
- Hey.
(birds chirping)
(knocking)
- Fix this.
It looks like shit, I'm telling you.
Hey.
- Hola, Kimmy.
(chuckling)
- Oh, come on.
Honey, I missed you.
Show me some love.
This is my baby girl, Shara.
- Hi.
- Yeah, Cap, how you doing?
All right, fuck it, come on in.
- All right, let's go.
(groaning)
- Room's 300 bucks a month.
All the utilities are included.
You have a small fridge
and a hotplate right there.
- This is so ghetto.
- Get out.
- Is she always fucking like that?
- Yes.
- Fuck.
Washer and dryer.
If you wanna use that
it's gonna be an extra
hundred bucks a month.
Or you could use the
laundromat down the street
but I don't recommend.
- I'm sure, if we need to use the laundry,
we can work something out.
(giggling)
- I'm sure we can.
- We can.
- She's not gonna be a problem, is she?
Because, you know, I don't usually allow
other people's kids here or anything.
- She's fine.
(water bubbling)
(pleasant music)
(somber violin music)
- Hello?
(water sloshing)
Did you enjoy the show?
- What show?
So you guys moving in or?
Are you one of my dad's whores?
- Is your dad Cap?
- Yep.
- My mom met your dad in
a court ordered rehab.
They used to fuck.
We're renting a room.
(chuckling)
- Okay.
So I guess we're housemates.
Nice.
By the way,
nice tits.
I know you love it.
(somber beat music)
Here you go.
What?
I thought this was yours.
You shouldn't leave your purse
lying around, what're you doing?
- Not mine.
- Not yours?
Okay, let's see if there's an ID in here.
And there is no ID.
Just a bunch of Benjamins.
(chuckling)
- Can I have a sip of that?
Please.
- You normally take beers from strangers?
- Sorry, what's your name?
- Jamie.
- Jamie, can I have a sip of that?
- Yeah, I guess,
considering I've already seen your tits
and you're crashing at my pad.
Yeah, why not?
You a...
Are you fucking kidding me?
You said a sip, whoa.
(sighing)
(people cheering)
- All right.
(splashing)
(people cheering)
- Your fascination with my tits
isn't impressing me at all.
- Jesus Christ, I'm sorry, you're hot.
What am I supposed to do?
And you put on a crazy show for me.
I ain’t complaining but
I didn't expect that.
- Didn't expect what?
To come home to random some chick
doing back flips in your pool?
- Pretty much, yeah.
- Who said it was for you?
- All I'm saying is that it was hot, shit.
Another beer?
- Do you got anything harder?
(laughing)
- What do you want?
- I don't know, vodka?
- Vodka?
Okay.
Let me check.
- Actually, nevermind.
I'll see you later.
(somber beat music)
(somber piano music)
- So you know what to do.
He's obviously got dough, which is good.
- How long should I give you?
(moaning)
(coughing)
- If I'm not out in like three hours.
- What?
- Look at this neighborhood, girl.
Time is money.
(whistling)
- Hey, sugar britches, over here.
I'm gonna bring you in through the side.
- Okay.
- It'll be a little more discreet.
- How's yourself?
- Oh, I'm fine, thanks.
- You know, I'm not trying
to be an asshole or anything,
but you look a little older
than I thought you'd be.
I mean, your ad said 27.
- Yeah, well, it's bright out here.
- I guess it is.
So who's the little chick
in the car with you?
- My daughter.
And don't ask.
You couldn't afford her.
- Really?
Mother, daughter tag-team.
I've never tried that.
It sounds so freaking hot.
- Yeah, well, I didn't
say we'd do it together.
Woo!
- Would you?
- Oh.
Five grand.
- Is that all?
Done.
We'll save it for next time.
Tonight I'm gonna take mommy
out for a little test drive.
(giggling)
- Okay.
(birds chirping)
(car engine rumbling)
(girls chattering)
- She's fucking gross.
(seatbelt alarm beeping)
- Put your seatbelt on.
- You fucking stink.
- What?
You smell.
Like a dirty whore who
just got her ass fucked.
- Really?
(tires screeching)
Are you fucking kidding me?!
You stupid, fucking ungrateful bitch!
Fuck you!
Once again, you fucked us
out of our living situation!
Now I've gotta work double
time to pay for this shit!
You think that's okay?
Is that okay to you, you
stupid little bitch?!
Idiot!
Fuck, damn it!
(Shara whimpering)
(sighing)
You hungry?
Hello?
Are you hungry?
- I don't care.
- Okay, you don't care.
Good.
- [Server] Here you go, thank you.
(crickets chirping)
- So you're not mad at me anymore?
Don't be mad at me.
You little piglet.
Here, eat your fries.
(laughing)
Your soggy fries.
- My favorite soggy fries.
- I know, I got them for you.
(Shara pig snorting)
(laughing)
Oh my gosh.
I know you don't see it,
but I'm doing all this for you.
- You're right.
I don't see it.
- Okay, feel this.
Stick those fries in
your mouth and feel that.
(laughing)
- I know, I don't wanna gross you out.
- What is that?
- Feel it.
- Mom, what is that?
Is that a scar?
- Hmm.
This guy had me facedown
in a bed in a motel room
with a knife like this big.
Tried to cut my head off.
- What?
- Do you fucking blame him though?
(laughing)
You probably wish he did.
Seriously.
Because of me,
you're gonna know how
to avoid fucking sickos.
You're gonna know how to
make money the right way.
How to do this correctly and
not be taken advantage of.
You know?
I wish I had someone like
me when I first started.
You're so lucky.
You have no idea how lucky you are.
- How come you didn't
tell me this until now?
- I don't know.
Up until now, why would I?
It seems like you're
old enough now to know.
- I guess.
- Yeah.
Please get this sauce out of here
because if I stick my
finger in it one more time,
I'm gonna kill you, okay?
- Ew, I just did it.
- That's disgusting.
You're like a little piglet.
(laughing)
(gasping)
- Shit.
(chuckling)
Watch it!
- Relax, I wasn't gonna hit you, shit.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
Where you going?
- The beach.
- The beach?
Do you want a ride or something or what?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Be careful.
- Right.
(pleasant piano music)
(waves rushing)
It's pretty here.
- I guess.
I see it so much I don't
really think about it.
- Have you ever thought
about walking into the ocean?
Like, you start at the shore
and you just keep walking
until the water covers up your head
and you keep going
till you can't.
- And then what, you drown?
- You float away,
to a happier place.
- Yeah, I wish it was that easy.
- It's that easy for you.
You have a house.
Your dad seems okay.
- My dad's a fucking tweaker.
You can't really take
everything he says too serious.
- Tweaker?
Like meth?
- Yeah.
Fucking ice.
- Isn't he worried about his teeth?
(chuckling)
- His teeth are jacked already.
Do you know how much
ice you gotta smoke
for your teeth to rot out?
- No..
Like... every day for a year.
- Do you ever do it?
- I'd be lying if I
said I haven't tried it.
It's not really my thing.
Cap let's me do whatever the fuck I want.
Fuck it.
It's all good.
Hey, look here.
Smile.
Perfect.
- Let's do one together.
- Okay.
- Ew.
That's so sick.
Get away from me!
Ugh!
(laughing)
- Oh my god, dude.
- Come here.
- Okay.
- There.
- Wow, you weren't kidding.
(laughing)
(coughing)
- This is strong.
Oh god.
Where'd you get that shit?
Okay, listen.
"A former playmate looking for honest,
"Sincere, generous gentlemen for..."
- Former playmate?
- Yeah, I coulda been.
Whatever.
Get up.
- I'm trying to sleep.
- [Kim] Don't fuck with me!
Get up!
- Shit.
- [Kim] I wanna take some new pics of you.
- What?
- [Kim] You should have your own ad.
- No way.
- [Kim] Yeah way, sit up.
Just take another hit, it'll relax you.
Stop acting like an idiot!
(camera snapping)
Sit up on your knees.
- I am.
- [Kim] Drop the sheet.
Just relax, okay?
Get your hair out of your face.
Give me a little, sexy smile.
- Like this?
(camera snapping)
- Ass in the air.
Show me that butt.
You look gorgeous.
Give me the look of sex.
(camera snapping)
Just do what he wants, okay?
He paid for an hour but
it's a 45 minute hour.
I'll bang on the door when the time's up.
Just stop it!
Your hair looks like fucking shit.
- Ow.
- Just relax. Jesus.
Okay, okay, listen.
Let me give you the
harsh reality, all right?
We've got no money, we've
got no place to stay.
We got nothing.
All we have is you and me.
I could go in there right now
and make enough money to
pay the rent for one week.
You go in, you pay the
rent for two weeks, get it?
All these sick fucks want young.
Here.
Take a hit of this.
It'll relax you.
Not too much.
Don't wanna stink.
All right, ready?
Let's go.
(knocking)
Hi.
- Hi.
(giggling)
- [Kim] Thanks.
- Come on.
Are you nervous?
- Um.
- Don't be.
Come on, let's have a little fun.
Have you ever tried blow?
- Yeah.
- Come here.
Here.
(sniffling)
(laughing)
You're no joke.
I wanna see you dance.
Will you dance for me?
- There's no music.
- Sing.
- No way.
- Hum?
(laughing)
(humming tune)
(somber music)
(laughing)
(giggling)
- You're kinda hot for an older guy.
- Older guy?
Since when did I become the older guy?
Shit.
(laughing)
(dramatic music)
Dance with me.
I just wanna look.
(dramatic music)
(crickets chirping)
- Hey.
- You just get in or?
- A little while ago.
- I'm exhausted.
Wanna?
- I'm good.
- Oh, I almost forgot, shit.
I got this for you.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
- Why are you being so nice to me?
- You're so fucking cool.
You get me.
You don't judge me.
You're so different from
everybody else I've met.
I don't know, most girls
in Venice are just bitches.
- How do you know I'm not a bitch?
- Are you?
- Sometimes.
If you're a dick.
- Never.
- Yeah, that's what they all say.
- Okay.
That's kinda harsh.
- It's just,
I've seen my mom get fucked over
like a thousand times by guys
and it's getting old.
- Maybe it's a problem.
She's kinda rough, no offense.
- It's not her fault.
She's just totally fucked up.
- Obviously.
- Seriously.
My mom never had a family.
She started stripping at 18.
She had nothing and she
had to take care of me.
She could've easily given me up.
So,
considering all that,
she's done pretty okay.
- I really don't get
why you keep doing this.
- Doing what?
- Like defending her.
- All we have is each other.
Thanks for thinking of me.
- Everyday.
Fuck.
Whoa.
(giggling)
All right.
- You want another show?
- Whoa, what're you doing?
- What?
- Look at me.
I really like you.
- Did I do something wrong?
I'm sorry.
- Listen.
(somber music)
(Shara giggling)
- You ever try ice?
- I smoke weed.
- Wanna try some?
There you go.
- Whoa, whoa.
What're you doing?
What about your teeth?
- I'm just trying it.
- Let me do it for you then.
Shit.
(coughing)
You all right?
- Yeah.
- Oh hell yeah.
Get it boy.
God, that shit turns bitches on.
I love it.
This is better than porn.
(giggling)
(shower trickling)
- Sorry.
I'll be out in a minute.
(urinating)
(coughing)
(Shara yelling)
(metal clinking)
(whimpering)
(sniffling)
♪ Jesus loves me ♪
♪ Yes, I know ♪
♪ For the Bible ♪
♪ Tells me so ♪
♪ Little children ♪
♪ We below ♪
- Hey, don't go in there.
He said we could use the
kitchen and the laundry.
- What?
- No!
Seriously!
- Get your fucking hands off of me!
(Shara whimpering)
What the fuck, man!
(crying)
What are you doing? Let's go! Let's go!
Goddamn fuck!
I told you not to fucking touch her, man!
Let's go.
Come on, baby, let's go, let's go.
(ominous music)
Cap has a stash.
Well, had a stash.
Fuck, it's only 260 bucks.
I need a drink or ice or
something to get this edge off.
Baby, you want something?
- I don't care.
- Everything's going
to be okay, all right?
Don't worry about it.
I'll be right back.
(faucet rushing)
(distant police sirens)
(sighing)
(water trickling)
Yo, babe, where you at?
- [Shara] Just a minute.
- Okay.
What're you, on the rag?
- Huh?
I don't know.
- Did he do that to you?
- He didn't touch me.
(waves rushing)
(seagulls squawking)
I can't believe we're on our own.
What're we gonna do now?
- About what?
- We kinda blew all the money already
and I'm worried about you getting caught.
- Don't worry about it, Hun.
I got a plan.
- What?
- Sweetheart, we're not going back, okay?
We're moving forward and
everything's gonna be okay.
No more bullshit, you hear me?
- Okay.
(exciting beat music)
- What's happening, man?
My man!
- What's happening?
- How you been?
- Word.
You ready?
- Yeah.
- Let's do it.
(exciting music)
- Jill.
- Hi.
- Can you get this one suited up?
- Sure.
- How is Cap?
- Fucked up.
- Kristi will take over from here.
- Well hello, Kristi.
(beat music)
(bottle clinking)
Yo, these just came in.
- Leave it there.
(dramatic music)
- God, you're so fucking hot.
You like staying here?
- It just needs some flowers,
then it'll be perfect.
Like our own little home.
- You got it.
Tomorrow.
Flowers.
- Daisies.
- Daisies?
(sensual music)
(sexual moaning)
(beat music)
- There she is.
Miss America.
(laughing)
- Hey, my friend's talking
to you, Miss America,
don't be rude!
- Ow.
- Bet you got a virgin ass, hooker.
- Get off me!
If I'm a hooker than you owe me this.
- The hell I do!
Give it back!
- Back the fuck off of me!
Pervert!
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
- This little bitch just stole my money.
- Hey, asshole!
- Check her tits! Check her tits!
She's got 250 in there.
- Stupid ass!
- Come on.
(whimpering)
(yelling)
(glass shattering)
(crying)
- What the fuck happened tonight?
Did you rip some guy off or what?
- He stuck his finger up my
ass and he called me a hooker.
- Maybe you shouldn't be wearing a skirt
with your fucking ass hanging out of it.
- I could be walking around naked.
That doesn't give him or anyone
the right to do that to me.
- Spoken like a true fucking
whore, congratulations.
Did your mom teach you that bullshit?
- My mom taught me not to
give anything away for free!
So no, I didn't steal anyone's money.
He owed me.
- So you Ar a whore?
I knew it.
I fucking knew it.
- You don't have any idea.
- I have no idea?
I have a fucking idea, babe.
I saw those sick fucking pictures of you
on your mom's computer.
- What?
You were creeping on her computer?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
- What's wrong with me?
You're the fucking whore!
- My mom made me take those pictures.
- She made you take those pictures.
She made you stick your ass in there
and make those stupid
duck lips at the camera?
What, are you fucking joking me right now?
Maybe you should just go back to whoring.
It seems to work best for you.
- Fuck you!
Fuck you!
- Oh, fuck me?
- Fuck you!
- Fuck me?!
Huh?!
Why don't you just go
fucking cut yourself, baby?!
Don't think I haven't noticed
this fucking bullshit on your leg!
You fucking psychopath
motherfucking bitch!
(crying)
- How could you say that to me?
- I can't believe,
I can't even fucking believe
I thought I loved you.
(crying)
- Where are you going?
Please don't go.
I'm sorry.
- No.
- Please.
(sobbing)
Please don't leave me.
Please.
- Get the fuck away from me, you slut.
(crying)
(yelling)
(ominous music)
- Fuck!
(coughing)
(thudding)
(dramatic music)
(huffing)
(groaning)
Fuck!
(thudding)
(speaking foreign language)
(yelling)
- Shut the fuck up, bitch!
Shut the fuck up!
(women whimpering)
What the fuck are you talking about?!
Shut up, bitch!
Don't say another motherfucking word!
- Please, just--
- Shut up!
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, okay?
- Shut up, bitch!
(smacking)
- [Woman] God!
- [Man] Shut the fuck up!
- [Woman] I'm sorry.
- [Man] Don't tell me what to do!
- [Man] Shut up!
(dog barking)
(birds chirping)
- You got the money for last night?
Your boyfriend said he would pay today.
I can't keep letting you without pay.
- Yeah, I'm gonna go meet him right now.
He has it.
- Get it to me by 5PM.
If not, you're out!
- Okay.
(giggling)
(dramatic music)
- Hey.
You okay?
- [Shara] Yeah.
- Hop in.
You're all right, I won't bite.
What are you doing walking around
in a neighborhood like this
in the middle of the night?
You know how dangerous that is?
- Yeah.
- You're lucky you found
me and not some lunatic.
Will that help?
- Yeah, thank you.
Thank you.
- All right, let's do this.
- I didn't know.
- Hooker school 101,
you negotiate before you get in the car.
Don't tell me you're standing
here for your health.
You wanna make the 20 bucks or not?
If you don't you can give
it back and you can get out.
- Okay, okay.
- That's my girl.
(dramatic music)
(man yelling)
(coughing)
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(metal clanking)
(chuckling)
- [Cap] Douchebag.
(riders chattering)
(knocking)
(groaning)
(sighing)
(birds chirping)
- Yo!
- Ow.
- What the hell are you
doing in my backyard?
- Hi.
Sorry.
How are you?
- How am I? I'm fucking fabulous.
What're you doing here?
- Well,
remember when you offered
me a hundred dollars?
- Yeah.
- I was just wondering
how much you'd offer
me for the whole thing.
- What is it you need?
- A place to stay for awhile.
(groaning)
- Tell me what a fucking slut you are!
(whimpering)
Can I offer you a cocktail?
- Thanks.
- What're you on?
Instagram or Twitter
or some shit like that?
- Mhmm.
- So...
How's your mom?
Not that I actually give a shit.
I just thought I'd be nice.
You know,
the only reason
I let you and your mom stay here before
was because of you.
I really feel like we have a connection.
Age
shouldn't matter,
you know?
Age is just a number.
That thing that happened
between me and your mom.
Stupid fight.
Your mom,
she pushed me there, you know?
You know how she is.
Really wasn't my fault.
Anyway.
Glad you're here.
Nice of me to let you stay here, huh?
God, you are perfect.
(sighing)
Suck it.
(coughing)
(chuckling)
Goddamn, you're a sexy little bitch.
(ominous music)
- Hi.
- Yeah?
- I'm here about the job.
- You're the girl I talked
on the phone earlier.
- Mhmm.
- Yeah.
Yeah, follow me.
- I'm 18,
five, two.
Long dark hair.
B-cup.
What do you say, baby?
You wanna come by?
I have a girlfriend here too.
If you want to play with both of is.
- Come, come in.
Don't be scared.
Come closer.
(chuckling)
What are you? Runaway?
Am I going to see your face
on a milk carton anytime soon?
- No.
My parents are dead, so
you don't have to worry.
- Are you aware of what exactly this is?
- I've done it before.
- What have you done before?
- Like, with guys and stuff for money.
(speaking foreign language)
- I have a very rich clientele.
VIP.
VIP only.
That means famous actors,
Hollywood producers,
business men.
Very, very important people.
Got it?
You get a thousand dollars an hour
and I'll keep 40 percent.
And this is the best deal you can find.
Trust me.
Most people take 60, 70 percent
and some take it all.
So what are you willing to do?
- I don't know.
- Can you do girls on girls,
double penetration, anal?
Any specific fetishes?
I have this client, he gets off on
sexual necrophilia.
(laughing)
Most girls love it.
You have to pretend you enjoy yourself.
Just pretend you're dead.
Very easy.
You can do it, right?
- Mhmm.
- Are you okay with C.O.F., B.B.B.J?
- Sorry?
(laughing)
(speaking foreign language)
- "C.O.F." is "cum on face."
And "B.B.B.J." is "bareback blowjob."
- Okay?
- Mhmm.
- Oh my god.
Okay, just go with Sero.
I'll talk to you later.
- Sit with them.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- You'll learn to check up.
It'll seem like nothing.
(knocking)
- I'll take her.
- How old was that girl?
- I don't know.
- Come on.
Let me take some pictures of you.
(Sero speaking foreign language)
I can text some clients.
They'll want to come to see you.
(speaking foreign language)
(camera snapping)
Hi.
You should be a professional model.
Oh my God.
Come on, honey.
Get in the picture.
(speaking foreign language)
Oh my, incredible.
You like snow?
Makes you feel sexy, huh?
(thudding)
- What the fuck do you think
you're doing, you little asshole?!
Huh?
(thudding)
Get up, you little fucking bitch!
You little punk ass!
I'll fucking murder...
(groaning)
- I fucking hate you, man!
Fuck!
(groaning)
- Little fucking cunt.
You little motherfucker.
(engine starting)
Come back here, you little motherfucker!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
You son-of-a-bitch!
- You want some?
- Sure.
- Safety first.
- For sure.
- You ever been with a girl before?
- No.
- It's no biggie.
I mean, everything's basically the same,
just softer.
- Okay.
How long have you been working here?
- Like three months.
It's pretty good.
Plus, I wanna get into porn
and this is better for that.
- It is?
- Yeah, your price goes up
when you become a porn star.
- What do you mean?
- I mean, guys are willing to pay more
if they've seen your movies.
I met an agent the other
day and he's gonna help me
get into the industry.
We took a bunch of photos
and he's gonna send them
to some big time porn producers.
I'm excited.
- That's really cool.
(knocking)
- Follow my lead.
Hi.
- Hi.
If you'd like to take a shower first,
you're more than welcome to.
- Will you join me?
♪ I turn my sexy on ♪
♪ I don't think they're ready for me ♪
♪ My camera-basking tone ♪
♪ Will make them lick their lips for me ♪
- I heard you were great.
Such a good worker.
Such a beauty.
I'm very happy to have you here.
(sighing)
- Um.
- You owe Sero for drugs, honey.
I took it out of your pay.
- What that fuck?
- You think it's free?
Come on.
- Thanks for the warning.
- Only because I like you.
Come back tomorrow, honey.
You're gonna make twice more money.
Maybe three times with your beauty.
Oh.
Honey, you're gonna make lots of money.
I promise you.
Okay? Chop, chop.
(crickets chirping)
- Shara!
Have you been smoking
this shit in my house?
- It's just water vapor.
- Disrespectful fucking little cunt!
You gonna get blood on my fucking
furniture, I swear to God!
(whimpering) Get up!
Fucking little bitch! You're
worse than your fucking mom!
- [Shara] No!
- Shut the fuck up!
Shut the fuck up! (screaming)
Shut the fuck up!
(yelling)
(muffled screaming)
(screaming)
(gasping)
(crying)
What? What? What? What?
(muffled screaming)
(gurgling)
(coughing)
- Hey.
- Can I stay with you for a few days?
(crying)
- Look.
- That's your parents?
- Yeah.
We don't talk much though.
- I don't even know who my dad is.
- Maybe that's better.
- You think?
- Yeah, I mean, what if he's a jerk?
- I guess.
- Those are the pictures
my agent took of me
to get into porn.
What do you think?
- I think you're beautiful.
Aren't you scared?
- Of what?
- You know,
of never getting out.
- When I turn 30, I'm
gonna stop doing this.
I'm gonna get married and be a housewife.
Have lots of kids and pets.
I can't wait.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Yeah, I'm calling about your ad.
- You wanna come by and play with me?
- I'm calling about the
girl in the pink dress.
- You're talking to her, sweetie.
- Okay, whatever.
Just let me know where you're at.
Okay.
Fucking bitch.
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
(city commotion)
- Have a nice day.
- You too.
- Why, what's going on?
- Can I talk to you?
- Let me call you back.
(city commotion)
- Where did those come from?
- He said you would know.
- How'd he find me?
- I don't know.
- I don't want them.
You can have them or
you can throw them out.
- Really?
- Really.
(somber beat music)
- Bring all the tips to me.
I'll hold everything.
If you they want extra, let me know.
I'll give you the price.
(giggling)
(exciting beat music)
(men cheering)
- Yes!
Yes!
(men cheering)
(exciting beat music)
- [Man] Oh, fuck!
Smack that ass!
(men cheering)
(exciting beat music)
(city commotion)
(giggling)
- And then the groom wanted me
to stick liquorice up his butt.
- That is so sick.
- Ew.
- Ugh.
Did you do it?
- I tried.
It was like sticking a
wet noodle up a cat's ass.
- Not happening.
- Okay.
- Girls, pull it together.
We have a customer coming up.
Come on, let's go, let's go!
(somber beat music)
- You've never needed this?
Really?
- No.
- I feel like I can't
do anything without it.
(sniffling)
(dramatic beat music)
- It's in that pocket, right there.
(women chattering)
(knocking)
- Hello.
Welcome.
Are you Alex?
- Yeah.
Where's the girl I called about?
(helicopter buzzing)
(horn honking)
- Are you sure this is the right spot?
- I think so.
- I think we should leave.
- For 500 bucks, I'm staying.
- I guess.
- That's it.
That's the car.
(rock music)
- Hey, ladies.
How are you?
- Fine.
- I hope you like metal.
(intense rock music)
(thudding)
- This is classy.
- Yeah, where do you take the bodies?
(liquid sloshing)
- Drink this.
- I don't drink.
- Drink this!
(intense rock music)
- Get off me, you pig!
(screaming)
- Fucking watch!
(whimpering)
(intense rock music)
- Help!
- Shut the fuck up!
You fucking cunt!
(whimpering)
You can just fucking sit here and watch!
(crying)
(intense rock music)
♪ Waiting in darkness ♪
♪ For all of your life ♪
♪ The spell is broken ♪
♪ We will not die ♪
♪ Pulling, you wonder ♪
♪ Nothing you can do ♪
♪ The angel of death ♪
♪ Is coming for you ♪
- Yeah!
Yeah!
Look over here, you fucking crybaby!
You fucking crybaby!
Look here!
Yeah, this is you next!
You're next!
You're fucking next!
(intense rock music)
- Tell me what a little slut you are!
Tell me what a fucking slut you are!
(yelling)
- You fucking dump cunt!
(gagging)
(intense rock music)
Get the fuck out of my car.
(gagging)
(sobbing)
- Did it work?
- It was good.
- I have to talk to you tomorrow. Just go.
Hello ladies.
You did so good.
I have a present for you.
Go ahead, open it.
Come on.
Beauty, isn't it, huh?
This is my gift to you.
More than a thousand dollar each.
Well?
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
You can go now.
- Aren't we getting paid?
- You said 500 each.
- Those are pure million
diamond carrot studs.
Much more than a thousand dollars.
I already told you that!
Much more than 500!
Don't be dumb.
Just go now.
Sero.
- [Sero] Mhmm.
- Shara can not leave.
There is a customer here for her.
- So lucky.
- No, I can't.
I'm feeling really sick.
I need to go home.
- But he already paid.
- No.
- And he only wants you.
- Come on, you can do it.
Just one more, then you can go home.
You'll be fine, go!
- I'll do it with you.
- Oh, no, no, no.
He paid only for one
and we don't any thinking
they can get freebies.
- I'll wait for you.
- Okay.
(speaking foreign language)
- You're more than welcome
to shower if you need to.
- I don't need a shower.
But I'm thinking you definitely do.
You look like shit.
Can you talk to me? Can you say something?
You're killing me.
- You left me.
You left me.
- It's okay, you're coming with me now.
- No.
I'm not.
I don't trust you.
- You don't trust me.
But you're running around with that scum?
(chuckling)
Listen, I'm sorry.
Okay?
I fucked up.
Baby, I fucked up.
I just can't stop thinking about you.
You're doing blow?
- You're one to talk.
- Come on.
Please.
Please, just come with me.
We could live our life together,
like we planned.
We'll figure it out.
Baby, you're better than is.
Don't turn into your mom.
Please, come on, you're
way better than that.
Look,
I never told you this
but it's true.
I love you.
- You do?
- Of course.
I can't live another second without you.
- I had a feeling you'd come for me.
But I can't go.
They own me now.
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- I can't just leave.
- Just make her pay you for fucking me
and let's get the fuck out of here.
- It's not that simple.
- What do you mean it's not?
It is that simple, baby.
- Like, trust me.
- It's not.
- Trust me.
I got you.
- Fine.
I'll take care of it.
Just leave.
Go.
- I'm not gonna leave you here.
- I'm trusting you.
I need you to trust me, okay?
Go.
(dramatic music)
- Shit.
We need some money.
How much you get from those sick fucks?
- These are worth something.
- You gotta be fucking kidding me.
- What?
- They're fake.
- No they're not.
She wouldn't do that to me.
She said I was her favorite.
- If you fog up a diamond with your breath
the fog evaporates off that
spot if the diamond's real
and if not,
they stay cloudy and these
are fucking cloudy as fuck.
You got scammed.
Where's all the money?
I'm not about to let them fuck
you out of what they owe you.
- Doesn't matter.
Forget about it.
- Yeah it does fucking matter.
- I'm serious.
Forget it.
- You fucking kidding me?
Let's go.
Let's go, get your fucking bag.
(ominous beat music)
- What are you looking for,
there's no money in there.
I told you.
Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
(sighing)
- You think I'm gonna
let them do this to you
and get away with it?
- I'm worried.
- Don't be.
Just stay in the car
and I'll be right back.
You got it?
Yeah?
Okay, come here.
No one fucks with my girl, okay?
- Okay.
(ominous beat music)
Fuck.
(dramatic beat music)
(knocking)
- Shara is not here.
Do you want to see someone else?
- Where's the money?
Don't fuck with me, lady.
Now you fucked with my girl.
Not only do I want her
money, I want all the money.
Do you understand me?
Do you understand me?!
- Yeah.
- Then move.
You too, let's go.
- Beauty, are you still here?
- Sit the fuck down!
(dramatic music)
Where's the fucking money?
(gunshot booming)
(dramatic music)
(heartbeat thumping)
(screaming)
(crying)
(sobbing)
(dramatic music)
(knocking)
- Hey!
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
- [Shara] Have you ever thought about
walking into the ocean?
Like, you start at the
shore and keep walking,
until the water covers up your head.
And you just keep going
until you can't.
(waves rumbling)
(dramatic music)