Let me tell you something?
New York is the greatest fucking
city in the world. My city.
I was a kid in these streets,
I started in a fucking gutter
and made it to the top.
This life ends one of two ways
dead or in jail. I did both.
I made my bones doing a piece
of work for Don Carlo Gambino.
I don't need to tell you
what happened. You know.
But the Commission is moving.
The families will not allow
this type of crime to go unchecked.
I mean Carlo,
he paid the kidnappers
he complied with every demand.
And how did they respond?
By leaving the kid
in a fucking dumpster.
Now, each of the families
is organizing a team
to head the hunt for the kidnappers.
But as far as I'm concerned,
this is the Gambino matter.
And we will not fucking stand down,
this is our responsibility.
So John, I want you to
head the Gambino team.
We are not only doing this for Carlo,
we're doing this for the whole family.
I understand.
I want you to take
care of this for me.
It would be an honor.
Consider it done.
Oh Jesus Christ.
Look at these fucking bums.
- Missy, hit me again, will ya?
- Whiskey nib, coming right up.
James McBratney?
You're under arrest.
I guess somebody better
call the cops now huh?
Let's go.
Come on, don't fuck up! Hey!
Down, not a word.
After I had a successful
hit on my belt
Carlo Gambino opened up the books
for the first time since 1957.
And like that I became the made man.
Can you believe the way
they bring me in here?
Like I'm Hannibal the fucking
cannibal or something.
I got the trifecta. I got
jaw, neck and throat.
They took my tit and put it on my face.
I do one-armed push-ups.
Cause the took the whole chest muscle out.
Fucking butchers.
My body betray me John,
but not my mind.
And not my heart.
That will never happen.
I'm still here, John. I'm still
motherfucking these guys at every turn.
So,
what's up?
You ordered me a visit. I thought at
least I would make me get a phone call,
but the judge insisted
I get the visit.
John, they didn't do it inside
the kindness of the heart.
So, I'm gonna ask you again. What's up?
I am thinking about taking a plea.
A plea?
And are their expectations
of you and this plea?
- Five and a half to seven years.
- Five and a half or seven, which is it?
Look, I don't want you should stay in
prison one motherfucking more day.
I'd rather have this cancer
that you'd have a cold.
But I'm telling you if I robbed a church,
and I had the stipple sticking
out of my ass, I would deny it.
I know, daddy.
OK, so I'm telling you as a father,
not as a boss, but as a father
if you say you're
innocent, I believe you.
So why would you stand up in
front of these motherfuckers
and say that you guilty.
Why would you do that?
Because if I take this plea, it's over.
They are not gonna keep coming after me,
or more charges.
- I'll get closure.
- Closure?
Let me make sure, I heard that straight?
Closure?
What kind of a
milli-mouthed word is that?
This is a word for
over educated,
under intelligent motherfuckers.
This is not a word
that's in my vocabulary.
My boys are still young kids, dad.
If I take this plea, I'm back with
them before they are teenagers.
If I lose at trial, I'm doing 20 years.
Like they never had a father.
She's a nice woman.
She's a nice woman now,
cause she's dying in cancer.
Two weeks ago, everybody hated her.
Now she is Miss Popularity.
I'm just saying.
- When is Halloween?
- Next week.
Next week, this week, what do I know?
Everyday is Halloween in this place.
What are you going to be?
Officer Mike down the block is gonna lend
me his police dress. I'm going as a cop.
What's the matter with you?
- What me?
- What are doing with my son?
Oh now, it's your son alone.
Cause of you, I'm a lonely.
Let me tell you something.
No kid of mine is going to
be a cop for Halloween,
and that's it.
That's not gonna happen.
He's just a kid, today he wants to
be a cop, tomorrow an astronaut.
If I ever hear that you let
my son or any of my kids,
and you for that matter,
talk to that cop or any cop, I'll kill you.
- Relax. He's just being nice to your son.
- Don't make me repeat myself Victoria.
And you, you don't dress like a cop.
You don't act like a cop.
You don't talk like a
cop, you understand me?
- What's the matter with you?
- Me? What's the matter with you?
Don't star Victoria OK?
I'm not in the mood.
Don't talk to me like that.
You think you're such a tough guy. Do you
know, what you're doing to this family?
You are gonna kill me?
I'd like to see you try.
Don't get smart with me. Now...
look, what you wanna be?
Would you ask him, what he wants
to be instead? What do you wanna be?
A baseball player?
No, no, you don't wanna
be a baseball payer.
Why don't you be Casper the ghost?
You put a sheet over.
"Casper is for five years old."
What was you?
Who was you last year? You were a
princess last year. Right?
And what was you... You was...
Time is out, Gotti.
Ah! Gotta go.
- I love you.
- Love you too!
After being IDed by the barman,
they sent me to Green Haven Penitentiary
where I served 2 years
of the 4 years sentence.
With the guards on my back pocket,
I was able to get medical payroll
to see the family dentist.
Not a cavity inside, Mr. Gotti.
We'll see you next time.
And while I was at it, I was able to clean
up some unfinished McBratney business.
Remember what I used
to tell you as guys
it was me, Angelo and Frankie.
We said we was going out of town,
and we'd have a construction job
we was gonna build this big wall,
that was gonna take 2 years.
Do you remember?
John, I want what's best
for you and your family.
Then the idea, just one day you'll
be in a prison, made me sick.
But I don't know what makes me sicker,
you being in prison
or you bowing to these
pieces of shit.
What bowing?
There is no bowing.
It's a compromise.
They get their pint of flush,
I get my peace of mind.
The peace of mind that one day,
I'll be there for my family when I need it.
That's what this is.
How can you be so naive?
Once they get
you laid, you will never be free again.
Do you understand?
They say you win this time,
but next time, they'll
- make sure that you don't.
- There won't be a next time.
I have always felt in my
heart that the day would come
when my family and I
get separated by prison.
I am just thankful that it isn't for life.
And this plea will ensure that.
I had high hopes for Johnny boy. Me, I
was born with 4 fucking sis to my name.
Now I got a kid, going to the
New York military academy.
Johnny boy. Come on.
Let's go, we ain't got all day.
What's the matter? You
guys look like your
brother's going to electric chair.
Cheer up.
Why don't you go get some ice cream?
Pizzas!
- I don't like ice cream.
- You love fuzz sticks, get that.
I do not like pizza either.
How about the movies,
what's that movie you like
so much?
About spaghetti, meatballs or something.
Go see that.
Come on, we ain't got whole day.
Alright, guys, come here.
Alright, you guys better not get
into any trouble while I'm gone.
Look out for your
brother, alright?
Alright, enough, enough!
Let's go.
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Ma! Ma! I gotta go!
Hey
Please I gotta go.
I made you a Tunasandwich,
for the road.
You know what? You're gonna
see him this weekend.
At my house, more often or
not, was Angelo Ruggiero.
My best friend
since we was kids.
Hey, Ang.
Hey. He up yet? You talk
to him, I have tried.
Hey, uncle Ang.
Hey! Whoa! You know
what's good for you?
You don't let your
dad see the cop car.
Come on, you fucking prick.
Look at this. Come on.
Oh, motherfucker!
You know what fucking time it is?
Did you see that?
I got 6 tons of Buffalo,
they killing us. 10 to nothing.
I put 6 dimes on the winger,
they killing us.
I put 6 dimes on the
Chicago, they are losing.
And now I put 3 dimes on
Kansas city, they are
winning. But they'll fucking
blow it, motherfucker!
Maybe you should hang yourself,
leave all your troubles behind.
Smart ass. Listen, you wouldn't believe
how much I lost last week.
- I don't wanna believe. Don't wanna know.
- Just once...
I would give my fucking life, just to have
The Redskins win once.
I got a Redskin named Willi boy in the car.
I gotta clean up. Motherfuckers!
- Uncle Angelo, look.
- What do you got there Frankie?
Oh! No you didn't?
You straight A's?
You straight A's? I never
seen anything like this.
Hey Frankie boy, did you show
Uncle Angelo your report card?
Can you believe that? My
son is a goddamn genius.
My Frank is gonna be a rocket scientist.
What do you think about that Ang?
Let's go. I won't be home for dinner.
What are you talking about?
It is Sunday night...
What? I gotta repeat myself? I'm
not coming home for dinner.
- Johnny it's family night?
- I'll make it up to this.
Manhattan's Garment District has
long been the central to the
Mafia portfolio of lucrative rackets,
and a hugely profitable adjunct
to the mob's historic stranglehold
on trucking and laboring unions.
Authorities believe that, this
man, John Gotti, a feared captain
in the Gambino family
is the mobster primarily in control of the
extortion, corruption
and robbery
with in the multi-million dollar New York
fashion industry.
Gotti, is perceived as
the up incomer in the
Mafia, organized crime
family considered...
Johnny boy was tough.
He knew how to handle himself.
I told him to tell
anybody who had a balls
to ask what his father
did for a living,
that I was a 24 hours 7
days a week street guy.
Who the fucking god think he is?
He is Greek. He doesn't
have his head screwed up.
He has got off the boat yesterday.
Who gave him permission to
run pock in Howard Beach?
- I told him.
- What did you tell him?
How the fuck does he have
a phone talking about me?
My name!
He says he's with the Greek Mafia, the
smoke is so full of shit, it ain't funny.
Miss Luzio, hold up, hold up.
Lou... Louie... Go help her.
I'll take care of it.
Take that shit off your face.
He looks like a hippie.
Why don't you grab 50 % of this?
Look, I want this shut
down yesterday.
This guy is a nobody, even if he
was a somebody, I don't give a fuck!
- You understood me?
- Okay.
Mr. Gotti.
- How are you?
- You still working out?
- Not that much any more.
- Come on, what's the matter?
- He was a quite hope.
- They just fucking closed on Tully's.
Tully's an institution? How
long Tully's been around?
I have been walking by
Tully's for 40 years.
- What happened? What the fuck happened?
- I don't know.
The rent's gone up, they got sited for
some code violation or something.
Don't you worry. It will
be back in business.
How's your father?
How is his liver?
He is still here.
You tell him hello
from me, alright?
Mr. Gotti. Thank you.
I don't give a fuck who it is.
He is using my name on the phone.
So you tell this cocksucker, that if
he ever deals another card in Queens,
or ever he whispers my name again,
I, me, John Gotti,
will sever his motherfucking head off.
- Put on the ice.
- Ma, I'm good. Ma!
OK.
I will fix you something to eat.
Get your feet off the couch.
Get up.
You got suspended, huh?
What do you think you're doing?
These local kids jumped a couple of our
guys. We was just handling our business.
You were handling your business?
- I guess.
- You guess?
You show up?
Yeah. I would say so.
Attaboy.
You stood your ground.
You didn't back off.
You never back off.
You always stand up. You fight,
till you can't fight no more,
never take backward step ever.
Dad, I'm thinking maybe I don't wanna
try for West Point anymore.
- Maybe, I could take a year off.
- Take a year off?
Drop by to school, not
go to college,
become a bum on the street...
which one?
What are you thinking?
You wanna hang out with me?
Is that what you're thinking?
Jesus Christ...
Booch, I'm hungry!
They get it, if they are good.
Well, they get what they get paid.
A lot of them are bummers.
That's for sure.
The Lucchese is here.
I don't like that guy.
Which one?
His name is Gas pipe.
Yeah, I heard him.
He is trouble.
He is up in Angelo's face
at the apartment of the 59th street.
He is real sick of him.
Look at him, this is making sure
all families know his name.
Prick.
Relax. He is not our business.
Sweetheart,
could we get another round here please?
You got it.
Let me ask you something.
What do you think the Genovese
think of their boss?
What are you talking about?
I can understand the
whole insanity pleading.
Come on, running around
town in a fucking
pajamas, give me a
fucking break...
Vincent THE CHIN Gigante,
according to the government,
the powerful boss of the
Genovese crime family.
To me, he was a rival.
Chin is a very smart guy.
He runs his family as he sees fit.
I can tell you this,
you'll never see Chin
and his girl in a
place like this. That's
for fucking sure.
Well, talking about bosses who hide.
- Don't start.
- Just telling...
He is never here.
How can you run a family
if you're not on the ground with them?
Johnny. You got to shut the fuck up.
Paul is your boss.
End of fucking story.
Who is that guy with Frankie?
What's his name again?
It's Sammy Bull.
That's Sammy. Why Bull?
- The bulls hit dead man.
- I know about him.
You don't like anybody here tonight.
I just don't like what
I hear about him.
OK? That's all I'm saying.
He is a good earner.
And he's Frankie's guy.
He never done time.
I don't trust anybody, who never done time.
He's our friend now.
Hey listen, you trust
Frankie, don't you?
Frankie would vouch to the fucking oomph
for this kid. We gotta give him a chance.
Here they come.
Hey boys.
How you doing tonight?
Hey, Johnny.
How you doing, Neil?
How are you, Sammy?
Hey, Frank.
Sammy, I would like to meet,
a good friend of ours and
a dear friend of mine,
John Gotti.
How you doing John?
Heard a lot about you from Frankie.
Good to finally meet.
- Well, good, I hope.
- Of course it's good.
I'm gonna talk about my brother.
Let me tell you something.
Time with Lewisburg
will make a man out of you.
OK. Am I right Frankie?
You come out of the Tick N the Tips.
Brother Johnny.
Let's raise a glass
to our new friend.
- Salud.
Neil...
Frankie...
You trust this kid?
Thank you.
We walked together and
we fall together.
This is the life.
I chose my side over
40 years ago.
The hardest thing in
this world for me to do
would be to have to say
goodbye be to my kids.
- I can't do it.
- I don't want you to,
I don't want you have
to lie to your kids.
And you tell them you are out
on some construction job.
You and me, job, we never
had to lie to each other.
But it's the lies that
you tell yourself,
these are the lies you gotta live with.
You are missing your kids?
You think that's bad?
Do I really have to say it?
Do I?
Frankie...
No, leave the light on.
- Frankie, we are just down.
- Oh, leave the light on. Kids
are scared of the dark.
- This till John gets back?
- Till John gets back.
Good night, Frankie. Love you.
- See you tomorrow.
- I love you.
Oh God, no, Frankie, Frankie.
- I did not see him.
- Frankie.
Mommy is here.
Oh, Frankie. Mommy's here.
The sun has blinded.
Mommy's here. Stay wake.
Johnny boy, it was an accident.
It was an accident. It happened.
He is gone.
But he will always
be your brother.
Now, you listen to me.
I want you to be strong, okay?
I'm proud of you.
We gotta do this for your mother.
Go ahead.
Come on.
Come here.
Come on, I'm late.
What the hell are you waiting for?
- What are you doing?
- Frankie is cold.
- He needs a blanket. No!
- Come here.
Come here.
It will be fine. Come here.
It will be fine.
Calm down, Vicky. Calm down.
I need to go. I must.
Listen to me, listen to me.
I need to go.
I have to bring him a blanket.
He is cold!
What happened? Is Vicky OK?
This piece of shit Favara.
She smacked him around with a baseball bat.
She's gonna be alright.
He's a stupid fucking asshole, John!
He never fixed the dent in a car!
He leaves it there even in the driveway,
day after day for Vicky to see.
John, we can't know why
God lets these things happen,
but there has to be a reason.
A reason?
For these things?
He was 12 years old. He didn't
have a hair in his prink.
There ain't no fucking reason.
There ain't no fucking God.
Don't say another word.
I'mma take Vicky down to
Florida to see her family.
I think, it will be good for us.
Clear our heads.
On March 12, 1980,
12 year old Frank Gotti was riding
his mini bike on this street,
157th Avenue,
just 3 blocks from his home,
John Favara's car hit 12 year
old Frank Gotti and killed him.
The people who know the Gotti they never
came to terms with young Frank's death.
Police however believed someone,
did come to terms with John Favara.
On July 28th, Favara left his job and
walked to his car which was parked
next door at the Capitol Diner.
The Diner's owner told Police he saw 3 men
clubbed Favara and
shoved him into a van.
The best witness Police had
in the abduction of John Favara
was Leon Papon, the man who
owned the diner,
he had seen the whole thing,
he told that to Nassau County police.
But then the assailants returned
to the diner, several days later.
They reportedly ordered coffee
and as they Sept it,
they stared at Papon.
Right after that, Papon stopped
cooperating with Nassau County Detectives.
His memory of the incident faded.
He sold the
diner and moved away.
OK, that's it. That's it.
That's it.
Vicky...
Enough.
I love you, but we
got four other kids.
We'll never let go of Frankie,
do you understand me? Never.
He is in our hearts forever.
For ever. Till the day we die.
We are gonna always live like
we are seven.
I'm gonna make you some coffee.
Alright.
No problem. Merry Christmas.
Look at him. That
lousy bastard father
turns out to be a good grandpa.
- Who knew?
- You never know...
Tell you something,
maybe if we didn't have such crappy parents
we would have so much in common.
You understand?
Yeah. I would be living in Flat bush
married to a dentist.
What are you talking about?
You get a bad tooth
I will happy to knock that
right out of your mouth.
There is my smile, there is my girl.
You didn't think you'd be used to having
hundred people around this house, huh?
Yeah. One night a
year, I can handle it.
Can you believe it?
We used to barely have
enough for the two of us.
But we had each other.
That's what it matters.
That's all it matters.
You and me, we get through this together.
We get through anything.
- Merry Christmas.
Let me ask you, who is that
guy sitting in my chair?
You've been meaning to ask?
That guy has been in your chair every
Christmas for the last 15 years.
For 15 years.
Let me get you a drink.
- How about a cigar?
- Let's do it.
Sammy Gravano told me
something.
What did Sammy Gravano say?
You was over at
Paul's house just now.
Yeah, I was at
- Did you see Sammy there?
- No. I just stopped by for 2 minutes.
He tells Paul, he says I wanna go see
Neil, wish him a merry Christmas.
- Why do I give a shit about all this?
- Paul said:
What the hell you wanna do that for?
You are on our side.
And what did Sammy say to that?
He said "We are all a family, ain't we?"
Sammy told you that?
Sammy told me.
You need a woman.
- Now I know.
- I can not believe.
Paul...
Paul Castellano was a
fucking fish in the desert.
A fish out of the water.
I never respected Paul.
Neil was much more of a boss
that Paul ever was.
- Give my regards to Victoria.
- I will, thanks.
She will be glad to hear it.
I'm just saying, if Paul goes
to prison for them indictments
they're gonna make Tommy
Bilorti the street boss.
Happy days! We're gonna have
hold it to wig business.
Neil, what's going on here?
Keeping Paul
He's not concerned making the deal with
those other families than his own.
He's the boss. End
of fucking story.
Time Magazine says,
you, the boss.
Shows you what a disreputable
fucking profession that is.
- You know why.
- I tell you why.
Because we have never been under
this kind of scrutiny before.
They can see you, Neil.
- Yeah. Too fucking much.
- No, no, no!
You could see, he could talk man to
man with you. Know what I'm saying?
What's Paul's contribution to
society, fucking his
Portuguese maid?
As long as it keeps him off my back...
Yeah but, 35 years, in the same house
as his wife. I mean, that ain't right.
I guess you gotta give him credit.
For what? His penile implant?
You got his house bugged? Do you?
Yeah, I defeated that 50 thousand dollar
security system with my good looks.
That Portuguese maid
was crazy about me.
She is Guatemalan.
So, you have seen it? What ever country
she is from they probably made her leave.
I would not fuck her with your dick.
Listen. Paul has got diabetes.
It's not a subject I feel
comfortable discussing.
What the fuck is so fucking funny?
It's hysterical,
we're gonna get a fucking accident.
Oh, look at this place.
What a dump!
What are we doing here?
We get a couple of drinks get the fuck
outta here, go get something to eat.
Let's go to "Little Pete", it's got that
shrimp in there. I mean you like this.
It's a cop zone.
It's fucking Garry and
his fucking shrimp...
How about a little shot, it's on me.
- No, we are good. Thanks.
- What the fuck you guys are talking about?
I went there the other week.
It's not filled with cops.
Do me a favor, take a walk, you
and your fucking mustache.
Five cops, last week, heading...
- Three shots for me and my boys here.
- We're good, thank you.
Hey, you're too good to
have a shot with me?
I said take a fucking walk.
Stay down motherfucker!
- Connard!
- Fucker!
You motherfucking piece of shit!
Little shit!
John, come on! Come on!
Fuck!
I didn't give a fuck,
when he came in, I
grabbed the ball stool,
I grabbed 2 ball stools
I was going over, I don't give a fuck.
I just kept going.
Oh my God, I was swinging I didn't
know who the fuck I was hitting.
You swinged at the wrong guy 3 times.
- No I didn't.
- You kidding me?
You hit the wrong kid. He
wasn't even with them.
You little motherfucker!
Did you have a fight tonight?
Did you?
Someone got killed!
Did you know that? Did you?
- No I did not know that!
- You shut the fuck up.
You cocksuckers! You
gonna ruin your future!
Don't you understand?
It's gonna follow you for the
rest of your fucking... life!
- Someone got killed?
- Not when I was there.
Proudest moment of his life was watching
you graduate from military school.
And now this. You father is crushed.
- You know that?
- I know.
- No! You do not know anything!
- Dad...
Now shut up. I will talk to you later.
The sharks are circling.
The cops are gonna shake him down.
And that man's gonna,
pay to protect you.
I didn't kill the guy!
I will answer for it, anything!
- We didn't kill anybody.
- I know that.
But it doesn't fucking matter.
You two stupid motherfuckers.
You brought a lot of fucking hate down
on this family.
Actually, it was Angelo
who put the heat down on the family
when the government
released what would become known as
the "Angelo Ruggiero tapes".
They picked up Ang on a wire tap.
Taking about various activities that
neither Paul or the
government would've sanctioned.
Fucking Ang.
This is ridiculous!
You got popped Ang.
Let me just ask you one question.
Are you bad mouthing Paul on them tapes?
Are you?
- I don't know, there's hundreds of hours.
- Oh come on!
- What? You don't know nothing?
- They bugged my daughters'.
What were you saying on the tapes?
I said a lot of things
that could get a lot of
people in a lot of
trouble. It's what I said.
My friends are on those tapes.
Our friends are on those tapes.
Neil... OK...
If Angelo decides that he's gonna turn
these tapes over to Paul? What happens?
- Is that it?
- No.
That is most definitely not fucking it.
If Paul wants the tapes,
we gotta get him the tapes.
He's the boss. Boss is the boss is
the boss, that's the Cosa Nostra.
Tell me I don't know
something about it, please!
If it was just some fucking asshole,
getting called out of some Joe,
he know I would authorize the
handover in a second.
- But this is our friends.
- Look...
If the government has a case,
Paul will find out when it comes to trial,
because it will be matter of public record.
You are fucked either way.
We are fucked.
OK. We are fucked either way.
No no, that's not gonna happen. Get
it out of your head right now.
Listen...
You know, Paul doesn't give
2 fucks about me or you,
He shit picks over his fucking case.
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about?
Ang, just shut the fuck up, will you?
You got us into this mess.
- Please.
- Get the fuck out of here, Ang. Go on.
Christ almighty...
I ain't saying you're wrong.
But what do you want me to tell Paul?
Ang is saying to the boss, "Fuck you! I
don't wanna handover those fucking tapes!"
I've been trying to make
this thing go away, but...
Paul keeps bringing it up.
Unless I say it to him, Fuck you!
Go fuck yourself!
And then, you know,
we gotta do then...
We roll a mother, we go to war.
That's right. We gotta do what we gotta do.
We strike him before he gets to us.
What?
- What's the matter, you OK?
- Yeah.. no.
- What do you need?
- It will pass.
It's funny.
All these fucking tapes
and trials...
We spend all these time trying
to stay one step
ahead of the game...
But this fucking cancer...
And it's the ultimate fuck you.
I'm really not painted.
You got something for me?
You see this kid here?
Used to give him 5 dollars,
he went to candy store.
Now look at him, he's a fucking earner.
Here.
Buy yourself a nice sports jacket.
Because we are going to Binge tonight.
Tonight, tonight.
I'mma tell you something
about your old man.
When he was sent off to Green
Haven on the McBratney thing,
which you probably know about
Carlo Gambino was so
grateful to your father
for his service to him...
He got him Roy
Cohn to defend him.
Roy Conh, the biggest fucking
lawyer in the country.
Your dad wasn't even a
main man at that time.
Cohn, he makes a deal into plea...
He gets it reduced to involuntary
manslaughter. And your dad's
out in four.
One of our people who know about this,
how your dad going to
arrested in the first place.
Your dad was lying low,
in the wind,
he has to have this problem
with the Genovese family.
He showed up.
He receded up my behalf at a seat down
near here in Maspeth.
And the FBI picket him up on
a tip-off as he was leaving.
Loyalty cuts both ways for them.
Your honor,
the prosecution contains that Mr. Gotti
is a clear and continuing
danger to the community.
And in lieu of potential
life sentence in this case
it would be imprudent
to grant him bail.
Thank you, Miss Giacalone,
but you have not convinced me
that Mr Gotti is a flight risk.
Court grants bail on the
amount of one million dollars.
Your honor, as the court has
granted bail for Mr Gotti
we also request that there be set
at a reasonable amount for Mr.
Johnson.
Your honor, we have strong
reasons to believe
that the defendant's life
will be in serious jeopardy
- if he is granted bail.
- And why would that be?
Because Wilfred Johnson
has been a confidential informant
for the FBI for the past 19 years.
- Order!
- Liar!
- She is lying! I'll fucking kill you!
- Order!
- You're going to kill me!
- You will have order.
Counsel, restrain your client.
In light of that information if confirmed,
bail is denied on Johnson.
I stand strong...
I refuse to testify
and we win...
Can I get a pass? I beg of you.
Swear it.
Swear it on your kid's grave.
You won't kill me.
How am I gonna kill a ghost?
Me and Willy Boy Johnson
beat the case
due to the lack of credibility
of the government's witness.
Find the defendants John Joseph
Gotti and Wilfred Johnson not guilty.
As for Willy Boy
it's another story.
Dominic always took
charge of the fireworks.
He's not kidding.
It's my gift to that.
You do the fireworks the way I like you.
That's not what I...
- Look.
- I can not believe...
- You would have some fun?
- Let's go have some fun.
Is there a problem here?
We are shutting it down Gotti.
This is an un-permitted street gathering.
And illegal fireworks at this premises.
What are you talking about?
We've been doing this for 20 years.
Let me ask you something.
You gonna put these good people in jail
because they are
proud of their country?
Is that right? You got
my lawyer on the phone?
- He is standing by.
- You got bail money?
With interests.
Send them up!
This is your turf, John.
Look at this. I'm good at my deal.
Go ahead, taste.
It's not bad. I know.
Hey. Excuse me.
I don't normally do this, but
I saw you walking over.
I'd hate myself the rest of my life
if I don't come and talk to you.
Stop it, Johnny, you're not funny.
- Wait, do we know each other?
- What? You lose your memory
at the military academy or something?
It's me. Kim.
Come on John! Joey Rugs' daughter!
I'm sorry. It's just...
You looked different.
Guess I grew up.
I guess you did.
You wanna get a beer or something?
John, I'm 16.
You wanna get a soda?
Yeah, that sounds nice.
Alright. Let's go.
See you.
Joey Rugs...
Paul wants to see you.
And I hold him back as long as I can.
The fucking Angelo Tapes again?
It's got nothing to do with Angelo.
Paul has decided to break up
your crew.
He's gonna break up the crew?
The fuck does that mean?
If Paul goes to prison,
he wants to make sure
that everybody knows he's still the boss.
It's like Carlo fucking
Gambino all over again.
Everyone knows that it
should have been you.
What you want and what we get
are 2 different things.
Well, he wants reassurance. Forget
about it. No, he will get it.
You better fucking agree with him.
Or at least look like you do.
He doesn't deserve it, Neil!
Look, you gotta earn yours
like we did.
- What world are you living in?
- All fucking Paul is
about his money.
That's his get off. That's it.
- Coming from a fucking degenerate gambler.
- You are goddamn right.
Can't take it with you.
If Paul makes a move on Angelo...
You'll live with it.
If he gives you that choice.
There is no choice.
There is only what you do.
Listen to me.
You kill the boss's boss...
I will defend my position.
- You will bring down hellfire.
- I'll do what I gotta do.
Not as long as I'm alive.
Jesus...
I can't get over Willy Boy.
Shows that life is full of surprises.
He's been with you since
Fulton Rockaway boys huh?
A bunch of punk kids
who had the balls to take
on one of my poker game.
You never know.
He broke my fucking heart.
You gave him a pass?
Attack from the outside,
you can deal with.
But attack from the inside...
you're history.
Once you take that first step,
there is no turning back.
You either succeed, or you
are lost in enemy territory.
And if you miss, you die.
And all your friends will die.
So you will need DeCicco.
If he is on board, then
Joe Piney would join you.
He will take care of the old timers.
And Gallo will go along.
"The Lord is my shepherd."
He maketh me to lie down
in the green grass...
He leadeth me beside the still waters
he restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me in the path of righteousness
for his name sake.
Either I walk through the
valley of shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for thou art with me.
In the presence of my enemies.
In the name of the Father...
Obviously Paul couldn't make it, but
he sends his prayers.
Let me tell you something.
Neil could have taken the family
from Paul anytime he wanted.
Everybody knows that.
Paul, up on there, the hill.
We gotta kiss his ring
like he was the pope.
Fuck pope.
I hear you. I am with you.
You will need DeCicco.
If he is on board then
Joe Piney will join you.
He will take care of the old timers.
And Gallo would go along.
D.B. is important he was through
that all the rough ventures and
make sure that everybody knows
it's only business we are talking.
But you are gonna need the approval
of the other families.
Franck and Sammy Bull
will represent Brooklyn.
The Lucchese won't be a problem.
You got Pescuchi on your side,
so the Bonnanos, we
are not worried about.
Leave the Colombos to Angelo.
He will fill the pause with
Freddy DeVico and Benny Cans.
And that leaves The Chin.
Chin...
Do you think I am
stickler for the rules?
Chin will not be happy no matter what.
But he will be outnumbered so...
We could have a peaceful transition
he will just have to accept.
I dunno.
Paul and Chin are pretty tight.
They got lot of money on the street.
You'll take care of that after.
You use D.B. for that...
Now listen,
No body has gotten in on Chin's act.
On the contrary, with Paul out of the way,
with Chins
free and clear
I have no doubt that the other
families will back you.
But only if you have support
of all five bureaus.
Queens, Brooklyn, Manhattan,
Staten Island, the Bronx.
Ain't that a fist?
So it comes down to:
is what you wanna be?
You wanna be on the boss?
Because we are gonna do this thing.
We are gonna do it right.
It's gonna be Cosa Nostra,
the Cosa Nostra till I die.
Atta-boys, John.
Paul has set up a
dinner next Thursday.
Friends only.
To discuss the reorganization
of the family.
December 16, 1985
We are on a piece of work.
It's a big job. There
is no 2 ways about it.
It's gotta be done.
Get them their coats and hats.
Hats is all anyone's gonna remember seeing.
We are on the corner
from the United Nations.
They will take the fucking
Russians are coming.
Listen up. Pay attention.
We are hitting Paul.
And anyone else is in the car with him.
It's gonna take place
at Sparks Steak House.
That's up on 46th, between 2nd and 3rd.
He has a 6 o'clock reservation.
At 18 o'clock.
There is gonna be a lot of
Christmas shoppers,
but that's perfect for us.
We are gonna get in and out in a zing,
like the Pittsburgh Steelers.
It's to kill or be killed.
Let's go.
- How you doing?
- Good.
A whiskey and ice please.
So, Franck...
this business with the Gotti's crew..
It's very troublesome to Paul.
I know you like John.
Hell, I like to.
Now that Neil's out of the picture,
Paul just wants to...
shake the whole registration.
And he wants you to be comfortable with it.
Paul is late.
Paul is here.
He's not gonna make dinner.
We gotta go.
This assassination of Paul Castellano,
has local and federal officials looking for
the men who did it and for the motive.
Finding either are both
extremely difficult,
given the secrecy
of organized crime.
We may never know why
Castellano was killed.
Louis Young is standing
by in Staten Island,
at the Castellano home.
Mafia kingpin Paul
"Big" Paul Castellano,
was gunned down gangland style
in midtown, Manhattan.
The 70 year old, reputed,
head of the largest and
the most powerful crime
family in the country,
the Gambino family.
Uncle Ang?
Where is my father?
- He's gonna be here soon.
- Is everything OK?
He is OK.
I learned for Paul.
It would be a terrible
mistake to think that
this is a good time going
around and shooting up people.
He is on a jet,
he's over Iceland
and the stewardess comes up and she says:
"My name is Pussy Galore".
He says: "I must be dreaming."
Fellas...
We don't know who killed Paul and Tommy.
But we are gonna find out.
Conduct our investigation,
get to the bottom of this.
That being said...
our job is now to maintain continuity.
Make sure nobody thinks
family is falling apart here.
So...
I nominate...
John Gotti.
I second the motion.
To the new boss!
Here he is.
Congratulations, John.
How does it feel?
Feels like times have changed.
It's good.
I mean how does it feel to be here?
This was Neil's joint.
It feels right.
It feels like it's what
he would have wanted.
It feels...
Wherever he is, he is watching us.
Yeah. And he ain't the only one.
I'll talk to you about that...
Nick Vilante's widow lives
upstairs.
We can't take her out on the street,
but if we have a serious conversation
or she whining or it's annoying, we give
a little something,
she vacates the premise for 20 minutes
and then we take care of it.
I would like some
to clear the floor.
Let them know.
Let everybody know.
Now, everybody comes to me.
They come to me.
"The new godfather"
John Gotti has been the most
note-worthy figure
in the last 50 years.
The head of the Gambino crime
family, a real life godfather.
Shots fired here before the Steak house,
were heard around the world.
People shout at me from cars:
"Say hello to John!"
The most powerful crime boss in America.
Does he glorify the Mafia? Yeah. He's
glorified the Mafia. He's the headhunter.
If I have to go to
another fucking wedding
I think I'd rather go
back to Lewisberg.
Jesus, everybody
have been there. There was good-fellas,
there was non good-fellas.
My brother Pete clocked, 75 guys
come up to me.
Those 75 guys come up to talk to me
but they got nothing to offer me.
Conversation, if
conversation is the cow it'd
be the fattest fucking guy in in the world.
Jesus...
Rudy?
Can I talk to you a minute?
Yeah, John.
You deliver the envelope
to Dominic's wife yesterday?
Yeah, just like you told me.
No. Not just like I told you.
- I dropped it off.
- Who did you bring with you?
Well, I was gonna bring my niece...
But you didn't. You didn't.
One simple rule.
Don't you ever go to a guy's
house while he's away
and see his wife alone.
And if you ever do this again,
I'll perk a bus upon your
ass fucking sideways!
You understand that?
Yeah, John.
Sorry, John.
Sorry.
Stay seated.
John's getting too much press.
Ought to learn to duck.
He's got too much pride to duck.
If he don't give a fuck
he's gonna die in jail, the gutter.
Making us look bad.
Then this DeCicco...
We know he arranged the hit on Paul.
That can't go unchecked.
Otherwise, we got capos working their
left N right in home.
Not now, not ever.
Frankie!
Frank! Frankie!
Whore!
It was meant for you.
What are you talking about?
I am telling you it was,
you know who did it.
I heard it on good authority.
He and Gas pipe Casso are like
two piece in a fucking pie.
Who heard... You heard! Your ears
are bigger than your mouth.
OK first of all, I'm friends with Chin.
Sam and Pipe go way back, am I right Sam?
Am I right Sam?
What? And they are all grieving about Paul?
Why would they grieve about Paul?
Look, whoever killed Paul
did everybody a fucking favor.
Maybe it was the cops, yeah, you know.
They put us against each other.
That's what they want us to believe.
Am I right?
Let's take care of business.
Angelo tried to take matters
into his own hands.
With an unsanctioned hit
on Gas pipe Casso.
That didn't workout too well for nobody.
- Gas pipe?
- Who the fuck are you?
Good guys, bad guys,
come in many different colors.
New York's finest
serving 2 masters.
I got all day.
I got whole week.
My man, it's just me and you.
We are just, hanging out in the basement.
Just give me a name.
Tell me who it was.
That hurts, doesn't it?
I can make it stop.
I can make it all go away.
Give me a name.
Angelo Ruggierio.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You handle it,
Angelo try to whack another
main guy without permission?
You got no proof of that.
The shooter need a little encouragement,
but he told Gas pipe,
he named Angelo.
And there is no reason to disbelief it.
Do I believe everything I hear?
No!
So I'm gonna do my own
investigation in this.
Oh yeah?
How's the other investigation going?
Heard anything about the
Sparks Steak House?
Yeah. Their Caesar salad
is to die for.
Angelo has been asking for this a long
time. There is no dispute about that.
Let me tell you something Chin.
Nobody touches Angelo. Nobody.
If it's true that he acted
without my approval,
I'll put him on a fucking shelf like that.
I know Angelo's more than a brother to you.
But Angelo went off the record.
- This was unsanctioned.
- OK. But let me tell you something.
Life means more than anything to Angelo.
OK. He is a war horse.
It means more than it does to you or to me.
He wakes up thinking about it,
he goes to bed thinking about it.
If I put him on a shelf for life
it's worse than putting a fucking
bullet through his heart.
Then I vow to close this matter.
The matter is closed.
The last time
they moved me John, do you know
the only thing I took with me?
Your indictment. That was it.
And do you know why I brought it? Because
I don't give a fuck about my cancer.
I don't care what they do to me in here.
My concerns are you.
I know that.
I must have read it 50 times
and I tell you I don't see it.
I told you once I would
follow you over at cliff.
And I meant it.
But I am thinking about my family now.
Your family? What family are you talking
about? You talking about your 400
brothers, cousins and uncles?
Being a man is not being some guy
who is looking for closure, John.
My freedom and my life
take a back seat to my duty
and manhood.
These are my standards, John.
OK, now listen up. This is important.
Never do anyone a small injury.
You wanna hurt someone,
hurt him so bad
he will never come back at you.
Neil used to say to me:
"The boss is the boss is the boss."
It ain't titles that honor men.
It's men that honor titles.
What did you do?
I did what I thought was best for you.
I save your life Ang.
I all I can do.
Son of a bitch killed Frank!
I am not going to war
with the Chin for the sake
of Gas pipe fucking Casso.
I ain't doing it.
Now listen to you
Just 10 kinds of
shitstorms coming down
on us and you know
what I had to do?
We had to have a meeting
with the Commission.
Why? Because of you. Because of you!
Every boss wanted you dead.
Everyone.
You're on the shelf for life.
That's it.
Go.
Get out of here.
Uncle Ang, he needs you.
He made a big fucking mistake.
Don't say another word. Don't you say
one word against your father.
You hear me?
I was forced.
I can not treat him
differently than others.
If I let you violate my rules,
the very principles that we live by,
it weakens me and that weakens you.
Now, one day, you may be the shot caller,
you may be the one,
there is making the rules,
and then you would be responsible
for enforcing those rules.
You know what I'm saying?
You give me my middle name Angelo.
How do you expect me to
turn my back on him?
You pray that I don't know about it.
I love him too.
Go to bed.
Who cares if he goes to see Angelo?
It's not like John's a part of that life.
Victoria, please...
Don't start. OK?
Will the defendant please rise?
Has the jury reached a verdict?
"We, the jurors, in the above case"
"find the defendant, John
Joseph Gotti, not guilty."
I won this trial
fair and square.
Thanks to little down payment
to one of the jurors.
But by 3rd victory over the government,
the media nicknamed me
"The Teflon God".
I guess it stuck.
Mr Gotti, are you the head of the
- Gambino crime family?
- I'm head of my family.
Ms Gotti, do you know what your
husband does for a living?
He provides.
- Do you know why we're here?
- No.
- Do you know everybody in this room?
- Yes.
This is a society of brothers.
The Cosa Nostra.
You are now about to be inducted as
a member of the Gambino family.
Honor this oath. If you divulge
any secret of
this family, your soul
will burn like this saint.
Never raise your hands made man.
Or quote with the made man's wife
you will be killed.
You don't fuck with bums,
engage the civilians.
Use of drugs, prohibited.
Lastly,
most importantly
we don't like rats.
We kill rats.
You are questioned by law enforcement?
You tell them to go fuck themselves.
You are now reborn.
This is your baptism.
And we are your family.
Come here.
I would like you to meet your new soldier.
This is your boss. Your chief.
This is the proudest moment of my life.
I am so fucking proud of you.
Look at us!
Hey.
Come on.
Hi Elisa...
Johnny.
Like I said, it's getting tougher.
It's not getting easier.
You look around you. You got a
few good soldiers, am I right?
- Yeah dad, I think you are right.
- OK.
But this is not the time to make 20 bucks.
You know what kind of guys I need?
I need guys
that do more than just kill
I need guys whose hearts
beat the same,
otherwise, this won't work.
And the law is coming down hard on us.
You know that.
Of course, if it comes to worse,
we could find you a safe house,
get you out of the country.
I don't run.
And I don't hide in shadows either.
You know what I need?
I need one year on the street uninterrupted
and I will build something
that nobody can destroy,
100 years from now, we are both dead but it
will be and continue to be a good thing.
Being one hell of a legacy to leave.
A legacy. Be it
an hour from now, be it tonight
be it a 100 years from now, when we're
gone, it will be the Cosa Nostra.
And I'm not talking about the gangs,
I'm not talking about clans.
I'm talking about New York, far to
the fucking west coast and back.
It's gonna be the way
I say it's gonna be.
About a year after I put him on a shelf
Angelo Ruggierio died of cancer.
Ang... I know I hurt you.
But you've fucked up.
And I had to do
what was best for the family.
Frankly,
I think he died of a broken heart.
By the way, I almost forgot...
Sammy thinks that you should
be running your own crew now.
Your credit to your father..
Normally I don't show you no favor, but
this time, I'mma help you out.
I'mma hand pick your crew.
I'mma give you Bobby.
Because I trust him with my life.
And I trust him with your life.
- Is that okay with Bobby?
- Go ask.
What? Be under a little punk like you?
Holy Virgin... never in life.
It's you, the boss, now.
You say the word, I will go for a...
You are already hurt, you're
getting married today.
Yeah. Where is Victoria?
Hey. Good to see you.
Congratulations.
Nice work, John. Nice work.
Vic?
Hello. How is it going?
- Good to see you.
"Neil used to say:
This life of ours is a wonderful life."
"If we can get away with it."
The man some people consider to be
organized crime's boss of all bosses,
John Gotti, was indicted today for
the 4th time in 5 years.
Gotti is charged with the 1985 murder
of the mob boss Paul Castellano.
The prosecutors hopes their best testimony,
this time will come from
Gotti's own mouth.
You look at me like I don't know who I am.
I am the new boss.
I do whatever the fuck I want, without
stepping all the bounds.
Now I'm telling you.
If something happens to me,
and I end up in a can,
I want Sammy to be the acting boss.
- Is that clear?
- Clear.
These are my wishes.
I would be a billionaire
if I was looking to be poor.
All I want is this sandwich.
Every time I fucking turn around,
there is a new company.
Every time we got a partner
or the boss to fuck with us.
We kill them...
- He's a yellow dot.
- I took your word for, Sam.
I allowed it to be done.
Yeah he probably won't.
He is not gonna be here
for breakfast.
They took him away the last night.
Please give your name.
Salvatore Gravano.
Do they call you Salvatore?
Sammy.
Mr Gravano, could you please
speak in through the microphone.
Sure.
I didn't follow my own advice.
Never trust anyone who
hasn't done time.
That's where men are made.
Sammy the bull became Sammy the rat.
The government cut him a deal after
admitting in his part in
19 murders and
testifying against me.
John Joseph Gotti,
you have been convicted on all counts of
criminal racketeering, murder, and
conspiracy.
You are hereby remanded to serve a
term of no less than 5 life sentences.
You will also be assessed
to 50 dollar court fee.
Do you have anything to say?
Yeah, your honor.
The 5 life time bids, that's okay,
but the 50 dollars surcharge...
You are a tough guy.
Today... another milestone in the
fight against organized crime.
The Teflon is gone
the don is covered with Velcro
and every charge in the indictment stuck.
Mayhem outside Brooklyn's
federal court house
as John Gotti gets life.
And his supporters cry foul.
Demanding a retrial
they rushed police line...
They pulled a lot of dirty tricks.
I don't believe there are witness.
Then tried to break into the
court to free the mafia boss.
He's a good guy.
He does a lot for the community, you know?
Put him away for nothing.
After today's arrest his supporters smashed
and overturned cars.
The verdict on John Gotti
is less likely to be overturned.
Law enforcement officials
fear that a violent
power struggle may happen
within Gotti's family.
May happen within Gotti's family.
And ironically, the only
one who may be able to keep the peace
is John Gotti.
My loyal crewman, Eddie Lino
was the first to go down.
Bobby Boriello, my closest
friend and my son's right arm
was next.
That's the life.
They understood that.
What's going on?
There is a contract out on me
and the rest of Sammy's crew.
- Who's behind it?
- Jimmy Brown and Joey Fanatti.
Jimmy Brown and Joey Fanatti...
They are after you too Johnny.
"Like father, like son".
- Why are you pissed off?
- I had to read about it!
It's on the cover of the paper!
- What papers?
- Our son is a target!
- The Daily News? The fucking post?
- Yeah the Daily News and the Post.
I already buried a son.
You want me to bury another
then you will bury me too.
You swore to me in our own bed,
you promised that you would not
bring him into that world.
What world? What world
are you talking about?
Tell me the world you're talking about!
I brought him into this world,
you brought him into the life.
Ah come on, shut the fuck up!
You don't know what...
Where are you going? Get back here!
Fuck!
I am not gonna beat around the bush.
I am gonna ask you a question.
According to your answer, one
of us is gonna stand down.
The chief ordered this?
No. So don't play dumb with me.
This fucking nonsense about
Sammy's and his crew
you telling me it came from my father?
Then I suggest you stand down my friend.
Oh, you're prepared to defend these guys?
No. I am prepared to defend my father.
Whatever he says goes. Period.
Okay.
Five organized crime families
are in a state of a
New people are moving up taking the place
of the older ones who are now in prison
or who ever killed.
Locked up, or held under indictment,
virtually, every
boss of every family in New York city
and throughout the US.
You can't be fucking kidding me...
What the hell is going on?
What do you think is going on?
Jesus...
Kids, come to daddy. Come here.
I will be gone for a little while.
Come here.
Don't worry about daddy.
I will be back in a little while.
We are today
4 federal indictments
charging a total of 40 defenses
with a wide spread pattern of
racketeering and other crimes
including multiple extortion,
murder conspiracy,
telecommunication fraud, illegal gambling,
money laundering...
Defendant's charge include, John A.
Gotti, also known as "Junior",
who was alleged to have exercise
supervisor control over the Gambino family
since his father John J.
Gotti was convicted
of federal racketeering charges in 1992.
These are just bullshit charges.
John, there's no way
that they can tie you to
any of those specific crimes.
They don't have to.
It's the recoil conspiracy,
that's the problem.
They just have to prove I'm
a member of the enterprise.
- We can beat them.
- And then what?
They just throw more charges at
me, like they did with my father.
I've had enough.
I have been pulling back.
I am ready to move on with my life.
Are you saying what I'm
think you're saying?
Alright.
John, if that's what you want to do, if
you're ready to walk away from this life,
I am happy for you.
Just understand there are potential
consequences to that decision.
And there gonna be people out there
who are gonna be very unhappy
with the decision you make.
That's why Charlie, you need to arrange
for me a meeting with my father.
And he's is to come for me directly.
He is dying.
He was my cause.
Now it's time to move on.
I want closure.
John, I got no cancer in my brain
and I got no cancer in my heart.
But what I wouldn't do, to have one
more time to go into that court room
and show them what a man
is, break their holes.
You show them what a man in.
You show them what it takes to have this.
Now, we only got 5 minutes left.
I don't know when or if
I will ever see you again.
And I don't know if I got through
to you or not, but I know,
you got a lot of thinking to do.
I know.
I miss seeing you, John.
You have no idea how
much I miss seeing you.
You know,
this meeting, today,
was worth 55 years
hanging upside down.
Because now you know how I feel.
I love you and I adore you...
I know.
So...
You do what you have to do.
And don't worry about me.
It doesn't make sense.
What will be will be.
You stand up strong, put your head up.
Don't Cry.
Don't let this have this satisfaction.
Come on.
PLEA AGREEMENT
Scissors.
Here sir.
What are you looking at me for?
You are gonna be here when I'm 82.
- You are beautiful.
- Thanks Gotti.
You ever met my wife much?
Why you fighting so hard?
If you keep this, they are just
gonna send you back to solitary.
Every day I am alive
is to fuck your government.
You understand?
My son Peter was at my bed
side till the very end.
I didn't want Vicky or
girls to see me like that.
I made Vicky promise
and she respected my wishes.
He is in a lot of pain.
I know that Morphine's no longer working.
Now, we can give him Ativan.
It will induce a coma.
He will be alive, but
he won't feel the pain.
Think about this, Peter.
It's your call.
You keep your head up...
and be strong.
Okay?
Promise me.
I promise.
Alright.
Hey yo J! Check it out!
One of the high profile
mobsters of recent times,
John Gotti, died today
in a prison hospital in Missouri,
after a battle with throat cancer.
Gotti was known as "The
Teflon Don"
or "the deper don,
nickname due to his taste"
for wearing fancy double breasted suits.
Gotti was acquitted
a number of times
prior to being sentenced to
5 consecutive life terms
in 1992.
John Gotti dead today
at age 61.
Everybody here knows
that he was a great man.
Look he might have been in jail, but you
know something, nobody is the saint.
He didn't go around killing civilians,
normal people of the street
or anything like that.
He killed his own kind.
"John Gotti forever"
When he went to prison,
the crime rate
started going up.
The street wants to taken over.
It was a lot cleaner neighborhood
when Mr Gotti was around.
"John Gotti will live forever"
How could you be so naive?
Once they get you in,
you will never be free again.
They say you win this time but next time
they will make sure that you're gone.
This is bullshit!
A hundred more fucking years?
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
John! Calm Down!
No! My father told me they
would never let me go!
He told me that. They wanna
fight the legacy of John Gotti?
Well, let them fight John Gotti!
We would like to believe
that a trial in its purest form
is a search for the truth.
But search for the truth requires
willingness to see the truth.
Yesterday, the prosecutor
spoke to you about what he perceived to be,
the courage of his witnesses.
Well the truth is,
speaking up behind someone
and shooting them in the
head is not an act of courage.
It's an act of deception,
it's a display of treachery,
and it's a demonstration of
a cold blooded willingness
to put their own interests
above that of anyone else,
regardless of the consequences.
Contrast that with the
courage required of John,
who admittedly was in that life,
but who paid for his
crimes with many years in prison.
But John had the courage
to walk away from that life.
The courage to tell
his dying father,
to whom the life was everything,
that his obligations were to his family,
not to a crime family.
But reality is John left the life
on his terms.
Cooperation in return
for a reduced sentence?
No thanks.
He said, "I will do my own
time for my own crimes."
In 11 years,
since then the government has spent
millions of taxpayer dollars
in five prosecutions.
They shift John all across the country
under the most horrible conditions
and what they jokingly refer
to is "diesel therapy".
But in the end, they could not provide
even a single credible allegation
of any contact
between John and the enterprise.
Once again, the government just
refuses to see the truth.
When the government goes off the rails
driven by ego and obsession,
it's incumbent upon its citizens to
guide the government back on course.
In this system, in this courtroom,
you, the jury, are the
conscience of the government.
It's time to do the right thing.
Send him home.
Send him home to his wife and his kids.
Send him home to live the
life he chose to live.
He's earned it.
The government tried hard
to break Johnny boy,
but my son took him to task.
5 trials in 37 months,
and the government
walked away with nothing.
Listen to me. And listen to me.
You are never gonna see
another guy like me
if you live to be 5 thousand.
Subtitled by CLARITY.