[THUNDER SOUND EFFECTS]
[HEAVY STONE BEING
PULLED SOUND EFFECT]
[OMINOUS AMBIENCE
ENSUES AND SPEEDS UP]
[FUTURISTIC SOUND EFFECTS]
[CRICKET SOUNDS]
♪ HAPPY PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYS ♪
MAX:
That's enough dufus!
It's my turn!
ROBERT:
Hey, you guys better
save some for Walter
or he's going to be pissed!
Look it's not
even half gone yet.
Here give it here--
You idiots are
going to spill it! Stop it!
Give it here! It's my turn!
Holy shit!
...Is that them?!
Gentlemen...I give you...
Boobs!
Hey! Easy! Don't bend them!
ALL:
[Laugh and Giggle]
BILLY:
Look at the boobs on this one!
Your brother is going
to kill you if he finds out.
Don't worry. He's
out with his friends.
I'll get them back
home before he gets back.
♪ OLD TIMEY MUSIC PLAYS ♪
Vaginas are
just weird looking.
What?
They are just weird looking...
that's all I'm saying.
Fairy.
WALTER/BILLY/MAX:
[LAUGHING CAN BE HEARD]
ROBERT:
Hey! I ain't no fairy.
MAX/WALTER/BILLY:
Fairy! Fairy! Fairy!...
Fairy! Fairy! Fa--
Stop it!
Hey! Watch the magazines!
Help! I'm being
attacked by a fairy!
Guys, stop it!
[LOUD RUMBLING CAN BE HEARD]
[LOUD SWOOSH LIKE SOUND EFFECT]
[GLASS SHATTERING SOUND]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING SOUND
EFFECT CAN BE HEARD]
Holy cow.
Looks like a rock.
Think it's Russian?
WALTER:
It's a meteor dumbass!
Like from space?
No...
It fell out of your Mom's ass.
Shut up would ya?
Dibs!
Yes.
WALTER:
Hey man-- Let me see it!
Let me hold it.
ROBERT:
Let me hold it, come on!
No! I called dibs.
He did... He called dibs.
60's PHOTOGRAPHER:
Alright boys. Let's stop
fighting over that space turd
and get this picture...
I need you to move
in a little closer together.
Squeeze in nice and
tight, nice and tight there.
Now let me see that meteor.
Say cheese!
GROUP:
CHEEEEEEESE!!!!
[STATIC GLITCH SOUNDS]
♪ ROCK AND ROLL MUSIC ♪
GEEK:
What's that?
You talking to me?
Oh that? Thats just a--
--thats just MY
sweet ass meteorite.
Oh yeah...
Chicks are going to dig you.
[LIGHT BEEP SOUND EFFECT]
TV COOKING HOST:
So what you want to do
is mix your dough thoroughly
otherwise your cookies
just wont be moist.
Cause no one
likes an un-moist cookie.
After you are done mixing
and you have added your nuts
[NATURE SOUNDS]
[RATTLING SOUND
EFFECT CAN BE HEARD]
[DOG WHIMPERING SOUND]
[LOUD SWOOSH AND
SPLAT SOUND EFFECT]
[FIRE SOUND EFFECT
AND CRICKETS CAN BE HEARD]
[OMINOUS AMBIENCE]
FARMER:
Stay there Roxy.
[CRICKETS CHIRP AND
FIRE CRACKLING SOUNDS]
[SPOOKY AMBIENCE]
♪SPOOKY SCI FI MUSIC
BEGINS TO PLAY♪
[BLAST OFF SOUND EFFECT]
[WHOOSH SOUND]
[LOUD BANG SOUND]
[MACHINE BEEP SOUNDS]
[CRICKET SOUNDS]
[LIGHT TECH SCI FI
SOUND EFFECT PLAYS]
[SCI FI BEEP SOUNDS]
[SCI-FI TECH SOUNDS
CONTINUE TO BE HEARD]
[WARPING SOUND EFFECT PLAYS]
[LOUD WHOOSHING SOUND]
[WARPING TECH SOUND
EFFECT CONTINUES]
[BUZZING SOUND]
[GUNSHOT SOUND]
Ah! Ah! Ahh!
Ahh! Ah! Ah....Ah...
[SPOOKY DRAMATIC AMBIENCE
CONTINUES TO PLAY]
[SQUIRMING SOUND]
[DRAMATIC SOUND BEAT]
[INTENSIFIED AMBIENCE BEGINS]
[DOG BARKING SOUND]
[DOG WHIMPERING]
[CRUNCHING NOISES]
[CINEMATIC AMBIENCE CONTINUES]
[CINEMATIC MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[MYSTERIOUS AMBIENCE BEGINS]
ANNABELLE:
Hey Dad... I got your
favorite cookies.
Dad?
Are you here?
[RATTLE SOUND]
♪ SPOOKY MUSIC ♪
♪ MUSIC BOX PLAYS ♪
[PHONE RINGS
Dad?
You here?
[STATIC SOUNDS]
[DEEP DRUM SOUND]
[WEIRD SCIFI SOUND]
[INTENSE SOUND BUILDS]
[SHE SCREAMS]
[DRAMATIC AMBIENCE
ABRUPTLY STOPS]
[OTHER WORLDLY SOUNDS]
[TECH, ODD SOUNDS
BECOMING STRONGER]
[TECH BEEP SOUNDS
WITH OMINOUS AMBIENCE]
[DRAMATIC SOUND
BEAT CAN BE HEARD]
[OTHER WORLDLY
AMBIENCE CONTINUES]
[CLICK SOUND EFFECT]
[TECH BEEPS AND
OTHER WORLDLY AMBIENCE]
[WHOOSHING MACHINE SOUND]
[LIGHT DRILLING SOUND]
[MACHINE REVVING AND
BEEPING SOUNDS ENSUE]
[MACHINE BEEPING AND EXTRANEOUS
SCI FI SOUNDS CONTINUE]
[LOW RUMBLING SOUNDS BEGIN]
[SOUND HITS FOLLOWED BY
MYSTERIOUS AMBIENCE]
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS ARE HEARD]
[TRAIN WARNING SOUNDS]
[OTHER WORLDLY
AMBIANCE CONTINUES]
[CHIRPING BIRDS ARE HEARD]
[MACHINE BEEPING SOUND EFFECT]
[LOW DRAMATIC AMBIENCE]
[ROBOT-LIKE ALIEN
SOUNDS CAN BE HEARD]
[HEAVY BREATHING CAN BE HEARD]
[CRACKING SOUND EFFECTS]
[DRAMATIC TECH AMBIENCE]
♪LIGHT SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC BEGINS TO PLAY♪
♪COUNTRY MUSIC BEGINS♪
PHONE:
[INDISTINCT VOICE]
TOW TRUCK DRIVER:
I have no clue where
your darn keys are!
No, I can't come
help you find them!
I'm all the way over
on freakin' Kettle road!
PHONE:
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Yeah. Yeah, you do that.
She would lose her freakin'
head if it wasn't attached.
Alright...let's see
what we got here!
♪COUNTRY MUSIC CONTINUES♪
What the hell?
[ZIPPING SOUND
EFFECT CAN BE HEARD]
[BIRDS CHIRPING SOUNDS]
[OMINOUS AMBIENCE ENSUES]
[CELL PHONE
RINGING SOUND]
♪UPBEAT COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS♪
[CELL PHONE CONTINUES TO RING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER CAN
BE HEARD FROM PHONE]
TOW TRUCK DRIVER:
That's great that you found your
keys but I'm gonna need ya to
shut the fuck up for a minute...
I need you to get your ass in
the car and I need you to come
pick me up on Kettle road.
Just three clicks south of
Cooper's Mill...
Maxine!
Shut up and do it would ya?
And bring some damn
clothes while you're at it...
Because I'm standing in the
middle of the road in my damn
skivvies!
Maxine, that's why!
Just shut your damn
pie hole and start drivin'.
Geeez Louise! That lady
is gonna be the death of me!
[CITY AMBIENCE CAN BE HEARD]
[TRUCK SOUNDS]
[DRAMATIC AMBIENCE
BEGINS TO PLAY]
[BUZZING SOUND]
[OMINOUS AMBIENCE CONTINUES]
[SCARY THUMP]
(she screams)
[DRAMATIC AMBIANCE CONTINUES]
ANGRY DRIVER:
What the fuck man?
Watch where you're going!
Idiot!
GROCERY STORE CASHIER:
Sarah! Hey who's that guy?
SECURITY GUARD
Excuse me sir.
Sir. Yo!
I need you to put
that meat down!
Ma'am no, I am going
to need you to back off ok?
FARMER:
[SCREAMS]
AHH! AHHH!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[CAMERA SNAPSHOT SOUND]
GROCERY STORE CASHIER:
Get down!
[LOUD THUMP SOUND]
BUS DRIVER:
Is everybody OK?
I'll be right back.
[LIGHT OMINOUS AMBIENCE PLAYS]
[LIGHT OMINOUS
AMBIENCE CONTINUES]
[FOOT STEP SOUNDS
WITH CREEPY AMBIENCE]
[SCI FI AMBIENCE
SOUNDS CONTINUE]
CORONER:
Son of a--
K, This is case 7638.
[CREEPY AMBIENCE CONTINUES]
Well you've had better
days there ay buddy.
CORONER:
K, We've got a male,
approximately 45 to 50
years of age.
Struck by a vehicle.
A bus to be more precise and
pronounced dead at the scene.
by paramedics.
K, there is significant blunt
force trauma to the head,
the right upper thoracic,
the right mid torso...
and this is consistent with
this type of vehicular accident.
K...
It appears the large and small
intestines are visible from...
the outside of the body.
And this is due to the large
laceration to the
lower abdomen area.
K, moving on to the
posterior examination--
Jesus!!!
It appears to be
some sort of...parasite.
It's nothing I've ever seen or
any clue what it may be...
[SCI FI AMBIENCE SOUNDS CREEP
IN AND SLOWLY INTENSIFY]
I'm gonna try removing it
from the subjects neck.
[ALIEN SHRIEKS]
CORONER:
Ugh! Aagh!
CORONER
[SCREAMING]
[DRUM ROLL SOUND EFFECT]
[SUSPENSEFUL AMBIENCE BEGINS]
[ELEVATOR DING SOUND]
CORONER:
[ALIEN SCREAMING SOUND EFFECT]
[CYBER BLAST SOUND]
♪SUSPENSEFUL
CINEMATIC MUSIC PLAYS♪
[CYBER BLAST SOUND]
♪CINEMATIC CHASE MUSIC♪
[MUSIC STOPS, EERIE SOUNDS]
♪ SUSPENSE MUSIC ♪
[FIGHT SOUNDS AND SCREAMS]
[CYBER BLAST SOUND EFFECT]
[CAR ALARM SOUND CAN BE HEARD]
♪CINEMATIC ACTION MUSIC♪
[MUSIC STOPS WITH CYMBAL HIT]
[LIGHT CITY AMBIENCE]
CORONER:
[YELLING SOUND EFFECTS]
CAT LADY:
Get off of her!
[SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE]
[BONE CRACK SOUND EFFECT]
[ALIEN-LIKE SCREAM/
HISSING SOUND]
[CYBER BLAST SOUND EFFECT]
[HIGH PITCHED SIREN WAIL]
[EERIE STRING SOUND]
[DRUM HIT SOUND EFFECT]
ALLEY COP:
Hey!
Don't you move!
Put your hands in the air
and lace your fingers
behind your head
Do it!
[CYBER BLAST SOUND EFFECT]
♪ SUSPENSE MUSIC ♪
[CREAKING DOOR SOUND EFFECT]
♪ EERIE MUSIC AND SOUNDS ♪
♪ELECTRONIC DANCE MUSIC♪
PATRON #1:
What was I just saying
about the universe providing?
PATRON #2:
You are right
man what can I say?
Tell her how much you
like blondes... love them.
PATRON #1:
Who are you
supposed to be sweetheart?
PATRON #1:
I don't know what look you're
going for there but ah...
I like it!
♪ELECTRONIC DANCE
MUSIC CONTINUES♪
[CHARGING MECHANICAL SOUND]
[CYBER BLAST SOUND EFFECT]
[UNIFORM SCREAMING ENSUES]
[SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE
AND GRUNTING]
DANCER: Ahh!
[SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE CONTINUE]
[MECHANICAL POWER
OUTAGE SOUND EFFECT]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS CONTINUE
WITH SCREAMS AND GRUNTS]
♪ELECTRONIC DANCE
MUSIC CONTINUES LOUDLY♪
[EXPLOSIVE SOUND
EFFECT CAN BE HEARD]
♪ELECTRONIC DANCE
MUSIC CONTINUES♪
[DOOR OPENING SOUND]
[CYMBAL SOUND]
♪SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
SLOWLY CREEPS IN♪
♪SUSPENSE MUSIC CONTINUES♪
(footsteps underneath)
TACTICAL OFFICER #2:
Clear! Coming out!
[DOOR OPEN SOUND]
[LIGHT
ATMOSPHERIC AMBIANCE]
GEEK:
Yeah, yeah, yeah...No, shit.
♪LIGHT GROOVY MUSIC PLAYS♪
[CREEPY SCI FI SOUND]
[OMINOUS AMBIENCE]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION
COMES FROM THE TELEVISION]
[OMINOUS AMBIENCE
CONTINUES AND INTENSIFIES]
[ALIEN HISSING SOUND EFFECT]
GEEK: Ahhh!
♪ACTION MUSIC ENSUES♪
[ALIEN HISSING SOUND]
♪CINEMATIC ACTION
MUSIC CONTINUES♪
WHAT...THE...FRACK.
Oh my God.
This is isn't happening.
This isn't happening.
Okay...Okay.
Calm down...breathe.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
LANDLORD:
What the hell's
going on in there?!
Oh shit!
I saw you come home
and I know you're in there.
Now open the Goddamn door!
Just go away and call
the police Mr.Bartell...
And animal control
while you're at it!
Can you hear me?!
Open the damn door!
Between all the noise and
your rent once again being late
you're really starting to try
my patience.
Not to mention piss me off!
Ugh!
--the damn door!
Call the police!
Dumbass.
I can't open the door!
That's it!
I'm coming in!
No, no, no you idiot!
Hello?
Where are ya kid?
Get your ass out
here and talk to me?!
Just get the hell out of
the apartment Mr Bartell
What are you talking
about kid? Where are you?
I am in the bathroom!
Just call the police!
The police?
Why do I need
to call the police?
What's all the
commotion in here?
You need to get the hell out
of the apartment Mr Bartell!
There is some sort of ugly ass
creature in there with you.
And I think I
really pissed it off !!!
There's a what?!
Like I said...
there is some sort of creature
thingy in there with you.
A...a what?
What's in here with me?
Are you on drugs or something?
I can't afford rent! How
am I supposed to afford drugs?
Speaking of rent--
--where's my money?
[ALIEN SCREECHING
SOUND EFFECT PLAYS]
LANDLORD
AHH! AHHH!
AHHHHHH! AHHHH!
[SQUISHY LIKE SOUND
EFFECTS ENSUE]
[DRAMATIC AMBIENCE]
[DRAMATIC/SPPOKY AMBIENCE]
[DRAMATIC/SPOOKY
AMBIENCE CONTINUES]
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
[CELL PHONE DIAL
TONE SOUND EFFECT]
911 OPERATOR:
911--What's
your emergency?
911 OPERATOR:
Hello? Please state
your emergency.
Are you there?
I'm sorry...Ha.
Never mind...forget about it.
No, no.
They will lock you in the loony
bin and throw away the key
No more--No more
buying shit online.
[ATMOSPHERIC AMBIENCE]
[HEARTBEAT SOUND
AND DRIPPING SOUNDS]
[FIZZING SOUND AND HER PANTS]
[LIGHT MECHANICAL ZAPPING SOUND]
[MECHANICAL BEEPING
SOUND EFFECT]
[ATMOSPHERIC AMBIENCE]
♪SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BEGINS♪
OFF DUTY DANCER:
Oh! Jesus! You scared me.
Oh, Is this your room?
I--I can leave
if it is. I am sorry.
Anyway do you know what
the heck is going on downstairs?
I tried to come in through the
front there was a whole
bunch of commotion and shit
so I had to go through the back
Hello? Anyone in there?
What? It was on fucking sale.
♪CINEMATIC MUSIC ENSUES♪
[CITY AMBIENCE,
EERIE SOUNDS UNDERNEATH]
DRIVE THRU CASHIER:
Welcome to Mucho Burrito,
how can I help you?
DRIVE THRU PATRON:
Hey hey hey,
(Spanish) Hey girl!
Ayy...I ahh I am
Very hungry
here, I'm hungry right? Eh?
(Drunken Spanish)
I'll have a dos el Classic. Ah
mucho carne, con pollo right?
Um...add some guac...that would
be good. And I, I, I--
Oh wait a sec, wait a sec...
we could get a tango trio here,
give me one of those and um,
scratch the first one, have a
taco trio add the shrimp
add the guac and um...
and the triple, eh... Ay--y--you
know what wait. wait a second.
My--I cut out--My PH
level,my doctor says--
So yeah. Back to the Classico
ok? Yeah and maybe a large
drink, a jurrito.
Ah dos. That would be...good.
DRIVE THRU CASHIER:
Is that everything today?
Si.
-Are you sure?
-Y--Yeah.
Yeah I'm sure,
how much more sure can I be?
Your order is $16.78--
♪ROCK AND ROLL MUSIC BEGINS♪
What? Whaaa!
MOOCHO FUCKO!
♪ROCK AND ROLL MUSIC CONTINUES♪
Hey dude! Asshole!
[CREEPY SPOOKY AMBIENCE]
[CREEPY ALIEN LIKE SNARL SOUND]
[CREEPY LIKE ALIEN
SNARL CONTINUES]
PARKING LOT JOHN:
Oh ah...just like that, ah.
-Oh, you like that?
-Mhm.
Ah, keep going.
Don't stop. Come on.
-What the fuck?
-What?
Don't go anywhere,
I'll get rid of this freak.
The fuck's
your problem man?
Get the hell out of here
you fucking meth head!
[SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE
AND SCREAMING ENSUE]
Please, oh, no...Please!
[CREEPY AMBIENCE,
HER PLEADING]
No, please, no.
[GLASS BREAKING,
HER SCREAMING]
[SHE CONTINUES SCREAMING]
RADIO:
I say unto all the evil--
DRIVER:
Those sinners man
they're going to hell!
RADIO:
Go to hell
one day. We live--
DRIVER:
...the gospel truth,
the gospel truth!
RADIO
Where nothing makes sense,
Satan and his claws into us.
You would look up and say oh
lord Jesus please save me,
--there is only one way out
my brothers I am telling you to
avoid the hell fire and that
is to say yes to Jesus.
[OMINOUS CITY AMBIENCE]
[BELLS JINGLE IN BACKGROUND]
[OMINOUS ALIEN SOUNDS]
[DRAMATIC DRUM HITS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[SPOOKY MYSTERIOUS
AMBIENCE ENSUES]
[DRAMATIC DRUM BEATS]
[ALIEN HISSING SOUNDS]
Please, help. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no! Please help me!
Please help me--
[ALIEN HISSING]
[OMINOUS/MYSTERIOUS SOUND]
No! I beg you! No!
No! I beg you!
[SPOOKY DEADLY
AMBIENCE CONTINUES]
[ALIEN HISSING
CAN BE HEARD]
♪MYSTERIOUS MUSIC
CONTINUES TO PLAY♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
CAN BE HEARD]
Ok! Come on. Let's go. Get her!
[ALIEN HISSING QUIETLY]
[GLASS SHATTERING
IN BACKGROUND]
[MYSTERIOUS AMBIENCE]
[MYSTERIOUS
AMBIENCE CONTINUES]
[HER FOOTSTEPS ARE HEARD]
[ATMOSPHERIC AMBIENCE]
[EACH TRACKS THE SOUND
OF THE OTHERS FOOTSTEPS]
[MYSTERIOUS AMBIENCE
SLOWLY INTENSIFIES]
[CYBER GUN SOUND EFFECT]
[SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE
WITH GRUNTS AND CHAIN SOUNDS]
[CINEMATIC MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[FEMALE SCREAMS]
♪ WEIRD ALIEN MUSIC ♪
[MORE FIGHT GRUNTS,
SCREAMS AND GROANS]
[CINEMATIC MUSIC
WITH CHOKING SOUNDS]
[DRAMATIC DRUM HIT]
[PIERCING FLESH SOUND]
[SCREECHING SOUND]
[SHE COUGHS]
♪LIGHT ATMOSPHERIC MUSIC♪
[JARRING, PIERCING SOUND]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC
FOLLOWED BY HER SCREAM]
[PUNCHING, GRUNTING,
FIGHT SOUNDS CONTINUE]
[CINEMATIC MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[CYBER GUN BLAST]
[PIPE CLANKS, DRAMATIC
MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[DRAMATIC DRUM HITS]
[SQUISH SOUNDS OF FLESH,
HER BREATHING HARD]
[WEIRD SCREECHING]
[HEAVY BREATHING
WITH FOOTSTEPS]
[LABORED ALIEN BREATHING]
[LIGHT WHOOSH SOUND EFFECT]
[DRAMATIC DRUM HITS,
CLANK OF ITEM HITTING FLOOR]
[MYSTERIOUS AMBIENCE]
[SCRAPING SOUND]
[COUGH]
♪ DRAMATIC MUSIC BUILDS ♪
[OUTDOOR AMBIENCE,
BUS DRIVING SOUND]
HELP!
(knocking sounds)
We need your help! We don't have
any money and we have to get her
to the hospital! Can
you help us please?
BUS DRIVER #2:
I can take you to
the next stop. Get on.
BUS DRIVER #2:
It's a two minute
walk to Mercy Hospital.
Thank you so much.
[MYSTERIOUS AMBIENCE]
♪LIGHTER TONE MUSIC BEGINS♪
[TIRES SCREECHING
SOUND EFFECT]
[BUS, NORMAL SOUNDS]
[EERIE AMBIENCE
SLOWLY INTENSIFIES]
[GURGLING, ODD BREATHING
SOUNDS, STRUGGLING]
Are you OK?
[COUGHING, GASPING]
[FEMALE SCREAM,
TIRES SCREECH ON BUS]
[SCREAMS,
MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[ALIEN HISSING/SCREECHING]
[CONTINUED SCREAMS
MIXED WITH ALIEN SCREECHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC
AND SCREAMING INTENSIFY]
[ODD QUIET]
[DRAMATIC DRUM HIT]
[DRAMATIC AMBIENCE BUILDS]
[OTHER WORLY AMBIENCE]
[AMBIENCE INTENSIFIES,
BECOMING MORE DRAMATIC]
♪ DRAMATIC MUSIC BUILDS
WITH AN OMINOUS FEEL ♪