~ Guardians of the Tomb (2018) ~
a.k.a. "7 Guardians of the Tomb"
"The Nest" / "Riddle Nest" / "Spider Nest" / "Spiderweb"
[Even though we are fighting,
you're still my big sister.]
- What are you doing here?
- I'm sorry.
I did try to call.
Jia, we need to talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
I didn't ask you in.
It's your brother.
He's missing.
What?
Are you kidding me?
He called from
the research site in China.
Were you there too?
What was that?
- Go take a look.
- Ethan!
Whoa!
Luke.
Luke!
I will find Luke.
But I need your help.
I have a team on the ground
in China.
We fly out tonight.
Could be in Shanghai
drinking beer.
Oh, come on. You should
take pride in your work.
Work? We might as well be
looking for Bigfoot.
Yeah.
That's what makes it fun.
Fun? A wild weekend in Bangkok...
that's fun.
You need to get out more,
mate.
Get my phone.
Righto.
Whoa-ho!
Who's Jia?
Oh, Jesus.
She just doesn't give up.
Are you nuts?
She's smoking hot.
Hey, if you're not interested,
I could...
Hey.
She's my sister.
The taipan.
One of the deadliest reptiles
in the world.
They are also
the most aggressive.
But I am an expert
in venomous animals,
so if anyone who says
the snakes are more afraid of you
then you are of them,
has never met
one of these.
One bite can paralyze
your entire
central nervous system,
shutting down your major organs
and killing you in hours.
But don't worry,
we can play with this one...
It's fake.
- You want to play?
- Hmm.
Be careful.
It's gonna... bite you!
Don't worry,
I have a little brother too.
I bet one day
you'll be just like him.
He's a super-brave adventurer.
The rosy periwinkle...
long rumored
in its native Madagascar
for precious healing powers.
Nobody else believed it,
but our investors took a risk.
Together we've saved the lives
of over 12 million children
who would have otherwise
died of lymphocytic leukemia.
That, and it's the best
investment they ever made.
This is all very educational,
Dr. Kitteridge,
but if you want us to commit,
we need details.
And you'll have them.
We have a team in the field
due to report back any minute.
Gentlemen, I have a reputation
for achieving the impossible.
I'd like you to trust that.
Thanks for coming.
Lisa, will you please
see our friends out?
It'll be my pleasure.
- So, are you flying out tonight?
- No, in fact, tomorrow.
- There's other investors.
- Mason, we're almost broke.
- We need money.
- I know.
- I'll get it.
- When?
Every big pharma company
on the planet
is looking for a breakthrough,
and you've got guys
chasing a fairy tale.
It's not a fairy tale.
I better myself before, Andrew.
I'm willing to do it again.
We're on the cusp of something
no one has ever seen before.
Something that would
bring Biotech back
as a leader in life extension
pharmaceuticals.
Here. Let's have a look.
You sure this is the place?
Here is where the locals
put the last sighting.
The northern edge.
Man,
it smells like someone died.
What the hell's that?
Gas build-up from
the old mine, I bet.
Probably methane mixed
with hydrogen sulfide.
It's only dangerous
if you strike a match.
Wasting your time.
The sooner we look around,
the sooner you'll get your beer.
Aaah!
Luke! Luke!
Luke, talk to me!
You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- What the hell's going on?
Answer!
Luke!
- Aaah!
- What?
What is it?
Luke, you're freaking me out,
man. Say something.
I can't believe it.
Ethan, get down here!
- What? No way!
- Now, Ethan.
I have
air transport waiting in Beijing
to take us to the rescue camp.
I'm... so sorry, Jia.
Especially after
what happened to your parents.
Authorities have confirmed
they've found the wreckage
of a light plane
which disappeared
from radar screens
over three weeks ago
near the northern border.
It is believed to be
the plane of Biotech CEO
John Lee,
and his wife Catherine Lee.
You come to my house...
my parents' house...
and you tell me the same thing
that happened to my parents
has happened to my brother.
It's not the same.
He's alive.
- I know he is.
- Shut up.
You were my father's partner.
You're nothing to me.
Lee, who founded the
Biotech pharmaceuticals empire
with Dr. Mason Kitteridge,
was 52 years old.
They leave behind
two young children.
Hi Jia, I'm now at the airport.
Er, what we talked the other day,
don't let that bother you.
Because, I'm not a kid anymore.
Don't worry about me.
I'll keep that in mind.
Luke!
Jia...
Sister!
Oh, don't land there.
Got all the room in the world,
and lands beside the car.
Watch your head.
- Looks like a big one, huh?
- Oh, yeah.
Jia, this is Chen Xhu,
our archeologist.
- Hi.
- Milly Piper. Logistics.
- Milly.
So, she's your consultant, huh?
Consultant on what, exactly?
It's need-to-know only.
You don't need to know.
Oh, well, that cleared
everything right the hell up.
Earlier today
we picked up a signal.
It's patchy,
but it could be
a real-time beep
from Luke's GPS.
But, we have a problem.
It started about eight hours ago
out of the Gobi Desert.
This one's a monster.
Surface winds
at about 20 knots,
the pressure dropped,
the speed started picking up.
- What's that?
- The last coordinates of Luke and Ethan.
And the signal's still moving.
It'll be a category 4
dust storm
by the time
it hits this valley.
We'll be looking
for a needle in a haystack.
- How long?
- Hard to know.
With the air this dry,
the storm could hit
any time in the next 24 hours.
We got two choices.
We wait, we lose
whatever life's left on the GPS.
We go,
and we get caught in this,
then I'm putting
all your lives at risk.
Where did you come from?
This is our search
and rescue specialist,
Jack Ridley.
Jack, thanks for coming.
Good to see ya.
Dr. Jia Lee.
One of the men
we're looking for
is her brother.
You serious?
- Can I just explain something?
- Emotion clouds judgment,
and bad judgment
is how people end up dead.
Maybe you are right.
- Oh, oh, uh.
- Okay.
Not okay!
Who do you think you are?
You don't know me.
I don't need anybody's permission
to be here.
Especially someone who rides a Harley
and hasn't shaved for a week.
Two days.
And that is a Royal Enfield.
Not a Harley.
Actually, I asked her
to join us.
She has skills that could
be very helpful to us.
All right.
Have it your way.
But you do what I say...
when I say it.
Deal?
Okay.
Now, we have a four-hour drive
into the mountains,
and that is a long way,
especially with the dust storm
breathing down our ass.
? A know-it-all. ?
? I also speak Chinese. ?
Let's go!
Hah.
You know
that's bad for you.
Eh, not if you
only eat ten a day.
Hey, Jack.
I want to put my bag back there.
Jia, go ahead.
All right.
- Do you know him?
- Ridley?
He came here
about two years ago,
after his last rescue mission
in Nepal.
The boy wonder.
Used to be a first-responder
for International Rescue.
They had him set
to run emergency response
back in New York.
What's he doing here?
Something bad went down
on his watch.
He won't talk about it.
Though I wouldn't mind
trying to get him to.
Pack that on this side.
I'm in the back?
Come on.
What am I, the dog?
Don't answer that.
Got everything you need?
All right.
You all right
back there?
The storm's closing in
on the south ridge at 20 knots.
Come on, Gary,
let's go.
Otherwise we're gonna
lose the signal.
It's so barren.
It's amazing, isn't it?
How nature always finds a way
to survive.
The storm's holding for now,
but, the signal's getting weaker.
There's gonna be
a lot of electrical discharge.
We need to stay ahead
of this monster.
Not far now.
Look out!
What are they?
Keep an eye
on that storm.
Okay, got it.
What's that smell?
Hydrogen sulfide.
This area is dotted
with old coal mines.
Gas is probably escaping
from underground.
- Ohh!
- Jeez.
There's nothing inside,
but there's puncture wounds
all over the body.
Looks like
some kind of bite.
Nah?
Don't know what you're missing.
Type 2 diabetes.
- Oh, my God. Jack!
- Yeah?
- My God.
- I can see it.
- Look at the size of it!
- Get to the jeep!
To the jeep! Jia!
We have to go!
Get in!
Go on, Gary!
- What's happening?
- It's a firestorm
from the coal mine.
It only takes a spark.
You hit a gas pocket
in the wrong place...
- boom! Fourth of July.
- Go, Gary!
- Come on, let's go!
- The wheels are just spinning!
Drive. Drive!
Chen, get out!
Gary, get out here!
I'm the driver.
Why am I pushing?
Push! Push!
- Okay!
- Gary, let's go!
- Get in!
- Hurry up!
- Move! Move!
- Drive, Jia!
Why is she driving?
Where do I go?
There's an abandoned mine
less than a mile ahead.
There may still be buildings
there we can shelter in.
If they're still standing.
Good luck
finding 'em in this.
Be careful.
Get back on the road!
It's a monster.
We're never gonna make it.
The rocks!
Go, go, go!
Mason, go!
Gary, get into the house!
Come on!
Milly, come on!
Everyone inside!
Aaah!
Get the curtains
off the windows.
Shut those windows.
- Ow.
- Anybody here?
Jia. Here, take this.
Drink slowly.
- Hello!
- Hello, anyone here?
Good.
You do what I say
when I say it.
Got you.
Thanks.
Is that thing sanitized?
Don't be a baby.
Never should have come.
Now eight us will die out
here, instead of two.
You knew what you were
getting into, huh?
Everybody listen to me.
With a burn this intense,
the radiant heat will kill us
way before any flame does.
There must be something
underground.
A storm cellar.
Let me take a look.
What about Luke and Ethan?
They're on their own
until the storm passes.
Right now we need
to take care of ourselves.
So for now,
this rescue mission's over.
Is that a fact?
The mission might be over
for you, but not for me.
Ridley, there's something here.
Mason.
Why haven't we
seen any people?
Mason.
I know it's not my place,
but what was Luke looking for?
You're right.
It's not your place.
What?
I was just trying
to comfort you.
I should...
I should go with her.
Just to, um...
just to keep her safe.
Oh.
Oh my dearl...
why are you hiding in here?
Just you?
Put down the knife.
I won't hurt you.
What is your name?
Yin.
What about your family?
It's very dangerous here.
Come out here quick.
Quick!
It's about to catch fire here.
Move quickly!
Chen.
Hello.
You okay?
Chen,
we better get out of here.
Now.
Now! Let's go! Trust me!
Chen.
We gotta go, right now.
Come on.
Come on, trust me.
Huh?!
- Aaah!
- Chen!
Let's get out of here!
Come on!
Come on, I've got you!
Let's go! Let's go!
What happened?
- Jia!
- Chen.
Is everything all right?
What happened?
This is a funnel-web bite.
As in funnel-web... spiders?
As in funnel-web giraffe.
You could be wrong.
It's not like you're an expert.
Actually, she is.
I don't like spiders, okay?
Wait. Funnel-webs are only found
in Australia.
What are they doing here?
Chen. Breathe slow.
Panic only pumps the poison
faster through your blood.
You are a first-responder,
right? So respond.
You know the pressure
immobilization technique?
- Of course.
- Do it.
It's ineffective
with a torso bite.
Jia, no!
Aah!
Let me lean you up, okay?
We need to keep you elevated.
His pulse is dropping.
Open the door!
- How's he doing?
- Not good.
Jack, out back there's
a storeroom with a trap door.
Gary, come here.
Show me.
Watch Chen.
We got five minutes max
before this place goes up
in flames.
You'll be all right, Chen.
Hang in there, mate.
You're gonna be okay,
buddy.
This is gonna make you sick.
So sick you want to die.
That's the anti-venom
fighting the poison in your blood.
Aaaah!
It's locked.
We gotta get it open.
Look for something.
- The storm's getting closer.
- I know.
If you and I survive this,
we should get a drink.
Fertilizer, fuel oil...
Not the kind of cocktail
I have in mind.
What's happening?
Why isn't it working?
But that doesn't make any sense.
I gave him enough.
A double dose would kill him.
He's already dying.
Aaaah!
We're running out of time.
All right.
Can you lift that up for me?
You should run now.
Very creative.
- Go!
- Oh.
It's gonna blow!
Aah!
- What the hell was that?!
- We have a way out.
Get Chen up.
- Yin!
- Gotta hurry!
Yin, come back!
- Come back!
- Yin!
Let's go!
Come on!
We're all safe.
Come here.
Up you go.
I got you.
Don't touch the line.
The funnel-webs
react to vibration in the silk.
To them,
it means feeding time.
Feeding time?
Awesome.
Made it!
Ah, I don't think
this is a very good plan.
- Come on!
- Go!
Roof ain't gonna hold
much longer.
Relax. I'm coming.
I don't want to go.
Don't be afraid. Just follow me.
- I'll go first.
- Come on!
- Just follow my lead.
- Everybody's gonna be okay.
I got you. Good girl.
Everyone spread out.
Mason! Milly! Hurry.
Come this way.
Come on.
Be careful.
- Move it!
- Aaah!
Milly, watch out!
Ohh! Ow!
Milly!
They kill you
in the walls!
Milly, watch out!
Milly!
Ohh! Aaah!
Aah! Milly,
get away from the wall!
I got you! Come on!
- Guys! On the stairs.
- I see 'em! I see 'em!
- Ridley!
- I see it.
Aaaah!
I hate spiders!
Is everyone all right?
What is this place?
Looks like a cave system.
No, it looks like a place
where spiders come from.
Milly...
Where's my pack?
Do you have a tourniquet
in there?
- Stay down.
- Wrap this around here.
There were six vials.
Two broke,
and two were used.
Where are the others?
How much time does she have?
I don't know.
A single bite causes death
in under 12 hours.
And she's been bitten
three times.
And this venom...
is stronger than anything
I've ever seen.
Has anyone else been bitten?
- No.
- Mason. You good?
You knew all along. Didn't you?
Why didn't you say anything?
I had my reasons.
Did you at least tell Luke?
Did you lie to him?
Hey! Save the soap opera
for later.
Ridley, I know
I'm just a driver,
but a bag's not supposed
to do that, right?
Yin! No, wait!
No!
The GPS... it's totaled.
Our rescue mission
just got harder.
Oh, you stupid little...
Look what you've done!
I'm sorry. I thought...
The light was flashing.
That's him. I know it.
Wait.
GPS doesn't work underground.
It can if you boost the signal.
Boost it?
That's how Milly
got a reading before.
You got a strong antenna,
leave it at the entry point,
toss down a few receivers
as you go...
you don't lose your connection.
It's like a trail
of bread crumbs.
Luke found a way in...
and we have a way out.
Come on.
- You good?
- Yeah.
- Mason, help Milly.
- Yeah, yeah.
You got her?
Come on, Milly, we gotcha.
The signal won't last
much longer.
- Jia!
- Come on, guys.
I've sent you some
pictures... check it out.
Those two marks.
Are they what
I think they are?
It's too early
to confirm it now.
But it's a spider bite
for sure.
Ahh.
- Need a breather?
- Yeah.
Tool marks.
What were they building here?
There's a legend
of an underground tomb
built over 2,000 years ago.
But it's just a myth.
- Ahh!
- Milly!
I got her.
Let's keep goin'.
Relax, Mason.
I didn't want to call
until I knew what
we were dealing with.
Hold on. Yeah.
Let me get the sat link up.
I've never seen
anything like it.
It's just incredible...
the state of preservation.
I'll send you some pictures.
Check it out.
Okay, uploading now.
Our tests
date him from 200 BC.
But there's no sign
of mummification.
There shouldn't be
any flesh on him at all.
Well, that dating
can't be right.
- The CT scans confirm it.
- Yeah.
And now for the news
you've been waiting for.
When this man died,
he was 300 years old.
It's real.
Ridley, over here.
Oh, good.
I was worried there wasn't
gonna be a mass grave.
You'll be okay, Milly.
I'm slowing you down.
No, you're not.
They were slaves.
See how their heads
are bent over their necks?
That's from chaining their heads
to their hands
so they couldn't run.
I think they were buried alive.
Listen to that carefully.
you would hear this sound first,
then, you couldn't hear the birds singing.
She said the sound came first.
The birds stopped singing.
Then, scratching sound started to
come from the rooms.
Over the walls and on the floor.
It started in the house.
Scratching in the walls
and the floor.
We fought against them.
But there's just too many of them.
They tried to fight back,
but there were too many.
Then, the people were dead.
Then everyone was gone.
It's starting again.
She said it's happening again
right now.
Mason, hang on a second.
- What is it?
- What's going on?
- You hear that too?
- What's happening?
We're gonna take a look.
Say, what was that?
Luke!
Oh, my God!
Get off me!
Can we go now, please?
Milly, let's go.
Let's keep
following this path.
What's it doing?
It's acting as if
there is a web there.
Normally, they wait for
their prey to come to them.
They never hunt in packs.
But here, it seems like
they're working together.
Come on,
let's get out of here.
Let's go. Follow me.
Watch your step.
The spiders behind us...
They're communicating
with the ones around us!
Do funnel-webs do that?
Well, these ones sure do.
These are 2017 funnel-webs,
probably follow each other
on Twitter.
Actually, Weibo.
They don't have Twitter here.
Huh, my bad.
Up there.
Fall behind me.
Stay close.
They're coming! Hurry!
- Mason, help me!
- Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Hurry!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, waiter.
Sorry. I, uh...
I, ur... I forgot to order
a river of molten lava.
You aren't helping.
Here, Milly,
just rest here.
There's no way across.
Chen. Look. Gods.
Jia! Mason!
There's no way across.
- Uh...
- I... I didn't mean to do that.
Gary, what'd you do?
It's a bridge.
Gary, you genius.
Good work.
Totally meant to do that.
All right, you're first.
Come on. Hurry.
Mason, you're next.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
One step at a time.
Slowly, Gary.
That's it.
Let's go.
I don't want to go.
Yeah, okay.
Gary.
Gary!
- Ah, ar...
- You okay?
Be careful, guys.
Gotta switch it to salads.
- Watch your step.
- Easy now.
Good job, you guys.
Come on, we have to go.
Come on, Chen.
- Come on.
- Okay.
- Over here.
- Come on, nice and easy.
Hang on!
- I got you!
- Arr!
Come on! Milly!
It's not gonna hold
much longer.
I got her.
Hurry, Ridley!
The bridge!
- Guys, hurry up!
- We have to go!
- Guys!
- Find him.
Find your brother.
Quickly. Hurry up!
Quickly!
Jump!
We got you!
Come on.
Oh, my God, Milly.
- We have to help her.
- There's no way back.
Milly!
She's gone.
We gotta keep going.
Come on, Jia.
What is this place?
Like an old... armory.
A barracks.
Take this.
Good work, Ridley.
That smell,
what is that?
Whale oil, used to
light the flames of eternity.
Huh, huh.
Well, it's what I use it for.
Well done, Ridley.
The myth says
the underground was built
with traps and secret passages
The passages, to help you
escape from death.
Be nice to escape
from death.
What's she doing?
She's scattering
mugwort leaf.
I remember the smell
from when I was a kid.
It's a herb used in
ancient Chinese medicine
to resist the Five Poisons.
Five Poisons.
Forgot about those.
Spiders taste with their feet.
Maybe there's something in it.
She was the only one
to survive in the house.
We got company.
Back up.
Uh, guys,
I think we should leave.
I think they're
calling their friends.
Never knew an animal
that wasn't afraid of fire.
Come on, come on!
Let's go! Come on!
Uh, Ridley...
Guys, get over here!
Come on, let's go!
Did any get through?
None I can see.
Thought that only happened
in Scooby Doo.
Okay.
This way.
Yin, what's the matter?
Afraid.
Don't be afraid. Come with me.
I don't want to go.
Let me show you something.
My parents left me this when they died.
It brings me luck when I'm lost.
Sister!
Hold on to it.
Trust me.
Will sure lead you out of here.
Mm.
Let's go.
Come on.
This must really be it.
The Emperor's
underground palace.
The myth.
You see, The Emperor believed
that life underground
would be a continuation
of life in the real world.
So he built an exact replica
of his city
around his burial tomb.
But The Emperor
had a great fear of death.
So under the city
he built a series of tunnels
that only he knew about.
So if death really did find him,
he would escape it.
If this is what I think it is,
we are talking about one of the
greatest archaeological finds, ever.
Glad to be a part of it.
This isn't the first time
someone died on your watch,
is it?
Well, look at that.
You're kidding me.
He's close.
Come on, Mason.
Right there with you, buddy.
You look how I feel.
They built this 2,000 years ago?
Yes.
That's Wu Fu.
The Emperor's necromancer.
It's a story about The Emperor's
quest for an elixir.
And he made it
Wu Fu's lifelong task
to fulfill it.
To discover the secret
to eternal life.
So Wu Fu traveled the world...
And on a great island
to the south,
he met men, dark as night...
- Aboriginal Australia...
- Yes, giant masted ships
were found etched
in aboriginal cave paintings.
A shaman there
told him of a secret magic.
There was a crawling creature
and that once a year,
the creature's blood
yielded an enzyme...
Produced only during
their mating season.
The shaman could only make
a few drops of the elixir.
So Wu Fu
brought the creatures home
in their thousands
so he could breed them.
Oh, my God.
Genetic engineering.
Don't you see? These spiders
are built only for two things...
Breeding and killing.
Aggression
often goes hand in hand
with the desire to mate...
Wu Fu unintentionally
strengthened their venom,
their aggression.
He gave his Emperor
and himself
unnaturally long life...
but he also gave the spider
unnatural power to kill.
That's what you get when you
mess with freaking spiders.
Mason! Give me the GPS!
Stand back!
I'm not sharing this.
You do what you can, Jia,
to stop life
from falling through
your fingers,
but you can't.
Back off!
Everything you touch
leaves, runs... dies.
Your parents, your brother...
And now you!
Mason!
You were bitten,
weren't you?
The toxins in your blood
are making you crazy!
I gave you
everything I could, Jia.
All you gave me was hate.
Now go choke on it!
- Mason!
Go to hell!
Mason!
It won't budge!
We're gonna have
a hell of a time
getting out of this place
without that GPS.
Any ideas?
There are often concealed
secret doors, secret switches...
Where's Gandalf
when you need him?
Look around the chamber.
Gary. Table.
What about it?
Get over here.
Just lift it.
- What are you doing?
- Ready?
What has this guy been eating?
Chen.
Look.
Watch your step.
Come on.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
This spider
has an extra set of legs.
All right, on three.
One...
two...
three.
What're you doing?
Put it down.
Please.
That is beautiful.
Come on,
we gotta keep moving to
catch up with Mason.
This way.
Jia...
Yin,
"It's only as frightful as you think it is."
Do you remember that saying?
I remember.
I'll always be by your side.
What's that?
It's an aqueduct.
Now, thanks to the mines,
as dry as the farmland above.
- Let me see that.
- Yeah.
What is it?
I think we should go back
the other way.
It might lead somewhere.
Everything good?
Yes.
Oh! Yes!
Chen!
Jia!
What's happening?
No!
What took you so long?
You mean "Thank you?"
You should be thanking me.
I just cured
your fear of spiders.
Huh?
Thanks.
Hurry!
It's not gonna hold for long!
Go, go! Go in!
Hurry! Go on!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Come on, Gary!
Gary! Quickly!
This place can kiss my ass.
Mine too.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Come on.
Mason has a head start.
Yeah, let's also not forget
that Mason is bat-shit crazy.
I don't think we have to worry
about Ethan anymore.
You know,
I got exactly the same shirt.
What?
That's Luke's.
That's Luke's handwriting.
They have been underground
for several hours.
They found Wu Fu's chamber.
Then the spiders came.
The rest is just
coordinates and symbols.
Jia! Wait!
- What is it?
- A flashlight.
Luke.
It's not Luke. Look. The GPS.
Mason's been here.
Here, take this.
Really?
You will be needing it.
Let's go.
This way.
Through here.
Well, smashed by a rock
and totally waterlogged.
See what I can do this time.
Whoa.
This is the way.
Yes, the murals.
Look. The underground aqueduct.
Water. It all makes sense.
Huh.
Jack.
Get out
and move slowly.
Funnel-webs
can survive underwater.
Get out. Now.
Did it bite me?
It didn't bite you.
It's funnel-web's blood.
Should come in next...
next...
No rush, just...
Just be... next door
when you're ready.
Sister!
Luke!
You okay?
He's gone,
isn't he?
Mason was right.
Everything I touch...
"These things we do,
that others may live."
That's the motto for
Search and Rescue.
Two years ago.
The man I lost in Nepal.
He was my teammate
and best friend.
He slipped.
Busted his ankle.
Before I could get back to him,
there was this
massive aftershock.
That was the last time
I saw him.
Sometimes
you can't save everyone.
The best you can do is try.
Luke!
Thank you.
I promise you,
we're gonna find him.
I think your brother is
showing us the way out of here.
This is the map
of the underground tomb.
And this, this is the symbol
for water.
The Emperor's myth declares
there is an underground aqueduct
around the tomb
so The Emperor could come and go
in the afterlife.
But it would also act as a way out
to the living world
should he escape death.
Tell them about the
pipe thing-o.
If we follow these pipes
into the tomb
and figure out what's north,
we can get out of here.
How good is that? Eh?
We figured it out.
Come on, high-five.
This way.
- Come on, Gary.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- This way!
- Gary, come on!
I can't wait to see
what you got for us in the
next room, Mr. Wonka.
The Emperor's tomb
is through these gates.
Watch out for the lines.
Think before you step.
Careful.
Watchout for the spider lines.
Take your time.
Watch that one.
Watch your head.
That one right under you.
Watch that one, guys.
All right.
This way.
What? Is there another
code to crack?
Yes, of course.
But if we push the wrong tile...
No, no, don't tell me,
let me guess.
A giant dragon
will come out of nowhere
and bite my head off.
Funny, Gary.
We need to hurry.
Okay, well,
has anyone got any ideas?
Well, the tiles
seem to be arranged in pairs,
except these two.
It's a pattern.
I know it.
- ...need to be a level or a switch.
- ...like an encryption...
Luke.
Jia here.
Luke!
Jack!
It's Luke!
You found him?
Luke?
How is he?
He's alive.
Wait! The line.
It's booby-trapped!
Chen, whatever you
were trying to figure out,
you better do it fast.
Okay.
We need to get him up.
Come on.
I got you.
Chen, you got
a way out for us?
The Emperor associated
number six with perfection,
so if we push...
- Chen.
- the number six tile...
Or you could punch it.
Come on!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
So, you found it.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'm a little pissed
at you, Jia.
You forgot to mention that
funnel-web spiders can swim.
Ran into a little trouble
back there
at The Emperor's Jacuzzi.
Don't tell us
you got bit again, Mason.
Yeah, it would be so sad
if that happened.
Luke. We did it, son.
You and I,
we found the miracle!
The Fountain of Youth!
We found hell.
The hell The Emperor created
2,000 years ago.
No. No, no,
you can't believe that.
When I drink this,
I will taste immortality,
the secret men have sought
since the dawn of time.
It's just a pity
it's too precious to share.
Sure you couldn't share
just a little bit?
It's just I've got
this corn here on my pinkie...
Shut up, Gary.
I'm talking now!
You.
I'm on to you.
They're inside you.
Just like they were
inside your mother.
That's how they know
where we are.
She's been leading them to us
all along.
You're lying.
And you lied to us
from the beginning, didn't you?
Yeah. I lied.
I'm a businessman!
What about our father, Mason?
You said you didn't know
where he was going
the day his plane went down.
It's because my father
was close to finding something.
I thought they were dead.
Alright!
A plane crash
in that kind of terrain,
the odds were a million to one
they could survive.
What if they were alive...
but because of you
nobody knew where to look!
I made a decision. I did what
was good for the company.
If I'd given away
their location,
our competition
would've gotten here first!
It wasn't your decision
to make!
And now you're doing it
all over again.
Playing God with people's lives.
Playing God?
This is about becoming God!
Go to hell!
Yeah.
You first.
Ridley.
Luke! Luke!
Are you okay?
Jack.
The elixir.
Mason never got to try it.
Hand me the bottle!
Wu Fu made enough of the elixir
to keep The Emperor alive
and to keep himself alive
to serve him for eternity.
Go get it.
Here, drink it.
You never gave up.
Luke!
I'll never give up on you.
Let's go.
Yeah, I reckon now is
a pretty good time to leave.
This way.
The terrible thing has happened.
What's wrong?
This... The most frightful thing...
Oh, my God.
It's some kind of nest.
They've been leading us here...
Herding us like cattle
to the slaughter-house...
Wu Fu foresaw what happened.
And here the story ends.
As the creatures multiplied,
they mutated and eventually
took over the palace...
and then,
the whole kingdom.
To get out from here
we have to find
"North."
That has to be it.
Stay close to the wall.
Let's go.
Oh, God.
Yin, come on.
Look how big it is.
Look, there's something
strange about the tiles.
What do you mean?
Yeah, but not one says
"Push here to exit."
I'll tell ya why,
'cause nothing's ever simple
on this freaking joint.
Huh, great,
now her friend's join her.
They're communicating
with each other.
Be careful, Yin.
Be careful!
Everything's gonna be okay.
Hey!
We gotta go.
Hurry!
Hold on.
Luke, punch the tile!
Watch out!
It's coming down!
Yin!
- Over there!
- Got an exit!
- Go!
- Gotta get out now!
- Come on, Jia!
Go!
Let's go home.