Let me be very clear
with all of you.
One of you in this room
tonight...
is going to die.
Welcome to Headgame.
Out you go, little guy.
- Okay, how do I look?
- Perfect.
Hot, rich guy asks you out
at the gym.
Why can't that happen to me?
It's bad luck to open that
in the house.
Oh.
Okay, he's here.
I got to go.
I love you.
Have fun...
bitch.
♪ Oh, I wouldn't
Be surprised
♪ If somebody pinched me
And I opened my eyes
♪ To find out
You were just my design
♪ One step from a dream
Inside of my mind
We got two more
states to drive through.
I was going to say,
where are we going?
We're in the middle of nowhere.
I know we are,
and it's getting
really hot right now.
♪ I hold you
So close to me
So...
did you have
a good time tonight?
Yeah.
Me, too.
I hope we're able
to do it again sometime.
♪ Somebody pinched me
And I opened my eyes
♪ To find out
You were just my design
♪ One step from a dream
Inside of my mind
Hey, do you want to meet
some friends of mine?
I'm betting you'll fit right in.
So, what do you say?
Are you game?
Yeah, I'm game.
I thought you might be.
Now the game is set.
Let's meet our players.
This is Jackson.
Strong-willed, motivated,
extremely confident.
I've done McKinley, K2,
Kilimanjaro, and Everest.
This year I'm doing
Puncak Jaya and Kosciuszko.
Next year I'll do Mt. Vinson
to finish off Seven Summits.
Typically excels
in high-stress situations,
although I don't imagine
he's ever had to deal
with anything like this.
Nevertheless, he's...
Impressive.
I think so.
And he knows it.
Here is Anton.
He spent five years
in the South African military
before coming to the States.
Physically dominant
with an extensive
weapons background.
This is Keith "the Thief."
Everything about him is a lie.
Deceptive and crafty,
he'll be whatever he needs
to be in order to survive.
I've got to show you this.
Put that down.
Here we go.
Okay, loosen up.
Up, up, loosen up.
Ow!
Ow! Fuck, man!
Anton also knows jujitsu.
Yeah, I was on tour for a while.
I was even nationally ranked.
I love tennis.
We should play sometime.
Leah doesn't
play well with others.
I'd crush you.
Banned from the tennis circuit
after assaulting a line judge,
she's extremely competitive.
Leah does not like to lose.
This is Nick.
"Iron Man" Nick.
Marina is bringing Nick,
the iron man.
He's a triathlete.
Very durable and just
an all-around nice guy.
- Oh, a triathlete.
- Yeah, that's right.
Nice. Ever climb the Y?
Oh, yeah. Three times.
All right.
Carlo, skip dinner with Cat.
She won't be much
for conversation.
Her vocal cords were crushed
in an accident
that killed both her parents.
She's a gymnast
and incredibly agile.
I'll get you a drink.
Who are you here with?
- Victor's date is Sarah.
- He's cute.
An orphan with the anxiety
disorder trichotillomania.
Basically,
she pulls her hair out.
No athletic history.
She probably won't
be around long.
She's also a bit awkward.
I don't really know anyone here.
You know me.
Jackie.
Sarah.
Let's do this!
Carly is bringing Mike,
"Magic Mike."
He's a male escort,
so I can't imagine
it was too hard
to get him to come.
And, finally,
my piece is Jackie.
She's the new teacher
at my yoga studio.
She teaches that yoga serves us
so that we may serve others.
You must love yourself
so you can spread that love
everywhere, to everyone.
I'm still working on that part.
What is this stuff?
It's a bottle of vintage.
You'll love it.
Thanks.
Good luck, everyone.
To our guests.
Every one of you
was invited here for a reason.
Now, while at first glance
those reasons are obvious...
Beauty, strength,
intelligence...
what's not quite so obvious
are the qualities
lurking beneath
such glowing exteriors.
Where better to reveal
those hidden qualities
than in the exciting
new arena of friendship.
To new friends.
For a night you can't remember.
And a day you can't forget.
You fascinate me, Jackie.
And I haven't felt that
in a long, long time.
What is this on my head?
Some sort of lens.
What did they do?
Good morning.
I hope everyone slept soundly.
You have a big day ahead of you.
What the fuck?
This is a game.
You have one night
to complete it.
Somewhere in this space
is a key.
There is also
a very special door.
To win the game, find the key
and unlock the door to freedom.
But only one of you can win.
What does that mean?
It means we're fucked.
Whatever.
I'm out of here.
Help me, assholes!
- Come on...
- It's welded shut.
The door will only open
when one survivor remains
and the others are all dead.
I'm not playing.
We're not playing.
You hear me?
We're not playing!
You can take your twisted
Hunger Game fantasy
somewhere else.
Your third eye
cameras allow us to see everything you see.
Do not manipulate these cameras.
If you obstruct or obscure
the lens in any way...
This is bullshit!
What the hell?
Wait, wait, wait,
what are you doing?
I'm taking this thing off!
Ah!
Oh, my God.
As you can see,
each camera contains
a vial of acid.
After 12 hours, the acid
will degrade those vials
and you will suffer
the same fate as your friend.
Only if you win the game
and escape
can the camera
be safely removed.
For those of you tempted
to do nothing
and sit the game out,
that is not an option.
The game begins...
now.
Hey, guys?
What should we do?
What do you think?
I'm not going to stay here
with the dead guy and the puke.
Betting is
open. Place your chips.
Kris, let's see some data.
This round is now closed.
This place is like a maze.
I feel like we've been
going around in circles.
Hey, what do you do
for a living?
I'm a yoga teacher.
Why?
And you're a climber?
Yeah.
You play tennis.
I'm a tennis pro.
Tennis pro.
Big guy,
you're obviously in shape.
What do you do?
Personal trainer.
- And you're a marathoner?
- Triathlete.
So we all have some sort
of physical prowess.
Well, I can't do a push-up
to save my life.
And she can barely stand up.
I work out.
Sometimes.
Takes a dump on your theory.
They're never going
to let us out of here.
Yeah, well, we all know
what the solution is, huh?
Why don't you just relax?
Hey, I'm relaxed, bubbles.
Why don't you relax, huh?
You mean we have to kill
each other?
No. I refuse to accept that.
None of it matters.
The only thing that matters
is that clock ticking down,
and this little conversation's
a fucking waste of time.
What the fuck?
That's disgusting.
Let's keep moving.
There's something in here.
Now what?
Nothing.
We just leave it.
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
I'm just taking a look, okay?
- Guys, don't.
- I'm not doing anything.
Yeah, that's right, you're not.
What are you, the boss now?
No, I'm just trying
to contain the situation.
Contain the situation?
What a douche.
Okay, okay, all right.
Let's just...
let's just move on.
Okay? Move on.
There are going to be
other weapons.
And we'll leave those, too,
and we'll work together.
We're not animals.
Can you help me out here?
Whatever you do,
just be sure about it.
What, are you
going to follow this guy?
Guys, this is not happening.
Please, just...
just... just think
for a second.
Okay. Let's think.
Let's group think, huh?
All boils down
to one simple question:
do you believe in this thing,
in what's going on?
Do you believe what's going on
around you, huh?
Do you believe what's going
to happen to us
if we don't do anything?
Yes or no?
Yeah.
When that meathead
had his face melt off,
we all knew the answer.
So the real question is
what are you going to do?
Huh?
I want to live.
We all want to live.
Oh, well, that's the rub.
Only one of us
get out of here alive.
No. I believe
there's another way.
No, you don't.
Listen,
what I think we should do is...
Shh! Shh!
There's two sides
to every coin, okay?
What we want to do
and what we don't want to do.
And what I don't want to do
is listen
to another fucking thing
coming out of your mouth.
No, no!
No. No, no, no, no.
No, no, please!
Please!
Oh, my God!
I can't believe it.
I can't fucking believe it.
Let's get out of here.
Run!
Hey...
Whoa.
Kill me later...
after we clean house.
Okay?
I don't want to be here.
I don't want to die.
Listen to me.
You're not going to die, okay?
I promise.
We're going to find
a way out, okay?
We're all going to go home.
I promise.
Hey, hey, check this out.
Some kind of message.
Like a clue?
Yeah, exactly like a clue.
It looks like a baseball.
Why a baseball?
What do you think it means?
It's got to mean something.
It must mean something.
Ah! Oh, my God! Nick!
Wow.
What in the...?
Huh...
What is this place?
That bitch on the P. A. Mentioned
something about a key
and a door.
I got this.
How do you feel about it?
Killing someone?
It happened pretty fast,
you know?
Are you okay?
I knew it meant something.
Oh, wow.
Uh... uh, yeah.
We need to get
the hell out of here.
Baseball.
No killing.
I'm not going to kill anyone.
I can't say the same
for everyone else.
It was you or him.
I just want to get
the fuck out of here.
How do you feel about it?
It was unavoidable.
A police badge.
Musical note.
Sunglasses.
Suggestions?
Sunglasses could mean sun.
Sunlight?
Outside?
Escape?
Why not?
Good job, Sarah.
Whatever it is,
let's just be careful.
It's a ruse.
They're trying to keep us
in one spot.
Yeah. Fuck!
Let's get the fuck out of here.
I don't... I don't want
to go down there.
I'm sure it's fine.
Did you see that?
Down this way.
Do you see that?
These lights.
They aren't random.
It's a pattern.
There's got to be something
valuable on the other side.
Maybe the way out.
How can you be so sure?
Because that's how
these sick bastards work.
Okay, so there's...
seven sections of the hallway.
I'm going to call out
which one the light falls on,
and you remember the sequence.
- I don't understand.
- You don't have to understand.
- But you do. You got it?
- Got it.
You're going to call out the
numbers, remember the sequence.
- Two.
- Five.
She's playing, man.
- Three.
Six.
Less than six hours remain.
We've got to go.
I don't know what you're doing,
but we need to go right now.
Okay. Those sequence of numbers
I counted, what were they?
Two, five, three, six.
- You're sure?
- Yes.
Okay, we start with you,
and we stay in the light.
Everyone stand tight to me.
When I move, you move.
And we stay out of the dark,
no matter what.
Okay...
go.
Five, five, five!
Ah!
Oh, my God.
Three.
Holy shit.
All right.
We did it. We did it.
She totally owned
your shadow trap.
No one's ever done that before.
Are you happy about it?
Never said that.
Plah. She's filler.
Like the rodent and the misfit.
Ground meat to feed the beasts.
She's not a real challenger.
You never know.
Want to bet she dies next?
I don't bet.
I run the odds so you can.
With nothing at stake.
How convenient.
Like it matters if I bet or not.
Tell me, when was
the last time Victor won?
Never.
I've never lost.
That's just as important.
Sad, Victor.
Most play to win.
You play not to lose.
Take it easy
on the vapor spikes, cowboy.
Might increase your chances
of not losing.
I could out-spike you
any day of the week.
Now that is a wager
I'm willing to take.
You gonna let him bitch you out?
Come on, Vic.
- Let's do it.
- Fine.
- Yes?
- Yeah! Let's do it!
Which way do we go?
Huh?
Let's kill these fuckers.
Do you have any pets, Jackie?
I have a dog at home.
A Maltese.
She's probably wondering
where I am.
We need to go home now, Jackie.
I know, Sarah.
We're going to figure
something out.
I promise.
Why did they do this to us?
Because...
Because we're not like them.
We're good people.
Some people...
are just empty inside.
They don't feel anything.
For anyone.
I believe we're all born good.
Somewhere along the way...
...something turned them
into monsters.
What's your story, Nick?
Parents?
They died a long time ago.
Sarah, how about you?
No.
I haven't talked
to my family in a long time.
I bet everyone here
is just like us.
No family.
Unattached.
Alone.
A bunch of lost souls.
Let's go.
Someone will come
looking for us.
Who?
And even if they did...
they're probably not in time.
They're watching us,
aren't they?
Probably.
It's okay.
Getting in the mood, are we?
It's a shame she has to die.
I wonder who's going
to kill her.
You think it's going
to be her, don't you?
Well, thanks for the tip.
That doesn't look good.
Flashlight?
Wait, let me see.
A key.
It's phosphorescent paint.
Black light.
It just ends.
There it is.
Who's going up there?
We don't have time for this.
Let's go.
Kris's girl
is going to get the key...
unless she falls
in the hole first.
Jackie, careful.
- Jackie, please be careful.
- I see it.
Don't look down.
Shh.
Can you hear that?
- They there.
- Shh.
- Oh, my God!
Be careful.
Come on.
Let's go say hello.
Looks like we're
going to get a fight.
I got it. I got it.
Whoa, good job.
Nick!
I got it. I got it.
I got this.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
Sarah, climb up here.
You'll be safe with me.
Come on, get it!
I'm going to kill you!
You give me that key!
Bring it, boy!
Sarah?
Get to fucking you up. Come on!
Sarah...
don't look down, okay?
Just come to me.
Sarah.
It's Sarah, right?
Come here.
Come to me.
Give me your hand
and you'll be safe.
Don't listen to a word she says.
It's not safe out there.
You know I'm right.
Just look down.
Don't listen to her, Sarah.
Don't listen to her.
The fall will kill you, Sarah.
Please, just make
your way towards me, Sarah.
- You don't want to die, do you?
- I'm here for you.
- I'll protect you.
- I'll help you get out of here.
Give me the key
and I'll let you live.
I can help you get out of here.
- Please come to me.
- Give me the key!
I'll protect you, Sarah.
I just want to go home.
- No!
- Fuck!
No!
Keith, go get the key!
Jackie!
Let go.
It's over.
You bitch!
You fucking bitch.
Oh, my God.
Jackie!
Say hi to Sarah for me.
No!
Fuck.
Help me, please.
Please.
Help.
Help me, please.
Where is the key?
I haven't found the goddamn key.
Well, let's find it.
There's no key.
The other chick
must have got here first.
Well, let's get them.
How come you didn't
get here first?
I didn't come this way.
Bullshit. I took the same
staircase you did.
It practically
led me right here.
How could you miss it?
You're hiding something.
Where's the key?
I don't have it.
Bullshit.
Then who does?
I told you, that quiet bitch.
Hmm.
She took the other staircase,
which clearly doesn't lead here.
You're lying.
Search him.
What the fuck is this?
I found it.
I found it in the barrel.
What were you
gonna do with that, huh?
Stab us in the back?
Hmm?
So you don't have the key?
No.
And you don't know who does?
No, I swear.
Then you're useless to us.
You silly little bitch!
She's alive.
She's fucking alive?
You.
I don't want to fight you.
I don't understand.
Nick.
Have you seen Nick?
Okay, let's...
let's find him.
Together.
That's hot.
Let's make it a little hotter.
You smell that?
Gasoline.
Uh-uh.
Don't move!
You're hurt.
Let us help you.
Shut up.
You think losers like us
were brought here to win?
We're meant to die.
Entertainment
for the asshole overlords
while contenders like her
fight it out.
We're sideshow freaks.
We're intermission.
This isn't you.
You don't have to do this.
You and your
"glass half full" bullshit.
You don't know me.
My glass...
my glass is full of blood.
There it is.
The door, we found it.
- It's locked.
- Oh, come on.
Now what?
Let them come to us.
- Okay, sit here.
- It's okay.
Shh, just let me take a look.
Oh.
You going to look around?
Okay. Be careful.
And don't leave without us.
What are you doing?
I'm going to re-dress it.
Okay.
Sorry.
I see you picked up a stray.
You trust her?
She's just like us.
Scared and wants to get
out of here alive.
Okay.
It's not much, but...
...it'll help.
It's perfect. Thanks.
You saved my life.
And you took one.
Yeah.
I just ran as fast as I could.
Almost on time.
But I knew in that split second
I had a choice to make.
Kill him, or let you die.
And I'm not going
to let you die.
Come on.
If that's the door,
they still need the key.
They're waiting us out.
Okay, look,
Anton is the main threat.
So you draw him towards me,
keep the key away from him,
and I'll do the dirty work.
She thinks I'm dead.
Let's use that to our advantage.
How?
I need you to take
your clothes off.
You wait here in case
he circles back around.
Still alive, Jackie?
That's too bad.
You?
Now!
Nick!
Nick.
We have to go.
Come on.
You're going to be okay.
We're gonna get out of here.
I swear, Nick.
Come on.
Somebody do something!
Please, no, no.
Player termination.
Down to our final three players.
Going somewhere?
I'm not going anywhere.
I don't think any of us are.
One...
The door will only open
when one survivor remains.
You have to kill me.
No, I can't.
I can't do that.
I wouldn't do that.
I'm dying.
So just save yourself.
Please.
Nick... I can't.
I don't want to do that.
I can't do that.
You can't let both of us die.
They'll win.
Don't let it happen.
So just do it.
Go on.
Let me figure something out.
I'm gonna figure something out.
Wait...
Time is running out, Jackie.
Please.
We did it.
What did you do?
No.
All right, it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's over.
It's over. It's over.
It's over. You won.
You won. You won.
You won.
I can't... I can't...
I can't...
Quite the surprise.
Better luck next time, Carlo.
Shh. It's okay. Relax.
Don't touch me.
Where am I?
You're safe.
Don't fucking touch me!
You're safe now.
You've been reborn.
You're free to do
whatever you want to do,
be whoever you want to be.
How could you do this to me?
Who are you?
Everyone brings a piece
to the game.
You were mine.
Are you game?
Yeah...
I'm game.
I'm just like you.
We're all just like you.
You're one of us now.
What do you mean, "one of us"?
You might not remember.
You were initiated, Jackie.
We have rules in this game.
And our loser must die...
Help! Somebody!
...at the hands of the winner.
Help me!
Help!
Somebody, help me!
This feeling is natural.
- Help me!
- It'll pass.
Help me!
If you want to go...
go.
We're not going to stop you.
But there's something
you should know.
Your roommate.
They haven't found the killer.
But they're looking.
That's your name, right?
They're looking for you.
Your prints were all over it.
And you haven't been seen since.
So if you want to go...
By all means.
Quite the game.
You were watching?
We always are.
You know that, Kris.
Did you win?
No.
But I didn't lose.
Drink?
I'm here about the girl.
She's recovering.
Not as quickly
as some of the others.
She'll be well soon enough.
Will she?
I've never seen someone
like her win before.
She inspired hope
where there was none.
She outsmarted
and she outfought.
She was a sheep...
meant to die.
But she didn't.
She won.
She's not like the others, Kris.
And we're not convinced that
she'll become a team player.
So we want her dealt with
immediately.
What?
You can't do that.
She won the game. She's worthy.
She's more than worthy.
I'm absolutely sure of it.
But we're not.
And that's all that matters.
Are you familiar with the term
"adelphophagy," Kris?
It literally means
"to eat one's brother."
Sand sharks.
They do this in the womb.
Devour their siblings
so they grow strong enough
to survive in the wild.
The dominant shark,
there is no instinct
to help or to hope.
Only to kill or to be killed.
And that instinct...
starts before they're even born.
Please.
Ask the elders to reconsider.
In all my time
running this game,
I have never asked them
for anything.
I believe I've earned
their trust.
She will come around,
and when she does,
she will be special.
We need someone like her.
We need?
Or you need?
Both.
She will be your responsibility
from now on, son.
If she is to stay...
she will be the one...
to cut the dead weight
from our ranks.
The game...
how did it start?
That...
is a very long and old story.
But...
I can tell you
how it started for me.
It started with a feeling.
This intense feeling of...
being alive...
for the first time.
I think ever since then,
I've been chasing after that.
Then why don't you bet?
Because I run the game.
They say it's quite an honor.
They say a lot of things.
But don't worry about me.
You get to bet.
Just make sure you don't lose.
I'd rather help you
run the game.
I mean, if it's okay
with the others.
It's okay because
I say it's okay.
I can't tell you
how happy that makes me.
In fact...
that calls for a drink.
Uh... but last time...
Trust me.
It's okay.
It'll pass.
I want you here with me.
It doesn't do anything
for me anymore.
I wish it did.
I miss it.
Well, what does?
Come on, I want you to...
I want you to feel what I feel.
You mix this.
Three parts vodka to one part.
For the game.
But this...
is the real deal.
Pure.
I forgot how that feels.
For a night
you can't remember...
and a day you can't forget.
Good morning.
I hope everyone
got a good night's rest.
Kris? Kris?
Unfortunately,
your time here is running out.
Enjoy your last 90 seconds
on this earth.
This is not a game.
Please don't.
There is no magic key.
There is no special door
for you to find.
There is no winner.
There is no escape.
Well...
that was...
Unavoidable.
How do you feel, Jackie?
Alive.
So now what?
Well, that's up to you.
This is endgame.
And it ends...
...now.