Subtitles by explosiveskull
[ORCHESTRA PLAYING]
Well, it's not bad, not bad.
Um, less vibrato in the strings.
Tuba, well, it's really not
your afternoon, is it, Michael?
Okay, let's pick it up
tomorrow.
Thank you for a good
day's work, everyone.
Sofia, good work today.
Oh, thank you.
Um, cues 17 and 28.
Perhaps you could go
over them for me?
You might hear something
I can't quite find.
Of course.
I haven't had time to get
the copyist...
to have them transcribed
into Braille for you.
Oh, it's okay. I still have
your demo tracks on my phone.
It will be my pleasure.
See you tomorrow morning.
[CROWD CHATTING]
[CITY NOISES: TRAFFIC, PEOPLE
TALKING, POLICE SIREN]
[SECURITY ANNOUNCEMENT]
- All change, please. All change.
- Damn! Excuse me.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
What did he just say?
Someone has gone under a
train at Oxford Circus.
That's the third one this month.
All off at the next stop.
Can I give you a hand?
No, I am fine, thank you.
[TRAVEL ANNOUNCEMENT]
[GASP]
Between 1992 and 1995.
Two coffees, please.
Over 10,000 people
were killed...
and 1.8 million people
displaced.
And reports of genocide.
Rape is widespread in the
region.
Tribunal hearings continue...
on whether to revoke
political asylum...
for alleged Serbian war
criminal Zoran Radic.
Radic was accused
earlier this year...
of using his charitable
organization...
to shield arms dealing...
- Take away, right?
- ...and human trafficking.
- Pro European groups in Serbia...
- To take away, right?
Yes.
...have been calling
for investigation...
over allegations of human rights
abuses during the Bosnian War.
Wagner. Overture to Tannhauser.
I'll get you the next time.
Thanks for the coffee.
You're a hard one to find.
Has my new favorite
neighbor been avoiding me?
I can smell you before
I hear you.
It's such a beautiful scent.
I think I put too much on.
I can't smell anything
at the moment.
Oh, are you all right?
You do sound a bit bunged up.
A few days in bed sorted me out.
I didn't hear you in
the apartment as usual.
I wanted to thank you...
for agreeing to play
my father's benefit.
You are not nervous, are you?
Oh, I am used to playing
in front of people.
That is not what I meant.
I need the money.
My father is sick.
So is mine!
You never asked me if he did
those things people say.
Most people ask.
He's your father.
That's for you to know.
You're going to make
quite an impression.
What is that scent
you're wearing?
That's my little secret.
Play Temp Thriller Cue 17.
I don't want anything from you.
I don't want anything
to do with you.
Because I say so...!
I changed my mind.
Don't tell me what to do.
You want me to tell my
father that you said that?
I don't care.
We have talked about it...
and then you don't have to deal
with that.
Hello?
Are you okay?
Fine.
I found your scarf
earlier downstairs.
Do you want me to bring it up?
No, no, not now.
Please look after it for me.
Sofia!
My secret scent...
it's liquid gold.
Stay calm and be
sensible about this.
Who's going to do that?
Why you, huh?
No, listen to me.
Why does it have to be you?
Anything could happen to you.
[MUFFLED ARGUING]
It is not going to happen.
Not the way he wants.
Not the way your sister wants.
[MANIC LAUGHTER]
- [SCREAM]
- [CAR ALARM]
If you could not touch
anything, please.
Thank you, Liberace.
What's this? An AA meeting?
Get out, all of you!
You too, Nancy Drew!
Detective Inspector Oscar Mills.
Sorry, that's a habit - my I.D.
I believe you.
Um, listen, I know it's late...
but if I could just ask you
a few questions.
Did you know Miss Caval?
No.
You weren't friends?
I didn't even know
that was her surname.
How long did she live above you?
Well, she was here
when I moved in.
I have been here
nearly six months.
But you didn't really talk?
You never borrowed
a cup of sugar?
Or had a girly night in
with a bottle of wine?
No, I mean, I knew her to say
hello to in the lobby...
or in the lift, but...
Do you mind me asking,
were you born blind?
It happened when I was five.
It is in my family.
My mum was blind.
You can't see anything at all?
I'm light sensitive, like
most blind people, but no.
Is it true that the loss of one
sense sharpens the others?
That's what they say, but what
have I got to compare it to?
Of course.
But you would be pretty sure
about anything you hear, right?
Mm-hm.
You told the PC that you
were in the apartment.
With my headphones in.
With your headphones in?
So you didn't hear anything?
No.
You're a pianist.
Is that correct?
Mm-hm.
My daughter Lily plays.
She's seven, asthmatic,
I think the playing calms her.
In the breathing, you know.
[FOOTSTEPS UPSTAIRS]
Sorry, Guv, forensics
are asking for you.
I'd better get back up there...
before they start moving
everything.
Sharon here will
take your statement.
Um, I would leave you
my card, but...
It's all right, I've got
friends with eyes!
Oh, yes.
If you can think of
anything at all...
please do call me.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Right, let's make
this quick, shall we?
Marc. Marc.
I need you on this.
Can I have it, please?
She didn't have it.
It is on her person, or
in her apartment. Go back.
Radic is a very
important person to us.
He needs that USB back before
the Russians get hold of it.
What?
There was a woman
in the elevator.
She saw me.
Take care of it.
Shhh!
Morning!
Morning, Tanya!
Here, do you want the other
half of this sandwich?
I'm not really supposed to
be eating it, that's all.
- He's chatty.
- Who?
I thought you were on a diet?
Well, it is half-fat mayonnaise.
Let's get started.
What are these?
Lithium pills, they were in her
personal effects.
For the treatment
of bi-polar disorder.
So external examination suggests
that all injuries...
are consistent with a fall
from the second floor.
Multiple broken bones, back,
neck...
fractured skull, extensive
bruising.
Suicide?
No signs of a struggle.
Tell me about the nose.
Oh, rhinoplasty.
Nose job, about a week,
five days ago.
Now why would I go to the
trouble of dying my hair...
and getting a nose job
to throw myself out of a window?
[PIANO PLAYING]
No! No! No! No!
You're not concentrating, Sofia.
You're behind the beat.
Okay, let's pick it up tomorrow.
[GASP]
Okay, thanks.
Yes, all right, speak soon. Bye.
Pretty little thing.
Important little thing, too.
I just found out who Daddy is.
Call me once you've had
a good look around inside.
Thanks, Tanya.
[ANGRY SHOUTING]
Earlier today, Zoran Radic
was seen leaving the morgue...
where he offically identified
his daughter's body.
28-year-old Veronique Radic...
fell from her apartment
building in central London...
in the early hours
of the morning...
in what appears to be a suicide.
Police are not treating
her death as suspicious.
Protesters took advantage
of this rare public appearance.
Accusations of human rights
abuses during the Bosnian War...
continue to be heard
against Mr Radic.
Murderer!
- [CAR HORN BEEPS]
- Watch out!
[FLOORBOARD SQUEAKS]
Mills?
Can you talk?
Go for it.
There were traces of cocaine
and valium in her system.
Highly strung?
And there was something else.
She was pregnant.
How long?
About 12 weeks.
So she would have known.
No doubt.
All right, thanks, love.
Wait a second, have
you told anyone else?
No, not yet.
Keep it that way.
[PARTY CHATTER]
The USB, it wasn't in
Veronique's apartment...
or her personal effects.
Maybe she had already
given it to the Russians.
She hadn't. She has hidden it
somewhere in that building.
It's there.
It's not, Alex. I just
told you it's not.
I'll show you something
I did find, though.
I want to believe you didn't
know she was pregnant.
I really do.
Then... believe.
Veronique really got
to you, didn't she?
Whether that baby is yours,
or not is irrelevant.
Radic is a dangerous fucker who
just had his daughter killed.
And you, little brother,
were the hand that pushed.
[GLASS BEING TAPPED]
Good evening.
I wanted to personally thank
you all for being here tonight.
I am sure most of you
have heard...
that I lost my beautiful
daughter Veronique.
These difficult last months...
the only strength I have been
able to manage came from her.
But also from the work of this
incredible foundation.
Your help with refugees...
and victims of global
conflicts, is truly priceless.
I can tell you from the
bottom of my heart...
that Veronique would have wanted
us all to be here tonight...
continuing to fight that fight
for that great cause.
So if you will join me
in raising a glass of Rakia.
- Ziveli.
Yeah, he's good.
You write that shit, too.
What about that other thing?
What?
The woman who saw you.
That's not necessary.
She didn't see anything.
How can you be so sure?
She's blind.
[LAUGHS]
Seriously?
I'll find it, okay?
[PIANO PLAYING]
[APPLAUSE]
Beautiful.
I haven't heard it
for a long time.
How do you know it?
Veronique, I am sorry
for your loss.
Where did you know her from?
She lived above me
at Blackheart Gardens.
Allow me.
[CHAMPAGNE CORK POPS]
Did you know Veronique well?
No, we were just neighbors.
She was always kind to me.
She was a very
troubled young woman.
It's been difficult between us
towards the end of her life.
She asked me to play that
piece for you this evening.
She said you used to hum it to
her when she was a little girl.
Please, if you would
excuse me a moment.
Police are still
calling it a suicide.
If anything changes,
I'll follow up.
I have a contact
at Scotland Yard.
I see you've been making
friends.
Where did you find her?
She was a friend of Veronique's.
They lived in the same building.
I didn't know Veronique
kept friends.
You played beautifully.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Miss Gordon... not now.
And well done to you.
You concentrated on the
charity, like I said...
and what with Veronique's
death...
it can only be viewed
sympathetically.
And the tribunal?
All of this helps.
The war is long forgotten
and I am working hard.
I hate to be a party pooper...
but I think you need
to be out there...
using this exposure
to be seen grieving.
Not seducing the
blind piano player.
Grieving?
Lets people see you have
feelings.
You're a businessman
and a philanthropist.
Leave the rest to me.
Excuse me.
I am very sorry, Sofia.
I have to get back to my guests.
I understand.
But I would love
to see you again.
Would that be possible?
Well, you know where I live.
[GLASS VIAL CRUSHED]
[GLASS SMASHED]
Sorry.
Leave it, please,
it's only champagne.
Nina will see you out.
It's been a pleasure.
[PANTING]
[HIGH HEEL SHOES WALKING]
[TOILET FLUSH]
[CANE TAPPING ON FLOOR]
Thank you.
How do I look?
Like a million dollars.
Nice shoes!
[LAUGHTER]
[YOUTHS LAUGHING]
Do you know what, I told him
last night, don't come back.
Because if he does come back.
What do you mean?
Don't listen to that.
Shut up, bruv!
You're really pissing
me off these days.
- Whoa! Look where you're going!
- Sorry.
You fucking blind or something?!
What's going on?
- Fucking hell! She is blind!
- Fucking hell!
Go on, girl!
Please, just leave me alone.
Just leave me alone!
[FIRECRACKER BANG]
Please, I have some money.
You can take it.
Do we look skint to you?!
Test she can't see you.
Idiot!
Hey! When was the last
time you got fucked?
Been a while, yeah,
because I could show you.
Easy! Whoa!
There's no need for that.
Yes, that's a bit mean, girl.
You little sket.
- Whoa! Whoa! Where you going?
- No!
On your knees already, love?
- [PUNCHING AND FIGHTING]
- [GROANS]
[FOOTSTEPS RUNNING AWAY]
- Don't hurt me!
- I won't.
Do you usually hang around
street corners fighting crime?
I work for my sister.
She runs a security
consulting firm.
Does she boss you around?
Yeah!
Yes, me and my sis,
we came from nothing.
Mum was a druggie,
Dad wasn't around.
Sorry to hear that.
How is your Mum doing now?
Oh, she's dead.
Mine, too.
You sure you don't want to
report this to the police?
Oh, no more police for me
this week!
Why, are you a troublemaker?!
The woman in the apartment
above me...
she fell from her window
last night.
- Detective said it was a suicide.
- Detective?
So you were questioned?
What did you tell them?
I told him I didn't see
anything.
I told him I didn't know her.
But you did.
Not well. We spoke
every once in a while.
She seemed kind of lost.
This is hers.
You can still smell her on it.
- There's blood on this.
- It's mine.
I tripped on it in the lobby
yesterday morning...
and I cut my finger.
I didn t want the police
to think I had anything...
to do with it, so I kept it.
It's silly really. It's
just a little bit of blood.
You don't have to say
anything, you know.
I mean, if the police think
it's a suicide...
they are probably right.
What do you think happened?
I don't know. I had my
headphones in.
Thank you for saving me.
If you ever see that man again,
play something by Satie for me.
[SCRATCHING]
I want to take away
everything he's built.
I want to destroy him!
I want to destroy him! I want
to destroy him! Destroy him!
The Russian Ambassador has
urged the British Home Office...
to revoke political
asylum for Zoran Radic.
The Serbian national's
relationships...
with prominent members
of Whitehall and the city...
have always ensured that calls
for his extradition...
have been refused in the wake
of his daughter's death.
The government seems to be
sticking...
with its sympathetic stance.
Veronique Radic was
born in Serbia...
but sent to London
to be educated...
and later finishing her
education in the U.S.
[METRONOME TICKING]
Shhh!
I wanted to thank you
for agreeing...
to play my father's benefit.
I found your scarf earlier
downstairs...
do you want me to bring it up?
Sofia.
Please look after it for me.
My secret scent...
it's liquid gold.
[FOOTSTEPS UPSTAIRS]
[ELEVATOR]
[KNOCKING]
Miss McKendrick?
It's Detective Mills.
Good morning.
You're an early riser
like myself, are you?
- Morning.
- Yes, sorry to interrupt.
I thought you'd paused. I was
listening upstairs. Beautiful.
Thank you.
I could hear you surprisingly
well through the, yeah...
These old buildings, the
sound really carries.
Yeah, you haven't had any more
thoughts about the other night?
I'm sorry, Detective Inspector.
Oscar, please.
Why would a pregnant woman
throw herself out of a window?
You didn't know?
Oh, of course, she is
a mystery box.
What do you mean?
Well, she's a suicide, and then
we find out who she really is.
Who her father is.
I'm sure you've heard the news.
Yeah, then I find out
she's pregnant.
Another mystery box.
Thanks, Miss McKendrick.
I'm sure we'll speak again.
[COUGHING]
I got your card.
You need to disappear.
The police questioned you?
Yeah.
Detective Inspector Oscar Mills.
Divorced, one daughter
aged seven.
He's dedicated.
He'll be checking you out.
Your background, your
identity, everything.
[COUGHING]
You're not taking
your medication.
You look tired.
And whisky doesn't count.
Are you sleeping?
Nightmares, huh?
I was interrupted.
Yeah, well, you didn't take it.
The Kremlin want his
head on a stick
They can do it,
you don't have to.
I have another way in.
I'm being followed.
[RATTLE]
For this.
That USB leads all the
way back to Radic.
Whoever wants it, can
get me in front of him.
I've waited too many
years, come too far.
That bitch planted it on me.
I don't know what's on it...
but whatever it is was worth
killing her for.
You don't have to do this.
You're not a killer, Sofia.
Poisoning someone is one
thing...
using your bare hands
is another.
Don't you dare change your mind.
I carried you through that
mile-long hell-hole...
under Sarajevo airport.
So you could have
a second chance.
That second chance was
so I could do this.
You know what he did to
my family, my sister.
These people kill every day.
- Live your life.
- You never did.
There was war where I found you.
Genocide.
This... this is more...
Personal? You tell me what's
more important than that.
I have to finish this.
You, above all people,
know that.
[COUGHING]
Give me a few hours
to look through the USB.
There'll be a password.
Try LIQUID GOLD.
It's Veronique's perfume.
Niall, how's Oliver?
Oh, you know what he's like.
Arthritis. His leg's
still giving him gyp.
He's as tough as
nails, that old cat.
Yeah, I know someone
else like that.
Good girl. Good girl.
[GASPS]
Where is it?
[RUSSIAN]
- [BONES BREAKING]
- [SCREAM]
The USB, she gave it to you,
where is it?
[RUSSIAN]
[SCREAM]
[CAR CRASH]
[HORN BEEPS]
[GUN FIRE]
[EAR RINGING]
[MUFFLED SHOUTING]
Come on, it's okay.
I can't hear.
It's okay.
- I can't hear.
- Shhh!
- Hold on to me.
- I can't hear.
If you don't tell me what
you're doing, I can't help you.
I know Veronique
gave you something.
I don't have anything.
A USB, you need to
stop lying to me.
Who's lying to who? How long
have you been following me?
Look, this won't stop
until they get it back.
We need to move, or...
Or what? You're going to kill
me like you killed Veronique?
I heard you with that old man by
the river speaking Serbo-Croat.
Is that what this is about?
Revenge against Radic
for the war?
You don't know anything
about me.
I know whatever game you think
you're playing...
you just stumbled into
someone else's.
Your only option is to
let me help you.
Did you give it to
the old man?
I don't need your help.
Did you give it to the old man?
I'm trying to help you.
Why? Who are you? Why are
you always saving me, hm?
You're the one in trouble...
if you don't know why
you're helping me.
Help! Help!
[HUMMING FOLK SONG]
The first time I hummed
that to you...
I could lift you with one arm.
[COUGHING]
I don't have much time.
You were right
about the password.
This USB is everything
someone would...
need to know to take
over his operations.
All his business interests,
his commercial assets...
that he got on the cheap...
after NATO bombed the shite
out of them.
Veronique wasn't betraying
her father on her own.
There's communications...
two aliases.
Serebro and Zoloto.
Silver and Gold.
Veronique was Gold.
They were using this
information to betray Radic...
to the Russians,
to take him down.
You find Serebro, you find
your way back to Radic.
I've always tried
my best for you.
You're everything to me.
You can't stay here.
You've got to get strong.
Leave.
Your clothes are in your
locker on the right.
[COUGHING]
What kind of a mystery
box are you, Sofia?
Sorry.
Listen, can you call
me when she wakes?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
[PHONE RINGING]
[ELEVATOR BELL]
[VIOLIN PLAYING]
She said you'd know
where to find her.
Was she standing here?
Tell me what happened.
I heard a struggle...
and then her heels run
over to the window.
I was sent to kill her,
but I came to help.
She wouldn't listen.
She was scared,
making plans to leave.
Veronique wasn't well
and she never really was.
She was standing where
you are now, crying.
She asked me to go away
with her.
Why didn't you?
When I was a little girl...
my father used to sit me
at the piano with my sister.
And he'd blindfold her,
so she couldn't see, like me.
And that was how we learned
to play... together.
My father, he went out
of his way...
to make sure that
we were equals...
to make sure that my sister knew
what it was like to be blind.
Now you see what I see.
Shhh!
I'm from a village outside of
Bijeljina, North East Bosnia.
My parents knew Radic.
They were neighbors for years.
My sister and I used to play
in his garden...
before the war started.
One day, Serbian para-militaries
came to my home...
and they killed my family.
Radic was their Commander.
I was the only one
that survived.
Who sent you to kill Veronique?
My sister.
Alexandra Gordon.
She didn't tell you Veronique
was pregnant, did she?
"It was yours, wasn't it?"
Killing Radic won't change
a thing, you know.
It won't bring your family back.
You think that darkness inside
of you will heal? It won't.
Your soul just gets a little
darker, until...
until there's nothing left.
I didn't kill Veronique.
She jumped.
I want to meet your sister...
alone.
I was trying to think
of somewhere neutral...
for us to meet.
Slightly unfair choice I admit,
but I do love this place.
I love the silence,
but I also love the smell.
I thought you'd at
least appreciate that.
Well done, in using my
brother to get to me.
And it seems we both used
Veronique to get at...
the same thing, albeit for very
different reasons.
Only one of us killed her.
You have something
that belongs to me?
You came all this way for a
photograph you can't even see?
Did you copy it?
Of course.
Do you have the USB?
Why didn't you hand it over when
you were having your fingers...
broken in the back of the van?
Well, I'd only just realized
what its true value was.
You've no idea of its true
value without the password.
I love this painting.
I used to come here and sit
for hours staring at it.
What is it?
The Death of Actaeon by Titian.
In revenge, for surprising
Artemis...
while she bathed naked
in the wood.
She transformed
Actaeon into a stag.
He galloped off into the
forest seeking refuge...
and he was hunted by his own
hounds who didn't recognize him.
They attacked and killed him...
as he looked at his own
reflection in a pond...
and saw what he'd become.
Do you ever stare
at your reflection?
[LAUGH]
What do you want?
Liquid Gold.
Excuse me?
The password.
I wasn't much into art
when I was a little girl...
as you'd imagine.
But I loved chemistry...
and I learned all the
elements off by heart.
Where I come from,
silver is 'serebro'...
but the element is the same
in the period table...
wherever you're from.
AG, Alexandra Gordon.
I want to be alone with him.
Well, why would I put
you alone with Radic...
when you could just as
easily tell him who I am?
Well, what other
choice do you have?
And I'd be doing you a favor.
My enemy's enemy is my friend.
I can only imagine how awful...
this must have been for you
all these years.
Living in the dark...
dreaming of the day you'd be
face to face with him again.
Did he do that to you?
[LAUGHS]
We both know he has a
penchant for blind girls.
If he saw this photo
of your family...
he'd know exactly who
they are, wouldn't he?
You copied the USB?
Of course.
You're going to take me to
Veronique's funeral today...
and you're going to make sure
that I am left alone with him.
And if I walk out of here and
end up in the back...
of another van, then rest
assured...
that USB will find its
way to him before you do.
You are way out of your depth.
Maybe, but I'm not afraid
to die doing this, are you?
Marc... he's a good fuck,
isn't he?
You're a murderer! Murderer!
Murderer!
[PRIEST RECITING
INTERMENT SERVICE]
Good day, Sofia. It's Radic.
- Thank you for coming.
- Pleasure.
Please... come with me.
We are having a little
reception at the house.
[PROTESTORS SHOUTING]
They want me dead.
All of them.
If they could open the door,
they would pull me out into...
the streets and do to me all
of the things they accuse me of.
But would it make
any difference?
Would it change the past, Sofia?
When I was a little boy...
I used to play hide and seek
with my mother...
and I'd cover my eyes
with my hands...
and think that no-one
could see me.
Did you ever play hide and seek
when you were a little girl?
Yes.
Where was your favorite
place to hide?
There was a wardrobe
in my bedroom.
Strange.
The reassurance that can
be found in dark places.
You know, I don't
believe anything of you.
I think you're lying.
And you are weak.
Yes, you're weak.
And it's not your father's
weak, Bosnian blood.
I can tell you that.
You know why?
Some time before the War,
I lived in a small village...
and there was a blind woman,
a Catholic woman...
and she was married
to a Muslim man...
and they had a daughter...
and I thought I was in
love with that woman.
I came across her one day on
the road outside the village...
and we were friends,
so she knew me.
I led her into the forest
and I raped her...
and she never said a word.
She never told anyone.
And she became pregnant
and she had a little girl.
And a few years later,
that little girl became blind.
They never told you, did they?
Now, I left before
the war broke out...
but when it broke out,
I went back to that village.
You remember?
And I went to your house
again with my men...
and I raped that blind
Catholic woman again.
Then my men raped her.
All I remember is her
dead eyes looking at me...
and I knew in that moment,
she knew who I was.
And then? Then I killed
her dirty Bosniak...
and burned her house
to the ground.
You know, Sofia.
People have seen me and
the things I've done.
But they are just copies of me.
Just shadows.
But that woman, she saw me.
She really saw me.
And you look at me
just as she did...
seeing without seeing.
Cut me, Sofia.
Just stop me.
Do it.
Do it!
Do it now!
You want me dead
more than they do.
They've already
made up their minds...
and you can't decide?!
Serebro!
What?
Someone close to you was
betraying you with Veronique.
Serebro.
[PROTESTORS SHOUTING]
Drive!
Can I help you?
I need to talk to...
Sorry, love. I can't
hear what you're saying.
I need to speak to
Detective Inspector Mills.
D.I. Mills isn't around
just now.
Is there something I can
help you with?
But I... yes, he gave me
his card.
He said if I need to talk
to him, I can talk to him, I...
Right, oh, right, just wait
one moment then please, love.
Hello?
Can I speak to Niall?
Is he there?
I'm afraid that's not possible.
I really need to speak to him.
Belma? Is that you?
Yes.
He passed away last night.
He arranged a way
for you to get out.
He said he was sorry...
but he wasn't strong enough
to carry you any longer.
Thank you.
Belma? Belma?
[BELL RINGS]
I heard you were looking for me.
Sofia?
You can't help me.
You came to the police station.
I haven't committed any crime.
Not telling you who beat me
up is not against the law...
and Veronique, whether you
like it or not, was a suicide.
So, as far as I can tell, we
have nothing else to talk about.
Last time I checked, identity
theft was against the law.
Sofia McKendrick died when
she was three months old...
along with her mother...
in a car crash just
outside Glasgow in 1985.
Her father, Niall
McKendrick...
ex-SAS, was away on
tour at the time.
That's who was with you
in the hospital last night.
You stole Sofia
McKendrick's identity.
So, who are you?
I don't know any more.
Daddy, I pressed the wrong
button and my game is gone.
I thought you were going to wait
in the car like a good girl.
Here you are.
Go and choose a cake...
and then sit there
where I can see you.
Sorry, my wife's away
on business.
I had to pick her up
from school earlier.
She has bad asthma.
Yeah, you said.
That's Saint Rafael...
the patron saint of the
blind and travelers.
It was on your bed
in the hospital.
No more lies.
I'm an orphan.
Niall McKendrick adopted me.
Not legally. He wouldn't
have been able to.
Let me tell you what I think.
Veronique was using you,
manipulating you.
I've looked into her background
and her father Zoran Radic...
did a lot of very, very nasty
things during the Bosnian War.
With no doubt that had a
marked effect on Veronique.
He seems to like women like you.
Blind women.
Maybe she was happy to
throw you into the pit.
Maybe she was, what of it?
Well, maybe you were
using Veronique...
to get closer to her father.
Maybe, he hurt you and your
family during the War...
and now you want to hurt him.
That's what I think.
Do I look like someone
who could hurt him?
I'm tired and these painkillers
are wearing off.
I am sure you're going to find
out everything you need to know.
Nothing you do is by chance.
Even when you lie,
you tell the truth.
[CRYING]
Domesticated!
I had no idea.
Try my béarnaise sauce.
It's the best you've ever
tasted.
I'm 45 years old and a size 10.
Does it look like I eat dairy?
That's a pity.
Let's talk about the blind girl.
Is it finished?
It will be tonight.
Oh, if you need my assistance
in any way, I can help.
That's what I pay you for.
So, why did you call me over?
I have some papers
I wanted you to witness.
Of course.
Oh, I'd forgotten how
simple your signature is.
AG, like silver...
Serebro. Yes, you are.
That little girl became blind.
They never told you, did they?
Stop me, Sofia.
I want you to stop me.
You know where I live.
[GUN FIRE]
[METRONOME TICKING]
He knows.
What of it? Sofia?
All of it.
Marc, it's too late for her...
but it's not for me, for us.
I'm a dead woman if you
don't help me...
get out of here right now.
Get to the airport,
you'll make it.
Please, blood is blood.
You can't turn your back
on that.
Blood is blood.
[GUN SHOT]
[RASPING BREATH]
[GUN SHOTS]
I never came here when
Veronique lived here.
Two daughters living under
and above each other.
Both plotting to end me.
You're not scared of me?
I've been killing you every
day for the last 24 years.
There's nothing to be scared of.
It's not going to end that way.
[GLASS SMASHING]
- [AEROSOL SPRAYING]
- [SHRIEK]
[BONE BREAKING]
No!
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[GLASS SMASHING]
I had him. He was mine.
Yeah.
You'd have regretted it
for the rest of your life.
[GASP]
No... there's no time.
You can't save everyone.
Don't let me see you leave.
[POLICE SIREN]
Subtitles by explosiveskull