Subtitles by explosiveskull
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
MAN: So sorry to do this,
Mr. and Mrs. Gallup.
But I need to ask
a few questions.
[EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Honey, I really gotta pee,
you gotta hurry, Ray.
I gotta go, now. [LAUGHS]
I'm gonna piss my pants
in the seat right now.
- You want me to go in with you?
- No.
Wait, wait, um...
what do you wanna do
about dinner?
Get away from me.
[HOOTS]
Want me to stop
and get some coffee?
No. I'm gonna take a nap.
- You okay?
- Yeah, just tired.
I love you, Maggie.
Hello?
Ben? It's Ray.
[MAGGIE SHUDDERING]
Maybe he had an emergency.
Yeah, maybe. The signs are on.
It looked bigger
in the pictures.
Big as it needs to be I guess.
MAGGIE: Hmm.
It's all yours.
I can't believe, he'd
leave the key out
where anyone could just...
- Babe, where you going?
- Huh?
To get the stuff.
Well you don't have to
do that now.
I'm not gonna leave it
out there overnight.
Alright fine,
let's just get it over with.
No, no, no, I can do it.
You go on to bed.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I got it.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[HORNS HONKING]
[PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- Hey Ray, man, you made it.
Ah that's good, that's good.
You found the keys?
[WHISPERING]
You just left it outside.
Oh, yeah, I just wanted
to make sure you got in okay.
How do you like the place?
Pretty sweet, huh?
Well the microwave,
it's... it's not...
Oh, don't worry,
I got that taken care of.
You see by the phone?
I left a card
with all the numbers.
I think so. Numbers?
All the vendors, the vendors.
You don't really need
anything else, so good luck.
Wait, so I don't have
an email on you, or a cellphone?
If something comes up,
is there something wrong?
Fuck no man, nothing like that.
I mean, the place is yours.
I gotta tell you,
you guys are gonna love it.
- Wait.
- Look it...
You can handle this, I promise.
Just keep it simple. I gotta go.
[PHONE LINE BEEPING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
Ava, right?
Uh, I'm Ray, the new owner.
Yeah, so I'm Ray,
my wife Maggie, she's...
well you'll meet her.
AVA: Okay.
Oh, strange how cold it can get
out in the desert, huh?
AVA: Uh-huh.
Who's he?
He's my nephew.
Alright, well,
if you need anything. Just...
- Okay.
- Alright.
Who was that?
It's just the cleaning lady.
She wasn't very talkative.
[SIGHS]
Mm, I guess we're gonna have to
wake up early from now on.
You don't have to,
I'll let in her.
I'll get her a key.
You were gone for hours
last night.
I know.
I was already asleep.
I know, I was just...
just a little restless
thinking of everything
we have to do here.
- Hey!
- [LAUGHING] Ow!
Ow! Oh, that hurt!
- It hurt?
- Yeah.
Babe, can you grab us a new
frying pan when you're in town?
[PAN CLATTERING]
MAGGIE: Not a lot of room
in these cabinets either.
I'd call Ben and complain
but his number's
been disconnected.
MAGGIE: Really?
That's weird,
- MAGGIE: maybe he changed it.
- Yeah, maybe.
Maybe, I'll get a little frame
for those while I'm out.
That'd be nice.
Thank you.
A key.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Somebody here?
Our first guest,
I put her in room six.
Whoa,
I thought we were gonna wait
to go official tomorrow.
So, we're a soft launch,
it's okay.
I felt bad for her,
she looked tired.
Yeah, okay.
At first, I was really nervous,
but then I did
the whole registration thing,
I took the cash, it was cool.
So, who's the guest?
I don't know, some woman.
And, by herself?
As far as I could tell.
She said she needed to sleep.
This all feels
really good to me, Ray.
I... Once business picks up,
I think we're gonna be
real comfortable here.
Yeah. Good, me too.
You want a beer?
No, I'm okay.
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[TV BUZZING]
[HORN HONKING]
[COUNTER BELL DINGS]
Oh hey, you must be
the new boss man.
Something like that. I'm Ray.
Hey Ray, how are you? I'm Tommy.
[CHUCKLES]
Nice thing about my rig
being so loud
is I don't need to ring
that damn buzzer, do I? [LAUGHS]
I'll take number ten
if it's free.
It is.
Ah, good.
My lucky day, huh? [CHUCKLING]
Yes. Just kidding.
- Here.
- Oh.
And...
I won't be needing this,
because I'm pretty much
the regular around here.
But then again you don't know me
from a damn hole in the ground,
so how about
I put my name down here.
Yeah.
Still 35 even?
Works for me.
Good.
I like things that don't change.
Oh, no, that's a gratuity.
Just help us get off
on the right foot, you know.
- No.
- Yeah.
Thanks, but it's not necessary.
I know you're just
getting started.
Try in your pocket.
Thanks, but really.
Good night Ray.
[TRUCK ENGINE REVVING]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
WOMAN: Stopped in Laughlin.
You know that place?
Oh, yeah, it's for people
who can't get to Vegas.
What the hell?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[VACUUM CLEANER DRONING]
Ray?
I'll trade you for whatever
you're worrying about.
It's nothing.
Come on, Ray.
Babe, really, it's nothing.
[DOORBELL DINGS]
Well hey, look at that
for timing, huh?
Couldn't sleep anyway.
Well maybe I should give you
some of mine.
I plan on getting a lot tonight.
You need me to fill out
one of those...
Um...
You know Tommy...
I haven't really had a chance
to clean number ten yet,
so how about seven?
No, no I'm good with that,
I don't mind another man's mess.
You're sure, 'cause...
I'm that sure. Night buddy.
[DOORBELL DINGS]
I'm sleeping, baby.
[SIGHS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MEXICAN MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHING]
Where'd you go, sweetie?
Just... Just needed some air.
[VACUUM CLEANER DRONING]
[BUZZER BUZZING]
Unbelievable.
Someone's at the door.
[BUZZER BUZZING]
Hi, Ava.
Hi mister.
How are you this morning?
- AVA: Good.
- Oh I made you a key.
RAY: [BREATHING DEEPLY]
Here, so you don't... You don't
have to, you know, the buzzer.
Okay, let me get...
My wife, Maggie, um, we just...
we like to sleep in is all.
Okay.
- Thank you, mister.
- You... You have a good day.
[HORN HONKING]
Before I forget, I moved the
woman in room six to room 10.
She was real nice about it,
family needed double beds.
What is this?
What's what?
Your journey toward adoption?
Jesus Christ, Maggie.
It's just information, Ray.
It's not like
we never talked about it,
you said,
once we're settled in...
Th... This is settled in?
We just got here.
You promised me.
Shit Maggie, I need some time
for this, I can't just...
Fuck, I mean...
It's a piece of paper, Ray.
Okay, you don't have to pay for
it, you don't have to feed it,
you don't even have
to watch over it.
What is that supposed to mean?
When I said, I'd stay,
you promised we could do this,
and now you don't even
wanna talk about it.
It's like being married
to a brick fucking wall.
We came here to start over, and
everything is exactly the same,
it's exactly the same.
I have a relationship with her.
I talk to her every day.
[SOBBING] And you can't just...
you're not allowed to just...
replace her.
Don't you talk about her,
I was with her.
When you were off being just
fucking friends
with the neighbor,
I was there with her!
Yeah, you were there,
you were high.
You were a million miles away
when she was
sitting on your lap.
I'm gonna be better...
Ray.
[SIGHS]
You know, fuck it.
Are you happy now?
[SNIFFING]
Ain't you the fellow
who took over that place
across the street, the Motorway?
Yeah, Motorway, right.
- Ray, hi.
- Hey, welcome to town, Ray.
You and that young lady of yours
you need anything at all,
just let me know.
Alright, appreciate that.
You find you got any
ne'er-do-wells around your place
I got a lot of friends
in this town,
we can take care of that.
Me and my boys, we can take care
of anything in this town.
Okay, that's really cool.
You have a good night.
Yeah, you too.
TOMMY: Well I just don't know
why you gave away 10, Ray.
I told you, we needed the room.
Now five's just as good.
No, I'm a loyal customer, and
you know damn well that's true.
What can I do, Tommy?
Well, you know, I don't
wanna come in here and...
and shake the whole place awake
every time I come and
leave so early.
That's why I like it
down there on the end.
I know what you do in there.
[LAUGHS] Come on, Tommy.
You're not gonna tell me those
girls are your daughters?
No, they're not my daughters.
But I'll tell you
what's the truth,
is I am a married man,
and to be honest my
wife doesn't like to
get it on so much anymore and...
And I'm a sex addict.
Now I read up on it,
and it's a condition.
As long as you pay for the room,
what you do in there
is your business.
As long as you're not
killing anybody.
No, I'm not killing anybody.
Have a good night, Ray.
You are a good man.
Damn good fella.
[GREGORIAN CHANT PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You're cold.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Shouldn't you be watching
for customers, young lady?
I can see the cars from here.
- I have a phone. Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
I guess, you got it covered.
You know, the number 10 key
was in the overnight drop box.
Good, we can double-sell
the room, she was all paid up.
You're really taking
to this aren't you?
Mm-hmm.
- [LAUGHING] Ray.
- What?
Nobody's watching.
[LAUGHING] What are you doing?
What do you think that's about?
I don't know, probably nothing.
I'll be right back.
I gotta say, this is a first.
Sorry?
Not smelling Ben's coffee
as soon as I step in here.
He always had
a full pot right over there.
I'd be glad to make you some.
Yeah, that'd be wonderful.
Howard Kellor, welcome neighbor.
- Ray, good to meet you Howard.
- And you.
Um...
- That's a start.
- Plug it in.
I'll... I'll be right back.
Not going anywhere.
What does he want?
I think he just wants to
welcome us to the neighborhood.
Seems like a nice guy.
So old Ben finally went
and sold the place.
Only swore he'd do it
for six years. [CHUCKLES]
You a friend of his?
Me? No.
No. We only met after
I answered a Craigslist ad.
No shit. [CHUCKLES]
You usually run hotels?
No, I'm an electrician.
Carpentry,
whatever I can get my hands on.
I just wanted to try
something different, you know?
Sure, I mean, why this?
Well, I guess sometimes you just
need a change of scenery, right?
Yeah, I hear that.
[CHUCKLING WISTFULLY]
Hey, I don't suppose you know
where Ben ended up, do you?
I don't, and I can't even
get him on the phone,
- his number's been disconnected.
- Yeah, and you know what,
people around here are
just funny about that.
They just up and leave without...
There's this RV city
down the road, and they do
that all the time.
Just suddenly, boom, gone,
you're like...
Well I mean, was there something
you need to see him about?
No, no. I just wanna stay
in touch with him.
Well, don't worry Howard.
Every morning I'll be sure to
have a fresh pot here for you.
Well, that sounds like a deal.
[SLURPS LOUDLY]
Oh yeah. [CHUCKLES]
Well hey, I won't bug you, I
just wanted to poke my head in.
And listen, if you ever need
a hand around here,
I know it's the off season,
and now's the
time to get stuff done,
you just come to me first.
- Will do, thank you.
- Yeah.
Oh and hey, if you
ever do hear from Ben,
you get his mailing address
for me.
- Sure thing.
- Alright.
Ray.
[DOORBELL DINGS]
Mm, that feels good babe.
You deserve a night off.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHEERING HAPPILY]
♪ Just move your heart
Until it matches mine ♪
♪ Oh baby I just wanna feel
Your body keeping time ♪
♪ It feels so good ♪
♪ I do believe you're
Pressing up on me ♪
RAY: Officer, I repeat,
I am fine.
I only had a little bit
of wine with dinner.
MAGGIE:
Oh, then walk a straight line.
And maybe some whiskey.
And a beer or two.
Don't shoot, don't shoot.
Mister, you've been
a very bad boy.
And you're gonna finish what
you started by that pool today.
- Uh-huh?
- Yeah.
Well first I wanna get us
a couple more drinks.
Okay. Copy that. Hurry up.
MAGGIE: Ray!
Ray!
It's a body, Ray.
Ray.
Ray, what the fuck is it?
It's a pig.
[MAGGIE PANTING]
Oh my god.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
TOMMY:
Ray, where you been, buddy?
I rang a bunch of times, but
nobody opened up and let me in.
Thought I was gonna have
to do it in the hot box.
Is your sign busted?
It says no vacancies.
Ain't no cars
in the parking lot.
We had a little trouble
here tonight, so I...
Yeah?
Somebody threw
a dead pig in my pool.
Oh lord. Now that's a new one.
At least you got breakfast
for a few days, huh?
I burned it out in the desert.
Damn Ray.
You not only feed
the coyotes and the crows,
but you just cook 'em up
a mess of ham?
You're a hell of a guy.
[CHUCKLING]
I gotta get back out there.
But...
But we got time
for a couple of nips, huh?
I'm good.
What did you mean
about being a new one?
Ben didn't tell you
anything, huh?
I guess he didn't say anything
'cause... 'cause
he was worried about you
getting skittish on this deal.
And... there was this girl.
This girl was staying here.
You know.
And she decided
to take a twilight swim.
But not before she cut
herself up real bad.
But Ben had nothing
to do with it.
It wasn't his responsibility,
'cause that gate was locked.
She jumped over the gate,
bled out in the pool.
Look, I gotta get back there,
I got to do my duty
to my wiener.
And then I'll come back
and we'll drink some more.
No, I'm fine, you go on.
Alright, is 10 free?
Or is that 15 now?
You have a good night, Ray.
I know I'm going to.
Tommy.
Yeah?
Nothing, forget it.
You have a good night.
Alright, Ray.
Good night, buddy.
[DOORBELL DINGS]
[OMINOUS PLAYING]
HOWARD:
It's a nice little space, right?
It is, it's beautiful out here.
HOWARD:
There's the man right there.
Howard.
You been holding out on me, Ray.
You never told me you had
such a beautiful wife.
Can I bother you
for a cup of coffee?
I don't see why not.
Great. Pleasure.
- Same here.
- Hope I get to see you more.
MAGGIE: Yeah.
Yeah.
Little pick-me-up.
Heard you had some weirdness
here last night.
- How do you mean?
- Well the boys
over at the gas station said
you peeled outta
your parking lot pretty fast.
Like you was on a mission.
Oh, yeah.
Somebody tossed a pig
into my pool.
Pig.
Did you save it?
Well, it was pretty dead
already.
I'm sure it was just a prank,
that's why
I didn't call anybody.
And where did the carcass
end up?
I took it out to the desert
and got rid of it.
I really didn't wanna
make a big deal out of it.
Well you made one, Ray.
Because the rangers found
it this morning.
Or what was left of it.
Look, if you're gonna
roast a pig,
do it in a fucking campsite,
will ya?
I... I'm sorry, Howard, I really
didn't know what to do.
You know, Maggie
was pretty upset about it and I
just wanted to get
the thing outta here.
It was pretty weird.
So that happens, and what,
you're on your way back here,
and you get lost?
Because the boys say you
don't show back up here
for a couple hours.
Yeah, I just sat
in my truck and...
listened to music.
I just needed to decompress
from everything.
That's what I saw
on the general store cameras,
I appreciate
you leveling with me.
Do you know who did it?
Well who's to say?
Some punks with nothing
better to do, I'm sure.
They used to give Ben
grief all the time,
I will talk to them,
to back off.
I mean does this have anything
to do with that girl
who killed herself?
I can't quite understand
how anybody...
could come up with that.
Unless she knew how to slit
her belly clean through...
before she jumped
into the water.
Killed herself?
She was just a townie.
- Crissy Neal.
- Crissy?
Parents died
right outta high school,
she was just a drifter...
no one to care about her.
I mean she had some folks
that she was friends with here
in town, and I liked her
a lot, sweet pea.
Then the L.A. prick shows up,
does what he does to her,
and he stayed here
for a little while.
They're looking for him,
but you know,
L.A.'s a big town.
How long ago...
did it happen?
It's funny
you should ask me that.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Because the answer
is a real pisser.
It was the night after
you showed up here
to come see this place
for the first time.
I mean it was just
a couple months ago
you came here
to look at it, right.
And the boys across the street
said they saw your same truck
in this parking lot...
the day before.
Is that some strange-ass
timing or what?
Did you do it?
Did I do it?
- Did I do what?
- Ray, did you do it?
- Did I do what, the pig?
- Did you do it?
- Howard?
- Ray, did you do it?
- Did I do...
- Did you do it?
- Did I do what?
- Ray did you do it?
- Did you do it?
-Did I do what?
[CHUCKLES] I know you
didn't do it. It's all right.
So you in touch with Ben at all?
No.
Listen Ray, I want you
to give me a shout if you see...
just anyone unusual around here.
Unusual?
So far, just you, Howard.
Come again?
I've never seen anybody
who'd ask for coffee
in this kinda heat.
[CHUCKLES] Well you know,
you keep making it this good...
I might come an awful lot.
Take care of yourself, Ray.
[DOOR BELL DINGS]
- Hi.
Just one person?
Mm-hmm.
I'll give you...
room three.
Oh,
I really like that end room.
What number is that again?
Ten.
That's right...
Ten's a peach.
I'll take 10.
[SOFT THUD]
There you go. Have a good night.
You too.
Oh, and if you need anything...
say...
coffee, or...
just anything,
I'll have a fresh pot
here in the morning.
I know what you need.
- Brochures.
- What?
One of those racks
with all the brochures.
Goes right over there.
Or over there.
Good night.
[FAINT SIRENS]
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
- What? What? What is it?
- [SOBBING] [SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
It's a tiny little snake.
[SOBBING]
- I no clean.
- Okay, I'll clean.
- I no clean this room.
- I'll clean it.
- I no clean.
- I'll clean.
I no clean.
NEWSCASTER: Plane left alone...
MAGGIE: Oh my god,
Ray, come here.
NEWSCASTER: Found a body
and called the police.
- The woman has now...
- What?
- been identified...
- What is it Maggie?
NEWSCASTER: Jessica Phillips.
The cause of death
is still unknown,
but police are working with
the medical examiner's office
to determine exactly
how she died,
but so far results of an autopy
have not yet been released.
Is that her, Ray?
That's her, isn't it?
She was our first guest.
[DOORBELL DINGS]
[BUZZER BUZZING]
Ray, can you get that?
Ray?
[BUZZER BUZZING]
Okay, I'll get it.
Hi, can I help you?
I just wanted to ask
you a few questions.
About Ray.
[DIAL TONE RINGING]
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Ray, pick up.
Fuck!
[DOORBELL DINGS]
[DOOR CLOSES SOFTLY]
Hi, how are you?
Would you mind filling
this out for me, please?
Okay.
Do you have a room preference?
We've got double
or king available.
That I do. Room 10, please.
Been here before?
This your old man?
-Yeah, Ray, why? You know him?
Hmm.
I'd keep my eye on
that one if I were you.
[DOOR OPENS WITH A CREAK]
[ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you ready to do
everything I say?
- WOMAN 1: Yes, mistress.
- WOMAN 2: I'm sorry,
did I say that you could speak?
Get on your knees.
Are you ready to do
everything I say.
Good, knees.
Do my shoes look clean to you?
No, mistress.
WOMAN: I'm sorry,
did I say you could speak?
Why don't you clean them?
Good.
You have permission.
[DEEP BREATHING]
[CLATTERING SOUND]
God damn you fucks!
Hey, did you see that, just now?
Someone just threw red paint,
maybe blood,
over my wall down there.
- Did you see anybody?
- I wasn't watching.
- You weren't?
- No.
I thought you spent a lot
of time watching my place.
Figured you must've seen
somebody.
Now why would I watch
your place?
- You tell me.
- You want something or not?
Yeah, I want you out
of my fucking business.
And I might just
call the cops anyway,
tell them I suspect you.
Look, I got no time
for your shit.
It might've been locals, but
don't come in here accusing me.
So, that's your place now, huh?
That's right.
Sure as hell wouldn't want
your gig.
Why's that?
Seems like the pool would
be hard to keep clean is all.
Do you know that woman
from the news tonight?
Everybody knows
everybody around here.
Except you.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Nobody knows where
My head goes ♪
♪ Oh would you ever tell ♪
♪ Maybe your head knows ♪
Hi.
Do you remember me?
Should I?
I run the Motorway Motel,
over off to 55.
Congratulations.
Listen, baby, you're cute,
but check back with me
tomorrow, okay?
I have a date on the way.
No I'm not here about that.
Well, please,
just sit right down.
I saw you at my place.
You were with... you were
with that girl from room six,
the one they found out
in the desert.
You like to watch, is that it?
You got that look.
You know the more you
watch, the less you feel.
Come here.
I wanna see if I know you.
Easy baby, don't hurt yourself.
Mama won't let you fall.
Nobody's watching.
Hey, we're just sitting here
looking at each other, right?
You were with that girl
the night she died.
She needed a friend, is all.
I was her friend.
- What are you a cop?
- No, I just...
run the motel.
Well, why don't you go
do that then?
I'm meeting someone.
I'll move when they get here.
Yes, you will.
I don't know anything
about that girl
- or any other girl.
- Yeah, you do.
You just said,
you were her friend.
So, what else do you know?
I know get the fuck
away from me.
You got a problem here, Cassie?
Yeah.
But it's just leaving.
Time to go.
I'm talking to her.
Get the fuck out!
Now, motherfucker, go.
Alright! Alright.
Who else was in that room
with you?
Wanna be a hero?
Back up.
- Back the fuck up. Back up!
- Okay.
- Easy.
- Yeah?
You don't wanna
do anything stupid.
Stay the fuck away
from my motel.
The Motorway Motel.
You're not welcome.
Honey, I'm so sorry,
I left my phone.
Where were you this time, Ray?
What?
And don't tell me
that you went out for a beer.
I saw you go after
that bitch, I saw you.
It was not like that.
- Did you fuck her?
- What?
What are
you talking about?
And the girl that
was staying here,
the one that got murdered,
I bet you fucked her too.
What the fuck are you talking
about, Maggie?
Howard came...
Ray, and he was asking
all kinds of questions
about the night
that she stayed here.
You waited this long to tell me?
I was trying to call you!
What'd you say to him?
I told him that you were here
and that we were together
and that we got in a fight
and that you went to go
blow off some steam,
that you weren't here.
- Okay.
- Is that good enough for you?
- Yeah, that's okay.
- Don't you fucking touch me,
don't touch me!
Ow!
Maggie, stop, open the door.
- Goddammit!
- MAGGIE: Stay away from me, Ray.
Just calm down.
Would you just open
the goddam door?
MAGGIE: Stay the fuck away
from me.
No, no I'm not letting you.
No, you are not.
[MAGGIE SCREAMING AND YELLING]
You fucked the whore.
Calm down. Calm down!
Go in the shower.
You're gonna cool off.
- No, Ray!
- Calm down!
Fuck you, Ray,
I won't calm down!
- Cool off, cool off, Maggie.
- Fucking let go.
Calm down, that's it, that's it.
Ow!
Maggie.
Come on... just... please,
I don't wanna have a fight.
Okay, okay.
Dammit, Ray.
I just... just let it out,
that's okay.
Okay, alright.
Alright.
[GASPING BREATHLESSLY]
-Maggie?
Hey, Ray.
Remember my mom's cabin?
We went there one spring when
I was still talking to her.
I think I'm gonna go there
for a while
and sort some stuff out.
- I'm sorry.
- That's all right.
Last night was...
it was great
in its own way but...
I think it's best if you hold
down the fort here
for a little while. Yeah?
That way you don't have to...
feel badly about lying
all the time
when you fuck around.
It's okay.
It's who you are, it's who
you're always gonna be, but...
I realized something
about myself last night.
[SCOFFS]
I can't live like this anymore,
because no matter
how badly it might hurt,
I don't wanna be
lied to any more.
Maggie, I need you here with me.
If there's stuff
I didn't tell you,
it was because I was so worried
about you.
It's true, Maggie, please.
What?
You gotta stay.
[SOBS]
What is it?
Oh, Maggie.
Talk to me.
I... I'll just show it
to you, I'll show you.
You watched people have sex
without them knowing it.
That woman, you followed her
to the bar?
Who the fuck are you, Ray?
You sat behind this mirror.
Jesus Christ, look at you,
look at your face.
This is a crime, Ray,
we could lose the motel,
you could go to jail.
I feel sick.
It was stupid, I know.
It's my fault.
Something happened in this room.
Like what?
I don't know for sure.
Might have something to do
with that girl's death.
And maybe
the other girl, Crissy.
And I don't think
they're the only ones.
[BANGING SOUND]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Morning.
I didn't expect you on a Sunday.
Yeah, it surprised
the both of us.
Oh...
what happened there?
This, it's nothing, I just
banged it on a corner
last night, being careless.
Come here, come a little closer,
let me take a look at that.
Oh yeah, buddy,
you got your shiner.
- Let me get you an ice pack.
- No, no, I'm fine, really.
Why don't I get you some coffee?
I'm good. Iced tea.
You were right, why drink coffee
in this heat?
Listen, you just keep doing
whatever you were doing,
I'll just hang out
with you a bit.
I was just finishing up
cleaning some rooms.
Good by me. [CLEARS THROAT]
Yeah, after what you said,
I got to thinking...
how dumb it was to be
drinking something hot
when I'm already hot.
Guess there's something
to be said
for that big city logic.
Why do you think
I'm from the city?
You told me.
I did?
I don't remember that.
No? Somebody told me.
Now maybe it was Ben
before you, before you got here,
I don't know.
The hell was that?
Goddamn praying mantis in here.
You ever see the inside wings
one of these things?
It's like a dark, burnt orange,
kinda like a sunset.
When they fly at you, it's...
like there's a demon
heading right for you.
Ah, here's something.
Jesus,
that could've gone better.
Sorry, Ray.
-It's okay.
Here, just give me a wet cloth,
I'll clean this up.
No really, it's fine,
I'll take care of it.
Well listen, I'm in your way.
You know, you...
You just answer me one thing,
and I'll get outta your hair.
Okay.
I really...
need to speak with Ben.
Have you ever heard
anything from him?
No.
You don't think Ben has anything
to do with this, do you?
Well, only that he might
remember something
from the first time round,
help me make a case.
It's a poke in the grass,
but it's worth a shot.
So, do you know?
I... I don't Howard, I'm sorry.
You know, we're small-town cops
and all, but,
it doesn't mean that...
we don't have access
to the big city police reports.
You had some year, huh?
I mean it's bad enough
that your little girl...
falls...
from a window, but then
all these questions pop up.
Were there domestic
dispute calls
made to the residence?
Was the wife
a known substance abuser?
Or the husband a heavy drinker?
And why
was the husband socializing...
with the neighbor next
door during the incident?
Can the parents be charged
with child negligence?
I mean is this...
is this why you made some
kind of deal with Ben?
I don't...
feel like talking
to you anymore.
Look, I get it, you wanna
put all this behind you.
You move somewhere new,
you wanna start fresh.
But Ben Harling has left you
holding a steaming bag of shit.
And I don't know why
you're so loyal to him.
I need all the help
I can get, Ray.
How many times you
think she's been here?
Maybe five, six times total.
She was registered
under Sally Smith,
but I think they also
call her Cassie.
- Who does?
- Some guy did
in a bar last night.
You were with her
in a bar last night?
I just happened to be drinking
at the same place.
Yeah, with a gun, I heard.
HOWARD: I know who that is,
she goes by a ton of names.
It just... up to her
old tricks again.
But hey, do you remember
who it was?
- Who what was?
- Called her Cassie.
Just some guy did,
I didn't know him.
He was big, had a crew cut.
- What, like a military crew cut?
- Yeah.
Who knows, maybe she has a...
partner in this crew cut guy.
What do you mean, partner?
I don't know.
Maybe they're into some...
weirdness together.
You know, fetish stuff,
sick shit, theatrics, whatever.
I'm not sure exactly, but,
there's something
going on with her.
I'm afraid, I'm not following.
You said you wanted me to tell
you about anybody unusual?
She's unusual.
- Sorry, I got a customer.
- Yeah,
no you did the right thing here.
This... this could be a lead
in all of this, and if you...
end up seeing that Mustang again
I want you to call the station
and you ask just for me.
I'll get a GPS on that
- and I'll see where it goes.
- Right.
And Ray, listen,
are you in touch with Ben?
No, I am not.
Alright.
Ray, Ray look,
hey thanks for that.
[HOWARD CLEARS THROAT]
Uh, yeah, hi.
Can I... Can I get the number
for a Ben Harling, please?
Benjamin, maybe.
H-A-R-L-I-N-G.
I realize that, but I very much
need to speak with him,
so please if you hear from him,
would you tell him to call me.
Tell him it's an emergency.
[PHONE RINGING]
- Hello.
- BEN: Hey, Ray?
Yes, yeah, Ben.
- BEN: You called?
- Ben, I know,
I know, I've been trying
to track you down.
I need to talk to you.
Are you still there?
BEN: Just meet me
off a High Pass Road.
Just past the wind turbine,
by the old Country Two exit.
Ben, Ben?
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[APPARATUS CLICKING]
Ray?
Ben.
Are you alone?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Okay, okay.
- Good.
- What was that?
It's Russian-made,
they use it in the Ukraine.
Are you staying
up there somewhere?
Oh, somewhere, man,
but not staying long.
You can bet on that.
I don't think anybody
followed me,
if that's what you think.
Well it's conceivable, isn't it?
Everything is conceivable.
Oh, Ray, did you finish
that screen door for room three?
I had three guys working on it,
it was like major brain surgery,
and I would've done it myself...
The door's fine.
We need to talk.
About what?
I... I really shouldn't even
be here, Ray.
I came down because you
were calling everybody
- and you can't do that.
- Come on, Ben.
Ben. What is going on?
What is going on?
The world is demented,
it is peerlessly demented.
It's all this shit that's
coming down, and you know.
You built that thing,
didn't you?
That tunnel.
What did you see?
Did you see something, Ray?
I... I never did anything, I...
- I never even said anything.
- You put them in room 10, right,
and then you watched?
It was sociology,
it's the study of people.
I like to study people,
that's all.
- Right.
- Did you see something, Ray.
You should close it up.
And you should think
about getting out.
Was somebody killed in there?
Crissy?
Little Crissy.
Oh wow, she was a...
she was quite a child.
She was special, that one.
Listen, Ray.
I tell you what, I'll send you
back half your money, okay?
Half the money, you can
take it or leave it.
But take that lovely
wife of yours and go.
And maybe you'll be fine.
She brought in that
new microwave, right?
- You got a new micro...
- [GUNSHOT SOUND]
[BELL DINGING]
[MUSIC RISING TO CRESCENDO]
Come on, come on, pick up.
Maggie, Maggie please,
you really have to listen
to me very carefully.
We have to leave now.
We have to leave now, just
lock yourself in the house
and don't answer the door
for anybody.
Please, there's no time
to explain,
just do what I say,
I'll tell you everything
when we're on the road.
Just pack. Ben's dead, pack now!
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Maggie. Maggie?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Looks like your boy
is gonna chicken out.
I really wanted you to see me
blow his head off.
HOWARD: Yeah, he's just yellow
you know, you can kinda,
just kinda tell.
Probably just packing up
his shit to go right now.
But listen, when we hear
that truck pull away,
we can...
commence our getting it on.
[GROANING]
HOWARD: What's that,
I can't hear you? Hang on.
[MAGGIE GRUNTING]
Hang on, hang on.
Fucking freak, let me go!
- Let me...
- Hey, shh.
- Please.
- HOWARD: Shh. Shh.
- Get away?
- No, no, no, no.
- Please.
No.
I wanna get so close to you
that I'll be in front of you
and behind you at the same time.
And everywhere in between.
And I really wanted
this to look like
a murder suicide, but if Ray's
not gonna take the bait,
[GRUNTS]
then it's just
gonna have to look like
- he killed his cheating wife.
- [MAGGIE GRUNTS]
And I'll deal with him
on the road when I catch him.
[MAGGIE SCREAMS]
[KNOCKING SOUND]
What the fuck?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[RAY GRUNTING]
Son of a bitch, that's how
Ben knew what I'd done.
Fucking pervert.
You a pervert, Ray?
You see this?
Your boy's been whacking off
while watching the hotel guests
bang each other.
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
Ray!
[RAY COUGHING]
Shit that could've gone better.
Jesus fuck, Ray.
[SLOW PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey buddy,
ma'am. Uh, 10 available?
[ENGINE REVVING]
Subtitles by explosiveskull