Subtitles
[birds singing]
[kids giggling]
[kids laughing]
[hums a tune]
- Huh?
- [whirring noise approaching]
Whoa!
[cheering]
[Maya laughing]
Yes, keep going!
- Woohoo! [laughs]
- Maya! But I wanna get off!
Oh, can't we just... [screams]
Willi! Close your mouth!
You're slowing us down!
Woohoo!
Hey!
[Ben snickers]
- They're getting away!
- [Drago yelps]
[Drago] Whoa, whoa!
- Whoa!
- [all grunting]
[Drago]
Hey, ease up on the feelers!
[Maya] Sorry!
Go, Drago, faster!
You wanna go faster, huh?
I'll show you faster!
Maya, stop!
- Huh?
- Faster, Drago, faster!
- [Willi whimpers]
- [giggles]
[gasps] Oh no!
- What are you doing!?
- We can make it!
- [Willi] No, Maya don't even...
- Now, Drago!
[Willi] Maya!
- [Drago grunts]
- [Willi screaming]
Huh?
[screams approaching]
Whoa!
[cheering]
[groaning]
[giggles]
That was so fun, did you see?
We were flying upside down,
and were like... [mimics plane]
You guys were awesome!
Now who wants to race again?
Um, uh...
[whispering]
We've gotta go clean our leaf.
Bye Maya!
[Ronnie]
Wow, Maya, that was amazing!
You're so fast, you should
totally be in the Honey Games!
Thanks, Ronnie, I'd love to,
but our hive never gets invited.
Yep, and I think
that's a good thing.
I've had it with racing.
Aw Willi,
we were just having fun!
You were having fun, Maya.
I was having...
[stammers]
What's the opposite of fun?
- Not-fun?
- Not-fun. Thanks, Ronnie.
You're welcome.
- [Maya] Willi!
- What?
Tag! [chuckles]
[Willi] Oh, Maya.
Why don't you ever listen?
- Tag, you're in.
- In what?
- [sighs] It doesn't matter.
- Bye, Willi!
[Willi]
Bye, Ronnie! Hey, wait for me!
[indistinct chatter]
[buzzing]
Gather round children,
come and get your honey cakes.
- One for you.
- [gulps]
Here's yours.
[little bee]
Hey wait for me!
And for you... Oh! [chuckles] No.
[little bee 2]
Oh, happy Harvest, Your Majesty!
Oh! [chuckles]
And happy Harvest to you.
Is everything in order, Crawley?
Certainly, ma'am. The honey
barrels are being stacked
in the Great Hall as we speak.
[feet stamping]
[gasps]
[Pouring Bee shrugs]
Is... is that all of it,
Crawley?
Uh, it...
It was a short summer, ma'am.
Oh.
Don't worry,
everything will be just fine.
- [machinery creaking]
- [indistinct chatter]
[Maya and Willi laughing]
[Maya]
Come on, Willi, we're late.
- [Willi] Coming!
- [Maya woops]
I told you we're going
the wrong way.
No we're not! This is the way.
- [Maya giggles]
- Huh?
- [both scream]
- [guards grunt]
[both groan]
Ow!
Whoa.
[guards] Grr!
Hello, Mr. Important
Looking Big Bee, Sir.
Sorry we bumped into you.
I'm Maya and this is Willi.
Hmm, indeed.
- I am looking for Poppy Meadow.
- [Maya] Hmm. Huh?
I have a very important message
to deliver to the Queen.
[gasps]
You're from Buzztropolis!
Very observant.
[Maya gasps]
An important message?
That could only mean one thing.
Did you hear that, Willi?
- Did you hear it?
- Ahh...
- We're going to the Honey Games!
- We are?
- [Willi groans]
- This is really happening!
Yes!
Follow me, Mr. What'sa-Face.
I'll take you to the Queen!
Ahh...
- [Maya giggles]
- Oh, Maya.
[Beegood] Hmm.
[all cheering]
[Queen]
Hurray for Poppy Meadow.
I know it has been a long
and difficult harvest
for everyone.
You have toiled tirelessly
to collect the pollen...
Happy Harvest, Maya!
Happy Harvest!
Come on, this way.
[Queen] ...teamwork,
collaboration and community
is at the heart of the harvest.
- [guard 1 groans]
- [guard 2 chuckles]
By working together, we will
all see it through another year.
[all cheering]
Well done, Poppy Meadow.
I am Sir Beegood the third.
I come from Buzztropolis
with good news,
direct from the Empress herself.
- [gasps]
- As you know,
the glorious Honey Games
are about to commence,
and your hive has been selected
for a great, great honor...
Told you, Willi!
They're inviting us
to the Honey Games!
[Beegood]
...to generously contribute
half your honey harvest
to the Honey Games!
- [all gasp]
- Oh no!
Yay! [woops]
Wait. What?
What? Half our honey?
That's nearly 50 percent!
You can't do that!
It's not fair!
Maya, no.
[sighs]
It is an honor indeed,
Sir Beegood,
however, your request
is unreasonable.
We can certainly contribute
a little honey, but half?
Our hive won't make it
through the winter.
You dare refuse
the Empress' order?
[sighs]
Hmm.
[squirms]
As the Empress wishes.
[all gasping]
Quite right.
[hums]
No, wait, Mr. Bigbuzz!
I mean, Sir Bees... [groans]
Whatever your name is!
You've made a big mistake!
Oh, Willi,
we have to do something.
Well, yeah,
someone needs to do something.
Aw, it's gonna
be a long, hungry winter.
[sighs]
[Maya] Your Majesty?
We can't let the Empress
take our honey!
[scoffs] The Empress will do
whatever she wants.
It's not fair!
My big sister doesn't play fair,
she never has.
[gasps] She's your sister?
Oh! Well, then it's easy.
If she's your sister, then you
can just go talk to her.
[chuckles]
She won't listen to me.
Maybe I can help.
No, Maya.
There are some things
you can't fix on your own.
Excuse me, ma'am.
You're needed in the Great Hall.
Mm. It's not your concern, Maya.
I can help.
[sighs]
I can't believe
she's the Queen's Sister.
Yeah, and she's a real
meanie bug!
- We have to help the Queen!
- Mm-hm, yep.
Willi, what are you doing?
This is an emergency!
Yeah, and this
is my emergency pollen!
Anyway, how can we help?
We're just two little bees.
Hmm...
We go to Buzztropolis!
Oh, sure,
we'll just hitch a ride
somewhere we've never been
and tell a scary Empress
we don't even know,
"Sorry, but you can't
take our honey."
Yeah! That's a great plan,
Willi! Come on!
What? Plan? What plan?
- Oh, I've got a plan.
- Come on, Willi!
Oh, Maya!
[snoring]
[mutters]
[Maya] Drago? Hello!
[yawns] No more racing today.
We don't wanna race,
we need a ride to Buzztropolis!
Huh? That's a long way.
I don't want to go there.
- Come on, Drago. Just this once.
- No, no, no.
- Please? Come on Drago.
- [chuckles] Stop it.
- [chuckling]
- Come on. Come on!
Okay! Okay!
I'll do it, I'll do it.
[sighs]
Ready, Willi?
Uh-uh, not this little bee, no...
[screams] Maya!
[Maya]
Buzztropolis here we come!
[Queen]
Right, we must prepare.
Bronson, count up all the honey
barrels in the Great Hall.
Rupert go and tally
the reserves.
Yes, ma'am!
Crawley, you...
Crawley? Crawley!
[panting]
Your Majesty! Maya and Willi
were seen leaving the meadow!
It looked like
they were heading for...
Buzztropolis.
[Maya] Woohoo!
[Willi] Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa, Willi,
look at all those insects.
[indistinct chatter]
They're going
to the Honey Games.
Yeah, but they are invited.
Whoa, what is that?
That is Buzztropolis.
It's beautiful.
[indistinct chatter]
- [chuckles] Good luck, kids.
- Thanks, Drago.
Come on, Willi.
Let's find the Empress!
Uh, no, I'll just wait here
with Drago.
Whoa!
On second thoughts, coming!
[Maya giggles]
- Whoa.
- Wow.
- [Maya giggles]
- Maya...
- [giggles] Hello.
- Hello!
Whoa! Whoa!
- Maya, wait!
- Well, hurry up, Willi!
[gasps] Whoa!
So pretty!
[pants] This was a mistake.
I know what I'm doing, Willi.
Trust me.
- Bee best friends forever?
- [both chuckle]
[both]
Buzz buzz buzz!
- [both chuckle]
- Willi, look!
Maya!
- Get your honey treats here!
- Honey treats?
Must... have... honey treats.
Willi?
Willi!
Willi? Willi!
Where are you, Willi?
- Hey!
- Whoops.
Whoops yourself! Step away
from the hair, meadow bug.
Sorry, I'm looking for my friend
Willi, have you seen him?
Uh... no.
Ah. But we have urgent business
with the Empress.
[scoffs] You? With the Empress?
Oh, sure you do,
and my uncle's a dung beetle!
Really? [sniffs]
You don't smell like dung.
[sniffs]
- What? Ugh!
- [giggling]
Stop sniffing me!
Hmm.
Want to see the Empress, huh?
Her throne's right around there.
Why don't you just buzz over
and talk to her?
Oh! I will. Thanks.
[snickers]
I almost feel sorry for her.
Almost.
[all snickering]
[gasps] Wow.
[announcer]
All hive representatives
with donations to the Empress,
please assemble in the arena.
[Maya gasps]
Willi! I was so worried
about you.
I was worried about me too.
Now I'm worried I can't breathe.
[grunts]
How did you end up in the queue
to meet the Empress?
Empress? I thought this
was the line for lunch.
[bugles playing a salute]
[crowd applauding]
[salute stops]
Bring forth my gifts.
[claps hands]
- [bugle salute continues]
- [crowd cheering]
Please accept
our Honey Games offering
of fine moth silk,
noble Empress.
[grunts]
- Here!
- And here! [giggles]
[Buzzbington groans]
- [Buzzbington] Whoa!
- [crash]
Next.
Maya, what do we do?
I've never met
an Empress before.
Follow me
and put on a brave face.
This is my brave face.
She's actually doing it.
Seriously, I mean like, wow.
- You've gotta be brave...
- [Violet] Hmph!
...to front up to...
the Empress.
Or a real Fuzzbrain.
[Maya sings like a bugle]
May I present Hive Ambassador,
♪ Maya the bee ♪
That's me!
Representing the Queen
of Poppy Meadow, your sister.
Poppy Meadow, mm?
Come to donate
your finest summer Honey?
Uh, that's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
We don't have it.
[nervous laugh]
What? Is this some kind
of a prank?
Guards!
- Eject these meadow grubs.
- [guards grunt]
Wait! It's not fair,
Miss Empressy!
Why should we give you
our honey,
when you won't even let us
compete in the Games?
[all gasp]
[Buzzbington groans]
Why?
The child wants to know why.
[light chuckle]
- [Buzzbington laughs nervously]
- Because I am the Empress!
- That's why!
- [Willi shudders]
How dare my sister
send you here empty-handed?
No, no, no. She didn't.
Uh... um... [stammers]
Sir Willington, may I please
have the Queen's royal gift
- to the Empress?
- Huh? The what?
Give me the honey treat.
Nuh-uh.
One moment, Miss Empressy.
Willi, give it to me now!
[both groan]
- [wet thud]
- [Queen grunts]
[groans]
[all gasp]
- Let me help you.
- No! Stay away!
[both groan]
Willi, help!
[all groaning and grunting]
- [crash]
- [all gasp]
Ha! Typical meadow bug.
- [Queen] Maya?
- Oh.
[nervous chuckle]
I've never been so humiliated
in my life, Beatrice!
She must be punished!
I will talk to her, Catherine.
She assaults the Empress
and you'll talk to her?
This is why your hive
is a laughing stock.
- We are not!
- Really?
No order. No rules.
Little bees who talk
out of turn. [grunts] Grr!
And you wonder why I don't
invite you to the Honey Games.
[gasps]
Maybe you're scared we'll win.
[cackling] Oh, please.
The Honey Games
are for elite bugs.
You never had what it takes,
and by the looks
of this bumble bug,
neither does she.
Maya is one of my best bees.
Ha! She's no match
for the best of Buzztropolis.
- I am too! And so is Willi!
- Maya!
- [all gasp]
- [Maya] It's true.
Poppy Meadow bees
are braver and faster and nicer
than any of you city bees!
- Maya, hush.
- [Empress] No, no, no.
If your little bee
is so confident,
I invite her and her friend
to compete in the Games.
[gasps]
[sighs]
If they win, all is forgiven.
But if they lose,
I'll make an example
of this pair
and take all your summer honey.
Every last drop.
But our hive
won't last the winter!
Poppy Meadow doesn't even
have a team! We're not prepared.
[claps hands]
Beegood, assemble a squad
of Poppy Meadow's
most gifted bugs immediately.
[sighs] Yes, your regal-ness.
Of course.
Let the games begin.
I am very disappointed
in you, Maya.
I specifically asked you
not to get involved.
I know. I just wanted to help.
But I didn't, did I?
You have to stop buzzing in,
thinking you know what's best.
I'm so sorry, Miss Queen.
[sighs]
Well, we're here now.
And you can't win these Games
on your own.
You must listen to your team.
I will. I promise.
[guard clears throat]
Time to go, ma'am.
I believe in you, Maya.
I know you can
make Poppy Meadow proud.
Mm-hm.
[sighs]
- [Queen] Willi?
- Huh?
Maya, make sure
you stick together.
- And good luck.
- [Willi giggles nervously]
[sighs]
[sighs] Willi, the whole hive
is depending on us.
Hmm, yeah.
But hey, this won't be so hard.
I mean, you are the fastest
racer in Poppy Meadow.
[giggles] Whoa.
The Honey Games Village.
[announcer] All bugs report
to the gathering place.
Orientation will commence
in five minutes.
- Come on!
- Oh, hey, wait for me.
[Maya chuckles]
You're right Willi,
we can do this.
We just need
to put our best foot forward.
Uh, but which one
is my best foot?
[grunts]
[chuckles]
Hey, wait for me! Whoa!
Willi, look at all
the different bugs!
[bugs cheer]
- Look! Willi?
- [Willi screams]
[groans]
[gasps]
[choir singing]
[shimmering]
Can I help you?
[sighs]
Hello? Do you speak, goggle-bug?
Ahh. Hi.
I'm Willi,
and this is my best foot.
- Or is it this one?
- [chuckling]
[gong chimes]
Ugh! Let's buzz.
- [chuckles] Mm.
- Willi! There you are!
Willi?
[gasps]
That looks like our flag!
Um, where's our team?
[chuckles] The weird new bugs?
They're hiding
down at Skeeter Swamp.
Good luck with that bunch.
[bugles playing a salute]
Good evening, bugs.
Welcome
to the Honey Games Village.
I am Games Master Beegood.
[royal music]
- [Maya] Flip!
- [gasps]
[Maya] Hey Flip, over here!
Maya! Fancy seein' you
‘ere little buzzer!
[Beegood clears his throat]
Thank you.
Over the next three days,
teams representing
the five meadows
will compete against each other.
At the end of each day,
one team will be eliminated.
This year's teams are...
- Team Buggy Hollow!
- [cheering]
Team Burly Bluff!
Team Aphid Gorge!
Team Tropolis!
And finally,
the surprising addition
to this year's lineup,
Team Poppy Meadow.
[gasps] That's us Willi!
On the final day,
the two remaining teams
will compete
in front of the Empress...
...for The Honey Cup!
[gasps and applause]
Willi, we're gonna win that cup.
[Violet chuckles]
We're gonna win that cup.
Bye Willi.
Bye.
[sighs] So, where's our cabin?
Over here.
Uh, I don't know.
- It doesn't look very safe.
- [Flip] Hello little ones.
[Maya] Flip!
Are you lost?
We're looking
for Team Poppy's cabin.
Oh, you won't find it up there.
That's Slug Hill, a nasty place.
It's out of bounds.
Your cabin's just over there.
Who's on our team, Flip?
They said it would be
the finest bugs in Poppy Meadow.
Well, I hope
we know some of them.
There's only one way
to find out.
Thanks, Flip! Come on Willi!
- [Maya giggles]
- Good luck you two!
Poppy Meadow
believes in you, kiddo!
Hello, anybody there?
Hello?
- [both scream]
- [Willi gasps]
Uh, guys. You can come out.
It's, like, not Violet.
Maya, quick, hide!
Uh, maybe I'm in
the wrong place.
I bet it's one of her friends.
Beat it, city bee! This cave's
for Poppy Meadow bugs only!
I am a Poppy Meadow bug!
[sniffs]
She doesn't smell
like one of Violet's friends.
- Violet's not my friend.
- Lucky you.
That girl's meaner
than a scorpion
that stung its own backside.
And she's mean too.
And she thinks she's, like,
so funny, but she's so not.
She won't be laughing
when we win that golden cup.
Guys wait, she's serious.
No one thinks we can win.
But aren't you the finest bugs
in Poppy Meadow?
[all laugh]
That's so funny.
We're only here
because Beegood said
we'd won a trip
to the Honey Games.
He never told us
we had to compete.
Don't stress, the sooner we lose
the sooner we can go home.
What? No! I have to win.
We have to win!
Anyway,
what's your name little bee?
I'm Maya,
and that's my friend Willi.
- Hi. Maya, run now!
- What's your name?
I'm Craig,
pleased to meet... [gasps]
Don't worry about Craig,
he hates germs.
I'm sorry little bee,
I just don't shake hands,
unless they're mine.
The spider up there is Spinder.
She's a vegetarian.
If it's got a face,
I don't eat it.
[Willi whimpers]
And the angry little bedbug
over there is Bedford.
[chewing]
Just one thing with him,
sometimes he bites.
[gasps] Strangers!
Save yourselves.
[both]
Hut hut hut hut hut hut hut!
Privates Arnie and Barney
reporting for Games duty, sir!
What're you two doing here?
Well, Maya, a little bird told
us you might need some help.
And then it tried to eat us.
It was actually
quite a big bird.
So, here we are,
peak physical specimens.
- Higher!
- Faster.
- Stronger!
- Weaker.
[Arnie]
Beatle, sunshine, raindrop.
[Barney] Now you're just
listing words, Arnie,
- but who needs words?
- Not me, Barney.
Actions speak louder than words.
- Burpees!
- [both belch]
Chin ups!
Feel the burn. Feel the burn!
It's burning.
And shake it off.
These guys are strange.
Don't worry,
they'll grow on you.
- Huh?
- Grow on us?
Like fungus? [groans]
You can sleep over there.
[chuckles nervously]
Good night!
Hut hut hut hut hut hut!
[snoring]
We can't win with these bugs.
We can do this.
Every bug has a talent.
[screams]
I've got my eyes on you,
both of them.
[teeth chatter]
[crowd cheering]
[Mantis] Good morning bugs!
And welcome to day one
of competition!
Today's event is Dodge Ball!
The team with the fewest points
at day's end will be eliminated.
[Beegood] First round,
team Burly Bluff
versus team Poppy Meadow.
Teams into position.
Seriously?
Even their muscles have muscles.
This should be good.
[snickers]
We'll be great, just follow
my lead. Everyone ready?
[blows whistle] Play ball!
[thudding and grunting]
Whoa!
Okay time out, time out!
- Huh?
- What did he...? What?
[gasps]
Arnie how did you do that?
As long as you make a capital T,
you put this hand on top
of this hand, the game stops.
Show me again!
Oh sure,
you take this hand and...
[gasps]
Extra time... [gasps]
[both moan]
[Willi groans]
[Beegood]
Team Burly Bluff win!
[snickering]
Boom, show me the love.
[Beegood] Team Burly Bluff
versus Team Tropolis!
[crowd cheering]
[chuckles]
Well, well, more little bugs.
Oh, poor Violet, I can't watch.
[whistle blows]
[voice slowed down]
Oh, no!
[crowd gasping]
[grunts]
Oh no.
[whistle blows]
[Beegood]
Team Tropolis wins!
[snickers]
Next.
Oh, she's really good.
[sighs] She sure is.
We're good too!
If we work together,
we can achieve anything.
[groans] I think motivational
speaking is, like, her thing.
[Beegood] Team Buggy Hollow
versus Team Aphid Gorge!
Aww, how cute.
Don't worry, little baby bugs.
We'll go easy on you.
[cooing]
Let's get ‘em all!
[all gasp]
[whistle blows]
[groaning]
[Beegood] Team Tropolis
versus Team Poppy Meadow!
[crowd cheering]
[chuckles] Looking a bit
off-color, Team Poppy.
[sighs]
Team Tropolis attack!
Let's go, Team Poppy!
[screaming]
[chuckles then grunts]
Willi!
Pollen.
[whimpers]
Craig, throw the pollen!
- [sighs] I'm so out of here.
- [Maya] Spinder!
Bedford, you have to move.
[grunts]
Ha! Great team you got there,
Maya!
[snickering]
[screams]
[both groan]
You saved me.
You're my special friend now.
Arnie! Barney! Help Spinder!
[both] Aye, aye, Captain.
- What did she say?
- She said, "Help spin her."
Ten-four, bug daddy! Spin her!
Spin her, now!
[groaning]
- [Arnie] Incoming!
- [Barney] Outgoing! [giggles]
[gasps]
[gasping]
Victory to Team Tropolis!
- [crowd cheering]
- Ha!
Oh, we lost again.
But look, we got some points.
Huh?
[Craig] We got points!
We've got points!
We got points!
Uh, not that I care.
[whistling]
But, is it enough?
[Team Tropolis cheering]
[gong chimes]
And so ends day one
of competition.
You should all be very proud.
Unfortunately, one team
had to finish last
and today, that team is...
- Buggy Hollow...
- Oh, what?
...who finished just one point
below Team Poppy.
We made it through?
- We made it through! Ha, yes!
- Yeah! Woohoo!
[chuckles and woops]
- Yes!
- [Willi woops]
Go team! Let's get some food
and celebrate!
[yawns] I'm gonna go lie down.
- Yep. Nighty-night.
- [Barney snores]
[Spinder sighs]
See you back at camp, Maya.
[Barney] I gotta sleep.
Huh. Hmm.
Should we be worried?
About her?
[scoffs] Hardly.
[chuckles]
Every bug has a weakness.
[crickets chirping]
[Empress chomps on treats]
[Beegood]
Your Empressness,
I have the team scores
after Day One.
Excellent. We're first.
[Crawley panting]
The team scores, Your Majesty.
Excellent! We're not last.
[groans] Ew!
Yuck.
Taste it, Willi.
Trying new things is good.
But I don't like new things.
I like pollen.
[little bugs cheering]
[Violet] I have pollen, Willi.
Oh... okay.
Team Tropolis' food
is flown in specially for us.
Wanna join me?
Ah! Violet, thank you!
[slurps]
Hey, come on, Maya!
Yes, Maya. Please, take a seat.
Hmm. Okay, thanks, Violet.
- Sorry, that's Chelsea's spot.
- Huh?
[chuckles]
Oh, sorry.
Oops. That's Sandra's.
Hmm?
Spotty, Dotty
and Lotty are there.
Hmm.
[stammers]
That's reserved for Brian.
[grunts] Hey!
Come back here dinner! Hey!
Oh gee,
looks like there's no room
for you.
Why are you being mean?
Oh, I'm sorry how rude.
Here, have some delicious,
golden pollen.
[Maya gasps]
Oh, dear.
I must have eaten it all.
[growls]
- Ow! My hand!
- [Willi] What?
Maya, what did you do?
- Nothing.
- [Violet pretends to sob]
It hurts! It hurts!
What's wrong,
my little honey-puff?
She smashed my hand!
That's not true!
[sobbing continues]
Are you accusing my daughter
of lying, meadow bug?
- "Daughter"?
[voice trembling] Maybe if she
said sorry, I could forgive her.
Very well. Apologize, Maya.
[groans] But I...
Maya, just say sorry.
[grumbles]
[clears throat]
Violet, I'm sorry.
- But I didn't do anything!
- [all gasp]
[sobbing]
She's mean, Daddy!
I knew you were a bother
the moment I laid eyes on you,
little bee.
What? No, I just...
Silence! This is your first
and last warning!
Any more trouble from you
and you're out of the Games.
But I...
Uh, what she's trying to say
is she's really sorry.
Aren't you, Maya?
[muffled] No I'm not!
[Violet]
Thanks, Willi.
You're a pal.
[grumbles]
But... Oh, Maya.
[snickering]
You mixed-up weirdos
got lucky today,
but tomorrow, you're...
ow, ow, ow... out of here.
[groaning]
"My name's Violet
and I think I'm so super cool,
with my purple hair
and my fancy pollen."
Ugh!
[grumbles]
[sighs]
[exhales deeply]
[Willi] Maya?
Come back, please?
Hmm.
[sighs]
I don't think your new pal
likes me.
Violet's nice.
Give her a chance.
Nice? She called Team Poppy
a mixed up bunch of weirdos.
I'm sure that was a...
compliment.
[sighs]
Hey, didn't you say
that every bug has a talent?
Well maybe our talent
is being...
different. [chuckles]
[sighs]
Hey, Bee friends forever?
[both chuckle]
I'm glad you're here with me,
Willi.
Me too, Maya.
Me too.
[all snoring]
[horn blowing]
[gasps]
[both] Sir, yes, sir!
[both gasp]
Wakey-wakey, Team Poppy.
Your training session
starts now!
Huh? What are you talking about?
Yesterday was just a fluke,
Maya!
I'm outta here. Excuse me.
- Wait, you can't just give up.
- Pardon me.
[moans]
What's the point of even trying?
Don't you get it, Maya?
Beegood only picked us because
we're hopeless at everything.
That's not true.
Spinder, I want you to catch
this pebble with your web.
Really? Sounds kinda stupid.
But okay.
I know you can do it. Ready?
No.
[groans]
It's raining in my soul
right now.
You just need a little
more practice, that's all.
What about you, Craig?
Show us what great scuttlers
roaches are.
Yahoo!
That was great! You didn't
even notice the roof was dirty.
- [gasps]
- [thud]
Your turn, Bedford.
What's your special skill?
I like to dance.
Ooh, and singing.
I like singing best.
Maya, it's no use,
we're just not good enough.
Come on, sleepy bugs!
We've got two hours
until the Games start.
If we wanna win it,
we gotta be ready!
Oh no, she's doing it again.
[funky music playing]
♪ And even if you think
You'll fail ♪
♪ It will be alright ♪
♪ 'Cause everybody has
A talent ♪
♪ Everybody has a talent ♪
♪ There'll be someone with you
Who's prepared to fight ♪
♪ Let's go, let's go
Let's go, let's go! ♪
♪ Clap your hands
Shake your hips ♪
♪ Move your head
And shake your hips ♪
♪ Don't be too late ♪
♪ Can we push it?
Can we push it? ♪
♪ We do it, do it, do it
With our teammates ♪
And we push it ♪
♪ We do it, do it, do it
With our teammates ♪
And we push it ♪
[blows whistle]
[Mantis]
Welcome to Willow Tree Washout!
Teams will race to the top
of the tree,
avoiding the falling dew drops.
Only one member from each team
needs to cross the finish line.
Uh... it's too high.
Don't be afraid, Bedford,
I'll be right here with you.
And remember
your training, guys.
What training?
- You remember any training?
- Nope.
[Mantis] Ready, set...
[all grunt]
- [blows whistle]
- Go.
- Go! Go! Go!
- Let's go!
[cheering]
And Team Tropolis
taking the early lead.
Hmm? [screams]
[crowd gasping]
There goes part of their team.
Oh, the Aphids have
three members left.
Faster, guys!
We're not gonna make it!
I gotta get going.
What? You can't leave us.
[sighs] I have to.
Maya, wait!
Maya, what are you doing?
[all gasp]
[Mantis] Looks like Maya
has cut her team loose.
To victory!
This is fun. Hey, how you doing?
Woohoo!
[grunting]
No!
[Mantis] Team Poppy
continue to struggle.
[sighs]
Thanks for your help, Maya.
[chuckles]
[Mantis] Team Tropolis
down to their captain.
[gasps]
[screams]
Too slow, meadow bug!
- [grunts]
- [Aphid chuckles]
[giggles]
[chuckling] Yay!
Violet, shake your stinger!
[Violet panting]
[both grunt]
First place, Aphid Gorge.
[Aphids cheering]
Second, my snail-footed
daughter Violet
and her Team Tropolis.
And third...
Ugh! Team Poppy Meadow.
Woohoo! Yes!
[laughs]
Sorry, Daddy.
Mm. I should hope so.
[sighs]
We did it! We did it!
We made it through!
You made it through.
[Maya] What? What do you mean?
Where are you going?
You left us behind.
So much for teamwork.
[sighs]
But... but I had to.
[Crawley panting]
Sweet honey cakes!
We're in the last three.
They're in the last three?
Your daughter
better not fail me, Beegood.
[gasps]
The pride of Buzztropolis
is at stake. [grunts]
[gulps] Yes, Your Majesty,
of course, of course.
Hello? Everyone?
- I'm sorry that I left...
- [Willi] Maya?
It's okay.
It's not okay.
I shouldn't have buzzed off
on everyone.
It's just if I don't win
the Games...
The Empress will take
your honey, Willi told us.
- Yep.
- Mm-hm.
- [sighs]
- Hmm.
Maya, why didn't you
say something?
[sighs] I don't know.
I...
I didn't want to worry you.
But we're here for you, Maya.
- I'm here.
- You're here.
- They're here.
- He's here.
- He's here too.
[both] We're here for you.
Yeah, that's what teams are for.
You're right.
Team?
[Spinder chuckles]
[groaning]
Go Team Poppy!
[all chuckle]
[indistinct chatter]
[Mantis] Welcome to the Maze
of the Megabeast!
Teams will have to navigate
their way
through the many paths
of the maze
to the exit at the north end.
Flying is not permitted
in this event.
And beware.
Somewhere within
lurks the mysterious...
- Megabeast.
- [all gasp]
Wake the beast at your peril.
Racers, take your marks.
- [whistle blows]
- [Maya] Go!
[all coughing]
- Eat...
- Our...
Dust!
Willi, wait!
Spinder, spin me some web.
- We need to stay together.
- Huh?
This way, team.
[grunting and panting]
[groans]
[jeers]
Oh no!
Where are they?
Maya?
[echoing] Maya?
This way!
Um, Violet, I think the exit's
at the north end.
So, since the sun's...
Just let me do the thinking,
okay?
[all sighing]
[all gasp]
[distant bird tweeting]
Where's Willi?
Hmm? Hang on a minute.
Maya?
Maya, are you there?
[groans] Maya?
[echoing] Maya?
- Willi? Willi! Willi!
- [team grunting]
[low growl]
Willi! Over here!
I think we found the Megabeast.
Careful, Willi, don't wake it.
What?
[low growl]
[Willi] Whoa!
[screeches]
[giggles]
It's not as scary as it looks.
- [roars]
- [all scream]
[crowd gasps]
It sounds like someone's
found the Megabeast.
[all scream]
[Willi groans]
Follow that Megabeast!
[Arnie and Barney panting]
I don't understand.
We should be there now.
Um, Violet, that's what I was
trying to tell you.
If we just go north then...
I have had it with this team!
All you do is slow me down!
- Uh, can you guys hear that?
- [rumbling approaching]
The only thing you should
listen to is the sound of my...
[Violet screams]
[Team Poppy panting]
[both scream]
Jump, Willi!
[screams]
Willi!
[Mantis] Team Poppy
are first to cross the line.
- We made it!
- [Team Poppy cheers]
Yeah!
Not... so... fast!
I think you'll find I beat them.
Actually, it was first team
over the line.
[Mantis] And it's Team Tropolis
in second place.
- [panting]
- No! I am Team Tropolis!
Those slug bugs
are nothing without me!
- Huh?
- Excuse me?
- Hmph!
- Chelsea, Sandra?
I'm your captain!
Daddy, wait. I... I can explain!
Save it! Excuses are for losers!
I thought my daughter
was a winner!
But I am!
I am a winner.
[Mantis] Team Poppy
and Team Tropolis
- are our grand finalists.
- [all cheering]
[Mantis]
This calls for a celebration!
[growls]
[Empress]
Team Poppy?
How could you let this happen,
Beegood?
This is absolutely...
...wonderful news!
[Crawley] Uh...
Pack your pollen, Crawley!
We're off to the Honey Games!
Hurray! [chuckles]
[jazzy music playing]
Nice spread!
♪ Dance, dance, dance, dance ♪
Maya, don't let her get to you.
Yeah, she'll just get you
in trouble.
[sighs]
Come on, let's enjoy the party.
- Oh yeah.
- Hey, Flip!
Hi, Maya!
- Yeah.
- [chuckles]
Mind if I cut in?
- [giggles nervously]
- Yes.
Come on, Willi.
Hey! [groans]
[both chuckling]
We're friends, right, Willi?
- We're friends?
- Of course we're friends, silly!
[both chuckling]
[Violet] And friends help
each other, yeah?
And I gave you
all that pollen...
- [grumbles]
- ...remember?
Hi, Willi. He's dancing with me.
Uh-uh. He's dancing with me.
[Conga leader]
No, he's dancing with us!
What?
Why don't you leave us alone?
Because you don't belong here.
The Honey Games
are for the best of the best.
And you loser bugs are a joke.
We'll see who's laughing
after the grand final tomorrow.
[chuckles] Puh-lease.
You mixed up meadow bugs
don't stand a chance.
Why can't you just play fair
and leave Team Poppy alone?
[scoffs]
Tell you what.
I'll leave your precious
Team Poppy alone,
if you can beat me in a race
down Slug Hill, right now.
No. It's out of bounds.
I'm really going to enjoy
eating all your summer honey.
[snickers]
[sighs]
Okay. I'll do it.
[snickers]
[Violet]
Let's make it interesting.
- Or are you a scaredy-bug?
- Hmph!
[gasps]
[wind whistling]
[gulps]
Sandra will call out
when we pass the finish line.
[exhales deeply]
Ready, set, go!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[music continues]
[blows horn]
Maya and Violet
are racing down Slug Hill!
[all gasp]
Oh no.
[both grunt]
See you at the finish line,
loser bug!
Not if I see you first!
[snickers]
Am I at the finish line yet?
[gasps and screams]
- [crash]
- Oh, dear!
Oh, Maya!
[Maya groans]
Who... is.... responsible...
for this?
[coughing]
You!
But I wasn't! I mean... I'm...
I didn't!
[snickers]
Violet tricked me, again!
Silence!
You broke the Honey Cup!
I warned you, little bee.
You are hereby expelled
from the Honey Games!
No, please.
Out!
Oh no.
[sobs quietly]
Maya?
What happened?
Violet happened!
She got me kicked out
of the Games.
What? She wouldn't.
[sighs] Can't you see
what she's doing?
I'm sure it's just
a misunderstanding.
No, Willi.
It's up to you now.
You have to stay here
and save our honey.
Maya, wait!
[sobbing]
[wind whistling]
Ugh.
[gasps]
- [violin music playing]
- [gasps]
[Flip hums along to music]
Flip.
Hello there, little miss.
I thought I'd find you out here,
gazing at the stars.
They...
- kicked me out.
- Mm, so I heard.
Come on, sit down,
tell old Flip about it.
Flip, I broke the Honey Cup.
But... but the race
down Slug Hill
wasn't even my idea.
[sighs] You went out of bounds.
That's against the rules, Maya.
[sniffs] Violet breaks the rules
all the time.
Yes, but you're not Violet.
I just wanted to make
things right. [sobs]
I know, you wanna fix
all the problems in the meadow.
But you can't do it
all on your own, little buzzer.
You need to slow down
and listen to other bugs.
Okay.
I'm listening, Flip.
Maya, you gotta remember.
Good little bees don't blame
others for their mistakes.
So, let's think back.
Where did all
your troubles begin?
[sighs]
I didn't listen to the Queen...
and I messed everything up
when I went to see the Empress.
Well, a bug that wants
to make things right
would take responsibility
for the part they've played.
Don't you think?
Hmm. They would.
Thanks, Flip.
Good luck, Maya.
[Mantis]
Ladybugs and gentlebees!
Welcome
to the Honey Games Grand Final!
[crowd cheering]
May I proudly present
Her Majesty,
the Empress of Buzztropolis!
- [crowd cheering]
- [scoffs]
In our final event,
the remaining two teams
must navigate
the Dragonfly Rush,
and the Mudsucker Muddle
and then climb the summit
of Mount Stumpy!
[clap of thunder]
The competitors must then
retrieve the ruby pollen
from the Nani Nani Orchid!
The first team to cross the line
with the ruby pollen,
will win the Honey Cup!
[all cheering]
The losing team will receive
these novelty mugs! [chuckles]
[mug clatters]
And now, introducing
our first grand finalists...
- the favorites...
- Mm-hm.
...Team Tropolis!
[crowd cheering]
Team Poppy are gonna wish
they stayed in their swamp.
And this year's
surprising wild card...
Team Poppy!
[crowd cheering]
Go, Poppy Meadow!
- Oh, great! No one turned up.
- Oh, Arnie?
Yes, sir?
[gasps]
Oh, they turned up.
Everybody's here.
Where's Maya?
[snickers]
She's been disqualified.
[gasps] Disqualified?
On what grounds?
Oh, Beatrice, once again,
you and your hive
have proven to be a disgrace.
- But...
- [Maya] Miss Empress?
[crowd gasps]
Oh. [chuckles]
Little meadow bug.
You just don't give up, do you?
Please, hear me out.
It's not the Queen's fault.
Oh. [chuckles]
Really?
Then who's fault is it?
Mine.
I'm the one
who came to Buzztropolis
and made a mess of everything.
I didn't listen to you,
Your Majesty.
And in the Games...
I didn't listen to my team.
They trusted me and...
and I let them down.
I'm so sorry.
And I'm so sorry to you,
Miss Empress,
for not showing you respect.
Please don't punish our hive
because of me.
[bug] Give her a chance!
[crowd shouting in agreement]
How touching.
Such honesty should be rewarded.
Little bee, I'm going to give
you a second chance
to compete in the final.
[all cheering]
But if you lose,
we will still take
all your summer honey.
[everyone gasps]
This summer, next summer,
and every summer after that.
- [Queen] Never!
- [Empress gasps]
I should've stood up to you
a long time ago.
[everyone gasps]
We accept your challenge.
And we will win!
You can do it, Maya.
[Willi] No.
We can do it.
That's what friends do, right?
[Bedford] Maya?
You're the first bug
that's ever believed in us.
Oh, group hug!
[all chuckling]
Right, group hug!
Is she serious?
Competitors,
to the starting line.
- What are you, petal?
- I'm a winner, Daddy.
Right. And what do winners do?
They win, whatever it takes.
Exactly.
When you get to Mount Stumpy,
take the secret tunnel
on the right.
What? What if we get caught?
I'm the Games Master,
sweet leaf,
you won't get caught.
Racers, take your marks!
[crowd cheering]
Get set!
- Let's buzz these bugs!
- Ow!
Don't grab their feelers.
Steer by leaning your body.
Come on!
Let's go!
I'm flying!
- Hey, kid, let go!
- [all groaning]
[gasps] Let go of their feelers!
Go! Move move move!
[Violet]
Let's go!
Team Poppy
are taking an early lead!
Yes!
[Mantis] But Team Tropolis are
not giving up without a fight.
[Maya woops]
[gasps]
Whoa!
[Violet] Too slow!
[laughs]
Should've stayed in bed, bugs!
[Bedford screams]
Spinder, save him!
[Maya] You can do it!
[frog croaks]
[gasps]
Spinder, you saved me.
I did it. I did it!
[woops] Go, Spinder!
Thank you, Spinder.
[Mantis] And as they come up
to the Mudsucker Muddle,
it's Team Tropolis,
a bee's knee in front.
[bubbling]
[all groaning]
[Maya panting]
[gasps]
Ugh! So dirty.
I can't, Maya. I can't. [groans]
Let's help him.
- [Barney] Come on, buddy.
- [Craig whimpers]
[Maya] That's it!
[groaning]
- Craig!
- [Arnie] That's not good.
[Craig spluttering]
I'm dirty and muddy and...
I love it! [woops]
[laughs] I love it! [woops]
I am in control.
[clap of thunder]
I'm in control!
I'm in control! [screams]
I'm not in control!
Frozen aphid pops!
It's raining sky ice!
Everyone, under there!
Maya?
Maya! [grunts]
[all panting]
Where's Willi?
Wait!
[screaming]
[snickers]
This way.
[nervous laugh]
It's a bit dark.
Get in there, wobble grubs!
[whimpering]
[thunder rumbling]
Huh?
Violet!
What are you doing?
We're winning, Willi.
- And you're gonna help us.
- Huh?
Tell Maya
you've got a sore wing.
That'll slow her down.
What?
You'd do it for me,
wouldn't you?
[Willi stammers]
[chuckles] Thought so.
[chuckles]
Willi!
What's wrong?
I'm hurt.
I'm hurt that Violet wanted me
to lie to my best friend.
They've taken a short cut!
- [all gasp]
- Oh, the cheeky cheaters.
We don't have a chance!
We don't need a chance.
We've got each other.
Let's win this, fair and square.
Oh, yeah.
- Come on.
- Everybody, follow her!
Let's go, guys.
Violet do we have
to go this way?
- It's so creepy!
- Just be quiet and follow me!
[creaking]
[sinister cackling]
[all scream]
[clap of thunder]
Spread out,
the orchid's up here somewhere!
- [Arnie] Let's go.
- [Craig] We've got no chance!
[Barney]
We're never gonna find it.
- [Arnie] You're so negative.
- Arnie! We found it!
- Wow!
- Are you looking at this?
Yeah, and it's beautiful.
Barney, we found it!
I'll get Maya.
You wait here,
and don't touch anything!
Maya! Up here! We found the...!
- [muffled shouting]
- [wind whistling]
What's he saying?
I can't hear him.
I speak sign language.
He says he's found the flower.
This way, everybody,
single file, or no file at all.
This way to see the flower.
[all] Whoa!
I thought there'd be,
like, more.
[Barney belches loudly]
- What?
- Oh Barney, you didn't!
[belches]
We did it!
- [clap of thunder]
- [Willi] Whoa!
Uh, we should get going!
[Violet]
Help!
Huh?
Hey, hey, that's Violet.
It sounds like she's in trouble!
[Violet]
Help!
- But we're so close to winning!
- And what if she's tricking us?
What if she's not?
Help!
[sinister cackle]
Got ourselves
in a sticky situation, have we?
[screams]
Someone do something!
[cackles]
Hey! Let them go!
Be gone, raggedy bugs.
- My dinner's getting cold.
- [screams]
We have to do something!
[grunts]
Oh, you naughty bugs!
Arnie, Barney,
create a diversion!
Ten-four, Sergeant.
I mean nurse!
I mean coach! 10-4, coach!
[Barney]
Diverting a creation now!
- [Arnie and Barney] Hut! Hut!
- Spinder, sling that web!
[groans]
[Maya] Craig, Bedford,
scuttle and chomp!
- Scuttle and chomp!
- [teeth chatter]
[Craig whimpers]
[Maya]
Help them out!
[groaning]
[all gasp]
Nowhere to run now!
[cackles]
[Bedford sings]
♪ Drift away ♪
- Huh?
- ♪ My little friend ♪
[sighs]
♪ You'll find peace
While you're sleeping ♪
♪ Dream so sweet ♪
♪ So warm and deep ♪
- ♪ Drift away to sleep ♪
- [yawns]
♪ To sleep ♪
Oh, so lovely.
Wow! You're amazing, Bedford!
Yes, I know.
Why did you save me?
You were winning.
Because you needed our help.
And that's what real friends do,
they help each other.
They pick you up
when you're down.
- Put me down! Stop!
- Okay. Whoa!
[everyone chuckles]
[sighs]
I'm sorry I was mean to you.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
I'm really sorry.
[chuckles]
Thanks, Violet.
Come on,
we've got a race to finish!
You're on.
Oh, the thunder's passed,
but these two teams
are still storming on!
And who will be the first
back into the arena?
Oh, here they come now!
And it's both teams
neck and neck.
[woops] How exciting!
Woohoo! Team Poppy have won it,
for the first time ever!
Team Poppy?
Violet, what have you done!?
- Go, Poppy! [chuckles]
- Go Team Poppy!
[all cheering]
A-ha! They do not have
the ruby pollen!
No pollen, no victory!
- Daddy, enough.
- [Beegood] What?
We cheated.
I cheated.
[gasps]
- [crowd] Boo!
- They cheated?
[crowd shouting]
Team Poppy saved us!
They deserve to win.
- [crowd cheers]
- No they do not.
Hey, Beegood! I've got one thing
to say to you... [belches]
Use your words, Barney.
Use your words.
Ugh!
Oh! The Nani Nani pollen!
They have done it!
- [crowd gasps]
- [gasps]
- [crowd cheers]
- They won! They won!
Quiet.
Quiet!
Silence!
Please.
- Shh.
- [crowd goes silent]
Quiet.
Catherine, Team Poppy have won,
fair and square.
[stammers] I say who wins.
I am the Empress and I...
Yes, you are the Empress.
And I am your sister.
When is enough, enough?
You don't want our honey.
You have everything you need.
Look around.
Do what you know is right.
I can't believe
I'm saying this...
Team Poppy wins.
- [crowd cheering]
- Yes! Woohoo!
We won!
No! Your Majesty!
Oh, shush, Beegood.
Seems your little bee
has what it takes after all.
Yeah! We did it!
Team Poppy are the Honey Games
champions!
[crowd cheering]
♪ Can you feel it ♪
♪ From your wings
Down to your toes ♪
♪ It's time for the party ♪
♪ We made it
Come on, let's go ♪
♪ Shake, shake your body
Move to the beat in you ♪
♪ Come on, you got it
We're dancing with our crew ♪
No, I'm not dancing.
That is my final word.
Oh come on, it'll be fun.
Fun shmun.
A ruler should preserve
her dignity at all costs!
- Oh!
- [Queen laughs]
[both laughing]
[groans]
[giggling] Willi!
What? I'm trying new things.
You know what?
Meeting all these new bugs
has made me realize something.
You'll always be my best friend.
[sighs]
You too, Maya.
[both chuckle]
Ahh.
- [Violet] Hey, meadow bugs!
- Huh?
Come on, let's dance!
[giggles]
Sure thing!
Willi?
I'll just stay here and...
[chomps]
[both] Come on, Willi.
- [both chuckle]
- Bee best friends forever?
Buzz.
- Buzz!
- [all giggling]
♪ Let's dance
Come on ♪
♪ Jump up and down
Jump up and down ♪
♪ Dance and you can be free ♪
♪ Grab a friend
You know what to do ♪
♪ We're shining, we're shining
Free! ♪
[theme music playing]
♪ Every little party bee
Is coming down tonight ♪
♪ My friend Willi's joining me
He's such a jolly sight ♪
♪ There's music playing
All night long ♪
♪ And Flip conducts the band ♪
♪ And everyone bursts into song
We scream and clap our hands ♪
♪ 'Cause here comes Maya
Sing and take a chance ♪
♪ Go shoo-bee-doo
And shoo-bee-day ♪
♪ And do the Maya dance ♪
♪ And we are turning
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are waving
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-day ♪
♪ And we are jumping
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are singing
'Til the morning comes around ♪
♪ We are having such a ball
We're dancing all in line ♪
♪ Every creature great and small
Is waiting for the sign ♪
♪ Pay attention, here it comes
A star is in the house ♪
♪ Hit the lights
And roll the drums ♪
♪ We're quiet as a mouse ♪
♪ 'Cause here comes Maya
Sing and take a chance ♪
♪ Go shoo-bee-doo
And shoo-bee-day ♪
♪ And do the Maya dance ♪
♪ And we are turning
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are waving
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-day ♪
♪ And we are jumping
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are singing
'Til the morning comes around ♪
♪ And we are turning
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are waving
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-day ♪
♪ And we are jumping
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are singing
'Til the morning comes around ♪
♪ How I wish this party night
Would never, ever end ♪
♪ When we see the sunrise ♪
♪ We will say
"Goodbye, my friend" ♪
♪ But right now, we're dancing
And we're having such a blast ♪
♪ Come on and let's party
While it lasts ♪
♪ And we are turning
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are waving
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-day ♪
♪ And we are jumping
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are singing
'Til the morning comes around ♪
♪ And we are turning
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are waving
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-day ♪
♪ And we are jumping
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are singing
'Til the morning comes around ♪
♪ And we are turning
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are waving
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-day ♪
♪ And we are jumping
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ And we are singing
'Til the morning comes around ♪
♪ There's a place
Somewhere nearby ♪
♪ Amongst the flowers
And the morning dew ♪
♪ It's a secret paradise ♪
♪ Everybody's waiting
Just for you ♪
♪ Oh, here comes Maya the bee ♪
♪ With the greatest friends
That you'll ever see ♪
♪ Yes, here comes Maya the bee ♪
♪ With the grandest story
Just for you and me ♪
♪ Yes, here comes Maya the bee ♪
♪ With the grandest story
Just for you and me ♪
Subtitles