Subtitles by explosiveskull
[UTENSILS TAP ON PLATE]
[WOMAN] Can I get you
anything else today?
[MAN]
That's a nice necklace.
Thanks.
It was my grandmother's.
My mom gave it to me.
Beautiful ring, too.
Thanks.
It seems valuable.
I don't know about that.
But it is to me though.
I've worn it every day
since she passed it on to me.
When are you due?
In January.
Do you know
if it's a boy or girl?
No.
It's a surprise.
A mystery.
Yeah.
Well...
I can get you change.
It's all yours.
Thank you.
God bless.
You, too.
Thanks.
[PHONOGRAPH GROOVE CRACKLING]
[CHILDREN SHOUTING, DISTANT]
[KNOCKING]
[SIGHS]
- Yes?
- Hi.
I'm Daniel Coleman,
from Assembly Mutual.
[CAMERA BEEPS]
- What are you looking at?
- [CAMERA BEEPS]
If there is anything
you want specifically noted
as being in need of proper
appraisal, just let me know.
I thought that's
what you were here to do.
I'm here to make sure
the value of your home
is more or less what your
granddaughter Bethany assumes.
Anything like furniture or art.
You know, little odd pieces...
- Rare books would have to be...
- Rare books?
Yeah.
Come on.
Have a look around.
You think I got anything
like that laying around?
I don't know.
You probably don't know either.
We'd have to get somebody
who deals more with appraisals
to come in and let me know
what the value is.
Well, the place itself,
it's gotta be worth
more money.
Now, certainly.
But it doesn't matter.
You know why?
Because they'll just tear
it down and build it again.
I just went through that.
On both sides of me.
You still live here, though.
Well, what am I
supposed to do, move?
Because they closed
my spots?
Sure.
People have moved for less.
I raised my family here.
My wife, my two kids.
My wife died here.
It was not easy.
And you know what?
It's home,
and I still like it.
What are you writing?
Just that,
as best as I can tell,
nothing conflicts with what
Bethany claimed was here.
I told her,
"Get a Dumpster."
There are things
she might want to keep.
For sentimental reasons.
Well, then she
should be here.
She was going to be. Last-minute thing.
I couldn't reschedule...
Of course. Last-minute thing.
She had to change her schedule.
How come nobody thought to ask
me if I'd change my schedule?
You know, there's no need. In fact,
you don't even need to be here.
A lot of the times I'm not
even brought in until after.
After?
After I'm dead?
That, uh...
You could put that one down.
I haven't read that yet.
I thought everything
was trash.
Well, it is, or will be.
[CAMERA BEEPS]
Do you mind
if I take a picture of you?
Why?
- I don't know.
- Be my guest.
- I'm not a relic.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [CAMERA BEEPS]
- Wow.
- What, I break your camera?
- [CHUCKLES] No.
It's a great shot.
Thank you.
Why are you still
looking around?
Isn't all the stuff
adding up?
It all adds up, Mr. Ashmore.
Everything
is mathematically consistent
with a widower in his 80s
who collects pension regularly.
And what if it all turns out
to be nothing?
You still get paid?
I still get paid.
The next guy, the appraiser,
he only gets a percentage
of whatever this stuff is worth.
But he only comes if I
determine it'll be worthwhile.
And is it?
There are a few pieces
that should be looked at.
[CHUCKLES] Well.
Then it ain't
all trash, is it?
Thank you for having me,
Mr. Ashmore.
Hey, you got
a handshake, bud.
No one
shakes hands anymore.
Might you
be coming back?
No, I don't think so.
You can take that.
You can have it.
I think
I read this one already.
Have a good day.
[DOOR OPENS]
- [SIGHS]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
I knew he wasn't gonna be able
to deal with this on his own.
I knew it.
I knew he wasn't gonna be able
to go through all of his stuff.
I mean, no one's gonna fly
in there and do it for him.
"Thanks, Bethany."
You gotta understand
where he's coming from, though.
I don't want us to end up
with every single little thing...
I wasn't talking
about every single piece.
I was talking
about one thing, okay?
Just... Just one thing
that he could maybe say,
"Hey, this means a lot to me, and
I'd like for you to have it."
Just one thing. It doesn't
even have to be of value.
[DANIEL] There could
still be something.
I'm recommending a walk-through
with an appraiser.
I probably can't be there, but you
guys should be there for that.
Nothing major, but...
You know, with folks
like your grandfather,
there's always a chance that
underneath ten years of magazines,
there's a table
worth $10,000.
I don't like to think
about my grandfather dying.
I really, really don't.
And you being here can only
reinforce the notion that...
sometime soon
that's gonna happen.
[HUSBAND SIGHS]
Have a seat.
Thanks.
So let's say he does decide there's
something he wants to bestow.
While that's all warm and fuzzy,
I have to ask the question:
Is anything worth anything?
What, um...
What do you want
from your grandfather?
I don't think
there's anything left.
I mean, I got all of it.
Or Dad did.
And I couldn't really say
when the whole "if you want it,
take it" attitude started.
But, boy, I'll tell you.
[EXHALES] His whole "you can't even
wait until I'm dead" period started
right around
the time Grandma died.
He's not a very generous man.
Honestly...
I think he's probably right.
It's all just trash, you know.
It's all just become part
of the decor of the place.
That's why it's so easy
for him to be...
surrounded by it.
I don't think any specific thing
has a particular meaning,
an individual meaning.
But it doesn't mean
it's not related.
You know? Just...
It's some, um...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
some middle.
You know?
Maybe that's, um,
one of the advantages
of living a long life...
is you outgrow the tendency
to assign emotional meaning
to a piece of paper.
Well, we should
all be so lucky.
You don't have
to outgrow.
Me, I'm hardly the person
to tell people
that it's wise to accumulate
more things in their homes,
but you should remain open to the
possibility that something...
it could be anything...
of your grandfather's has
remained unseen by him for years.
And you...
maybe forever.
Undiscovered.
A box of love letters.
Diaries.
Photographs.
Lives lived.
So it all falls on me
because I live the closest?
That seems to be
the way it works.
He's lucky
to have you nearby.
- I'll walk you out.
- Yeah.
- Hey. Pleasure.
- Oh.
- Thank you. Have a good day.
- Thanks.
- [DANIEL] Everything will be okay.
- [BETHANY] Thanks.
[BETHANY SIGHS]
[SIGHS]
Oh! Are you
the insurance man?
Daniel Coleman.
You must be Helen Greare.
Yes. [SNIFFLES]
I'd invite you in,
but there is no "in."
[CHUCKLES]
- So?
- So sorry.
Yeah. This is my home.
[SNIFFLES]
This is my kitchen.
[WHIMPERS]
This is the living room.
This is
the powder room here.
So, uh, what happened?
You know...
I used to be
very sloppy about...
changing the batteries
on the fire alarms.
Ned was always the one
that did it.
I would wait until I heard
the beeping and then say,
"Oh, the batteries
ought to be changed."
But he did it
before they started beeping.
Every 90 days,
like it says on the package.
But I'm better now.
I've had to learn how to do it.
So, the fire department
still doesn't know
if it was just, like,
a spark that went wrong
or, you know,
roll of paper towel left
too close to the pilot light,
or what.
You probably know
all this already.
Well, the details,
they're helpful.
Okay.
Do you know why the fire
department was so delayed?
Something about
an electrical malfunction.
Oh. They were called,
like, 20 minutes
before the O'Bryans
came home, 11:00 p.m.
Response time is supposed to be...
Oh, I don't know.
I understand.
When the wind took
the fire to the O'Bryans...
that was when I had this moment.
You know, just an awful feeling.
I knew...
I need to go inside
and do that thing
that people wonder about
their whole life.
Decide what you take
from a burning building.
I mean, it's easier when it's
just a hypothetical question...
instead of when you see the...
the tree...
that touches both your home
and the one next door
is on fire.
It's just chaos at that point.
People in their yards,
screaming.
The police were here,
but a lot of good that did.
They were the ones
that came in after me.
I got, like, one minute
in my house...
before they came
and took me out.
[EXHALES]
Felt like ten seconds.
Well, the rings and broaches
belonged to my great-grandmother.
Standing out here, they were
the first things I pictured.
[CHUCKLES] I made for them like it
wasn't even a conscious decision.
So now I'm upstairs,
and already I can hear
the police calling my name.
They're inside, downstairs.
[SIGHS] So, wouldn't
it have been smart
for me to take
this whole chest?
[LAUGHING] Oh, God. I don't know.
I can't tell you why.
I knew that if I was gonna take
anything else, it had to be now.
From this room,
our bedroom.
And that's when I...
[CHUCKLES]
saw this on the mantel.
It was Ned's baseball.
He wasn't a player
or anything.
It just was
family history.
The ball.
His father gave it to him.
It's from the '40s.
You know?
If you asked me now who won what
game with it, I couldn't tell you.
It was just "the ball."
He always spoke about it
with such pride.
Such value.
Um...
It was instinct.
It fit in my pocket.
That's when they came in
and took me.
[EXHALES]
When Ned died...
um, the first thing
that Henry, my son,
said was,
"What about the ball?"
I mean, when we sat down
to go over the estate, you know.
He said, "What about
the ball?" [CHUCKLES]
He wanted it.
It was his birthright,
as far as he was concerned.
I said,
"Well, he could have it,"
but I just needed to keep
on looking at it for a while.
I wasn't ready
to not see it there.
It's been in some prominent place
in every home we've ever had.
I told Henry when I moved,
it would be his.
'Cause I knew that this house,
eventually, would be too much for me.
I just didn't know that there
wasn't gonna be an "eventually."
[EXHALES]
It could be worth more
than the house.
For claim purposes.
If it is insured and you
would have left it behind,
I'd be writing you a check next
week for the amount of, uh...
Well, it'd be substantial.
Ah.
Things that mattered more to
me, to the children, are gone.
But I have Ned's ball.
I don't understand it
or know what to do with it.
I have it.
[EXHALES]
- [WOMAN] Helen?
- Oh, hi.
This is Mrs. Singer. Jane Singer.
This is the insurance man.
Oh, very nice to meet you. Would you both
like to come and have a cup of coffee?
We've been kind of playing
welcome center these days.
- Oh, that'll be nice. Okay.
- [JANE] Good? Oh, good.
- [DANIEL] Thanks.
- [JANE] Oh, our pleasure. I'll just leave the door open.
[HELEN] Okay.
Thank you, Jane.
[MAN] The insurance covers the
home, the car, the valuables.
It's the stuff
that's left out.
We've lived here, um,
just over four years.
So our restructuring and cleansing
and pawning off to the kids
was done then.
We didn't get the worst of it.
Helen, I... I can't imagine
how it is for you.
Thirty years. [CHUCKLES]
We moved here
when Lisa was three
and Henry was seven.
Did anything make it out?
Well, we were very lucky
because Riley had
a safe in his office.
And not a small one either.
It was about this big.
And our valuables and irreplaceable
heirlooms, and, um...
My family's...
My family's immigration papers.
Things over a hundred years old.
We put them all in there.
Thank God.
It was
a Father's Day gift.
Kind of frivolous,
but I-I wanted it.
I always dreamt of having
a nice study with a safe.
Well, when I got the study,
they bought me the safe.
It was mostly
entertaining.
I love pushing
the buttons and...
resetting the code
out of boredom.
Never dreamed it
would come in handy.
I'm usually listening to people lament
that they never bothered to lock it.
What you're describing
is actually quite uncommon.
Not that there was anything
of extreme monetary value,
aside from my rings
and silver.
But you know how it is.
It's the personal things.
Personal things.
I'm really glad
we put 'em in there.
[RILEY] It's fine. We used to
hide little surprises in there.
As a... As a joke.
So if anybody needs a bobblehead
from the 1995 All-Star Game,
Anna put two in there to get back
at me the day before the blaze.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[MR. SINGER]
I shouldn't laugh.
[ANNA] Well...
- [RILEY] We should hit the road.
- No. Don't be silly.
Please, stay,
as long as you want.
We're staying about 50 miles
away, with our daughter.
You're...
You're welcome to stay.
I've got a drive to look forward to.
Thank you.
- [MR. SINGER] Daniel, can I ask you something?
- Please.
What does it do to a person
to take all of this in?
All due respect to Helen...
this is pretty common,
right?
You're clearly not hearing anything
that you haven't heard before.
You're just sitting there. You're
barely reacting to anything of this...
- Jim, Please. That's rude.
- No.
It's okay. I understand.
You're right.
It's best to not become
terribly invested.
I'm not a doctor or anything.
My proximity to tragedy
is a smidge further away
than somebody who truly
has to develop a barrier.
But to be honest...
it never
hurts me personally.
And it never gets old.
Every story has details
I've never heard before.
Every person I talk to,
I learn something new.
Not many people get to say that
about their jobs.
You will never replace
your things.
Or lives.
But...
I find something...
magnetic...
talking to people like yourself,
who could have easily have been
trapped inside a burning house...
and know it.
Or people who feel some relief
that the belongings they've accumulated
have avoided similar fates.
And here's the thing.
Nobody wants
to be talking to me.
And I think
knowing that...
makes my job a lot easier.
[CAMERA BEEPS]
Lives lived.
[SPORTS ANNOUNCER ON RADIO,
INDISTINCT]
[PHONOGRAPH GROOVE CRACKLING]
Hey, Mom. We're getting
ready to hit the hay.
You need anything else
for tonight?
No, thanks.
Everything okay?
[SIGHS] What do you think?
- Good night, Mom.
- Good night.
[WOMAN] Good night.
[LOCK CLICKS]
[BOY] You'll never
be able to get me!
- [BOYS CHATTERING]
- [BABY FUSSING]
[WOMAN] Hey, boys, settle down.
Shh, shh, shh.
- [CHATTERING CONTINUES]
- [FUSSING CONTINUES]
- [HELEN] There you are.
- Hi.
I wanted to ask you. Um...
That photograph in the
guest room of Christmas,
is that 2008?
Uh, actually,
I think it was 2010.
Oh. Yeah.
I was looking at it
this morning when I woke up.
Holidays have
been nice here, though.
Oh, yeah. But... [COUGHS]
Well, I love coming here
to see the boys.
But, you know,
Ned never had Christmas here.
His... I mean, you bought the
house after he was here.
It's been long enough
that I... [LAUGHS]
I just assumed
I was through giving things up.
Now this morning I realized...
more to give up.
It's the second Saturday. You know,
we had second Saturday cards.
So I guess there'll be no more
cards with friends at my house.
Hmm. But cards are light.
You can
take 'em anywhere.
Yeah.
But it's... [CHUCKLES]
not about the cards.
Okay. Thank you.
[HENRY]
I didn't mean it like that.
You could've fooled me.
I'm not
being insensitive.
You're just reacting because
you're afraid it's inevitable.
Assisted living?
It is completely
independent cottages.
But in a facility
with employees, staff.
Only if you need anything
or want something.
Even just a ride somewhere. Sometimes
maybe you don't want to drive yourself.
I like driving myself.
I'm fine driving myself.
You have to have thought about
where you're gonna live.
- The insurance money is...
- Yeah, you're right.
It's a lot.
It's quite a bit.
But you're cash poor.
I am accustomed
to having my own house.
Well, your house
burned down,
and you can't
live there anymore!
I don't mean to yell.
But come on.
Mom, things are not the same
as they were before.
Things have changed.
You need a plan. We need...
Well, you know,
I can sell some things.
Stop. Don't sell anything.
I mean,
the jewelry alone is...
You don't want it.
I mean, Lisa might, but...
We can take care of you.
[LAUGHS]
You've just been saying
that you won't.
That's not what I said. And you
know that's not what I said.
Those belong to you.
Lisa wants 'em.
She's never admitted to you
how badly she wants 'em.
Trust me.
[SIGHS]
You're just like him.
Always telling me what to do.
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
I love you, Mom.
Don't feel like you have a limit
on how long you can stay here.
Thanks.
[WOMAN]
She just needs more time.
She has to process it.
[HENRY] I know, but how much?
She has to understand by now
that pretending things will somehow go back
to the way they were before is ludicrous.
[WOMAN]
She's an old lady
who spent decades
looking at these objects.
She still thinks of herself as
living in or with these objects.
I just wish she could have
gotten more of Dad's things.
Then maybe she wouldn't feel
so untethered.
You know, she told me
that the logs in the fireplace
still had kindling
under them and everything
- from the last fire that your dad built.
- Mm-hmm.
She thinks that because
they'd been there for ten years,
it somehow made the fire worse,
like a bomb.
She loved that fireplace.
She loved everything.
Once he was gone,
she'd never let it be used.
Dad's fire.
The last fire he built.
Such a bummer.
[HENRY] I know her.
I know she can't have
half the jewelry
without thinking
of the other half.
She can't have the car without
thinking of everything in the garage.
- [WOMAN] She won't get rid of it.
- [HENRY] She's insinuating.
I know she'd never
go through with it.
She's too attached
to everything it represents.
It's just like his ball.
It's some thing
that makes no sense to her
but that she doesn't have the
ability to detach herself from.
No.
I'll know for certain
the day she seriously considers getting
rid of the jewelry or the ball
is the day I eat my hat.
- I almost wish she could.
- [PHONE: DIAL TONE]
I'd like the ball, just as Lisa
would like everything else.
[PHONE BEEPING]
But for Mom's sake,
I almost wish she'd get rid
of the stuff.
She's gonna drag it around
with her, like an albatross?
I'd be happier for her
to see it all gone.
[HELEN] Riley?
Hi. It's Helen.
I-I hope
I didn't wake you up.
I'm sorry to call so late.
Oh, good.
Listen, um...
I wanted to ask you
about that gentleman
that you mentioned
the other night,
the re-saler
that your daughter found.
Appraiser. I see. Yeah.
Oh, sure.
And you found him
really helpful?
Las Vegas?
Oh.
Uh-huh.
Well, no, I wouldn't...
I wouldn't send anything really
valuable in the mail either.
Well...
I'm... I'm not sure.
It's not definite yet.
I just...
Well, you know,
I just thought that I...
What could it hurt if I gave him a
call and see what he says, right?
Okay.
Yeah, thanks a lot, huh?
And listen, tell Anna...
You know, send her my love.
Okay. Thank you.
Bye.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[HELEN NARRATING]
These are our remainders.
Of our lives, of many forms.
Emotional.
Physical.
These are our artifacts.
Our scars.
Objects.
Memories.
Items that are tangible.
Memorable.
We live our lives and ask...
"What do we leave behind?"
When we look at the pictures
long enough,
they reappear.
What is the value of anything?
Can what we hold in our hands
be the same...
as what we hold in our hearts?
[LINE RINGING]
[SOBBING]
Um, hello, Mr. Bleam.
This is Helen Greare...
calling to confirm what time
it would be good for us to meet.
Can I help you?
I'm Helen Greare.
Oh, yes. Oh, my gosh.
I'm so sorry. Of course.
It's nice to meet you.
- Hi. Welcome.
- Thank you.
Will Bleam.
Come on in, please.
Uh, have a seat.
Let's see what you've got here.
- I know it's a lot.
- It's a lot.
Right?
Most of the stuff I get
is from people like you.
But I also get, you know,
some conventions,
and, uh, you know, trips I take
and other stores, what have you.
And sometimes the families
of players reach out...
- Please, please, have a seat.
- Thank you.
But honestly, mostly my
reputation, at this point,
gets most of the heavy
lifting done, so...
Uh, let's take a look
at what you have.
People my age
come to Las Vegas
to gamble away their pensions
and their life savings.
Mm-hmm. [CHUCKLES]
Well, you have come to unburden
yourself in a different way, huh?
[CHUCKLES]
So, why don't you tell me...
how you came across this.
Um, my husband's father
got it,
um, from his father.
And I think it was given
to him at a game.
And it's been
in the family ever since.
Huh. Well, the good news is I can
almost guarantee you it's authentic.
- Yeah.
- Um, you know, there's not a lot of things like this
that are in families for generation after
generation that turn out to be fake.
Yep. Why is that?
Well, honestly,
something like this,
it was just a more
honest time back then.
There wasn't as much money
to be made from collectibles.
That sort of thing.
The only thing we generally have to be
careful for is a situation like this,
where somebody passes away.
They're going through their
valuables, and it's mostly artwork.
You know, I just can't go
out 10,000, $20,000 out
on something that might
be proven to be false.
- Oh, no, there's no chance.
- Of course not.
Not with this.
I understand.
Uh, that said, if we're looking
at something like this,
we are probably looking at
something like 80,000 to 100,000.
Um...
it's in excellent
condition,
and, uh, Ted Williams
autographs are very scarce,
especially on an
actual piece of equipment.
- Do you know who Ted Williams is?
- No.
Well, it's a terrific piece.
And the people who specialize
in collecting this era,
they know what price point
they're getting into.
I guess everything here
has a story, huh?
Yes.
Yes. And, you know,
I try to relate that
to the buyers.
And some of them
are actually eager to learn.
- [HELEN] Mm-hmm.
- You know?
But also sometimes my buyers
come in looking for a gift.
You know? And so,
to that person,
the object
just sort of appears...
on their birthday
or their anniversary
or their retirement.
You get what I'm saying?
- Well...
- Saying good-bye is hard.
I know that.
And you-you shouldn't, you know,
feel ridiculous about that either.
- No.
- It's... It's-It's difficult.
What was your husband's
name, if I may ask?
Ned.
Edward Roger Greare.
I bet Ned liked
to talk about the ball.
- Oh!
- [LAUGHING]
I bet he... I bet he liked
to talk about it a lot.
Tell the same story
over and over again.
- Yes.
- Right?
And it's my understanding
from the brief conversations
that we've had
that you didn't retain
the legend of the ball.
- Is that correct?
- No.
No. Right.
And that's okay too.
- It's not your ball.
- Mm-hmm.
Ned loved the story
of the ball.
And you selling it to me doesn't... doesn't
change that, doesn't take it away.
You know?
[SOFTLY] Yeah.
Um, do you have
any children?
Two.
You know, would either
of them maybe want this?
Perhaps. Maybe.
Okay. Well, when you...
If you decide to...
But when you
tell them, uh...
Worst-case scenario,
they may be upset
with you for a moment.
But...
best-case scenario,
I think they will understand
and realize that you doing this
was the best for you.
Because you have so many
other things to remember Ned
other than this ball.
Right?
Right.
[SNIFFLES]
Do you have children?
No.
Are you married?
Not recently, no. No.
Uh, she...
she left me.
Why?
Well, uh...
She came in one day and said
that she had had enough.
She didn't love me anymore.
It was right around the time
when I started with this place.
And I was...
pretty unavailable,
to say the least.
But still a bit of a shock.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Uh, about nine years ago.
Still trying
to make sense of it.
Well...
it's just a thing.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
You've never
seen it before,
and by tomorrow,
it'll be up on that shelf.
And maybe by next week,
it'll be gone already.
Or maybe it'll sit here
for a year or maybe two years.
And...
you won't remember me.
When people come
and sit where I'm sitting
and feel what I'm feeling...
[SNIFFLES]
you'll just be able to tell them,
with a little more confidence,
that what they're feeling
is common.
Yeah.
You won't remember Helen.
Ned's wife.
With Ned's ball.
You'll just know
that these things happen.
And widows and... and children
have a hard time.
And you give them money.
And...
the money does make it easier.
A bit.
[SNIFFLES] And that's okay.
Because, um...
Ned's gone.
[EXHALES]
And now so is his ball.
Oh.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm. Thank you.
[SIGHS]
[PHONOGRAPH GROOVE CRACKLING]
[TYPING]
[PHONE RINGS, BEEPS]
Bleam Collectibles.
This is Will speaking.
Hey, Chris,
how's it going?
[CHUCKLES]
Yes, I did. I thought
you'd be interested.
Yeah, it's very fresh.
It's still warm, in fact.
I think it was
on her husband's side.
[MAN ON PHONE, INDISTINCT]
Uh... [CHUCKLES]
Yeah.
Yes.
Well, she knew
it was worth something.
Mm-hmm.
I was very fair.
Yes. Very fair for me.
- [PHONE BEEPS]
- Uh...
Listen, I got
another call. Can...
[CHUCKLES]
What do you mean, no?
I'm gonna take...
Okay, that's $10,000 more
than I'm asking.
And you know I'm asking
more than it's worth.
Uh...
Yes.
I mean, you've seen the pictures.
It's absolutely perfect.
No. No, no, no.
That won't work.
I'm, uh... I'm flying out
tomorrow afternoon.
I'm going home.
I'm going to my old home.
I'm gonna help clean out my
parents' house with my sister.
[CLICKS TONGUE] Yeah.
Yeah, well, look,
nobody knows more than me
that when it's time for it all to
go, you gotta get rid of it all.
That's right.
All right.
I'll talk to you Monday.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[JET PASSES OVERHEAD]
[WOMAN] Have you talked
to them recently?
I did. I called to say
that I was coming here.
They were less interested in that fact
than I thought maybe they would be.
Come on. Take it easy.
- [WILL CHUCKLES]
- No. This is important to me.
- I flew here.
- Just don't be...
I flew here for this.
That's more than they did.
You always fly here.
Just don't be negative.
- I travel twice a month for work.
- I know that.
So flying here twice a year
is not that big a deal.
I have a very favorable
mileage situation.
I just... I can't believe they didn't
take more of their stuff, you know.
- That...
- Well, duh.
It's not their stuff anymore.
You know what I mean?
At this point. They took what they
wanted and they left the rest.
That's the whole point of why old
folks move from a house to a condo.
There's less space,
less stuff.
[LAUGHING]
You talk down to me so much.
- I don't talk...
- You think I'm an idiot.
- I'm not... I don't. I don't.
- Yeah, you do. Yeah.
And I'm not talking
down to you.
[WOMAN] I wish you
would stay with us.
I don't want
to inconvenience you.
Besides, maybe staying here
a couple extra nights
might make me actually
feel something.
[LAUGHS]
Doesn't sound like you.
Oh!
- Whoa.
- Right?
Yeah, no joke.
Uff-da.
[WOMAN] This is difficult.
I love this house.
I love this place too,
but, you know...
Got a lot of good memories here.
It's just a house.
- That we grew up in.
- Mm.
- [HINGES SQUEAK]
- Boy.
I think Tallie's having
a really hard time with it.
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
And every...
Christmas
and Thanksgiving...
Every memory she has
is in here.
[WOMAN SIGHS]
Yeah, well,
she'll get over it.
I mean, she still
has the memories.
Make new ones.
[WOMAN] I think it's harder
on her them moving away
than...
than she even knows or...
I don't know.
She was really lucky
to have gotten to grow up so
close to her grandparents.
There's gonna be
other holidays.
Mm.
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
God, it was easy
to sneak out.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[WOMAN] I don't want
to spend Christmas in Florida.
Well, better get your serving trays
out, 'cause it's on you now.
[WOMAN SCOFFS]
[WILL GROANS]
Oh, geez.
But it's so weird to stay in a house
that's been empty for too long.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Well, if I don't make it
through the night,
you can tell everybody
that I died as I lived...
in my childhood home.
Uh... Yeah, well...
You're a puzzle, little Bro.
You're gonna meet me
at 10:00, right?
Yes. You know, I should refuse
to do that out of principle.
- Why? You have a principle against storage lockers?
- No. I love storage lockers.
In fact, I've probably found hundreds of
thousands of dollars worth of sales in them.
- I just don't think you should be renting one.
- Oh, God.
You know, just because you have nothing
in your life that you love or care about
doesn't mean
that we all should be the same.
- I care about things. I care about things.
- Sure, so you say.
- Okay. See you in the morn.
- Drive safely.
- I'll try. [LAUGHS]
- All right. Later, gator.
- Bye.
- Ooh!
- You got it.
[HINGES SQUEAK]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[DONNA] Oh, man.
I bet that the cost of your
two-year lease on this thing
is worth three times more than
anything you're putting in here.
- It's not about the money.
- [MUTTERS]
But you have an attic.
You have a basement. You have a house.
Can't you put this there?
Well, then I'd have to fucking see it
every single day, and I don't want to.
[BOTH GROAN]
Maybe I just don't want
to go downstairs every day
and see all this stuff.
Maybe it'll remind me of something
that's a little too hard,
and I just...
It would get to me. Do you understand?
No, you don't.
Well, just saying, what is this,
25 percent of their stuff?
They took 25 percent
of it with them.
You take whatever
you're gonna take.
So we just throw 50 percent
of it into a Dumpster?
I guess so.
Well, this is
exploitation of labor.
People usually
get paid for this.
[DONNA LAUGHS]
- [KISSES]
- I know why Carol left you.
Wow. What a shitty thing
to say.
[LAUGHS]
You're such a shit, man.
I love you.
[WILL] God, this is all junk.
We don't need any of this,
all right?
You wanted my professional opinion.
This is all junk.
[DONNA] Look through this and see
if there's anything valuable.
There's nothing valuable
up here.
That's why it's been
in the attic our whole life.
- These were their wedding present.
- Who cares?
No, because...
From Grandma and Grandpa.
And if it meant
anything to them,
they would have taken it
down to Florida with them.
Oh, come on.
These are nice.
I'm gonna save them. Give them
to Tallie to take to college.
What? You don't send
a kid off to college
with bowls and plates
from the '50s.
You buy her 60 bucks worth of plastic
shit that she'll throw away in two years.
All right.
I know. But, I mean...
Just shut up. What am I
supposed to do with it?
- Donate it. Get rid of it.
- No.
Give it to Goodwill. Send it
to the church donation center.
That is the solution
to all of this stuff
that isn't
direct family ephemera.
[GIRL] Mom!
[DONNA] You're just... sad.
- Uncle Will.
- Oh, my God, that's me!
- Tallie! Hi.
- Hi.
- Mwah.
- [TALLIE LAUGHS]
How'd you know?
"Uncle Will arrives
this weekend."
- About 1000 times.
- I get it. Right.
- [DONNA] Hi, babe. How was school?
- I don't know. The same.
"The same, Mom. It was the same.
School was the same."
But, uh, how long
is this gonna take?
[DONNA] But you just got here.
You got somewhere else to go?
Okay. Uh...
- Wait a second. Did I show you these?
- [WILL] Oh, God.
Dad's rackets. Did I tell you that
she got a scholarship to Vanderbilt?
Yes, you told me that. You've told me
1000 times. Of course you told me.
Congratulations, Tallie.
- That's very impressive.
- Thank you.
[DONNA] Yeah, these are cool.
I'm gonna save these for you.
I'm gonna play tennis
at Vanderbilt
with some
antique wooden racquets.
[WILL CHUCKLES]
Uh, how about this record
about a blind guy?
That's Grandpa's jazz. That's
his collection. Forget it.
This actually
might be worth something.
I thought everything
was worthless to you.
No, this is...
Some things are not.
These?
These are worth something?
Yes, they might actually be worth something
because they're first pressings.
And they're
in decent condition.
And they probably haven't been played or
seen the light of day in over 30 years.
But can't you just get
the music somewhere else?
No, darling,
this is not that.
But you can just download it.
- [DONNA] Honey, don't.
- No... Yes, but no.
Because then it doesn't exist.
Trust me.
This is what I do for a living.
Okay.
All right.
What are you doing?
No, I...
I just...
I don't need anything.
Oh, my God.
Suddenly you're so content.
Well, why... why would I bring
all this stuff into my room
just to move it again
in August?
She makes a very good point.
I mean, who are you? I don't...
[WILL] You know it's a good point.
Doesn't make sense.
[DONNA] No, it actually...
So, how long am I gonna
have to stay and help?
Are you... Okay, uh, this is...
I was thinking I could go up to
Kathleen's lake house with her and Marie.
They invited me. I could
be back Sunday afternoon,
if you guys
are still gonna be here.
No, you can't go, sweetheart.
You can't.
I'm sorry. You can't go.
I told you about it...
Donna, it's fine.
I don't care.
We can do this together. I don't mind.
Let her go to her friend's.
Please stay out of it. This isn't...
This really isn't...
This has nothing to do with you,
but it's just...
We made an agreement, and I just
expect you to stick by it, that's all.
No, I will. And I know...
I know that it matters.
It's just hard for me to understand
what this all means to you.
I get that you grew up with it and
that it's probably always been here.
There's just a lot of it,
and it takes up so much space.
Space that we don't
even have, Mom, so...
[CHUCKLES] I'm just a little confused.
That's all.
I mean...
I do like these, uh,
little grandma-y things.
[CHUCKLES]
But... I don't know.
I mean,
being up here,
it... it isn't fun.
And it doesn't remind me
of spending time here.
I actually never
even came up here.
So most of this stuff is stuff
that I've never actually seen.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I mean, most of it is probably where
it has been since before I was born.
So...
this is...
this is your space, not mine.
Uh... [CLICKS TONGUE]
But it's really cool that
you both are so into it, and...
I mean, I'm happy
that I get to see you,
that you flew here
to see us, so...
Yeah. Me, too.
Me, too.
Uh, so I'm... I'm glad
you found your records,
and if you come by
some cool tunes or whatever,
you can just send me the name,
and I'll download them.
- Deal.
- [LAUGHS] Uh...
But Kathleen keeps texting me.
Can I go or not?
Thank you.
I love you both.
[WILL'S VOICE] "Being away from
you and the kids is just awful.
I told them
now that Donna is born,
I can't go
on company business as often.
I thought you'd appreciate
the enclosed photograph.
I bought it at the gas station,
along with a Coke.
And it cost a nickel, but they
said I could just have it,
on account of how thirsty I looked
and how badly I needed the Coke.
I left my change on the counter.
I'll be home by the time
this arrives, most likely."
"Please show the enclosed clipping
from the newspaper to Will.
I think he'll be amused by the
sizable collection of geodes
that this town
prides themselves on.
Had I known
I would be in Arkansas
during their
annual geode festival,
I would have made an effort
to bring him along.
Do not tell him, but I will
bring him home a souvenir geode
that I purchased
from a merchant in town."
"Sweetheart,
I cannot express my excitement
to return home to you next week.
Our last Christmas
with just the two of us looms.
I may be bringing home a surprise
ornament or two for the tree.
I love you. I love you so much.
I love you deeper
than I've ever loved anyone."
[BLOWING]
[SOFT JAZZ PLAYING]
[PHONOGRAPH GROOVE CRACKLING]
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [WILL SIGHS]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Jesus.
- [HANDSET CLATTERS]
- [DIAL TONE]
Hello.
[SIGHS]
[RECEIVER SLAMS]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
- [GROANS]
- [VIBRATING CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
Hello.
[DONNA ON PHONE, INDISTINCT]
What? Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Whoa, whoa. Slow down. What?
What?
[DONNA] Tallie...
[CRYING]
Oh, God.
Oh, Donna. Oh, God.
Um... Oh. Um...
Uh...
[PHONOGRAPH GROOVE CRACKLING]
[MAN] Only one of them made it.
Police got ahold of us
at 3:00...
3:30.
A drunk had crossed over the line
and drove them off the road.
I guess they never had a chance.
They said, uh, she had died...
before the ambulance
ever got there.
I'm sorry.
[CAR APPROACHES]
[CRYING]
Why?
[CRYING CONTINUES]
Come here, baby. Come here.
Oh, God, no!
I got you.
I got you. I got you.
- I got you.
- No! No!
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
I wanna fucking do something.
[WHIMPERS]
I can't. I don't want... I don't
want anyone to fucking touch me!
Don't fucking...
I don't know what to do. I don't
know what to do. [CRYING]
- What do I do? What do I do?
- Let's take a walk.
- No, no. What do I do?
I don't wanna walk.
I don't want to.
- Let's be outside.
- I don't want to walk.
I don't wanna...
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[BOTH CRYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
I'll get it.
I'll get it. I'll get it.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, it'll be helpful, but
just give us a couple of hours.
I think we'll have...
We'll be ready.
Okay?
Okay. Thank you.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[CHATTERING]
Why don't you go see...
I'm sorry.
- [DONNA CRYING]
- Sorry.
I'm so... I'm so sorry.
Kathleen's
going to be okay.
She should be fine.
[DONNA] Thank God.
I'm... I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I don't know what to say.
- Okay.
- Okay. Okay, listen...
We all wish they
were both here. Okay?
- [MAN] Was it a phone call?
- Hi, sweetie. Hi, Hillary.
- Um, yeah. It was a phone call,
- [MOUTHING WORDS]
um, around 3:15.
[MAN] Right.
I guess it wouldn't make sense that
they would go to your house, too.
I mean, they wouldn't
do that, would they?
Oh.
[DONNA]
I woke up... I woke up...
I woke up and then a car...
I heard a car pull up.
And then...
the door slammed, and...
and there was...
there was these...
f... footsteps.
Really slow footsteps. And...
I, uh...
I thought maybe that
she had come home, you know,
that maybe the trip ended early.
And then we heard knocks
on the door and, um...
- [FATHER] There was two guys.
- Yeah.
- They were so... They were so sweet.
- [WOMAN] Yeah.
Young.
Their job is just to come
and tell a mother...
[LAUGHS]
outta fucking nowhere...
that, you know...
that her daughter's...
She's gone. Gone away.
[CRYING]
"Your daughter's gone."
- Gone.
- [WOMAN] We're so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
[EXHALES]
[KNOCKING]
- Hey.
- Yeah.
You okay?
She had her computer with her.
And her phone, of course.
Both completely destroyed.
What does that mean?
It means
we don't have anything.
I mean, there's access to everything...
computer, e-mail, text.
She left everything open. I never even
thought about asking for a password.
I'm down there,
trying to plan this memorial
and realized we don't have
any recent photographs.
We've got, like, two. She took 100 a day.
We didn't.
Donna wanted
to play some music,
and we realized
we don't know where that is
or how to get it
or even so much what it was.
Did she have an older phone?
No.
She wiped it clean.
Donated it.
Twenty years ago,
somebody dies...
you could find
some dog-eared book and open it,
see a passage
they'd underlined, read it.
You could find an album,
look at where it was worn and...
find the song they liked
and play it.
You could find a roll of film...
and develop...
We don't have anything.
[RADIO: SLOW ROCK]
[WOMAN SINGING,
INDISTINCT]
That one's familiar.
She liked that one.
[SIGHS]
[SOBBING]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
Hey.
Hi.
What's all that?
- Half the house.
- [DONNA CHUCKLES]
I took some of the stuff from your
storage unit. I hope you don't mind.
The Dumpster's being picked up tomorrow.
All right?
I wanna take
all this stuff off your plate.
Don't want you
to worry about it.
This stuff...
is from the Dumpster.
Most of it, anyway.
Some of it's from the attic.
You know, it's, like, letters.
Dad to Mom, Mom to Dad.
Nothing earth-shattering. But it
shouldn't have been in the Dumpster.
- You looked at it?
- Some, yeah.
Why do you
think I kept it?
Come here. [GRUNTS]
There.
[KISSES]
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
I'll be there for you.
- Got me?
- Yeah.
All right, Donna.
Come here.
All right.
You don't have to go back
to that house. It's all done.
It's all taken care of.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
That house is
the last place you saw her.
So maybe...
maybe one day we'll drive by
and we'll say hi.
The house
isn't going anywhere.
It's just a house.
Right?
Right? Right.
I gotta go.
Okay.
You leaving?
Not forever.
Just for now.
[TRUCK DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[HORN HONKS]
[PHONOGRAPH GROOVE CRACKLING]
You guys,
I'll be back, okay?
Hi, Kathleen.
You... You look like you're
doing pretty well there.
Yeah, I am. Thank you.
I won't ask how things
have been, though.
That would be stupid.
[FATHER] It's been
a trying few weeks.
Believe me, I know.
How much longer do you
have to be on those?
My... My physical therapist thinks
maybe only another few weeks.
At first they were saying it
could be the end of the summer.
Well, it's good
to see you up and around.
Thank you for coming
to visit me in the hospital.
[FATHER] Of course.
I mean,
I can't imagine what that...
what that must be like for you.
I hope that you
don't see me as some...
reminder.
I don't want you to look at me and ask
why I'm here instead of Tallie or Marie.
We don't feel that way at all.
We don't.
I know, but...
it'd be okay if you did.
I think it sometimes.
[FATHER]
Well, you shouldn't.
That's no way to think.
I'll remember Tallie.
I'll remember her so much.
Do you know
what "saudade" means?
Well, I wouldn't if I hadn't
have taken an SAT course.
It's, um...
a melancholy nostalgia for something
that perhaps hasn't happened.
Well, I never got it.
Tallie...
Tallie got it, though.
"A pleasure you suffer,
an ailment you enjoy."
A strong longing for something
that isn't... the present.
[SNIFFLES]
[ZIPPER OPENS]
Uh, on our way up to the lake we
stopped to get these key chains.
It's like a...
a little ritual that we had.
Tallie took Marie, Marie took
me, and I took Tallie's.
I don't know. It feels like
something that you should have.
It's unfair, isn't it?
There's gonna be so much
that she misses,
like things that I know
she would like.
Like... [SNIFFLES]
Like music and movies.
Everything.
I want you both to know that
I'll think about you every day.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
[PHONOGRAPH GROOVE CRACKLING]
[HELEN NARRATING] Love.
The remainder.
Hold it.
It may be all you have left.
Let it shine in you.
And let it find you.
Let it through that small,
unseen possibility
and wrap its arms around you
to take you home.
["LIGHTHOUSE"
BY PATRICK WATSON PLAYING]
[MAN]
♪ Leave a light on ♪
♪ In the wild ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm coming in ♪
♪ A little blind ♪
♪ Dreaming of a lighthouse ♪
♪ In the woods ♪
♪ Shining a little light ♪
♪ To bring us back home ♪
[PIANO SOLO]
♪ When to find you ♪
♪ In the backyard ♪
♪ Hiding behind ♪
♪ Our busy lives ♪
♪ Dreaming of a lighthouse ♪
♪ In the woods ♪
♪ To help us get back ♪
♪ Into the world ♪
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
♪ 'Cause I know ♪
♪ I've seen you before ♪
♪ Won't you shine ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ A little light ♪
♪ On us now? ♪
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
♪ Won't you shine
A little light ♪
♪ In your own backyard? ♪
♪ Won't you shine
A little light ♪
♪ In your own backyard? ♪
♪ Dreaming of a lighthouse ♪
♪ In the woods ♪
[MUSIC FADES]