My rise to the top of the Haden High School food chain,
happened faster than a three-second snapchat.
But it wasn't always that way.
A few weeks ago, I was just like you.
Then I updated my status, and some
pretty strange things began to happen.
I feel like I owe everyone an explanation,
so here it is.
Oh, and by the way, I don't play hockey.
Line by line resync and more
by Dandysubs on 20180421.
Or at least I didn't, until a few weeks ago.
Oh, come on, kid.
Knock-knock,
I'm invading your privacy.
Come on, get up!
You're gonna be late
for your first day of school.
- Ugh, it smells like a wet dog in here.
- See that guy?
- Hey!
- That was me not so long ago.
Listen, you need to finish
putting this room together,
so when you get home from school today
I want you to start unpacking, all right?
Breakfast in ten.
Wait, wait, Mom, Mom!
I don't think I feel so good.
Yeah, right.
- Hey, bud, how you doing?
- Hey dad.
Sorry for hittin' you up so early.
Did I wake you?
Aw, please, don't worry about it,
I had to get up early...
giant swells this morning,
everything okay?
This place sucks.
- I wish I could be there with you.
- Listen...
you just gotta hang
tough until summer, okay...
then you're gonna be right
back here in Cali with me.
I love you, Pop.
I love you too man.
Hang in there, all right?
Whoa!
- Oh, well...
- Sorry about that.
- Still getting used to having people in the house.
- Yeah, yeah, I'll come back later.
Maxi, don't play on your
phone at the table.
I'm not playing, I'm swiping.
- Swiping?
- Yes.
Get that app off your phone, young lady.
Put it on my phone, though.
Dude, you're gonna wear that
on the first day of school?
This isn't Huntington Beach.
Okay, eat up.
The bus will be here in ten minutes.
I don't know why
I couldn't bring my car.
Dad said he'd pay
to have it shipped.
Well, I love that money is
no object for your father,
'cause he doesn't make any.
Your dad's need to relax has gotten in the
way of him finding any kind of work.
I get it, you guys are mad at me.
But just bear with me, just trust me. I have a plan.
This is better for all of us, all right?
Hey, bro! You need to
drop the teen angst act.
Mom and Dad are over.
This is the new normal. Accept it.
Look, they're only separated.
They're not getting a divorce.
She moved 3.000 miles
to get away from him.
To me, that screams divorce,
but then again, I'm a realist.
No surf, no Dad, no car...
senior year in Connecticut.
23? Room 23?
Does anybody know
where Room 23 is?
Sorry, man, my bad.
Hey, do you guys know
where Room 23 is?
Cool skateboard.
- Thanks.
- 23?
- Yeah.
- Isn't that East wing, guys?
- Yeah, I got a class there.
- Yeah, it's on the other side of the school.
I really appreciate it, dude.
Not a problem... dude.
Come on, come on, where is it?
* The fourth the fifth *
* The minor fall, The major lift *
* The baffled king composing Hallelujah *
- Hi.
Sorry, I'm late.
Well, Mr?
Kyle, Moore.
Kyle Moore, I really hope this isn't how
the rest of the year is going to go.
Mm-hm.
Please have a seat, Kyle.
* I saw a sign of violence *
Great.
Hey.
Hi.
I saw you singing earlier.
You were, you were great.
I was a little flat, but, thank you.
I'm Kyle.
I'm Dani.
Are you trying to make me jealous?
Brian, this is Kyle.
Kyle, this is Brian Massey.
Hey, man?
Are you making a play
on my girl, Spray Tan?
Brian, I'm not your girl, okay?
You're gay.
37% percent technically ain't gay, baby.
And you were flat again today.
Do you wanna win the Slam, or not?
Yes, yes, of course,
I want to win the Slam.
Well, then, mediocrity isn't gonna cut it.
Okay, I'm not taking my shirt off.
I can not lose that
much water weight again.
You need to step it up.
Are you wearing women's jeans?
No.
Yes... my stylist picked them out.
Dude, you don't have a stylist.
Okay, H & M had a flash sale,
I blacked out.
Later, Kyle.
Don't even think about it.
You can think about this.
Hey, Kyle,
looks like you're acclimating nicely.
This is my boyfriend, Xing-Fu.
Xing, Mr. Unpopular here is my brother, Kyle.
Where are you from in China?
Oh, no, he's from Connecticut.
His real name's Donald.
But he only speaks Mandarin,
because he's so in tune,
with his Chinese roots.
Let's go, Fu.
What are you doing at my table?
Sorry, I didn't know it was yours.
Well, it is, so beat it.
Wait, wait, no, no, no, no, kidding, I'm kidding.
You thought I was serious?
That was awesome. No, I'm not, I'm not a fighter.
I know I look intimidating but,
no, I've never been in a fight. Well, that's not true.
When I was in third grade this girl kicked me,
in... the eggplant emoji...
and I just fell down and cried,
and pee'd a little.
Thanks for sharing that with me.
Yeah. Are you really from California?
Yeah, I really am.
That is gnarly. Is that how
you say gnarly?
- Sure.
- I've always wanted to go to California,
like just skateboard, you know,
like down the Venice boardwalk
and like hang out with Snoop Dogg, you know,
Straight Outta Compton-style,
except without, you know,
the smokies, because I have asthma.
But anyways, I can't go, because I sunburn
easily and I'm not really athletic.
I'm talking a lot, sorry,
my name's Lonnie. Oh, fist bump.
Sorry bro.
- But everyone calls me Grimace.
- Why Grimace?
Oh, because everyone
thinks I look like him.
I don't see it, dude.
Dude, I sound like a Californian.
Yo, Grimace?
Hey, Derek.
I got a B-plus on my history paper.
Yeah, that's not good.
That's unacceptable.
Stop eating, start studying.
Got it, dude.
You do that guy's homework?
Yeah, Principal Kim makes me "tutor" him.
He's the best hockey player in Connecticut.
He scored more goals in two periods,
than any other high schooler in history.
He's got a Youtube channel,
and I hear the pros are watching him.
And then there's Charlotte, Derek's girlfriend,
hottest girl in the whole school.
The queen of Twitter, Snapchat, Facebook.
She's got like half a million followers on Instagram.
Queen of all the hockey groupies.
They're expected to win the
state championship.
We haven't won in like 20 years,
so it's all because of that guy.
Yeah, well, I'm not a hockey fan.
Me, neither, but figure skating's cool.
I mean, whatever.
- Yo, Grimace!
- What?
Chocolate money shot!
You got your milk all over my titties.
Did I forget to mention he has
a really accurate slap shot?
He's good. Do I have anything in my face?
Oh, you got a little something right... here.
Yo, Point Break!
Hey. Come on, man.
I'm just messing with you. All right?
It's nothing personal.
We just do it to all the new kids.
So, uh, we cool?
Kyle! Look out!
Oh!
Five minutes for cross checking!
How's that locker feel, Point Break?
Oh... Cali!
Hey, come on, give me my phone back.
Oh, you wanna call your mommy, Point Break?
Oh, you can actually use my phone.
Give it back.
Too slow.
They didn't teach you any hockey in Cali?
Come on, Cali Boy!
Give me my phone back.
Whoa, they teach you manners in California?
All you gotta do is say please.
Please?
That wasn't so hard, was it?
Here, take it back.
Nice phone,
you might want to get that looked at... pussy.
Mortal enemy, check.
Hey, man, do you fix phones?
Mm...
You're tryin' to lock me into a lot of do's and
don't's right now, you beautiful angel.
Let me tell you something,
in a former life, I was a wolf.
Hm, cool.
Mm...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Your chi is way off.
Your chakras are not aligned.
You know what I'm saying?
The feng is not shui-ing.
Uh-huh. Can you fix my phone or not?
Yeah, I can fix your phone.
Let me see it.
Okay.
Yeah... say goodnight, this thing's done.
You've insta-ed your last gram,
tweeted your last twit.
I know, you left your whole life behind,
and you're pissed.
And the kids around here,
in pistachio khakis?
They don't really comprendo
a surfer dude like you.
Am I right? Or am I right?
How did you know that?
Because I'm here to enlighten the load, baby.
Mmmmm.
Listen, why don't you, tell me,
what I can do...
to make your life...
a little more namaste.
I don't know. I just~
I want things to be different.
Let's fly. Do it with me.
I'm not gonna do that.
Then nothing's gonna change.
Don't be scared. Come on, yeah,
yeah, there you go, fly.
Close your eyes.
Do you know what's below you?
All the haters, and they're
pointing and they're saying,
"Look at that beautiful, blonde bird
with well-conditioned hair."
You know what I'm saying?
That was intense, man.
How do you feel?
- Embarrassed.
- Great, me, too.
I want to show you something.
Take a look at this.
It's my own social media app.
It's called YOUniverse.
When you look at this screen man,
what do you see?
A blank page?
You're cute, but you are so stupid.
This is you, dude.
Not the "you" you are,
the "you" you want to be.
You can be anybody.
You just gotta fill this page,
a new beginning,
you know what I'm saying?
Because when you put positive
vibes out in the YOUniverse...
the YOUniverse listens.
Give me your hand.
Give me your beautiful, soft hand.
Take this... and go... to your destiny.
Thanks.
We're all made of energy,
me and you.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Whatever.
All you gotta do is fill the screen, baby.
- Pants up, hands where I can see 'em.
- What do you want?
I need to borrow your balcony.
My window's painted shut,
- and I need to sneak out.
- Where you goin'?
Xing-fu's taking me to
an Anime and Chill party.
What are you doing tonight?
That's right, nothing!
See ya'!
Good morning. Just warming up the pipes,
don't mind me.
Good morning, Sunshine.
Good morning.
You might want to take a look outside.
Is that my car?
That just showed up on a truck.
Yes! I can't believe it.
That's my car!
Yes, it is, and I can't believe it.
There's no way. Where's Dad?
Probably tanning on a beach somewhere...
and look, you need to get a job,
so you can pay for the gas,
but I will, help you
with the insurance.
Okay. Oh, I knew he'd come through.
Yes!
Yeah, I thought about trying out
for the hockey team,
but, my physician said that
I have the ankle strength,
of a ten-year-old girl.
But you know, multiplayer,
online gaming is my real passion.
It can get pretty physical, too.
Like one time, I passed out
after 17 straight hours of Warcraft.
- Really?
- Yeah, dehydration.
I went to the doctors
and I woke up in the ER.
And then, I met my girlfriend
through League of Legends.
She's a bikini model,
her name's Guadalupe.
Hey, Lonnie, can I ask you something?
Have you ever heard of an app
called YOUniverse?
No, and I'm on everything,
Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest.
Sure, I only have like two followers,
it's my mom and my granny,
and my dad blocked me for some reason.
That's weird, why would you
block your own son, right?
I haven't talked to him about that.
Wait, wait, what's YOUniverse?
It's just something I read about.
Gotta go, see ya'!
Cool, nothing, thanks for
starting that conversation.
I'll tell Guadalupe about that.
She's my girlfriend,
Guadalupe is my girl.
No one cares? Are you on Twitter?
* We can find a way to break through *
* Even if we can't find heaven *
* I'll walk through hell with you *
* I'm gonna stand by you *
Beth! Beth, thank you very much.
Um, I don't mean,
for you to take this personally...
but that was, and I say this
with the utmost respect,
like listening to two cats humping.
Is that fair?
Thanks, Beth!
Enjoy the stage as you leave it's...
it's the last time you'll ever be on one.
Okay.
All right, off you go everybody
who didn't make it, you can leave.
Grab your~
There, yes, you're one, certainly.
Yes, you were terrible.
Okay? Thanks, gang, have a good day.
All right, Dani, Brian, I'm gonna
need you up on stage.
Band and chorus, we got nine
weeks to do this, not a lot of time.
Excuse me... um... sorry.
I'm here to audition.
Okay, and you are?
I'm Kyle Moore.
Are you a singer, Mr. Moore?
Yeah... uh... I'm classically trained.
You're classically trained?
Yep.
Okay, everybody sit down,
we're gonna do one more up here.
You know where the stage is?
- It's this thing.
- Yeah.
Have a go at it.
All right, hey, uh, what will you be singing?
- Singing?
- Yeah.
Uh... it's a surprise, even to me.
I ah, usually just let my inner rock star,
do whatever he's feeling.
Your, inner rock star?
Yeah... yeah.
We're all just made of molecules, man.
We're just energy.
All you have to do, is soar!
* (opera singing) *
What the hell?
Quite a surprise, Mr. Moore.
My God,
that's the craziest thing I've ever seen.
You must be a very lonely person.
Come back when your balls drop!
Au revoir, mademoiselle.
Seriously, come back when
your balls drop.
Dude, I am freaking out!
You gotta tell me what
the deal is with the~
Dude?
Okay.
Dude, dude!
Huh? Oh!
I remember you.
You're the angry kid with no friends.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
stay with me here, now listen.
That YOUniverse app you put
on my phone, it's insane.
It worked, the things that
I wished for happened.
- Right.
- Then some things that I wished for,
- didn't happen the way that I wanted them to.
- I know!
Well?
- Let me ask you a question.
- Yeah.
If a unicorn wrote a tweet and then posted it,
and then he put it up and deleted it...
and then a tree fell down in the forest,
does anybody even hear it?
What are you talking about?
Listen, that YOUniverse app,
can you tell me how to control it?
Can you tell me if I can take
back something that I posted?
What do you want to take back?
Whoa, dude!
That's what you wished for?
- Listen to me, man.
- What?
You can't change the past,
that's crazy talk.
Is this forever?
Me and you?
No, no, I'm talking about the app.
- Oh, the app!
- Yes!
- All I know is this.
- Yeah.
The YOUniverse is changing
thousands of times every second.
You just gotta update your status.
Update my status.
- Update my status.
- The YOUniverse will assist.
My man!
Dad?
What's up!?
- Hey.
I can't believe you're here.
What are you doing here?
Dude, I don't even know.
I woke up and I was like, I gotta get out of here.
I gotta go, I gotta go, so I just did.
I don't know, I got on a plane.
Boom, I'm here.
- Wow.
- Hey, why aren't you driving Born to Run?
Mom says I have to get a job first.
Heard that before. Listen, grab a sponge, all right?
Can't have ladies getting in a dirty ride.
You got it.
- So tell me something, what's been happening?
- Oh, you don't even know.
I've been skating and surfing every day,
12 hours a day sometimes.
Hey! Anna Banana, how are you doing?
Hey, killer, you want to give us a second?
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
You look great.
I forgot what those scrubs do to you.
So great.
I'm tellin' you, these waves
were toppin' out like at 30 feet.
30 feet! That's like as big as this house!
I mean that's huge!
I don't think you truly
appreciate how big this is.
Annie, give 'em the arm wave,
show 'em, show 'em.
All right, this is me
on my board, right?
This is the 30-foot wave, look
at that! This is to scale, Maxi.
Ugh, ugh, shred, shred, bleed,
bleed, pull, snap through. Thanks Ann.
And they were just coming, one after the other.
And I surfed 'em, all day, all day, Allen!
Into the evening, even.
Then I fell asleep to the sounds of that angry ocean,
just pounding the beach.
It was pretty great.
Wake up the next day and
we did it all again. What?
It was one of the best times I've ever had
in my entire life. Except for the time...
you and I rebuilt the Alpha Romeo.
That was the best time I ever had in my life.
- Hey, agreed! Born to Run!
- Born to Run! Cheers to that, my man.
Well, it's good to have you back dad,
now Kyle has a shoulder to cry on.
Maxi, chill out.
- So, Darryl, what do you plan on doing for work here?
- Well, I connected with an old skate buddy of mine,
who's got his own brand out here in New Haven.
He's gonna hook me up with a job doin' graphics.
It's a real job.
So I hit the ground running tomorrow.
But, tonight, I just want to say,
that I am so happy to be here,
hanging out, with that sexy,
little surfer chick, I met 22 years ago.
Do you remember that girl?
Anna Banana, I think her name was?
- Sort of.
- Anna Banana.
Annie, Kyle, Maxi...
I love you guys.
There's no other place in the
universe I'd rather be.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Cheers, Allen.
So what did I do?
What would you do?
All right, YOUniverse...
let's make some moves.
Thank you, Doris.
- I want another shot.
- Huh?
I want another shot.
Uh, you want a Castrato role now? I don't think
you're gonna like the requirements very much.
* You, suck! *
See, that's how it's actually, done,
because I'm actually classically trained.
All right? Now get out of here.
Hey, can I borrow that?
* One, two, one two three *
* Oh yeah yeah, Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah *
* Never had much faith in love or miracles *
* Never wanna put my heart on the line *
* Swimming in your water is something spiritual *
* I'm born again every time you spend the night *
* 'Cause your sex takes me to paradise *
* Yeah your sex takes me to paradise *
* And it shows *
* Yeah yeah yeah *
* 'Cause you make me feel like *
* I've been locked out of heaven *
* For to long *
* Ah yeah yeah yeah yeah *
* Ah yeah yeah, ah yeah yeah yeah yeah *
* You bring me to my knees, you make me testify *
* Yeah you can make a sinner change his ways *
* Open up your gates 'cause
I can't wait to see the light *
* And right there is where I wanna stay *
* 'Cause your sex takes me to paradise *
* Yeah your sex takes me to paradise *
* And it shows *
* yeah yeah yeah *
* 'Cause you make me feel like *
* I've been locked out of heaven *
* For to long *
* Yeah you make me feel like *
* I've been locked out of heaven *
* For to long *
* And you make me feel like *
* I've been locked out of heaven *
* For to long *
* 'Cause you make me feel like *
* I've been locked out of heaven *
* For to long *
* Ah yeah yeah yeah yeah *
What did you think?
I had no idea what to expect after yesterday.
But oh my God, you friggin' killed it.
I'm so happy.
I hated singing with Brian.
The best part was watching Massey freak,
and then Mr. Moody kick him out of chorus! So good!
Since when did my brother
get so many friends?
And who has the non-dairy,
chocolate, caramel latte?
Oh, that would be me,
the lactose intolerant one.
Can't drink milk, because it goes through me
like lava through a Philippine village, just~
Just really thick.
Would you like to go out sometime?
No, thanks.
Is it because of the diarrhea?
Brian's here.
Let's go, outside, you and me, right now.
Brian, just go away.
You no longer have the privilege
of speaking to me.
And when I'm selling out the Garden...
- you'll all be kissing my waxed, platinum butt cheeks.
- Brian!
- Zip it, GiGi Haddada!
- All right, that's it!
- Kyle, don't, this is stupid.
- No, it's okay.
Let's go.
Brian!
Brian, don't do this!
Kyle!
Guys, come on!
One rule... no touching my face.
This is my money maker.
Whoa.
I am so gonna cream you!
* Somebody turn it up *
Be like water,
making its way through cracks.
- You're dead!
- Kyle!
Point taken. I'm good.
- Here you go, Gramps.
- Thank you.
Hey, Anime...
I don't know what's going on with this look,
but I am digging it, big time.
Our daughter is wearing a dog collar.
Darryl, um, how was your first day?
It went well. Yeah, it's just
a wait-and-see game now.
What do you mean, wait and see?
I thought you said you had the job.
I do, I do, I just had
to meet my boy's partner.
Big dog and pony show,
you know how it is.
Don't worry, I got the job, okay?
Hey, killer, what gives?
We were supposed to meet down
at the skate park today. You stood me up.
Sorry about that,
I got caught up.
He got into a fight.
You got in a fight?
- Yeah, oh, yes.
- Maxi.
You dropped him like a bad
habit, too, didn't you?
- It wasn't a big deal, Mom.
- Um, it is a big deal.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you fighting?
Relax, okay?
There's nothing wrong with him,
there's not a scratch on him.
He's looking good, he's walking tall.
I taught my son not to act like that.
Well, apparently he does,
and he wins.
Give me some.
Mom, I'm fine,
and it won't happen again.
- Can I be excused?
- Where you going?
Meeting up with a friend.
Friends, singing in the chorus, fighting,
you're not that cool, dude.
Get out of here, have fun,
enjoy your date.
Thanks. Thank you, Dad.
And try not to get in any fights.
See what I did.
Hey hold on a second,
why don't you take the Alpha.
You're the best, Dad!
I am the best.
What?
Okay, where are we going?
If you could do, anything... in the world,
right now... what would it be?
I would... ride a Ferris wheel.
- Really?
- Yeah, mm-hm.
- Why?
- I love Ferris wheels.
I've loved them ever since
I was a little girl.
Well, you're in luck.
I just happen to know where one is.
* I know that we will *
* We will last forever *
Oh, oh, no.
* I promise we will *
* We will last forever *
- Oh my God!
- You like it?
Oh, my God, this is so good.
Where did it even come from?
One night only... and it's all for us.
Come on.
This is just to good.
Hello.
Well, hi.
- Right this way.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
This feels right.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- This is so cool.
Yeah, it is.
Everything you wanted?
Oh, this is like, this is the dream.
I'm obsessed with this.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, how do you like singing
with our chorus?
- I like it.
- Yeah?
I just wish we were singing
something more... now.
- Yes.
- Or at least 2003.
Mm-hm. Mr. Moody plays it so safe.
It's probably why Hayden
has never won the Slam.
Hm.
Man, it would feel so good
just to win one time.
We're gonna win the Slam
this year... I promise.
This is the perfect fall night.
- I've never seen fall before.
- No.
I'm from Huntington Beach.
Well, you are in for a treat,
because nothing beats New England falls.
Have you ever heard of the
Heavenly Pursuit?
What's that?
Okay, well, autumn is the time
of year that the moon...
after pursuing the sun, since spring,
finally catches up to her.
But, then he out distances her,
and, the whole pursuit begins again.
It's kind of like,
two lovers who lose one another.
But, his love is so powerful that...
he spends his entire life trying to find her.
That sounds kinda tragic.
Yeah, I know, I'm a total sucker
for a tragic love story.
But I think every girl wants a moon.
Yeah.
This has been the coolest night.
I don't get it, I've lived here my whole life
and no one even knows who I am.
Come on, that's not true.
- Hi, Liza.
- Who are you?
Lonnie Gregory, your next door
neighbor for the past 17 years.
Doesn't ring a bell. Sorry.
Course not, hey, thanks for not
inviting me to your Sweet 16.
It was beautiful from what I saw
from the window anyways.
But that's what I mean, you.
You show up four weeks ago,
and now your life is like this
amazing fairy tale, right?
I keep thinking about it. I mean it's like,
it's a little annoying, actually, but in a good way.
Okay Lonnie,
I have to tell you something.
But you gotta promise me that
you won't tell anyone. Promise?
- Yeah, not even Mom.
- You sure? You talk a lot.
- I know I talk a lot, just tell me.
- Okay, okay.
I have a magic app on my phone...
and whatever I post on it... comes true.
- I'm sorry, what? What?
- It's insane.
Oh my God, I have the same app,
I thought I was the only one.
- Really?
- Yeah, no, dude! Come on, you lost your mind.
- Lonnie, I'm telling the truth.
- Okay, fine, if that was even a possibility,
which I'm not saying that it is,
how would that even work?
I'll tell you, okay, so my phone broke,
so I took it to the mall to this bearded dude.
- Bearded dude?
- Bearded dude.
He gave me a new phone with this
app called YOUniverse on it.
The YOUniverse is always eavesdropping.
There's this unicorn,
and if the unicorn posts a tweet in the woods,
and then deletes the tweet,
does it make a sound?
Oh, man, you Californians, okay.
I'm not crazy. I'm telling you the truth.
It does sound crazy, because
it's bullshit, all right?
Lonnie!
Look, if anyone understands the
need for fantasy, it's me.
I mean, I spend more of my time
on Azeroth than I do on earth.
But, I don't go around trying to convince people
that I'm Archmage Khadgar the Wizard.
Maybe you guys do things
differently in California.
Maybe it's the avocados, maybe it's the stuff
everyone's smoking, you know what I'm saying?
But, we don't do things like that.
No one~ What is that?
This is a gift.
This is my favorite skateboard.
- Cool.
- And I want to give it to you.
- What?
- I want you to have it.
- It's for you, come on.
- That's so awesome.
That's the nose, that's the tail.
And those two bolts, are what you stand on.
Oh, I don't know, my ankles, remember?
And it's like the height.
- Lonnie, get on the board.
- I'm afraid of heights. Okay, here I go, um.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
You smell like avocados.
You smell so good.
What do you put in your hair?
It's, my hair's just~
- You're good.
- It's so high up here.
- Does anybody get a nose bleed?
- You're gonna be fine, Lonnie.
- How high up are we right now?
- An inch.
An inch, that's a lot.
Just, what do I do now?
You kick back and enjoy
the ride.
Oh, my God, I'm getting light hands,
because it's so hot.
Whoa, whoa! What's going on!?
I'm not doing anything.
Why is it taking off?
Whoa, I'm actually skateboard~
Get out of the way!
Look at me!
Whoa, whoa.
Look at you rip, doggie!
Yeah!
Is that Grimace?
It's me, Lonnie.
You don't know my name, that's okay.
* Can't you hear what I say *
* Just get out of my way *
Watch this.
This is the coolest thing I've
ever done! Like, by far!
It's the best day of my life!
Lonnie! Lonnie!
Lonnie! You all right, man?
How many fingers?
- You have fingers.
- Come on, let's get you up.
You gotta watch what you're eating,
I mean, going.
What do you think you're doing?
You could've seriously hurt him.
Well it's not my fault he's fat, and uncoordinated.
Yeah?
Well if it's so easy, why don't you try it?
Or are you just some pussy in a letter jacket?
Look at me, I'm riding a skateboard.
- What are you doing?
- Watch this.
It's so easy.
Whoa, what? Whoa, slow down.
Yo, what is going on?
Yo, guys, stop this.
Yo, Oliver! Dude, hey, dude!
Stop, stop! Move back away!
Aren't you going to study
for the Spanish test?
I'm just gonna wing it.
Okay, wow, you know, you are the only person I know,
that never studies and gets all A's.
- You write music?
- Oh, it's nothing.
Sing something for me.
No.
Okay, shut your face,
it's not happening.
Dani, I don't know!
I've never heard of the game
Truth or Dare before!
What are you doing?
My mom will hear you.
- Dani, what are you doing?
- Kyle, stop it!
Dani, what's going on up there?
Nothing, Mom! Nothing!
Stop it. You're a freak.
Get over there.
If you so much as roll your eyes,
I swear, I'll murder you.
All right, cross my heart and hope to die.
Drowning?
Mm-hm, yes, I know,
it sounds a little morbid, but,
it's really just a conversation
between two people falling in love.
Yeah, leave it to me to write a
song that sounds like a eulogy.
Whoa, wait, wait, wait.
You gotta sing it for me.
- No, Kyle, no, you know I'm not~
- Just a few verses, please?
Just a few verses, that's all I'm asking for.
Agh.
* Seems like the love songs have got it all wrong *
* I thought I would fly *
* And it's getting darker the further we fall *
* And I'm feeling high *
That's great... here.
I think I got it.
- Okay.
- Keep singing.
* Remember the time I first saw you *
* I thought you'd be mine and it felt so good *
* One look in your eyes and I swear I knew *
* Of your kiss, your touch, your love *
* And I can't breathe *
* I'm struggling *
* Hey hey hey *
* My heart's at ease *
* 'Cause I'm drowning *
* Drowning in your love *
Oh!
That was bad, let me try it again.
Oh... so close!
* Now I've heard there was a secret chord *
* That David played, and pleased the Lord *
* But you don't really care for music do you *
Wait, guys, guys, hold on.
Hold up. What is it now, Pavarotti?
Mr. Moody, Dani and I have been working on something,
that we'd love to show you.
Kyle, what are you doing?
Kyle, I've been doing this a long time.
I think I know what song is going to work.
I know, but Dani wrote this song
and it's tight, Mr. Moody...
just, hear it out.
I'm sure it's very 'tight'.
It's just that, this song,
has a significance, for me.
Why?
- Because I sang it once.
- What for?
- Mr. Pookins.
- Who's Mr. Pookins?
- My cat.
- You sang a song for your cat?
My dead cat, he died,
I sang it at his funeral.
Sorry.
It was a suicide.
Can we just play the song
for you once, please?
You won't regret it.
- Do the short version.
- Yeah.
You got this.
* The ocean is heavy *
* Your current is strong *
* You're pulling me deeper *
* Been here all along *
* Remember the time I first saw you *
* I thought you'd be mine and it felt so good *
* One look in your eyes and I swear I knew *
* Of your kiss, your touch, your love *
I can not believe Mr. Moody is
letting us perform our song.
Our song?
It's your song, I just helped.
Tonight's the night Hawks hockey
season opener, be there, 7:00PM.
What is with the hockey insanity?
First game of the year is tonight.
What's even worse,
is the biggest game of the season,
is the same night as the Slam.
I'll be so surprised if anybody
even shows up.
Hey, you all should go to the Slam!
I'm telling you, if not, you're gonna miss out,
and you're gonna have to watch
it on YouTube. I'm telling you.
You know, nobody but you
could've got me to share my music.
Thank you.
I'm happy I met you.
I'm, kind of happy I met you.
You're so dumb.
I gotta go to class, bye.
- Bye!
- Later, gator.
- Jesus.
- Isn't that sweet?
The lady and the tramp were
about to have their first kiss.
What's with you, Massey?
I Google Chrome-d you... and
there's not a single mention,
of you singing anywhere
before you came to Hayden.
Something about you stinks,
and I'm gonna figure it out.
And then, I'm gonna stuff, and mount you.
All I'm saying is be careful,
things are rarely what they appear to be.
Take my girlfriend from Honduras,
the bikini model, Guadalupe?
She turned out to be Phil, from Cleveland.
Yeah, I got Catfished...
- without the TV show!
- What are you getting at?
I'm sayin, we don't know anything
about this bearded dude.
I mean, what if he turns out to
be some kind of like, you know...
master of dark arts.
Look, anything that got my
family back together, can't be bad.
Yeah? Speaking of family...
um, it's my birthday Saturday and
every year, we go to my favorite place.
It's a Greek restaurant,
there's hummus, there's a belly dancer.
Yeah, I took some lessons.
She asked me to leave,
but I'm wondering, if you wanted to go,
you could go, it's gonna be lame...
you probably... no, forget it.
Lonnie! Of course, I'm coming to your birthday.
I wouldn't miss it.
Cool. All right, I'll just text
you all the deets and stuff.
Line by line resync and more
by Dandysubs on 20180421.
- That guy is such a douche.
- Yeah, but he's Emperor Douche.
And you just joined the chorus, so you're kind of like,
at the bottom of the barrel, too, you know?
Jealous, Chorus Boy?
- No.
- Hey!
Oh ho, gettin' a little angry?
No one cares about Kyle Moore.
I own this school, and there's not a
damn thing you can do about it.
Down... boy.
Jokes on him, this is how I eat
my mashed potatoes, so~
Somebody has to bring that guy in check.
Yeah, somebody's gotta check him.
It would be kind of cool if you went out for the hockey
team, though, right, beat him at his own game?
Our own little miracle on ice.
That would be so rad, dude, so rad.
Yeah, it would.
Let's go! Let's go!
Pass it!
Come on! What are you, girls?
Let's go!
Come on, get up, you push!
That's the best you got?
You skate like my sister.
Bring it in!
Two-on-two back check drill.
If we're gonna beat the Bulldogs...
we gotta get this right.
Look who it is.
Set it up!
Whoa.
Can I ah... can I help you with something?
I want a try-out, Coach.
Try-outs are over, all right?
That's too bad.
I'm way better than Derek.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
that's a pretty big claim, son.
Let's hope you can back that up.
The ice... is yours.
Can't wait to see this.
No, YOUniverse, we're here to play hockey.
No, no, no, no!
Not again!
What are you doing?
Whoa!
You can't even do that.
I can't look away.
That is so beautiful.
Holy smokes!
That's not what I meant.
Well, kid, you're no Wayne Gretzy but,
guess what, you made the team.
Boys, meet your new equipment manager.
All right! Play time's over.
Let's go! Set 'em up.
Nice one, Cali.
Wayne Gretzky.
Why didn't I think of that.
All right, let's try this again, shall we?
Hey, bitches! Where you goin'?
I'm not done yet.
Okay ah, Frozen...
let's see you score on the goalie.
Wreck him.
Get the ice packs ready.
Get him!
Come on!
* Like a boss *
* We are the wild beast *
* It's a bloody feast *
* Like a boss *
* We put you on the ice *
* Throw in the towel *
* You are the sacrifice *
* We are the warriors *
* We take the low road *
First line, get out there!
Not you, Lowe, stay put.
How you feeling, baby?
I could go all night.
Well then, get out there and take the face off!
Jeez! Come on! Come on! All right. Whoo!
- How good is he?
- Okay, Kyle!
What are you doing?
Why aren't you out there?
Let's go. Come on, boys!
* I am your champion *
* You're a great survivor *
* Check out my moves man *
* This kid's on fire *
* You can't get the message *
* I'm writing your history *
* Stand back as I roll up *
* I owe your soul to the sunshine *
* I am your champion *
* This kid's on fire *
Kyle, you're so cool!
- Hey.
- What up?
What are you wearing?
It's pretty sweet, right?
You'll never guess,
I just saw a bunch of kids rocking my jersey!
- Wow.
- I can't believe it, it's insane.
You know,
you missed rehearsal this morning.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
I couldn't sleep last night after the game.
But it won't happen again.
You know, I'm a little worried you're not
gonna have enough time for rehearsal now.
You know that the Slam,
is the same night as the game.
Dani, Chorus is way more
important to me than hockey.
I'll make it work.
Dude! I got 2.000 likes,
on my last Instagram post.
What? Every time I post something,
I lose followers.
Hey, so, my parents, they are super stoked,
to meet you Saturday.
- Oh, yeah, I'm psyched to meet them, too.
- Yeah, this is funny...
they actually don't think you exist.
My dad sat me down the other day,
and he was like...
"Is this 'Kyle' another 'Gary Wiggins'?"
Who's Gary Wiggins?
He was my imaginary friend, when I was a kid.
Not anymore, 'cause he moved away,
didn't leave a forwarding address.
Anywho, my parents are super
excited that you're coming,
so I'm stoked for them to see,
that you're real.
Moore!
- What's up?!
- Good, man, how are you?
Moore, come sit with us, my man.
We're celebrating tonight's win.
That's all right.
I'll catch up with you guys tomorrow.
No, no, go with them. I gotta go home anyways,
and do some gaming. I'm a gamer, so~
You sure?
- Yeah, no, celebrate.
- Cool.
- Yeah, go.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
- There he is.
So ah, where's Derek?
Probably picking the splinters out of his ass,
from sitting all game.
The Zamboni saw more ice than he did.
Can I get you anything?
Yes, I'll have a cheeseburger,
fries and a shake.
Oh my God, Cassie!
What are you gonna name your food baby?
J-k, obviously.
I'll just take a stick of celery, please.
- Hi.
- I'm Charlotte.
- Yeah, I know.
Cool.
So, how's it feel to be the guy
that everyone's talking about?
I don't know if that's true.
I bought a new perfume.
Do you want to smell me?
Uh~
Yeah. I do, I mean, sure.
Do you like it?
I-I love it.
I'm not wearing any perfume.
Cassie's having a party this Saturday.
I am?
Oh right, that party.
Of course, I am.
Do you have plans?
Saturday, no, I don't think so, no.
Well, now you do.
* Tonight is the night, yeah.
You know we gonna run *
* We do this all the time
All right tonight's the night *
* Yeah, you know
I'm in the mood *
* Yeah you know we shine so bright,
tonight's the night, yeah *
* You know that's how we do *
* So Baby Girl come on take
flight tonight's the night, yeah *
* You know we're coming through *
* And I'm ah make you feel all right,
tonight's the night, yeah *
* Hey yo step up on the scene *
* Gotta stay fresh so fly super clean *
What's up, man? Where you been, bro?
Everyone's out back.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
My man! Hey, you look thirsty.
Let's go.
No one told me it was a costume party.
Don't worry about it, bro.
Boys! The man of the hour has arrived!
To hockey!
One-timers, slap shots and kick saves!
Bone crushing hits that send
opponents to their graves.
Hat tricks, power plays and crosschecks.
Hayden Hawks hockey, it's better than sex!
Drink up, boys.
It's the golden boy,
the king of the ice.
Just remember... ice breaks,
and when it does...
all these people are gonna do...
is hold your little blonde hair under the water.
Don't worry about that.
He's just sore 'cause Charlotte cut him loose.
Charlotte broke up with him?
OMG. Are you gonna pay any
attention to me tonight or what?
Hey, Cassie, sick party.
Do you like my costume?
I'm a very naughty brave.
Of course, I like it.
I wore it last year.
I don't remember th~
Want to go for a walk?
Yeah.
Damn, he just made Derek, disappear.
What?
We thought you were over this.
Kyle is real, Mom! Okay?
He's not another Gary Wiggins!
Of course, he's not.
So, you broke up with Derek?
I think we just grew apart.
I'm extremely driven, and I want the best of
everything life has to offer, and Derek...
well he seems to be skating backwards.
I have over five million social media followers.
I take more AP classes than anyone else.
And I'm a state champion tennis player.
I don't even like tennis, it's boring.
What about you?
Do you want the best of
everything life has to offer?
Yeah, yeah, I guess, I do.
Well, you're on your way.
You have the looks, the grades,
the popularity.
You're just missing one detail.
What's that?
Me.
Without me, you'll be idolized.
But with me, you'll be deified.
So, do you want me, Kyle?
Because I want you.
Sorry. Oh, no! I totally forgot.
I gotta go, I'm so sorry.
Our lives are made up of
seemingly simple decisions.
This decision, right here,
right now, is one of yours.
So you have to ask yourself...
do you want to be a God...
or don't you?
Dani! Dani, wait!
Sorry.
Hey, are you okay?
You know, that was a really cute
picture Charlotte posted of the two of you.
At least, I think it was you.
You know, I couldn't quite tell, because she
was practically swallowing your face.
- I was gonna tell you, th~
- Why?
We're just buddies.
You don't owe me anything.
I'm happy for you Kyle.
You're the new Derek.
Hey! Hey! I'm still me.
Are you sure about that?
Lonnie. Lonnie!
Moore! Yeah, baby, let's go!
Come on, now, kid!
Moore, wake up!
I've seen better hands on a clock!
Now get your head, out of your backside!
Skate! Oh, come on!
Congratulations boys,
that was the worst practice we have ever had!
What's up, Grimace?
Do it, Grimace.
- Hey.
- What do you want?
Look, I'm sorry I missed your party, all right?
You embarrassed me.
- I thought we were friends.
- We are.
Look, you don't have to be the
person people pick on anymore.
- You want to go on your magic app, change me, too?
- Yes!
Yes, you can be whoever,
whatever, you want.
We can rule the school together.
We can do whatever.
I am who I want to be.
You're the one who changed.
You know what, you, and that thing,
that's a virus.
You've catfished yourself.
Alden residence.
Kyle Moore... here.
Hey. Oh, no, Kyle.
What? What's wrong?
You drove that old thing here?
Charlotte, it's a classic Alfa Romeo.
Hide it, and take it around the back,
and park it with the help.
Say something.
So, Mr. Alden, ah,
Charlotte tells me you're a lawyer?
- Where did you say you were from again, Carl?
- It's Kyle, Daddy.
California, sir.
Sun-baked hippies.
What does your father do for work?
He was a professional skateboarder.
Professional... skate... boarder.
But now, well, he's an entrepreneur.
Entrepreneur,
that's a fancy word for 'unemployed'.
Kyle just got named captain
of the hockey team.
Brutish sport.
I'm going to cut to the chase.
You're a nice looking, young man.
But the truth is,
you're just not one of us.
Daddy, he's the most popular boy at school!
- It's for the best, trust me, poopy.
- Dad!
- Can I use the bathroom?
- Masterson...
show the boy to the washroom,
and make sure he doesn't steal anything.
Now, poopy, don't pout,
you'll give yourself wrinkles.
Not one of you, huh?
Let's see what you think of me now.
So, how are we doin' in here?
Kyle! I was starting to miss you, son.
Weren't we, Pet?
We certainly were.
Daddy, are you feeling okay?
Never been better.
And Kyle, call me Dutch,
Mr. Alden sounds so stodgy.
Well, Dutch, you are a bit 'stodgy'.
To be honest...
I don't know how Kathy puts up with you.
You son-of-a-gun.
You're terrible.
He's so awful, it takes me three of these,
just to get through dinner!
She's plowed 24/7. I'm so awful,
I can't stand to be around me!
Just trying to get away from myself.
Hey Masterson, can you stand me?
Be honest. He hates my guts!
I think it's time for dessert.
Kyle... would you give me a hand in the kitchen?
I'd love to.
- Look.
- Enough of that.
- You're the greatest.
- Now there's a real man.
Mm, smells good, what's cookin' Kath?
You and me.
Mrs. Alden, what are you... doing?
Let's run away together,
far, far away from here.
Uh, your husband's in the other room.
I love you.
You need someone more flexible.
I was a ballerina, you know.
That's great, whoa!
Oh, I like that game.
- This is out of control. This needs to stop right now.
- I'm totally out of control and I don't give a damn!
- Hi, Pet.
- No, no, no, stop!
Hey!
Come to me, my little pet.
Come to me!
- Mrs. Alden, chill!
- Just don't ever say no.
Stop! Stop!
Oh, oh, yes! Oh, baby!
More, what?
Okay. Come on,
don't do this to me, YOUniverse!
YOUniverse, come on, what are you doing?
Kyle! Come back, Kyle!
- Take me with you!
- Oh God!
Take me to Paris!
Oh, you didn't!
- Wear berets!
- Oh, goodness!
Frere Jacques, Frere Jacques, Dormez-vous~
Send me nudes!
Wait up, wait up, wait up, two minutes!
What?
Uh, excuse me, ma'am?
Excuse me, have you seen the Bearded Dude?
Could you be a little more specific?
Real weird, makes bird noises...
he had a kiosk, over here,
and he sold phones.
Are you sure you're in the right mall?
Because, we don't allow sales carts in here.
Yes, I'm in the right mall.
I've seen him here twice!
Sir, are you under the influence?
I'm not even old enough to drink.
I need the YOUniverse app!
Sorry.
Maxi? What's going on?
They're fighting again.
- And I know you didn't get that job.
- It fell through.
I mean seriously, what do you want me to do,
put in an application at the local coffee shop?
Let me tell you something, that's never gonna happen,
because that ain't me, babe.
I did not ask you to come here,
but you came here on your own.
I don't know why.
Do you want it to work?
Show me that you're trying!
You need to be responsible.
Don't come at me with responsibility,
you always do that.
Listen, I know about responsibility, all right?
- Oh, do you?
- Hell yes.
- Do you?
- Yes.
You know, Kyle still thinks that you
wanted him to live with you...
and I pulled him away from his dad...
and moved him across country,
because I'm a bad person.
And I don't dare tell him
the truth, I don't dare.
It would break his heart.
I'm sick of covering for you all the time.
I'm sick of being the bad person.
Who took a dump, in Anthony's trumpet?
Nobody?
'Cause that's what it sounded like.
So let's try that again.
One, two, three.
* You took on the love and played the fool *
* I found there's no getting over you *
* All of the~ *
All right, the only problem I have with what
you just did, is that it sounded terrible.
You know what?
Whatever's going on between you two...
figure it out... fast!
All right, from the top, here we go.
I'm sorry. I can't do this.
You can't do it?
It's your song, you wrote it!
You're gonna have to do it without me.
Wait!
You shouldn't quit... I should.
No no no, actually, you shouldn't quit either.
Neither should~ Stop quitting! Everybody stop quitting!
The Slam is in five days,
you can not quit, Kyle.
I just did.
All right, let's make some noise, for coach Milligan,
and our undefeated, hot hockey team!
Thank you. Thanks.
We came in second place last year.
One point shy...
of our first trip to the state championship in 20 long,
agonizing years.
The last 365 days have been,
very tough, on coach.
I shed a lot of tears.
My wife and dog left me.
I woke up one morning,
naked in a chicken coop.
And I, might, have killed a man.
And... ah but...
that is all in the past, because, tomorrow night...
we get our first shot at redemption. Yes!
The reign of the Bulldogs is over!
This is the year of the Hawks!
I would like to hand the stage over,
to the captain of our team...
and the man who is
gonna lead us all the way...
to the Connecticut Cup, Kyle Moore!
Wow thanks, thanks so much, ah.
It's been a fast and furious
ride ever since I got here.
Don't you mean fast and fraudulent ride?
He's got you all believing, he's a singer...
and a hockey player... and worst of all...
a heterosexual.
But he's none of these things.
Not without, his magic, app!
He's got a magic app, on his phone...
that allows him to be,
whoever, and whatever, he wants!
This boy you all worship, is a lie!
You're an idiot!
Boo!
It's the truth! I'm telling you!
Did you hear me? It's a magic app!
- All right, come on, let's go, buddy.
- He's a nobody! He's a... nobody!
Wait, wait!
Hold on I...
I gotta be honest about some things.
It's true, four or five weeks ago,
I'd never played a game of hockey in my life.
I never ice skated,
I've never even held a stick.
He's like the Roy Hobbs of hockey!
No, listen to me.
I don't deserve any of this attention, I'm a~
An incredibly modest superstar!
No! I'm trying to tell you! I'm a fake, a phony!
I don't even know who I am.
A role model to everyone here tonight.
Exactly!
Unless we lose to the Bulldogs,
and then he's dead to everyone of us.
Let's light this fire!
Kyle?
Dani... Dani, wait, please.
What do you want from me, Kyle?
You have everything.
You have the fame, the glory.
You even have the girl.
What more could you possibly want?
I don't want any of it.
This, these clothes,
this isn't me, you know that.
If I could take it all back right now...
if I could erase everything, I would.
- Okay, then why don't you?
- Because I, I can't.
You can't?
Look... everything Brian said, was true.
There's this app, and everything I wish for comes true.
And I wished that I could sing,
so I could get close to you, and then it happened,
and then, so did everything else, and~
I wanna take it all back Dani,
but there's nothing I can do.
Let me just get this straight.
You've been a jerk,
because of an app?
- I know it sounds crazy.
- You know what's even crazier?
I wrote Drowning,
the day after you took me on the Ferris wheel.
Hey, can I have your autograph?
It's been a really long~
Turn down for what!?
You ready to get up?
I'm not going to school today.
What now?
I just don't want to go.
Well, that's not really a reason.
You have to convince me
to let you stay home.
What is it?
What's going on with you?
I posted some things on social media,
and I've hurt people.
And it all keeps getting worse, and...
I've really messed up.
Okay, well... when you mess up.
And you're gonna mess up.
The only thing you can do
is take ownership of it...
and try to make it right.
That's it.
It's like ripping off a Band-aid.
It's gonna hurt,
but just do it, and it's done.
And look, social media,
that stuff isn't real, you know that.
It's just everybody's highlight reel of...
the stuff they want you to see.
It's all bullshit.
It's bullshit with a filter on it,
to make it look pretty.
Let's eat. Get up!
Hey, Mom...
you look really pretty today.
Thank you...
but you still have to go to school.
Good morning, family, huh?
- What's for breakfast? I'm starving.
- French toast.
French toast, sounds good.
Hey, you know what? You and I
ought to go down to the park,
- and do some skating today, that's what we should do.
- Well, how's that job going, Dad?
Wow, right out of the gates, huh? Just~
Well, if you gotta know, um...
that one didn't pan out.
I gotta lot of good leads though,
so don't sweat it.
More importantly, do we got any powdered sugar
to go with that French toast?
Only Annie knows the answer.
Annie, talk to me!
Powdered sugar!
Wait mom, sit down.
You okay, killer? You're acting a little weird.
I'm fine.
But Mom's not getting your
breakfast today, or any other day.
The free ride stops, right now.
What are you~
What are you talkin' about?
What's going on here?
Did I miss something?
- Did you say something to him?
- Darryl.
Clearly you said something
to him, he's all worked up.
Leave her out of this.
I didn't say anything.
- This is about you and me.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Well, what is it about you and me?
When Mom moved me away from you...
I was so angry... and hurt, and alone.
She took me away from my best friend, my hero.
I would have done... anything...
for you to come back in my life.
But, the truth is...
you didn't even want me.
You didn't even want me.
I was so wrong, and I made Mom
go through hell because of it.
But Mom, Maxi, and I,
we deserve somebody...
who wants to be with us...
and you deserve to live your life.
As hard as that is...
I get it now.
Maxi? You feel the same way?
Grampa, I know how you feel.
All right.
I guess you're the man of the house,
congratulations.
I'm gonna go get my breakfast elsewhere.
- Xing-fu, hey.
- Hey.
How goes it now, Xing-fu.
Hey, Kyle...
I'm sorry, for being such a lousy little sister.
I could do a lot worse.
- Hi, Mr. Gregory?
- Yes?
I'm Kyle Moore.
I just wanted to drop by and say hello,
I'm Lonnie's friend.
Good God in heaven, you're real.
Honey! Honey! Come quick!
What is it?
This is Kyle, Lonnie's friend!
Did he put you up to this?
Is he paying you?
No, Lonnie's really my friend.
To be honest he's, actually my best friend.
Hey, Lonnie.
- I gotta go, but it was great meeting you guys.
- The pleasure's ours.
Come back again! Soon! Please!
Lonnie!
Wait up, man!
Leave me alone, Kyle.
Hey, don't push off with yourfront foot,
that's mongo.
Don't tell me what to do.
Hey, so get this...
I met this guy in Cleveland,
says he's a bikini model named Phil.
You're lucky you're my only friend.
I'm back, buddy.
Kyle? Kyle! What are you doing?
If it isn't the prince of popularity.
What are you doing over here with us lepers?
You don't look so good, bud.
Well, let's see, I lost my girl,
I lost my scholarships.
Coach demoted me to fourth line.
My friends want nothing to do with me...
and now my dad's talking about sending me to military
school. So yeah, life's great, I'm doing fantastic.
You got something on your face.
I don't care.
What is Kyle doing with that loser?
- So gross.
- I can't believe I dated him.
Oh, I can't believe I slept~
I mean, through third period.
LOL.
Come on, Derek, where's that clean cut,
confident guy, that I hated a few months ago?
He's you now. I gotta go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Look, man, this isn't me.
I don't want to be this guy.
- I want to help you get on top again.
- I don't know what your game is, all right,
but if you're looking to bury me some more,
give it your best shot.
There's no angle here.
I just want to make things right.
* I thought you'd be mine and it felt so good *
* One look in your eyes and I swear I knew *
* Love your kiss, your touch, your~ *
Hold on, everybody. Hold on, thank you.
Dani... what's the matter honey, talk to me.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, it's the song,
it was written as a duet.
I don't think I can sing it.
It's beautiful, and you sing it so well.
It just doesn't feel right anymore.
Is there any way we could go
back to Hallelujah... please?
Oh, my God, these girls, with their boy problems.
Okay, everybody, Hallelujah, from the top.
All right, you remember how that goes.
Horns, you want to get your spittle out now,
so we don't have to watch that later?
Here we go.
Whoa... Charlotte, hey,
didn't see you stalk~ standing there.
Hmm.
Have you been ignoring me?
No, why would I be ignoring you?
No, I just~
You've been ignoring my texts,
you've been ignoring me at lunch.
You ignored me at the bonfire.
I will not be ignored, Kyle.
- Shh!
- Shut up!
I will eat your children!
Okay.
I don't want to fight you.
I just want to love you.
I love you so much.
We're gonna be together forever.
Good luck at the game tonight.
I'll be watching, every, little, step.
Oh, my God.
Let's go Hawks! Let's go Hawks!
* Play to win *
* We got all this to lose *
* Lay it all on the line *
* Reach for the stars *
* Look to the heavens *
* Waiting to give us a sign *
So, that's the end of my story.
Where it goes from here...
only the YOUniverse knows.
This my life now.
I have to live it.
But, I'm gonna live it my way.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome...
your very own, number 17, Kyle Moore!
How many goals you got in you tonight,
super star?
More than they do.
That's my boy!
Go out there and take the face off!
Come on, now.
That's my boy, Kyle. You are, my boy!
All right now,
let's play as a team! Okay.
Yeah, boys, let's go, boys!
Let's win this face-off, let's go!
Hey, Moore, I got your number tonight.
I'm gonna light you up.
Let's see what you got?
That's my best friend, right there.
- I love you!
- I love you, too!
Up! Up!
Look for the opening!
Nice.
Nice move! Move it up,
up the ice, up the ice.
No!
What the~
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no!
Yo, kid, where does it hurt?
- It hurts right there where you're touching it, ow.
- Sorry, my bad.
Listen, look at me!
I'm gonna tell you a story.
I once played with a broken
back, a broken pubis...
a broken leg, an infected urethra...
and one hell of an epic hangover!
So you are gonna be fine!
Now help him up! Jeez!
Okay, he's good. He's okay!
I can't do it, Coach.
I can't do it.
So that's a no? Or~
Don't make me do it, Coach.
Get him off the ice.
Why, God, why?
Back to the chicken coop.
- Coach!
- What?
Put me in.
- Coach.
- What?
- Stop crying.
- I'm not crying.
Stop it. I'm gonna win this game for us.
- Coach!
- Yeah.
Listen to me, put me in.
- Okay.
- Now.
Okay, you're in.
Go get him, kid! Go get him, kid!
Get back out there, guys.
I'll find you a doctor.
That was awesome. You totally deserve an Oscar.
Have you thought about acting?
I wasn't acting.
- Oh, sorry, dude.
- So, we gotta go.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Text my sister.
- Have everyone meet us at the Slam.
- Okay.
- Dude, why'd you park there?
- It's super cool!
- I'm good.
- What are you doing?
Just got excited.
* Crimson and clover, over and over *
Nice, Lonnie.
Speed Racer. Wait! Wait up!
You'll have to get through me first.
The Cutler High School band and chorus.
All right, this is your big moment.
If you go out there and do what
you can do, you will fail...
because you're not ready
and you're not talented.
I am so nervous, I'm sweating
like a wino in a liquor store.
We're all gonna die. I have gas.
Is there a toilet~
- Mr. Moody!
- Oh, hello!
When are you gonna get the message,
to stay away from my girl?
Brian you're gay...
and that's okay, just be yourself.
Whoa!
What, too soon?
But, I~ Okay.
- You're gonna need this.
- Thank you.
All right, go get 'em, man.
Ladies and gentleman, next up,
our very own Hayden Hawks!
Okay, kids, talent does what it can,
genius does what it must.
But you do what no one else wants to do.
Go out there, and stick to your guns,
even though they're not loaded.
And remember, Mr. Pookins is
listening from heaven.
So a big meow for him.
Meow... but not too loud.
Meow.
Let's go, come on.
* Now I've heard there was a secret chord *
* That David played and pleased the Lord *
* But you don't really care for music do you *
* The ocean is heavy *
* Your current is strong *
Drowning, Drowning!
* You're pulling me deeper *
Come on.
* Been here all along *
* Remember the time I first saw you *
* I thought you'd be mine and it felt so good *
* One look in your eyes and I swear I knew *
* Of your kiss, your touch, your love *
* And I can't breathe *
* I'm struggling *
* My heart's at ease *
* 'Cause I'm drowning *
* 'Cause I'm drowning in your love *
* It seems like the love songs have got it all wrong *
* I thought I would fly *
* No flying no flying *
* And it's getting darker the further we fall *
* And I'm feeling high, So high so high *
* I took on the lies and played the fool *
* I found there's no getting over you *
* And all of this time I never knew *
* Of your kiss, your touch, your love *
* And I can't breathe *
* I'm struggling *
* My mind's at ease *
* 'Cause I'm drowning *
* 'Cause I'm drowning in your love *
* Oh don't you break my heart now *
* Don't leave me wanting more *
* Give me love, give me someone to hold *
* Messing with the stars, It indeed is very far *
* Oh no. Oh no *
* I'll never break your heart,
You're one good looking boy *
* All I need, is you forever more *
* Messing with the stars, It indeed is very far *
* Oh no. Oh no *
* And I can't breathe *
* I'm struggling *
* My heart's at ease *
* 'Cause I'm drowning *
* 'Cause I'm drowning in your love *
* Love *
* Drowning in your *
* Drowning drowning
drowning drowning *
* Drowning in your love *
* In your love *
* Messin with the stars *
* Drowning in your love *
Thank you, Mr. Pookins. Meow.
Yeah!
What are you doing here?
Dani, I know I hurt you.
I was an idiot, I'm sorry.
Can you forgive me?
Hey, take a bow!
I got my life back!
Dani, I got my life back!
That was so good!
Thanks.
Kyle? You're about as authentic
as a Mexican Prada handbag.
So this, we're done, okay?
Have a good life.
- Kyle!
- Hey!
- That was amazing, oh, my God.
- You killed it.
- Thanks, Mom.
- I cried, I cried.
That was pretty dope, dude.
I helped him so, he's my best friend.
- Wow.
- What's Dad doing here?
Um... he just wants to say goodbye.
- Oh.
- Go on.
I'm here.
Hey, killer.
Hey.
That was some performance in there, Holy cow!
Thanks.
So um...
look, I think I'm gonna hit the road.
I just think it's the best thing for everyone.
Take care of 'em.
I will.
If you ever need anything~
I know, Dad.
You okay?
How could I not be?
Aw... group selfie!
Oh, Kyle, come here.
Everyone ready?
On three. One, two, three.
Hey, man.
Hey!
Hey, Kyle.
Hey, remember my neighbor?
She knows who I am now! What?
Hi, Kyle!
Dani, I just wanted to say, whatever happens~
I'm happy I met you.
Line by line resync and more
by Dandysubs on 20180421.
Hey.
I'm, kinda happy, I met you too.
* I get so tongue-tied when I'm with you *
* Ooh baby, all I know is that... *
* I like the way I feel when I'm with you *
* Tell me  tell me  do you  do you  feel it too *
* Over it flies, our in flight, hold on tight *
* I like the way I feel when I'm with you *
* Tell me  tell me  do you  do you  feel it too *
* Over it flies, our in flight, hold on tight *
* I get so tongue-tied when I'm with you *
* Ooh baby, all I know is that... *
* I like the way I feel when I'm with you *
* Tell me  tell me  do you  do you  feel it too *
* Over it flies, our in flight, hold on tight *
Hi, sorry to bother you,
if it's not too much trouble...
would you be able to fix my, phone?
It doesn't um... work.
You want to go to Vegas?
Uh, I should call my wife.
Yeah, your phone's broken.
Ha.
Line by line resync and more
by Dandysubs on 20180421.