Okay.
Whoo!
Upsy-daisy!
Up, up, baby!
Yeah.
Come on, baby!
Here we go!
Yeah! Whoo!
Fight for
that air, baby!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Remember when your mother
used to bring us here?
Ages ago.
Every single summer
for a week.
Till...
Till Dad passed.
I'm sorry.
I didn't...
What are you
laughing at?
Remember our first skinny
dip in the midnight moon?
We couldn't find our clothes
when we came back to shore!
I was freaking out,
thinking some maniac stole them.
Of course I remember.
I was the one that had to walk home naked.
And Mom was furious!
Yeah, but we were the ones that
stayed in the freezing water
until you got back.
Hey, Mom! Yeah.
We just pulled up.
No. We haven't been
inside yet, but, uh,
everything looks fine.
Sure. I'll call you in a bit.
Just give us the time to...
I will.
Okay. Love you, too. Bye.
Mom.
Let's go get our bags.
Everything is exactly
the way I remember it.
All right.
Pick your room.
Hm.
Ohh!
This is the best room
in the house.
Oh, my God!
It's just so cozy!
Oh, I miss this smell!
Oh!
Hey.
Whoo!
I wasn't sure that's where it was going.
Yeah.
Let's see a trick.
Lory? You need anything?
I hope this isn't
too hard on you.
The pleasure of
having you here
is stronger than...
any regret.
Thanks.
This was a beautiful way
to say goodbye.
Who is it?
David.
Jim's nephew.
Caretaker's my uncle.
Hey.
Where's Jim?
He's resting.
He caught a cold.
Oh. I'll stop by
in the morning.
Anytime.
Hey, you ladies
need anything?
We're fine.
Thank you.
Tell Jim I'll be here
until Sunday.
Right.
Are you expecting
any more guests?
No. Goodnight.
Goodnight.
Mm.
Connection always sucked
around here.
Lory, stop it.
There hasn't been any crime in
this area since I can remember.
Not even a stolen CD.
Perfect opportunity to tell
you about my new novel.
You're not gonna spook us again,
are you?
Readers like
to be spooked.
Not me. Not tonight.
Mm-mmm.
All right. Tell us.
It takes place...
in the house by the lake.
You must be kidding.
It actually takes place
in this very house.
It begins...
with an 11-year-old girl...
the age when the
boundaries between reality
and the inner world
are still blurred.
Somewhere in the woods...
three mysterious men
are discussing their evil plan.
A mere story
of home invasion...
mixed with
supernatural elements.
I don't like this already.
And yes, you're supposed
to be freaked out.
That's... That's the point.
You see,
this time I went for a story without a plot.
We never figure out
why they're doing it
and what they hope
to gain from it.
Why?
Cause if we know
their motives...
we can always
convince ourselves
that it will
never happen to us.
I want to explore fear...
and masochism.
I wanna know...
How does it feel
to be confronted
with the devil?
What if you don't
believe in it?
The only thing
you have to believe...
is that there are men...
capable of horrible acts.
All right. Enough.
Yeah. That's enough.
We'll read the book.
Are you finished
with it?
Haven't written
a page yet.
Oh, I'm going
jogging at dawn
if anyone wants
to join.
Yeah. Why don't you make us
breakfast when you come back?
I can do that.
Yeah. You don't have
to do that.
Anyway, night.
Goodnight.
See you in the morning.
It's not funny.
I know you're
in there, Kay.
Come out now!
Oh, my God.
What?
Dad?
I'm so sorry, Dad.
I'm so sorry.
Daddy!
Dad!
My God.
Come on. Hey.
Come on, baby.
There you go.
All right.
You're good.
Good girl.
I got you.
Oh, thank God.
I thought I'd lost you.
Never do that again, okay?
I promise.
Dad? Dad?
No!
No, no, no, no!
Daddy?
Daddy? No! No.
Dad. Dad!
Mom! Mom!
D-Dad!
No, Dad. No. No.
Were you waiting
for someone?
Who is it?
Do it.
Was that a publicity stunt
for your book?
Are you
out of your mind?
David?
What do you want?
I don't like this.
Yeah. None of us do.
There's a hotel
ten miles from here.
Good idea.
Let's get our stuff.
Oh, my God!
- Belle! Lory!
Who did this?
Calm down.
Just grab your stuff.
We're gonna go.
Sorry.
Damn! I forgot the keys.
I don't like this.
You scared us.
All four.
Ah, shit.
Try yours.
Back inside. Now.
It's disconnected.
- Of course!
We need to calm down and
figure out what to do next.
We're gonna sleep together
upstairs tonight.
Kids'
room is the hardest to break into.
Six hours till dawn.
Whoever's doing this doesn't
know who they're fighting with.
Well said.
We'll show them.
At least
we'll hear them coming.
We will.
They only have
one way in now.
Lift up.
Drop it.
Kay and Lory,
you sleep first.
I won't be able
to close my eyes.
Neither will I.
Just try, at least.
I wonder if they get off just
knowing that we're scared.
You're optimistic.
Shh.
What? What?
Shh! Shh!
- What happened?
Shh.
Angela. What?
Nothing.
Leave!
Right now!
Fuck. Fuck.
I saw it! It's here!
K... I saw it!
The terrace!
He's hiding
behind the wall outside!
Good evening, ladies!
How bout we drop
the weapons?
Lower them.
You too, honey. Mm?
Turn around.
Put it on the ground, slowly.
What do you want?
Move the bed!
Mr. Black is anxious
to make your acquaintance.
Let's go! Move the bed!
- Move it!
Let's go!
Come on.
Open the door.
Open it!
And say hello to Mr. Black.
Girls!
See...
I'm a little underwhelmed.
And a little disappointed.
I expected you to be
a little bit more polite...
and obey
every single word I say.
I said,
"Say hello to Mr. Black!"
Hello.
No. No, no, no,
no, no.
"Hello, Mr. Black."
Hello, Mr. Black.
And you?
Look at him.
Say it!
Hello, Mr. Black.
Thank you.
It wasn't so hard, was it?
Now, I think
we could do...
a little bit better.
Don't you, huh?
Look at him.
What do you have to say?
Hello, Mr. Black.
And you? Hmm?
Huh?
Hello, Mr. Black.
Say it louder, please.
Hello, girls.
Thank you for inviting us
to your party.
Shall we start...
with... the fun?
Please.
"Please", what?
Shh. It's okay. It's okay.
Please, don't kill us.
Kill you?
Why would I want
to kill you?
Blue?
Do you want to kill
these young ladies?
Blue!
Of course not.
Red!
All we want to do
is join the party.
You see?
Hmm? Okay.
Okay.
Really?
Very well then.
Let's begin.
Take off your clothes.
Hey! Girls!
Don't make me repeat myself.
You're gonna regret this.
Sure. Sure.
Sure. Sure. Sure.
Meanwhile...
Take it off.
I politely ask.
No!
Okay.
Come here.
Stop!
Stop.
That wasn't much fun,
was it?
No. It actually wasn't.
Not at all.
Do you have music?
Downstairs.
Aw, yeah.
Music.
A little tunes.
So what are we
waiting for?
No! No! No! No! No!
Stop! No!
No! No! No! No!
Hey! Hey!
Quit it! No!
Don't you move!
Don't move a muscle!
Stop!
Stop. Stop.
That will be a lesson
to all of you.
I don't want
to kill you.
But I won't hesitate.
Do you believe me?
Yes.
Huh?
I can't hear you!
Yes!
Okay. Okay.
Downstairs.
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
Come on!
Take off your shoes.
No.
Take them off!
Let's go!
You first.
Please.
I would love to please you.
I'll probably do it, too.
Downstairs.
Give me the chairs.
Come on!
Faster!
Go.
Continue.
Don't even think about it.
I will kill her.
Don't do it.
Come on! Move!
Come on!
Belle.
There's nothing you could
have done to save me.
You died for me.
No.
I died because
I had a weak heart.
What is this?
Don't let the darkness
get to you.
It will harden your soul
and erode your emotions.
You're next.
Your turn.
For what?
Take off your clothes.
Slowly.
Sensually.
Like a stripper?
That would be nice.
Uh...
Start.
Now!
Okay!
That's right.
There we go.
Okay! Sorry!
Sorry! I... I'm sorry!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Stop!
I won't...
Stop! Stop! No!
Let her go!
And you're next.
You want me
to dance for you?
You're going to be doing it for her.
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
You're gonna...
Please!
Stop.
Watch.
Stop!
Kiss her.
Give another kiss.
Mmm.
Yes. She likes that.
Enjoy.
Stop. Stop.
You're still
helping your friend.
Still helping her.
Go on. She likes it.
You want to make her happy.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Jim?
Jim!
Oh, Jim!
Jim.
No, Jim.
No.
Oh, yeah.
No! No! No!
Now you're going down.
Where are you
going? Huh?
Huh? Where are you going?
Huh?
Where are you
going? Huh?
No!
No! No!
Huh? Where you going?
Come here! Come here!
No!
Let's get
comfortable, huh?
No!
Get 'em off!
Please!
Shh.
No, please!
Where you going?
Huh?
Come here.
We got a runner, don't we?
No! No! Stop!
Stop!
Take your shirt off! Let's go!
Come on! Someone help me!
Let's see
what you got, huh?
No! No!
No! Please! Take these off her.
Can't leave these on.
Shh.
It's okay.
Look at me. No.
Look at me.
No.
Look at me!
I love you.
Come here.
Stand. Come here.
Upsy-daisy.
There we go.
Come here.
Shh.
Look at me.
Huh? See,
it's not bad.
No.
Wanna dance?
No. No.
"Yes. Yes. Yes."
Well, okay then.
Let's dance.
No.
Come on, baby!
Whoo!
There we go!
Yeah! Whoo!
Fight for that air, baby!
Fly for Mr. Red!
Yeah, huh?
Hang, baby, hang!
There you go! There you go!
You look pretty.
Come on. Hang 'em up!
Hang 'em up!
No!
Whoo! Woo-hoo!
Baby! Whoo!
Whoo! Yeah!
No!
There you go.
How's it feel, huh?
Just wanna join the party,
baby, huh?
Shh.
No!
Huh? Come on!
Hey, yo, Red?
Hey, you see him?
No. I don't see him.
Hey, yo, Red?
The fuck?
Fuck.
Drop your gun
on the floor.
I will kill her.
Then I'll kill you.
Open your eyes.
All right.
Say goodbye
to your friend.
Don't.
Don't do it.
Too fast.
Not enough pain.
Listen to
what she says.
It's not worth it.
Thank you.
Soon enough...
you'll wish you were dead.
Kay.
No.
No!
Kay.
Kay, it's me. It's me.
It's me. No! No! Get off!
It's me. It's me.
It's me. It's me. No!
No! Ow! Ow.
They're not gonna
hurt us anymore.
We're not alone,
you know.
You will regret this.
The other two
are in the basement.
They're out there...
watching.
See this?
This is live feed.
They're coming
any moment now.
And all of...
Shh.
What the fuck?
What is
your real name?
Fuck you.
Excellent.
Mr. Fuck You,
welcome to the party.
Maybe, just maybe,
I'll spare your life if you
tell me your real name.
Don't say shit.
What about you?
Three real men.
Courageous,
strong, defiant.
I like that.
They're coming.
Oh, God!
You're going
to die slowly.
That is what
you deserve.
No one is coming
to avenge you.
That really just
sounded good.
Who is watching us?
I don't... I don't know.
I don't know.
It wasn't part of the deal.
Oh, God!
I don't believe you.
What difference
does it make?
None... to me.
What are you doing?
My God!
Come on!
Yeah! Fucking bitch!
You fucking bitch!
Fuck. Fuck.
Yeah! Die!
Come on!
Fucking bitch! Fuck.
Fuck!
I just killed you.
Belle.
What?
Are we supposed
to be nice?
We should call
the police.
No phone.
The nearest house is too far. What...
What do you suggest?
We shouldn't do what
they did to us.
We're not.
We didn't provoke
the events.
We're just
reacting to them.
We shouldn't be...
Angela, shut up.
It's not right.
They just raped you!
I got...
For what?
Fuck! I'm sorry.
So you can make
your own snuff movie?
No. No. No. No.
No. No. I'm sorry.
Do it.
Please.
No. No.
Please. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Do it.
I'm sorry. Please.
Please, please, please. Don't do it.
Don't do it. Don't do it.
No! No! No!
Please! Please!
I'm sorry.
Don't do it. Do it!
Please. Please.
Fuck! Don't do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so fucking...
Please! Please!
What? "I'm sorry",
and all is forgotten?
I can't believe it.
Nothing is forgotten!
Stop! He's dying!
Look, I'll tell you
everything I know.
Okay? Which isn't much.
I'll take not much.
My name is...
Paul Collins.
Okay?
I don't know theirs!
Look,
we met for the first time this afternoon.
It was all preplanned.
And... And he's right.
The paint, the GoPro,
it was in a mailbox.
And then you
killed old Jim?
No! No, we didn't!
We weren't even
supposed to shoot at you!
Look, all we had to do
was scare you...
play with you
as much as we wanted,
and leave you here...
drugged.
Drugged?
Yeah.
Look in my pocket.
See? You gotta believe me.
I do.
You do?
Okay, so, what are
you gonna do with us?
Eye for an eye.
No. No. No.
Fuck, no! Please!
Fuck.
Please.
Come on. Faster!
Come on. Move!
Go!
Move!
I like the way
you're thinking.
Get in.
Come on. Shh.
Come here.
There you go.
It's been a good companion
of mine.
Too bad I'll have to
trash it after this.
On the bed.
Get on the bed! No! No!
Come on!
On the bed!
For you.
No! No!
Here!
Come here!
So, Mr. Red.
Wanna do us the honors?
This has to stop!
No, you gotta stop.
Belle.
Belle. Belle.
It's me.
Please.
It's Ange.
Are you really
gonna kill me?
Wait.
Wait! Wait!
No, don't open the door!
David!
- There's no David!
What if?
You're all going crazy!
No, no.
Please, no.
Wait.
No!
Talk to me. No!
No, no, no, no, please!
What the fuck?
I'm sorry!
Hey, come on.
Okay.
Almost there.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Okay.
You didn't wanna kill us.
Is that what you said?
I hope you're enjoying
this show.
Come on!
Move it!
Stop! Please!
Please! Okay!
Okay!
So?
No. No! No!
Do it.
No more, please.
Start!
I'm sorry!
Oh, no!
Say "Hi"
to Mr. David.
"Hi."
- Hi!
"Mister."
"David"!
David!
Hi, Mr. David.
Pathetic.
Oh, God!
Shut up!
Please. Please.
Please.
Shut up!
You gotta stop.
This...
You gotta stop!
...is for Angela!
No!
No! No!
Fuck! Stop!
No! No, please!
This is for...
Listen to me carefully.
Whoever is out there...
doesn't care
about any of us.
Including you.
He would already
have saved you if he did.
You have no choice.
Let's get
out of here.
Here's the plan.
Lory, you sneak out from
the window in the basement.
Try to get help
any way you can.
Red, Kay,
and I will try to create a diversion.
Red, I'm gonna
trust you with a gun.
Remember,
we're not the enemy.
Whatever is the amount of
money they promised you,
they never intended
to pay it.
Don't you dare touch me!
Stand back!
What?
He cut Lory's head off.
No!
No, no, no.
No, it's impossible.
No.
We're gonna make it.
I promise.
He's not gonna get us.
How?
Perfect.
Okay.
There must be a reason
for whoever's doing this.
Anyone in college
we hurt?
Anyone who wants to buy
this house for cheap.
I don't know.
Kay.
I know, I know,
I know.
That was stupid.
Have you ever witnessed
pure evil?
I wanted to write
about it...
but I didn't even
know what it meant.
Not until tonight.
I did.
Don't let the darkness
get to you.
It will harden your soul
and erode your emotions.
Belle?
Belle!
You got me worried.
You were far away.
I was just thinking
of my father.
I was thinking...
These old basements,
they usually have, like,
a crawlspace
under the house.
I don't know.
No! No! No! No!
Wait. Wait. Wait.
No. We have to find
another way.
Holy shit. Okay, go.
There's something there.
Oh, my God.
We gotta go.
You were supposed
to just have fun.
It didn't work out
that way.
No, it didn't.
Who the fuck are you?
You would have killed us any...
anyway.
Maybe.
Fuck! Oh, fuck!
How does it feel, huh?
Oh, my God.
Go!
I'm trying!
I'm trying.
I'm trying. Oh, God.
Oh, he's coming!
Please!
Oh, shit.
Okay, almost there.
Hold on.
I hear him!
Okay, grab my hand!
Grab my hand!
Get off of me!
Go! Go! Go!
Grab my hand.
Come on.
Let's stay here.
Now.
Belle. Belle!
Wait!
Belle!
Shit.
How long should we play this game,
huh?
You're trapped.
How about I spare the life
of the first one to come out?
Gonna get you
either way!
Now!
I think...
I think we're okay.
What?
We made it.
We did.
We're not far away.
"And that night,
I realized that there was no such thing
as a boundary between good or evil,
black and white,
right or wrong.
All I learned
is that this world
is divided by the executed
and executioners."
Hm.
So?
What do you think?
Well,
it's not Shakespeare...
or Styron.
It's certainly not Cormac
McCarthy or J.K. Rowling.
You know...
your proofreader
did a good job.
I was right
about your first book.
It was a piece of crap,
and it sold nil.
I really thought
your career was over.
Okay.
And what do you think
about this one?
Not great either.
But...
It's gonna make
a lot of money.
And as you well know...
wealth gives you the ability
to fully experience life.
That's Henry David Thoreau.
Sure.
So... you like it?
Not a bit.
But I'd be crazy not to publish it.
Yeah.
You would say the same thing about the Bible.
Probably.
Is this all true?
Yes.
It was
in the newspapers.
How... How do you feel?
Better.
Writing was cathartic.
That's why I wrote "A true story",
not "Based on."
Yeah, no, I, uh...
I got the nuance.
So did they ever prove
Belle did it?
She has never
been the same
since her father died.
Well, I'll give you this: You got an
amazing gift for capturing details.
I will never forget
a second of it.
It's all recorded...
in here.
Do you have it?
It's all there.
Not so fast.
Everything that happened last
night is recorded in here.
I trust the second half of
the payment will be there.
Trust me.
You'll be very satisfied.
Can I ask you
why you did it?
I'll have to kill you
if I tell you.
Now that I think
about it...
I have to kill you
anyway.
♪ You can take the real estate
the cash and the best car ♪
♪ I only want the little dog
and my orange guitar ♪
♪ You made me sell my comic
books for pennies on the pound ♪
♪ But I'll still love the Silver
Age when you are in the ground ♪
♪ Oh my teenage crush on you only
makes me crush and not create ♪
♪ I could search for 1.000 years
to find another word for hate ♪
♪ I would like to illustrate
the way you made me mad ♪
♪ I have my favorite
pen in hand ♪
♪ I'm reaching for my pad ♪
♪ You are the squeezy snake ♪
♪ Release your hold on me ♪
♪ I won't make the big mistake
that freedom must be free ♪
♪ Oh my teenage crush on you only
makes me crush and not create ♪
♪ I could search for 1.000 years
to find another word for hate ♪
♪ I now express my discontent
in the form of a song ♪
♪ You made me feel so criminal
when I did nothing wrong ♪
♪ You tried to make yourself so
tall by pushing down on me ♪
♪ All you did was set me back
which truly set me free ♪
♪ Oh my teenage crush on you only
makes me crush and not create ♪
♪ I could search for 1.000 years
to find another word for hate ♪
♪ You can take the real estate
the cash and the best car ♪
♪ I only want the little dog
and my orange guitar ♪
♪ You made me sell my comic
books for pennies on the pound ♪
♪ But I'll still love the Silver
Age when you are in the ground ♪
♪ Oh my teenage
crush on you... ♪