- Hi-yah!
- Sikhya!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Any changes in vision
or hearing?
No.
What about the headaches?
Are the meds helping at all?
Look... the reason I came in
here is 'cause I remember
you saying before
that altitude was a bad idea.
It is. At high altitudes,
your symptoms will get worse.
Headaches, seizures,
loss of consciousness even.
Yeah.
If there's severe swelling
around the tumour,
it could be fatal.
Yeah.
Don't go, Jamie.
I have to go.
Excuse me.
Hi. Sorry, guys.
I'm looking
for a friend of mine.
Just wondered if you've seen her face?
Her name's Sophie.
- No. Sorry, mate.
- Sorry. I hope you find her.
Thanks.
So we have no choice
but to follow the true way.
We fail to follow this way...
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt, guys.
I'm looking for a friend.
She went missing a while back.
She may have passed
through here.
I just wanna know
if anybody's seen her.
No, I haven't seen her.
This is the place.
But I don't recognize her.
Do you know this café?
You do?
- Yes.
- Can you take me?
Yes. Ah...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's okay?
Alright. Okay.
Uh, sir, the café.
This place is so beautiful,
Jamie.
And for the first time...
...I'm really getting
to know who I am.
Who is it?
Can I help you, man?
I'm sorry, man. I didn't mean
to barge in like this.
I just wanna ask you
a couple questions.
- What's up, man?
- Take it easy.
I... I saw your tattoo.
- I just wanna know where you got 'em.
- Who is it, Jesse?
- You have to get out here right now!
- Calm down.
A friend of mine
had the same tattoo.
- Now she's missing.
- This is your problem.
Jesse, stop it.
Breathe, breathe.
She had a tattoo.
She's... she's one of them.
One of who?
Her name's Sophie.
- Do you know her?
- Yeah. You're Jamie.
How do you know my name?
Why do you know my name?
You know Sophie.
Do you know Sophie?!
What happened to her?
Her heart.
They did something to her heart.
Here. Take this!
Be careful out there.
Where do I go?
They won't let her go
so easily.
Where? Where?
Tell me where. Where do I go?
Don't tell them anything
about you.
Who do I go?
- Hang on a sec.
- Get out!
- Tell me where to go.
- Get out! Get out!
- No...
- Okay, okay.
You've gotta get her
to a hospital.
Breathe. Come on.
I need to go north.
- North?
- As far north as I can.
Hey, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop, stop. Pull in, pull in.
Why you want to talk
to this man, sir?
I can take you, sir.
Don't worry. Namaste.
Ask him
has he seen this before.
- What's he saying?
- Sacred crossing.
Sacred crossing.
What's that mean?
Uh, where two rivers
meet together.
Okay. Where? Where?
That place.
Upside. We can go together.
What do you mean,
that place upside? Where?
From that road.
Upside from this up
and that place.
Give him the...
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Thank you.
Actually, I think he's crazy.
How long, man?
- Sir...
- Huh? Can you fix it?
- No.
- What do you mean, no?
- Big problem.
- What's wrong with it?
Sir, you give me money.
I give you... Why?
So that I can fix it.
You give me money.
Here you go, okay?
Not enough, sir.
I don't have that much money
to give you. Okay?
Understand, sir.
Big problem, big money, sir.
Hey. Please...
- Fix the bike.
- Okay, okay.
Hey!!
It's so crazy.
What is?
I've seen this flower before.
I know I have.
Another sign?
I mean this same flower.
The same... cliff.
The same moment.
There's signs all around us
that have deeper meaning.
If we choose to see them.
Just like the number 23...
What does it mean?
That we're
on the right track.
Everything we've ever done
in our entire lives
has led us to this exact
moment right now.
Here,
on this cliff together.
It's a miracle.
I love you.
You know that, right?
I've always loved you.
And I always will.
Ah!
You must be lost.
Trail is back that way.
I'm told all those who seek
are welcome.
And what is it you seek?
The truth.
The truth takes time,
my friend.
Hey, whoa, whoa. Hey! Wait!
You've no idea what I've been
through to get here.
Please!
Hey. Hey. You gonna let me in?
It's freezing out here.
I have no food or water.
Hey, please! No! Wait.
Do you wear these all the time?
As you bring your awareness
back to your breath,
I leave you
with this thought today.
Present, past, future,
thou art I.
I am thou, as one.
Wait here.
You certainly don't take no
for an answer.
- I'm Jamie.
- I'm Chandra.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry about the wait,
but we do have to separate
the casual seekers from the
serious, you understand.
- I do. Truth takes time.
- Hmm.
You're a quick learner.
Come, I'll show you around.
Please.
All the work you see here,
they're all forms of meditation.
Connect with them and you connect
with your higher purpose.
We are striving to remain
in balance with our surroundings
in everything we do.
Nitin?
Morning.
This is Jamie.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
brother.
You, too.
- Where you from?
- California.
- I like this guy already.
- You?
Cleveland, but you know, we all start
and end in the same place, right?
- Yeah.
- Nitin,
when you're finished here,
will you show Jamie to his room?
Absolutely.
Hope you don't mind
getting your hands dirty.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Nitin helps all the new
arrivals the get situated.
And you don't use any water
from the river?
Oh, absolutely not.
The river is sacred to us.
- Uh-huh.
- People have been coming
to this mountain
for thousands of years,
because it is believed
that the crossing of two rivers
is a sacred place,
where your soul can transcend
to a higher realm.
There are many other realms
of consciousness around us
and this mountain is a doorway
to help you access them.
What brings you here?
How did you know about us?
A friend.
Ah... Who?
Just somebody I met. In town.
On my travels.
We're, uh, extremely
out of the way and hard to find,
so I like to know...
No, I get it, you know.
Wouldn't want the secret
to get out. Would we?
Jamie, we do some very hard
work here, inside and out.
And just because you made it
through that gate
doesn't mean you belong here.
Anyway, that's not why
you're here, is it?
You're here for him, aren't you?
Don't worry.
You'll meet him soon enough.
Make yourself at home.
Headaches...
Seizures...
- Argh...
- Loss of consciousness...
Ah!
Jamie.
- Jamie...
- Oh...
Jamie.
Jamie!
- You okay?
- What time is it?
It's time to roll. Come on.
Once we get down there,
just remember to be silent.
Just do what I do.
I know it's your first day.
Try to be on time next time.
Tough love, bro.
Comes from a good place,
though, you know?
She's been through more
than you can imagine.
So what made you become
a seeker?
Something have to make me?
Come on, man. People come
here for two reasons.
They're either running
from something,
or they're running towards it.
Which one are you?
I've been running for years,
man.
I used to try
to turn one dollar into two.
Almost gave myself
a heart attack.
I didn't know how much I was
suffering until it almost killed me.
This place is the real deal,
you know?
You don't really see it until you
start being honest with yourself.
Must be tough,
training the new recruits.
Not really. Just you.
Maybe you knew
a friend of mine.
She passed through here
a while back.
- She's American.
- Well... a lot of people pass through here.
Her name's Sophie.
Pretty name.
Ah, Nitin!
Oh, shoot, I'm not ready yet.
Alright, come on.
Uh, Gayatri, this is Jamie,
Jamie, Gayatri. She'll take you.
- So nice to meet you Jamie.
- And you.
Follow me.
Who are all these people?
They're from surrounding
villages.
They've come to receive
Guruji's blessings.
- He's coming.
- Guruji!
Oh!
Guruji.
What's he doing?
He helps people
transcend their pain.
It's amazing, isn't it?
And if it weren't for Guruji,
I'd be dead.
What?
Six years ago, I was diagnosed
with stage-four ovarian cancer.
Doctors told me
I had three months to live.
So I made my way up here and...
...he cured me.
- You have cancer?
- Yes.
He cured you of cancer?
You don't believe me.
I think you believe it.
Belief is all we have.
- Hey... Sorry.
- Uh, no, no, no.
Hi, Guru. I'm Jamie.
I just wanted to ask you...
I have been waiting so long
for you, my friend.
Bring her to the library.
Chandra!
- What happened?
- Motorcycle accident.
- One hour ago.
- Take her to the library.
- Chandra, what can I do?
- Just nothing right now.
Hey. Is she okay?
Jamie! Jamie...
Jamie?
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Jamie.
Something the matter?
Mountains, uh...
Just the altitude, I guess.
Mm.
It can take some time
to adjust here.
Is she okay?
The little girl?
Yes.
Thankfully.
What did the old man do?
Guruji.
I'm sorry.
What did Guruji do?
Performed a miracle.
Miracles.
Give them a lot more credit
than they deserve.
Miracles are a matter
of perspective.
To some,
your cellphone's a miracle.
Yeah, but it's explained.
The science behind that
is rational.
Hmm. Enlighten me.
A phone uses electromagnetic waves to
send your voice all around the world.
Sending your voice
through invisible waves
around the world.
Sounds rational?
So you're telling me
he uses invisible energy?
I'm telling you that miracles
aren't contrary to science.
What else could be
right in front of us,
within us,
that we just don't know yet
how to use.
Hmm?
Come.
I'm gonna show you something
you might find hard to believe.
Please, keep an open mind.
What is this?
The story of this mountain.
Thousands of years ago,
there was a temple here,
and after meditating
for many years in this cave,
this monk...
became enlightened
and shared his wisdom
with the surrounding villagers.
One day...
soldiers from the north came...
and seized the temple
and... destroyed everything.
Then there was a period of
great suffering and oppression.
Until...
...this young prince
and princess bore a child.
This child...
possessed great power within.
And after meditating
for many years in this cave,
he, too, became enlightened.
The monk...
and the child...
are believed to be forms
of an enlightened being,
from another realm,
born into the human world
to end the suffering
of all sentient beings.
This mountain...
is that gateway...
to that realm.
This princess
is the caretaker...
who helps him transition...
in and out of this world.
And with her help...
...he has been reincarnating
for thousands of years.
Our Guruji.
We aren't the first ones
to realize
that there is something
so beautiful happening here.
Things I never thought
could be possible.
You just have to choose
to see them.
This place is so beautiful,
Jamie.
There are things
happening here
I never thought
could be possible.
I just had to choose
to see them.
And for the first time...
...I'm really getting to know
who I am.
I hope you get to know who
you really are too, Jamie.
I'm so sorry
we didn't work out.
At least in this life.
Maybe we'll meet
in the next one.
Take care of yourself, Jamie.
Hey.
- Why'd you lie to me?
- What the hell are you talking about?
You knew Sophie.
She passed through here.
Told you I don't know
who she was...
Don't lie to me.
You train all the new recruits.
I know you knew her.
Okay. Take your hands off me.
I got you.
I have to find her.
She left because of me.
You've no idea
how much this means to me.
Is there a problem here?
- No. We were just...
- It was my fault.
I was at the water pump and,
um,
Nitin spooked me by accident.
It's fast reflexes.
- Nitin?
- It's fine.
Meet me at the riverbank
at dawn; bring your boots.
Nice to see you're on time.
Hey.
Where we going?
You wanted to know
what happened to Sophie, right?
Here.
Found this spot a week ago.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Does anyone else know
about this?
No.
How long was she here?
Three months. She disappeared
about two weeks ago.
She and the Guruji
were very close.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm just telling you
what I heard.
They spent a lot of time
together,
made a lot of people jealous,
especially Chandra.
What happened?
I honestly don't know.
The last couple of times
I saw her, she wasn't herself.
Look, it's not really my place, but
instead of looking for Sophie,
maybe you should find out
what she was looking for.
I better get back
before Chandra notices I'm gone.
Why are you helping me?
It's the right thing to do.
She seemed very special.
I hope you find her.
I have something for you.
What is it?
Two souls...
You're bound to each other...
for all eternity.
So one's for you
and one's for me,
and as long as we wear them...
we'll always be connected.
D'you make this?
Yeah.
Getting better.
Shut up.
Do you like it?
It's beautiful.
I love it.
I wanted to make something for us.
Kind of representing...
where we've been
and where we are
and where we're going.
Where we going?
I don't know.
Somewhere special.
I hope.
Jamie, where have you been?
- For a walk.
- Have you seen Nitin?
What happened?
You can't just disappear
like that.
Yeah, I know. I know.
No, you don't know
what she's capable of.
What do you mean?
Just focus
on your own progress, okay?
That's where
you'll find answers.
Nitin?
Nitin left.
What do you mean?
Left the Ashram?
When you experience pain,
you are functioning
at conscious level.
But when you transcend pain...
...you experience the true
nature of consciousness.
Confront the darkness
within you...
and you will see the light.
Consciousness
is not only within us.
It's all around us.
...your consciousness...
...with that of the universe.
We're bound to each other.
You are making progress.
But your journey
is far from over.
We are running out of time.
You still carry too much fear.
You must learn to let it go.
Oh, Guruji.
You must heal him.
Are you sure?
Be of pure intent.
Oh, no!
No, please. Let me try again.
Give.
We are finished here.
Please, Guruji...
There is still time.
Time is not the issue.
It's your intention.
You will never be
the caretaker.
You can send the boy in.
You found my spot.
It's beautiful.
It helps me remember
why I'm here.
What do you want?
I just wanted
to say thank you.
I'm starting to understand...
what it is you do here.
Guruji knew this too.
He's asked to see you.
You can go up now.
Jamie, you tell me
what happens up there.
Hello?
May I offer you some tea?
No, thanks.
I need to tell you something
very important.
Are you listening to me?
Yeah.
A cup of tea
is always a good idea.
Come. Sit down.
Do you know why you are here?
To drink tea?
You are here
because you know something.
Not on conscious level,
but deep down,
you always knew it.
And now,
finally you have come here
to find the truth.
What do I know?
That there is
a universal consciousness
that connects us all.
Is there?
Of course there is.
Your soul.
- What are you doing?
- You have a secret here,
which is causing you
great suffering.
Guruji, I didn't come here
to find the truth.
I came here to find a friend.
I know.
But I'm talking
about what is in your brain.
You must not carry this weight
alone.
- It will destroy...
- Look...
I don't know what you think
you know... but I'm fine.
There's no secret.
You can lie to others,
but you can never lie
to yourself.
You know what?
Fine. Everybody else needs
your approval round here.
I sure as hell don't.
You have a gift.
You can experience...
the universal consciousness...
that surrounds us.
You can feel the beat
of all living things.
There are many things
within you.
Only you can choose
to see them.
What was that?
We are done for today.
Jamie?
What are you doing here?
- What's in the bag?
- Nothing.
- Gayatri?
Stop!
Gimme the bag!
No!
- What is this?
- Just herbs.
- Are you drugging us?
- What?!
- No!
- Is that what this is?
Is that why I'm seeing all this shit?
Are you drugging us?!
No! It's just medicine!
It's medicine.
- For what?!
- I'm just taking it to Guruji.
What's wrong with him?
He's dying.
What do you mean, he's dying?
He's dying. Guruji's dying,
and we can't tell anybody.
People here have devoted their lives
to him, and if they find out,
can you imagine
what will happen?
Gayatri...
You knew Sophie.
I know you did.
What did she say?
If you know something,
you have to tell me.
Is she alive?
- Is she alive?
- I have to go.
- No. Please.
- Yes. I have to go.
No one talks to me.
You have to tell me.
She's not the only reason
you're here.
Please don't follow me.
Please.
Gayatri...
One, two, three.
- Two. Pull it.
- Pull!
Slowly. Easy, easy...
What?!
You do this every time.
Got it?
- Yeah.
- Pull! Pull!
- One more, one more...
- That's it. Pull!
Wait, it's stuck.
Hold on, guys!
It's stuck. Hold on.
I can get it out.
Okay? Hold on.
Hold on, guys.
Almost got it, almost got it.
Yeah! Hold on!
Come on! Only got two seconds,
guys, two seconds.
- Watch out!!
- Argh!
- - No!
- Ah!!!
- It's just a number!
- So the fact that the day we met,
my birthday and your promotion all
happened on the 23rd means nothing.
It's just a coincidence.
There's no higher meaning.
It means something to me!
Why won't you just let me have...
Because it's bullshit!
It's a fucking lie!
I can't do this anymore.
I'm not asking you
to do anything.
I mean us.
This isn't working.
So what are you saying?
We're different people.
We want different things.
You want kids...
Is that what this is about?
I told you, I'm okay waiting.
No. It's not just that.
It's...
Then what is it?
Whatever it is,
we can get through it.
- No, we can't.
- Of course we can.
Because we love each other and
that's what being in love means.
It means being there
for each other.
I don't love you anymore!
Okay?
So the sooner you get that
through your head, the better.
- You don't mean that.
- Yeah, I do.
It's over.
Did you stop that beam?
Did you know you could do that?
Did the Guruji teach you
something, huh?
Jamie, did he share a secret
with you?
Jamie...
he shared that secret
with Sophie as well.
Yeah.
She was here.
And Jamie...
...the realities...
that you're beginning
to experience,
Sophie experienced them too.
It was too much for her,
so she ran away.
I figured she ran back to you.
Then you come here
looking for her.
I can tell you had hurt her.
Why would you have
thrown her away?
Why?
I'm dying.
I have a brain tumour.
And I don't have long.
And I never told her.
Maybe Sophie
came into your life...
...just to lead you here.
Don't you see?
You have a gift.
We're meant to do great things
together.
Guruji doesn't have
much time left.
No! No! No!
No, no, no! No! No.
I'm sure.
I'm sure...
Jamie?
Jamie!
Jamie...
Jamie, you cannot go up there
like this!
- Did you know?
- Know what? What's the matter?
- Nitin.
- Nitin what? What happened? What?
Did you kill him?
Don't lie to me.
- Nitin...
- 'Cause he was helping me?
No. I... I...
Jamie, please. Please don't
bring this up to him!
Get up.
Wake up!
You knew.
You knew this whole time.
Oh, Guruji, I'm so sorry.
I tried to stop him.
And you want...
Nitin. Nothing goes on here
without your knowledge!
Are you accusing Guruji
of having something to do...
- I'm not talking to you!
- Don't you yell in here, Jamie.
- Don't you raise your voice.
- Chandra, please leave us.
- Guruji is in no condition...
- Chandra!
Do as I say.
Come.
- Sit down.
- No.
Somebody's dead.
He devoted his life to you
and you don't even care.
Of course I care.
She thinks she's protecting me,
but her pain is blinding her.
I have a fear...
what will happen after I go.
Guruji.
I need to know.
If I keep digging out there, am I
gonna find Sophie's body, as well?
Please.
I need to know.
I'm sorry.
I was waiting
until you were ready.
There is something you must see.
What is this place?
A doorway.
Sophie.
Sophie!
Sophie. Sophie, hey. Hey, babe.
Soph. Soph?
Sophie.
Hey, come here. It's me.
I found you. I found you.
Sophie?
Sop...
Aren't those keeping you alive?
It's for keeping her alive.
Hey, baby. Hey, wake up.
Soph, wake up.
- Why won't she wake up?
- She is in a state...
of deep meditation.
So deep...
that her soul has left her body
and cannot find
its way back in.
- Is she in a coma?
- No.
She is in a realm
between life and death.
That's bullshit.
Wake up, Soph!
Gently. Gently!
We have to get her
to a hospital!
If you remove her from here,
she will die!
You did this.
You did this and you left her
lying here for weeks.
I was trying to help her...
but she carried too much pain.
I took her to the other realm
so she could transcend it.
But she was trapped there.
It's my fault.
How can I believe
anything you say?
Believing... is your choice.
What do you mean, trapped?
Sophie!
Jamie.
Soph.
You were right...
this whole time.
You were right.
Guruji, we gotta go back.
Guruji.
No. No, no, no, no, no!
No!
Come.
There's much to be done.
We will miss our Guruji.
But this is not his end,
only his new beginning.
And today we will celebrate...
the sending of his spirit
to the next realm,
so he may be born again
and return to us.
Hey. Come on, okay?
Where was she
when you saw her?
- She was on a cliff.
- Jamie, when our soul crosses
into the other realm,
we must confront
our darkest moment.
And overcome it
in order to come back.
Does this cliff
mean something to you?
Yeah.
But if Guruji couldn't save her,
how can I?
Sacred crossing.
The sacred crossing
provides a path for the
enlightened one to return.
It's not the crossing of rivers.
It's the crossing of souls.
Sophie always said
we were soulmates.
I didn't believe her.
If you are connected
to each other beyond this life,
then maybe you share
your darkest moment.
Then we have to transcend it
together.
Jamie... whatever happens...
just be honest with yourself.
You're getting a second chance.
Chandra?
- Where is he?
- Wait. No, no, no!
He needs me right now!
He can't be in there!
I am the caretaker, not you!
Not you!
Sophie's not...
Sophie's... inside?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Come home with me.
Soph, you have to come
with me now.
If you don't, I'm not sure
you're ever gonna be able
- to come back.
- It's too late. It's over.
- Doesn't have to be. Okay?
- Yes, it does.
This is something I have to do
on my own.
I have to find it within me
to let you go.
- What if we're not supposed to let each other go?
- Don't.
- What if we're supposed to do this together?
- We're not together!
- Yeah, we are.
- No, we're not! You left.
You completely disappeared.
We had something special,
but you threw it away.
And you have no idea
how much that hurt me.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
You know what? I'm sorry too.
I thought we were gonna be
together forever,
but... I was wrong.
No, Soph.
You were right.
You and I are always together.
And we always will be.
Jamie...
How could I ever trust you
again?
What are you doing?
You and I were meant
to bring Guruji back,
but you betrayed me
just like everyone else.
You have to help me...
bring Sophie back.
We don't need her.
We never did.
It's a shame
she'll never know the truth.
You're living on borrowed time.
What happened?
I need to tell you something.
I'm dying.
I was diagnosed
with a brain tumour.
And they can't save me.
That's why I left.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want
to put you through it.
But the truth is...
I was scared you'd leave me.
You didn't even give me
a chance.
I know.
And not a day goes by
I don't regret it.
You're the best thing
that ever happened to me.
I don't expect you to come back.
You just deserve
to know the truth.
I'm so sorry.
I hope you can forgive me.
I'll take care of Sophie, too.
Ah!! Ah!
Jamie!
Jamie?
Come back to me.
Jamie...
please come back.
Please come back, Jamie.
I forgive you.
I forgive you, Jamie.
Please...
Oh, Jamie.
Jamie!
Don't let me go.
I won't.
Yeah.
And?
What does that mean?
You got the bottle?
Yeah.
It was Dr. Michaels.
Good news?
Hey.
Whatever happens,
we get through it together.
All of us.
Tumour's gone.
- What?
- I'm in the clear.
- Completely?
- Mm-hmm.
Jamie... that's amazing!
You hear that?
Daddy's gonna be okay.
Shhh...
Ah, shhh...
It's a miracle.
What?
Subtitles by explosiveskull