Original Sub: GoldenBeard
Edited by- [Abs3nt-_-mind3D]
[Reporter] As nuclear fallout
over the Pacific
continues to fuel sandstorms
over southern California,
the last remaining pockets of residents
were evacuated by the National Guard.
The federal government,
already struggling to keep up
with flash floods
in Long Beach and Venice,
has declared Los Angeles uninhabitable.
[woman] The base is four square miles,
with a working population of 3,000 people.
Got 20,000 acres of training fields.
We even have a supermarket,
a cinema, and a mall.
All under NATO command?
Joint initiative
with the Defense Science Office,
and the British Department
of Science and Technology, of course.
To be sure, Lieutenant,
we're highly classified.
Communication with the outside world
will be limited.
No different at Edwards or Dryden, sir.
[woman] This whole street
is part of the new expansion.
A total new-build.
I'm excited to show you.
[door beeps open]
Welcome.
There's two bedrooms upstairs.
The lights are motion-activated.
There's three bathrooms, a media room,
and an automated kitchen.
Hey, don't listen to Jim.
I mean, Colonel Peterson.
If you want to call friends and family,
feel free. We trust you.
Look, if you need anything, call me.
Day or night.
Thank you, Freya.
[boy] Mom, come look!
- Come on.
- Check this, hon.
[laughs]
[smooches]
Which one are you going to?
You can't see it. You need a telescope.
But it's out there.
And you'll be there too someday.
Down, down, down.
- [grunts]
- [laughs]
Are you ready? Only got the one.
- Yeah.
- Careful.
[man speaking softly, indistinctly]
[boy] Okay.
[doorbell rings]
- Hi, Abigail. How was your trip?
- Professor Collingwood.
It is so good to see you.
You don't know how happy I was
to throw your Dryden test results
into NASA's face.
Absolutely incredible.
It's just an honor
to have been selected, sir.
I've been teaching the past years,
didn't think I still had it.
Don't call me "sir." I don't have a rank.
I'm just not gonna let you down.
I know how much this means to you, Rick.
But... pioneering isn't without its risks.
Yeah, well, first one through the wall
always gets a little bloody.
He's gonna get sick, isn't he?
Temporarily.
He'll need committed aftercare.
He won't seem himself at times.
Rick crossed the Syrian desert
injured and alone
without food or water for three days.
Well, this will make that look
like a walk in the park.
But we'll get through it.
Dr. Janssen, I admire your courage.
Rick wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for you.
I want to tell you that I'm...
I'm grateful.
You don't have to charm me, Professor.
I've studied your work.
I know what we're doing.
It's bigger than all of us.
Yes, yes, yes. I know that, but it's...
It's the concessions you made.
The medical career.
The nights of worry.
It's a small price to pay
for my son's future.
No one attempts the impossible
without belief in something greater
than themselves.
Even if that something is a someone.
Rick didn't cross the desert alone.
[engine turns over]
[Collingwood] Our population
has grown out of control.
Our environment is in decay.
Our resources have been depleted.
Wars have ravaged our planet.
We are fighting over the scraps
of what remains.
In ten years, half the planet
will be uninhabitable.
In 15 years, half the world's population
will have starved to death.
Time is running out.
We've outgrown our home.
Our children will witness the end of days.
But there is one place that gives us hope.
Titan.
The largest moon of Saturn.
The only other place in our solar system
with an atmosphere.
A primordial ecosystem, just like Earth,
seconds before life was born.
Liquid methane raining
into huge oceans and lakes
that we can't swim in,
and an atmosphere rich in nitrogen
that we can't breathe.
Too cold to exist in.
Fiercely hostile to life as we know it.
Beyond the reach of space science,
but not modern genetics.
No longer trying
to reshape planets in our image...
but evolving humanity into the stars.
Imagine, with a few minor enhancements,
you could breathe the air,
swim in the waters,
and survive the cold.
What if Titan...
could become our home?
Dr. Hernandez,
I was waiting for you to object.
I still don't understand how our bodies
won't reject the treatment.
Clinical trials were successful,
signed off by NATO's
Science and Technology Office.
- You are talking forced evolution?
- I'm talking survival of the species.
HPA-axis reprogramming.
Methane lipid bilayer injections.
G-force training under water?
There are no guarantees, Dr. Hernandez.
Some people won't take to the drugs.
Some people will break
during the training.
Most of you will fail and be sent home.
How many of us will die?
Twenty bucks says Iker goes first.
Can you read?
What?
I said can you read, idiot?
Because if you could,
you'd see that this book
is just a bunch of health warnings.
- Why are you here?
- I'm just pointing out...
You're pointing out nothing.
He's talking about the end of the Earth.
[sighs] You got kids?
No.
Shut the fuck up or get the fuck out.
Please. Go on, Professor.
I was sent 5,000 personnel files
from 16 NATO countries.
I chose you, because in your past,
each of you has shown an ability
to survive the harshest of conditions.
Each of you is here,
because you understand the dire necessity
of finding a new home for the human race.
Maybe you're mad,
ambitious, adventurous.
But each of you has a rare willingness
to put yourselves on the line
for the sake of others.
My hope is, when we're finished,
all of you will be able to stand on Titan,
take a deep breath,
and swim in its waters.
Maybe soar through its skies.
You will become enhanced humans.
Super men.
Able to live on another world.
You'll become you...
but better.
The slingshot around Jupiter
is 50-50 at best.
Not if you use a Hohmann Transfer.
All right, give me two minutes, guys.
You'd need propulsion of more
than 15 kilometers a second for that.
It's never been done.
Let's just worry about down here
before up there.
Have you ever flown
on an Orion-class manned space explorer?
- No, I haven't.
- I bet you're the first one to crash one.
- Better make sure you're strapped in.
- I'm riding with the astronauts!
You're mad!
It tracks your heart rate, blood pressure,
sodium levels, other vitals.
A lot of monitoring from now on.
I hope you're not squeamish.
I'll be giving you over 300 shots
in the next few weeks.
With what?
Amino acid solutions, enzyme inhibitors,
nucleic acid polymers.
The long, steady road of training
yourselves to burn nitrogen for energy.
Open. And use less oxygen.
- You're turning me into a sherpa?
- [laughs]
Well, you'll never black out
at high altitudes ever again.
What we call "air"
is more than 75% nitrogen.
Oxygen only constitutes 20%.
But where you're going,
the nitrogen ratio of air is 90%,
oxygen less than five.
So we don't need to reinvent the wheel.
Just go the extra 15.
- Good morning.
- Hi there.
Are we gonna see you on Saturday?
Oh, well, I have to see
how Zane's feeling, darling,
but I'm sure we'll make it.
[insects chirping]
Mom!
Look at this! What is that?
A fighting car.
All right.
["You Need A Little Something Extra"
by William Bell plays]
♪ You can be a beauty queen
And make believe, my baby ♪
Hey. What...
♪ You can be a poor man's dream
And make believe, my baby ♪
How did you two meet each other?
European Space Agency.
- What about you and Rick?
- College.
- Now, who wanted a tequila?
- Yes, please!
Thank you.
This is the last time some of us
will get to drink for a while.
[all groaning]
[laughter]
- [Tally] Again?
- No.
- [Tally] Yes.
- You and me Abi, together.
- Okay.
[female guest] Whoa!
I was in the KSK long enough
to know how these things work.
They're spending so much money
to get us there, they have plans.
They don't want us to come back.
[exhales]
That's your PTSD talking.
We'll only be gone two years.
I'm on a one-way ticket. Gone.
There is nothing left on this planet
but misery.
Let's see if we make it that far.
You know, Hernandez, Janssen was right.
Why the hell did you say yes?
I'd have felt guilty if I hadn't.
Here. You'll feel guilty
if you let that burn.
["Let's Dance" plays]
♪ Hey, baby, won't you take a chance? ♪
♪ Say that you'll let me have this dance ♪
♪ Well, let's dance ♪
♪ We'll do the twist, the stomp
The mashed potato too ♪
♪ Any old dance that you wanna do ♪
♪ Well, let's dance ♪
♪ Hey, baby, won't you thrill me so? ♪
♪ Hold me tight, never let me go ♪
♪ Well, let's dance ♪
[music fades]
[toilet flushes]
[Rick] Careful.
[Abi groans]
How much have you had to drink?
You know what?
It's none of your business.
[laughs] I can absolutely handle
my alcohol.
I see that. It's obvious.
I love you.
Come on. Be careful.
[Rick coughing]
I just...
- [coughing]
- Rick?
- I can't catch my breath.
[continues coughing]
- [gasps]
- You're burning up. Okay.
I got you. Come on. All right. Let's go.
Can you get up with me? All right.
[gasping]
It's okay.
- Come on up. Come on up.
- [groans]
Oh, my head.
One more. Last one. It's the last one.
You all right?
Yeah. [groans]
[exhales]
I never thought
I'd see something like this.
What's their oxygenation?
Four percent.
Vitals are strong.
[device beeps steadily]
[gasps]
[cheers and applause]
No, no, no! Don't do anything!
- [gasps]
- [applause]
Whoa!
Oh!
[laughs]
[screams]
[Rick] "Saturn's largest moon is
the second largest in the solar system.
Larger than Mercury.
Its rivers carve valleys into soil
rich in ammonia and nitrogen.
Nitrogen, which can be used
to generate breathable oxygen,
or to produce fertilizer
for growing food, just like on Earth."
Will I really go there with you one day?
Yeah, you will.
We'll go up there together.
Did you know Saturn's rings
are made of ice?
Did you know that there is a storm
four times the size of Earth
raging for 50 years on Saturn?
- Yeah. Did you know...?
- Did you know...?
That's a nice try. Get some sleep.
This would have blown Grandpa's mind.
Yeah. Yeah, it sure would have.
Can you put my stars on, please?
- [robotic voice] Good night, earthling.
- Good night, Dad.
[splash]
Is he sleeping?
Yeah.
You wanna come in?
You know, he mentioned my old man.
He does that from time to time.
I have a feeling
he's up there watching us.
Mmm.
He would be so proud of you.
He wouldn't have thought
I would have got this far.
You...
are gonna be the first man on Titan.
Hey. Look at me.
I believe in you.
You've given me hope.
Rick... Stop.
What is it?
What? What is it?
What's wrong?
Hey, I love you.
- [steady breathing]
- [machine beeping]
You little rascals.
All right. Okay.
Are you going to get dressed for the day?
- This is for you.
- Come on. Let's go play.
Barely dry.
I know.
Abi, can I ask you a personal question?
Sure.
Do you get scared?
Yeah, I get scared.
Does Rick know? Yeah, Rick knows.
Do you pray?
I guess I don't pray as much as I should.
I pray.
I didn't wanna come here.
He's a corporal
in the United States Marines,
about to make sergeant.
Could have chosen his own station.
He ain't got no business in space,
but I can't tell him that.
Why not?
'Cause he'll get mad, call me chicken.
Zane's here 'cause he has
a very important job to do.
He's giving us a chance.
And you're here because you love him.
And you want your kids to grow up
knowing that their father was a hero.
Dad!
[laughing]
[video game beeps]
[Rick and son laughing]
[shivers]
[air conditioning powers down]
What are you doing?
I was just hot.
Why didn't you wake me up?
There's no point us both suffering.
Want me to make you
an ice bath or something?
It's okay.
I'm okay.
- Go on.
- I don't wanna put my hands in there.
Go on. I wanna show you something.
[laughs]
Jeez!
It's so cold!
What? Now what?
I don't feel any cold.
[Rick] Let me show you something.
It's beautiful.
It's a shame we can't save it.
Doctor, be careful in there.
It's 20% liquid methane.
You okay?
Cold. Hurts.
Then get out.
No.
Mind over matter.
Hey, you guys losing any hair?
I don't think so.
I'm not losing any hair.
Still looking handsome.
I lost some hair.
Like, two days ago.
- Here.
- Let me see.
Oh, shit. A souvenir for you.
He's got something.
[screaming]
- Get up, get up, get up!
- What happened?
We were talking
and she started convulsing.
- How long?
- Thirty seconds.
- [screams]
- Stop! Get back!
Okay, keep her still. Hold her.
Get the case!
Hey!
[Hernandez speaking Spanish]
Stay with us. Come on, come on.
[Hernandez] Right now we're losing her!
[gasps]
No, no, no, no, no.
The question is: who's next?
They only need one or two
to prove the program.
One or two?
No, we're going up there together...
as a team.
I heard him say exactly the opposite.
No, he said we're becoming titans,
and we're going to Titan.
And that's the mission.
The program is the mission.
Nobody said we was gonna die.
We all knew the risks.
[door opens, closes]
- You know we're not supposed to drink.
- Yeah, that was before.
Where were you stationed?
Syria.
[glasses clink]
Yeah, me too.
You got family back home?
She was this bad-ass cadet
I used to see in the mess hall.
I fell hopelessly in love with her.
I used to write her poetry.
I had the worst lyrics.
Then one day when the war started,
they stationed her at Diego Garcia,
and, um, she left.
So what did you do?
Um...
I went and I found her.
Now he wants to start a family.
But they changed the law,
so it doesn't matter now.
We can't have any kids without a permit,
and we can't get one here, so...
Rayenne, give us a hand, will you, love?
He thinks if I go and come back,
I'll have got it out of my system.
Be the good wife.
I wouldn't have made it this far
without him.
Well...
Yeah.
That's Rick.
[mouthing] Are you okay?
No, no fucking way!
[yells]
No, back off!
[grunting]
- [grunting]
- No way!
- Calm down.
- No!
Zane, calm down! That's an order!
[screams]
- Hey...
- We're here. We're here.
- We got you.
- [groans]
Let him go. Let him go.
Look at me.
You're with us.
You'll...
make it.
[Freya] Good. 121 over 96.
The spleen seems to be having trouble
processing the treatment,
putting a burden on the kidneys.
Is that what killed Dr. Ramos?
Was it a known risk?
Yes and no.
Well, Captain Ramos
was predisposed to kidney stones,
which caused the complication.
I was there.
That wasn't the kidney stones.
Pills.
May I?
The pills are Flunarizine,
a calcium-channel blocker.
This is potassium citrate.
- Helps flush the kidneys.
- Potassium citrate's taken orally.
But it's in magnesium sulfate
so it bypasses the gastric tract.
- How much magnesium?
- Ten grams.
That's high.
I'd like to speak
with Professor Collingwood.
Well, he's not here, so...
as soon as he's free,
I'll get him to come see you.
All right.
[retching]
I think that's it.
[panting]
Mind over matter.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
[Collingwood] Titan receives
much less light than Earth.
By multiplying the rod cells
by up to eight times,
we change the aperture of the eye...
to more closely resemble
those of a feline.
Allowing you to see through the darkness.
[exhales]
- Peanut butter?
- Yeah. Jelly?
Yeah.
[Rick breathing heavily]
[Rick continues breathing heavily]
- [Abi] Baby?
- [Rick] Yeah.
[grunts]
[Abi] Rick?!
Help!
- I need somebody here right now!
- What happened?
He started rubbing his eyes.
He was complaining of pain.
Lieutenant, let me see your eyes. Okay.
Flush his eyes. Prep him.
Get him into surgery now.
No, Mrs. Janssen, you have to stay here.
When we know something, we'll tell you.
- What did you do?
- Abi, please.
He is blind!
- That's only temporary.
- You did not tell me everything.
Now, look. You're tired. Go home,
get some rest. Freya will take care...
There are cameras in our house.
I know you've been watching us.
That was the Pentagon's idea.
It was for your security and ours.
I argued against it at the time.
If you don't like it, I'll get rid of them.
There is something alive inside of him.
Something that your fucking book
doesn't talk about.
He is changing.
I need to keep this under control.
Rick needs me. Lucas needs you.
Go home. We'll talk about this later.
[sirens wailing] [indistinct shouting]
[sirens continue wailing]
[indistinct chatter]
[shouting]
- Get back.
- I know them.
[speaking Spanish]
[shouting]
[gunshots]
[helicopter whirring overhead]
[vehicle approaches]
Colonel Solano.
Where is he?
[indistinct chatter in distance]
With respect, Dr. Blake, you had your shot
at funding us and you blew it.
Blew it? Are you nuts?
We want to shut you down.
Anything now comes from envy
and resentment and is without merit.
What has no merit is your knee-jerk
program based on unproven science,
and your irrational ideas about forced evolution.
You're so desperate to prove it, you won't admit you dove blindly...
There's nothing blind here.
Either catch up, or stop holding me back.
This isn't space research.
It's criminal, and morally repugnant.
They're becoming violent, losing control.
The last people to try this
were the Nazis.
- You are lying to them.
- Nobody gives a shit!
This is NATO's call.
NASA's just advising.
Let's make it clear.
I want this off my base.
Well, then you better call
Field Marshall Howard at NATO
or the Secretary of Defense
at the Pentagon
because they own your base.
You need to look over Ramos's files.
I have. It's a miracle we got this far.
We have to stop and assess what we've got.
This wasn't in the trials.
What we've got is a fucking roller coaster
of reputation and money.
It'll work...
because it has to.
What if they all die?
Okay.
Off you go.
[grunts]
Your sight will come back in 24 hours.
You will regain your vision
and much, much more.
But we miscalculated your brain's ability
to process your enhanced senses.
Zane's brain just simply overloaded.
- How do you fix it?
- It's surgery.
That's not gonna happen.
- Without it, Rick's brain will...
- Tell me the truth!
- Stop it.
- No! No!
I won't sit here,
and watch him turn my husband
into a fucking animal!
We are in uncharted waters, Abigail.
What are we actually doing here?
During the first treatment,
we injected the subjects with an enzyme
that could alter human DNA.
- You mean animal DNA?
- Well...
He's giving you a name. Do you know that?
Calling them Homo Titaniens, right?
It's a new species of man, yes.
[Abi] If these enzymes
are doing the work,
how can you be sure
that his body doesn't just mutate
the eyes out altogether?
Or develop membranes like a reptile?
How can you possibly know
what he's becoming?
We don't know.
Nature is unpredictable.
Everybody evolves in a different way.
But I know for a fact
that if Rick doesn't have surgery,
within 48 hours,
he will lose control of his emotions,
and in 72 hours, he will be dead.
All we can do is move forward...
and hope and pray.
You said the test results were successful.
I said not everybody would survive.
You lied.
I told you what you needed to know
at the time.
You said you would become you, but better.
That's what you said.
And you will.
I have more than hope in you, Rick.
I have faith.
[phone ringing]
[Collingwood] Hello?
I can see. I can see everything.
The night. The sky. There's no darkness.
I want to finish it.
[Abi] "Saturn's largest moon is
the second largest in the solar system.
Larger than Mercury.
Its rivers carve valleys into soil rich...
in ammonia and nitrogen.
Nitrogen,
which can be used
to generate breathable oxygen,
or to produce fertilizer
for growing food."
Give me adrenaline!
Hold him down!
Dr. Wallis!
[heart monitor beating steadily]
[heart monitor beating rapidly]
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
[heart monitor flat-lining]
[exhales]
[Collingwood] We did it, Abi.
We stole fire from the gods.
Rick and Tally are the future now.
They leave in two days.
[Collingwood] They communicate
at low frequency.
And tactile contact.
Our hearing can't detect it.
They can go home until we launch.
It's still him, Abi.
His ring.
Let's see.
Looks like it's...
Looks like it's just a little tight.
Might just have to get you a larger size.
[Abi gasps] [gasps]
[breathes heavily]
[Lucas] Mom?
Everything's okay.
Go back to sleep, sweetie.
Will you turn my stars on?
Mom?
Come here. Okay.
Shh, shh.
Rick! Rick!
[soldier thrashing in water]
No!
[alarm klaxon wails]
[shouting in Spanish]
[Petersen] Colonel!
Colonel!
- He is the property of the U.S. Military.
- He's a threat to life on this base.
Lieutenant Janssen is $300 million
worth of scientific research.
- If you kill him...
- I'll do what I have to do.
Shh. Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
It's okay, honey.
It's okay. We're okay.
I know where he is.
Stay here. I'll be right back, sweetie.
[vehicles approaching]
[helicopter whirring]
Rick!
Please.
Please don't run.
[helicopter whirs in distance]
Abi...
Can you hear me?
Abi?
Where am I?
You mustn't go out on your own again.
We were lucky to find you.
I'm sorry they hurt you,
but you shouldn't have run.
Now, Rick's safe, and Lucas.
But we don't have any time.
What?
He's now the future.
And he's going to survive,
if we can help him.
But we need to get him on Titan
so he can live.
We need your help.
If we force him, I fear we'll kill him.
Do you understand?
[Freya] We need to stabilize him first
or he's not gonna make it.
The Pentagon's ordered
an immediate evacuation.
- We have to stabilize him. His vitals...
- We have to leave now!
Listen. Give me a minute, will you?
Abigail...
- If you can make him submit...
- Submit to what?
If you can make him take one of these,
you can end his suffering.
This is a chemical lobotomy.
You'll erase all of his memories.
He's resisting...
because he's attached
to too many things on Earth.
He won't remember who he is,
he won't remember who I am,
he won't remember who his son is.
What good would it do if he did?
You know he can't stay here.
He's a soldier.
There's no going back.
Be careful, Abigail.
Let's go. Trust me.
No! No! Get out!
[gunfire continues]
[alarm sounds]
What's going on?
Oh, my God! You switched it!
Hold it right there!
[gunfire]
Mom?
There's another way out, through the lab.
Dad?
Dad!
Rick!
- Let's get you down.
- Okay.
Be careful.
Here's something.
It's over, Abi.
It's done with.
They'll shoot...
and kill your family.
Just walk away with Lucas.
Go fuck yourself.
Shoot them.
What?
Shoot them!
No.
No, I'm not shooting
two unarmed women and a child.
Are you losing your minds?
Look at what we've got!
That's our research!
That's what we bled for!
I made him! I made him!
But if we can't control him,
all of us are dead.
All of us.
The crazy bastard did it.
Yeah.
Rick changes everything.
He gives us hope.
Your family's a miracle, Dr. Janssen.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Hey, Mom.
Hi.
- How was school?
- It was great.
Come outside. It's so clear.
Original Sub: GoldenBeard
Edited by- [Abs3nt-_-mind3D]