(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(RUSTLING)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
JESSICA: You know how this is going to end.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
(WHOOSHES)
(DOOR OPENS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(RATTLES)
(CLICKS)
JESSICA: You got everything you need?
Yup.
KEITH: First cam, this
is the live feed cams,
then I'm on to site by site
with the card cams.
JESSICA: I'll just be
here setting up the lab.
I've got a good feeling
about this.
This could be the mission.
That gun's not corporate issue.
You gotta have tools you trust.
(GUN COCKS)
As much as you trust yourself.
(RASPING)
(PAPER RUSTLES)
(LEAVES CRUNCHING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(LIGHT STATIC)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(LEAVES CRUNCHING)
(BUZZES)
TEX: (ON PHONE)
Everything's synced on my end.
Guess you're my eyes now.
KEITH: Well, that must be
a comforting thought.
First canvass went as planned.
TEX: How are things with you and her?
What do you mean?
(SCOFFS)
TEX: I'm just familiar with her profile.
They say she's smart, sure.
I bet she's a little...
obsessive.
What do they say about me?
TEX: That you never miss a beat.
(CHUCKLES)
(CLANKING)
(LIGHT STATIC)
JESSICA: Live feed cameras look good.
I was worried
they were gonna give us
the shit equipment again.
But nope.
What's it like out there?
Silent.
Pretty.
JESSICA: Till something
jumps out of the shadows
and rips off one of our limbs.
KEITH: They said "lack of animal behavior."
Not dangerous.
JESSICA: You remember that line
they fed us in the CRS?
This will make you famous.
Come be part
of the new gold rush.
I wish I did anything
as well as they bullshit.
And yet, here we are.
Yup.
Still chasing the work.
(CREAKING)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(LEAVES CRUNCHING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(BRANCHES CRACKING)
(CAMERA BEEPS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(BEEPING)
(RASPING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(LEAVES CRUNCHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
KEITH: Full cards for processing.
Anything weird happen today?
Nope.
Quiet as a grave out there.
(SIGHS)
JESSICA: What'd you get?
"Bird in the hand"?
No, "The...
unexamined life..."
KEITH: What are you doing?
Site three's
on the schedule today.
I know that.
That's where the cult
had its camp.
I've gotta see it.
I don't think so.
JESSICA: They had their tent city
up over that hill there.
And all around this field
are where the experts think
the bodies are buried.
What bodies?
The theory goes
they killed dozens more
we don't know about.
Indigents, homeless...
One of our lawyers went missing
during the trial.
They all might be here.
They call it the killing field.
You know an awful lot about it.
There's video of it, you know.
KEITH: Some of what they got up to.
Another government guy
showed it to me.
Which guy?
I don't remember his name.
Bleeker or Blecher...
KEITH: He showed me some clips
from some tapes they recovered.
Including...
highlights from
the Pleasant View Massacre.
When did this happen?
You're jealous.
No.
I just don't believe
he was walking around
with a thrill-kill cult's
home movie in his pocket.
KEITH: Don't know how he got it,
I just know that he had it,
and he thought
it was something that...
I should see.
The family didn't film anything.
It looked authentic.
It's an urban legend.
(SCOFFS)
What the hell is that?
(BIRDS SQUAWKS)
Someone's been
out here, digging.
Yeah.
And not too long ago.
KEITH: We should get back to the camp.
Right.
Digging, marking,
human activity.
Someone's been
in site three, do...
What? Why the fuck
didn't you tell us that before?
There was a CSI team out here,
not two months ago,
excavating,
looking for more
of the cult's victims.
And they didn't think
to tell us?
He said, "The information
was not pertinent
to biological analysis."
That sounds like bullshit to me.
Maybe. Or maybe it's innocent.
A lie by accidental omission.
KEITH: How many indigents
do you think have been...
(FIRE CRACKLING)
tortured and murdered
in these woods?
JESSICA: I think, in my heart of hearts,
you can take
their official death score
and double it, at least.
I was young when the family...
did their thing.
Never really took
any interest in it.
Hm.
(SNIFFLES)
JESSICA: The prosecuting DA
did a series of lectures
at my school.
I attended all of them.
How could I resist?
When I'm into something,
I can't let it go.
What the cult did
was lure kids in.
They'd hang out
at train stations
or bus depots...
concerts or parks,
on the lookout for runaways,
war vets, anyone down
and out and desperate.
And they'd bring them
back here to the ranch,
indoctrinate them.
Some joined up.
Some left.
And some disappeared.
Hm.
I don't really like
anybody enough to...
ever join anything.
JESSICA: Hm, they felt...
alienated from society.
Isn't that always what it is?
So, they rejected it,
disassociated from it,
and went looking
for something else.
Feeling alienated, I get.
Joining a cult,
I don't.
Hm. It's about survival
and belief, right?
JESSICA: Our brains are built
to be credulous of religion.
And here I was thinking
it was a...
just a bunch of kids
with daddy issues.
Here's one for you.
Does every cult
resemble a family,
or does every family
resemble a cult?
Hm.
(CHUCKLES)
So...
It lured a bunch of people
into the woods.
Then what?
JESSICA: They ate a lot of peyote.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
They read
the anti-establishment tracts
Father wrote by the bushel,
fucked and danced
to flute music.
Ah, yeah.
Wrote more tracts,
went out and recruited,
rinse and repeat.
And then that shit
went down in Portland.
Pleasant View Massacre.
Three of the four killers joined
the family the previous year.
Probational members,
proving themselves.
No one thought
they were violent.
Or maybe they weren't,
and then something changed.
(JESSICA SIGHS)
I wish I knew.
History is so full of shadow.
I shudder to think
what this land has witnessed.
Oh, it gives me the chills.
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(THUDS)
(JESSICA SIGHS)
Okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SIGHS)
Good for you.
(RASPING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(BRANCH CRACKS)
(MUNCHING)
(RUSTLING)
(LEAVES CRUNCHING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
(DOG PANTING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(DOG GROWLS)
(DOG BARKS)
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
(BIRD CAWS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(EERIE MUSIC)
(GROANS)
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
(BOTTLES CLANK)
(SOFT THUDS)
KEITH: What do you think our bosses
are hoping to find out here?
Really?
(SIGHS)
A, uh...
previously uncharacterized
element,
genetic-environmental
or otherwise,
one that might change
the way we view
our relationship
to the natural world.
That's what
you're hoping to find.
(CLINKS)
Yeah.
On that matter, the company
and I are aligned.
But...
How do they profit on whatever
is going on out here?
Maybe they won't.
Yeah, maybe.
But they'll definitely try.
For better or for worse.
Distrust is really
your default setting, isn't it?
(FIZZING)
KEITH: Only when it comes to people.
Please.
You give nature
too much respect.
The natural world
is far more ruthless,
far less altruistic
than culture.
Animals don't torture.
They don't lie,
they don't scheme.
A starving wolf just attacks.
Well, if you're hoping
to disappoint
our corporate overlords...
I've got good news.
Ain't no answers
in these samples.
(SIGHS)
KEITH: So, what's next?
I dunno. We keep looking.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(CLICKS)
(CLACKING)
KEITH: Card 27 B, stroke 6.
Camera triggered.
No visual.
Camera 207, site 9.
(BEEPS)
KEITH: Same thing.
Heat detection activated.
Nothing there.
JESSICA: Camera malfunction, must be.
KEITH: The same malfunction
across all the cameras?
No, it's like they're...
looking for something
that's not there.
JESSICA: Or they're seeing something
that we're not.
KEITH: I'm gonna move on
to the site three cameras.
(BEEPS)
Nothing.
(STATIC)
(ANIMAL GRUMBLING)
(ANIMAL GROANING)
(STATIC)
(BEEPING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
We just lost all video.
(JESSICA HUMS SCARY TUNE)
Hilarious. Will you help me?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
You dreamed this would happen.
That the video monitors
were on the fritz,
that you fucked 'em up somehow.
What'd I do?
Pour liquor under them?
JESSICA: What?
Like the...
T. Billings thing.
JESSICA: The first Dead Zone Mission?
What did you hear happened?
The team was...
partying at the site one night,
and T. Billings
got a little crazy
and dumped a...
full glass of scotch
on some circuitry.
Started an electrical fire
and "fwoom!"
KEITH: The whole site went
up like an arctic torch.
They all froze pretty fast.
Nobody left to tell the tale.
JESSICA: I met him once, Billings,
at one of Doctor Ryoko's
cocktail parties.
I don't get invited to those.
A people person like you?
Shocking.
(FIZZING)
Doctor Ryoko loved him.
JESSICA: Toshi collects guys like that.
Toshi?
First name basis, cozy.
What, do you got a key
to the château, too?
KEITH: No wonder you're on the fast track.
JESSICA: Jealous?
(BEEPS)
JESSICA: Oh, they're back.
It's not my work.
Must be something fidgety
in the air.
Feed one's still out.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
JESSICA: I've heard knocking on the hatch.
Two nights this week.
It's your imagination.
I think it's you.
Messing with my head.
KEITH: Did you check the feed?
JESSICA: Of course.
(SIGHS)
KEITH: Did you see me on there, knocking?
No. But you know
the angle of the camera.
You could make it to the door
without it seeing.
KEITH: Here.
Place this one, too.
Anywhere you want. That way,
I can't sneak up on you.
Why didn't you tell me before?
About the knocking?
I have to tell you everything
that happens to me?
(BIRDS CHIRPING IN DISTANCE)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(BEEPS)
KEITH: Mm-hm.
(PINGS)
(BIRD TRILLS)
(SIGHS)
Hilarious.
(THUDS)
Goddammit, let me in!
I know you can see me.
(LOCK CLATTERS)
Okay.
(CLANKING)
(RUSTLING)
KEITH: I rigged the den...
way up, past site three.
No sign of a pack, but, uh...
it's ripe for habitation.
Maybe we'll get lucky.
I had something
happen to me today.
(WASPS BUZZING)
JESSICA: I went out,
figured I'd do
a little collection myself.
You're not supposed to do that.
Yeah, well, I got tired
of the den mother role.
JESSICA: Figured it wouldn't hurt.
So, I went off down
into the south sector...
and found a huge nest
of these guys in the trees.
(BUZZING)
Cecidostiba semifascia
crawling everywhere.
In the trees, on the bushes,
all over the ground.
Scores of them
were clumping together
and falling to the ground
like ripe apples.
I've checked every case study
on record.
None of them
have activity like this.
It got weirder.
At first, I was repulsed.
The larvae,
moving together like that.
Then I started taking samples.
Put my hands right in there.
They didn't flinch.
They crawled up on me.
Up my arms.
Tried to get under my shirt.
I don't know why
I wasn't stung to death.
There were so many of them.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Never read any case study
where behavior like that
is even mentioned
as a possibility.
(URINE TRICKLING)
Insect samples coming your way.
I think you're going
to find them mighty special.
TEX: Hope so.
Still haven't seen shit.
Five guys here are
recommending a deeper canvass.
Great.
TEX: Hey.
You're not pissed about
the CSI thing, are you?
Pissed that you didn't give us
all the facts?
No, not at all.
(ZIPS)
TEX: You know,
if there's no trust
between you and me,
the work might suffer.
Oh, don't worry about me.
I'm all about the work.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(WIND HOWLING SOFTLY)
(SQUISH)
(GRUNTS)
(DIRT RUSTLING)
(SHOVEL CLANKS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(WIND HOWLING)
(RUSTLING)
(SPLASHES)
(WASP BUZZING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(EERIE MUSIC)
(DISTANT BUZZING)
(JESSICA MOANING)
(MOANING CONTINUES)
(BEEPING)
JESSICA: I want to start by eliminating
the obvious hypothesis.
Let's get water and soil samples
all the way back
from sites 12 and 13.
Maybe there's a dump site
on the land.
Maybe hunters
contaminated the water.
I'm gonna be gone overnight.
JESSICA: So?
I can take care of myself.
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DOOR OPENS)
KEITH: Hello.
Hello?
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(BEEPING)
(DOOR OPENS)
KEITH: Where were you?
JESSICA: Out in site three.
Researching.
KEITH: Great.
(SCOFFS)
Next time, leave a note.
Someone said my name.
It sounded close,
like right behind the bushes.
KEITH: Oh.
If you thought the bushes
were talking to you,
maybe we should
analyze the lemonade.
I swear somebody
stage-whispered my name.
(SIGHS)
Check the tree line?
Nothing there.
(KEITH CHUCKLES)
KEITH: It's a phantom voice.
Your subconscious
calling out for attention.
Happened to me a lot
when I used to get rummy,
scrunched into a blind.
Get tired enough,
you hear and see things
that aren't there.
I'm not tired.
KEITH: The mind gets bored.
It plays games. Acts out.
Yeah. Maybe.
JESSICA: It's just...
Then I had this dream.
Was your mother there?
I'm not joking.
It was sunset in the dream.
And this hideous redness
covered everything.
JESSICA: Made my eyes hurt.
Light seeped in from the sky,
and through cracks in the earth
until I couldn't see
anything, but...
shadows and blurry figures of...
People appeared.
They gathered around me.
Maybe they weren't human.
So, how did this dream end?
That's the thing.
I don't know if it ever did.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Everything just went black.
(JESSICA GASPS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(THUMPING)
(THUMPS)
(CLANKING)
(SLOSHING)
(CLATTERING)
(THUDDING)
JESSICA: Psst.
I wasn't being straight
with you earlier.
I did hear a voice.
Whoever it was, whatever it was,
it whispered my name.
But that's not all it did.
It asked where you were.
"Where's your friend?
Where's your friend?
Where's your friend?"
Then... Then it was gone.
And there was nothing
behind the tree.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(RUSTLING)
(CAMERA CLATTERING)
(DISTANT GROAN)
(DRIZZLING)
(RUSTLING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(BIRDS TRILLING)
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(FROG CROAKS)
(BEEPING)
(BEEPS)
JESSICA: What's with the new remote feed?
Tell me again about
the voice you heard.
JESSICA: So you can make fun of me more?
You heard it since then?
JESSICA: I don't think so.
What about the knocking?
JESSICA: No.
Something spooked you,
didn't it?
I'm just thinking,
it's not like they caught
every single nut case
that followed the cult.
JESSICA: They caught the
ones that mattered.
The rest of them fled.
Just drifting back
to regular old life.
Why are you so interested
all of a sudden?
What'd you see out there?
KEITH: Nothing.
(BIRD CROONING)
(WHISPERING)
(STATIC)
(DISCORDANT MUSIC)
(CHANTING)
(FLESH RIPS)
(GIRL LAUGHING)
(SHOUTING)
(DISTANT LAUGHTER)
(WOMAN SCREAMING IN DISTANCE)
(SLOSHING)
MAN: Let me touch your face.
(GROANING)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(CROWD LAUGHING)
(KNIFE PIERCING FLESH)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(BIRD CHIRPING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(CREAKING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CLATTERING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
KEITH: I found this.
Out past site three.
(CLINKS)
It's old.
In 19th century old.
There were people here
before the cult.
KEITH: Yeah.
And I think I know
where they were living.
(GRUNTS)
(METAL CLANKS)
It's obviously a farm
or ranch of some kind.
The wall marks some kind
of corral. Maybe sheep.
This must be
the original settlement.
KEITH: It's possible.
This area here...
There's something...
different about it.
(SHOVEL CLANKS)
(GRUNTS)
(SHOVEL CLATTERS)
This is bone.
JESSICA: It's all bone.
There must be dozens
of bodies buried there.
I've got samples here
from men, women, and children.
I thought we were here
investigating new phenomena.
Yeah, yeah, me too.
(CHUCKLES)
How does this relate
to the animal behavior
and how does that relate
to the cult?
It doesn't seem like
a coincidence.
I mean, it can't be
a coincidence, right?
(SIGHS)
There must be something there.
Hm?
Hello?
Sorry. What?
TEX: I said, they want the bone samples
back at the main lab.
Anomaly like that
has got their interest.
And I'm supposed to believe
that you guys had no idea
about the original settlement.
TEX: You can believe whatever you want.
Our records are what
the government gave us
when we bought the land.
We're on the same side
here, okay?
Right. Okay.
Anything else?
TEX: Yeah. Just one thing...
(WHISPERING)
Did you fuck her yet?
I'm not gonna answer that.
(PHONE CLICKS)
JESSICA: What'd he say?
KEITH: He says he is going
to send someone for samples.
But he thinks it could be
something, right?
KEITH: Yeah.
Yeah, he does.
Good.
We might have something here.
(EERIE MUSIC)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
What's going on
in the rest of the world?
The decline of civilization
continues apace.
Human remains, right?
Among other things.
(GRUNTS)
The rest of your stuff
is in here.
The last team dug those, too.
KEITH: CSI team?
Yeah.
Poor bastards.
What'd you mean "poor bastards"?
Well, I heard the lead
on the last team went nuts.
Started disappearing
at odd times.
Seeing things
that weren't there.
PILOT: Then one night,
one of the guys woke up
and Bart was right
on top of him.
Slashing his face to ribbons.
Jesus.
Took the other two
just to pull him off.
PILOT: I hear they got him locked
in one of the labs
for observation.
Weird fucking story, huh?
(BULLETS CLINKING)
I'm going on card retrieval.
(GUN COCKS)
What are you doing?
JESSICA: Standing around,
thinking about death.
(SIGHS)
I meant today. For work.
JESSICA: I'm waiting on the lab.
Nothing else I can do, really,
except stare at the same data,
over and over again.
Hoping to see something in it.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(BEEPING)
(RINGING)
(CLATTERING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(DOOR OPENS)
KEITH: What have you been doing in here?
It's a mess.
JESSICA: "Physical evidence
suggests no link."
KEITH: What?
That's the full report.
KEITH: "Dating suggests the deaths occurred
some 200 years ago
and were of a violent nature.
Some show signs
of blunt force trauma,
others no signs of violence."
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
"A history of violence is common
in newly settled territories.
As such,
the presence of corpses
does not suggest a causal link.
Return focus to
animal behavior."
Animal behavior.
JESSICA: So we found nothing.
Maybe there's some connection
between past and present.
Maybe it's genetics.
Maybe it's chemistry.
Maybe it's aliens,
maybe it's ghosts.
Maybe it's none of that shit.
KEITH: What are you doing?
There's never just one.
I'm not getting drunk
with you again.
(POPS)
JESSICA: What are you gonna do instead?
Sit in here and jerk off?
I don't think so.
Ah.
My parents never approved
of my career.
Biology, genetics,
field research.
I might as well told them
I was gonna sell my body
on the streets.
(SNIFFS)
KEITH: You really want to talk
about your parents right now?
When I feel like a failure,
that's exactly what I
wanna talk about.
You know, my mom died last year.
I'm sorry.
JESSICA: I never liked her, anyway.
JESSICA: The woman my dad married is worse.
Drunken witch.
My dad's fat as a cow,
and farts his way
through the news...
(SIGHS)
and tournament poker
16 hours a day.
They've all been
like strangers to me.
It's miserable.
It's miserable to feel so alone.
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
My father was a woodsman.
After Mom died, he...
disappeared into
the Olympic National Forest
with a backpack and a dog.
KEITH: We never found his body.
I bet he thought he was doing
what a real man
is supposed to do.
Going into the wilderness
to die.
So I'm not even sure
if that's true.
The world is large
and unknowable.
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
No one ever
really knows anything.
(RAIN PATTERING)
(PATTERING CONTINUES)
(KEITH PANTING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(CROWS CAWING)
(RASPING)
JESSICA: Site six today, right?
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
KEITH: Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
(DOOR OPENS)
(THUDS)
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
(DOG BARKING)
(BUZZING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
(RASPING)
(BABY CRYING)
(DOOR SQUEAKING)
(DISEMBODIED VOICES)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
JESSICA: I found this.
KEITH: Is it real?
JESSICA: Pretty sure.
KEITH: Where did it come from?
JESSICA: I found a cave, west of here.
Not so much a cave, really.
More like a deep,
vertical crevice.
I think they held
ceremonies there.
KEITH: "They"?
JESSICA: You know who I'm talking about.
The fuckers left symbols
on the walls
in chalk and paint.
This was just sitting there,
lying in the dirt, broken.
Chiseled from a curtain
of glaciated rock.
KEITH: That's got to
weigh 50 kilos at least,
how did you get it back here?
JESSICA: Hm, you aren't
the only one who knows
how to build a travois.
It was dark down there.
But it looked like
there was something big
fossilized in the cave wall.
I think this came from
whatever that was.
(STATIC)
KEITH: What?
Uh...
KEITH: What...
(JESSICA PANTS)
KEITH: Ow!
(GROANS)
(BOTH MOAN)
(SMOOCHES)
(KEITH GRUNTING)
(JESSICA MOANING)
(BOTH MOANING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(EERIE MUSIC)
(KEITH GROANS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
KEITH: Hello?
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
(KEITH SIGHS)
KEITH: I see the rock.
There are no rock formations
on the land.
Not anywhere.
I don't get it.
That must be wrong.
Something must be off.
Must be something off.
I don't get it. Must be wrong.
Yeah, something's off.
(BRANCH SNAPS)
(BIRD CAWING)
(KEITH GULPS)
KEITH: Oh, the places we'll go.
JESSICA: (ON RADIO)
Uh, what?
Where are you?
Site three.
JESSICA: What are you doing there?
KEITH: Well, it's a nice place to...
build a house, raise some kids.
JESSICA: Yeah, children
would love it out there.
KEITH: Where were you this morning?
JESSICA: Oh, you know...
out chasing the work.
Yeah.
So, why did you call?
Is everything okay?
JESSICA: You called me.
I did?
JESSICA: I finally have
work to do over here.
Why would I call you?
You're ornery today.
JESSICA: I'm not ornery,
I'm busy.
Not just you playing boy scout
out here anymore.
Right.
I'm tramping the woods...
and you're barefoot
and pregnant in the kitchen.
JESSICA: You're cooking for
yourself tonight, honey.
So, you really don't have
anything to say?
KEITH: You called me.
JESSICA: All right, then
I'm hanging up, too.
(PHONE CLICKS)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
KEITH: I don't understand.
JESSICA: Hm.
JESSICA: Me neither.
Yeah, me neither.
Maybe it's a signpost.
A guide pointing
the way toward...
Maybe it's a signpost.
KEITH: I don't understand.
I told you why.
JESSICA: Yeah, me neither.
Maybe it's a signpost.
A guide...
KEITH: Towards what?
Pointing the way
towards something.
When I saw the horn kinda...
KEITH: Towards what?
Peeking out of the rocks...
JESSICA: I don't know.
When I first saw the horn...
peeking out of the rocks...
this feeling...
I saw the horn coming...
peeking out of the rocks.
I felt this...
this feeling, this shock.
(JESSICA MOANING)
Hit me.
(THUDS)
(BOTH MOANING)
(MOANING CONTINUES)
(JESSICA MOANING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(KNOCKING)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
(KNIFE RASPING)
(RUSTLING)
(BUZZING)
(BUZZING CONTINUES)
(CLANGS)
(DISEMBODIED VOICES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(CLATTERS)
(METAL CLANKING)
(BULLETS CLANKING)
(GUN COCKS)
(DISEMBODIED VOICES)
(DISTANT VOICES MURMURING)
(GUN COCKS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(BIRDS CAWING)
JESSICA: Start getting laid,
go back to the Stone Age.
Why are you letting
all the bugs in?
I don't...
I don't know.
(BEEPS)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(STATIC)
What the fuck?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
KEITH: Did you hear knocking
on the module last night?
No.
Are you okay?
KEITH: Where did this come from?
Cave in the western sector.
There aren't any caves
in the western sector.
There aren't?
KEITH: No.
I guess that's not
where I found it.
Stop fucking lying to me!
I found it in the bushes.
KEITH: Where?
Near an anthill
I've been studying.
Canids dug it up, probably.
(TAPPING)
(BEEPS)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(TAPPING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(EERIE MUSIC)
(EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(RUSTLES)
(BIRD CAWING)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
Where's your friend?
KEITH: Where's your friend?
(WHISPERING)
Where's your friend?
KEITH: What?
I didn't say anything.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Where were you this morning?
Uh, nowhere.
(CHUCKLES)
I was right here,
working through newest data.
KEITH: Right.
JESSICA: I noticed you're not following
the schedule anymore.
Yes, my partner.
She's not handling the stress.
She's lying, she's obfuscating.
TEX: Sounds to us like
you're not handling things well,
your reports of the disaster.
So there's nothing
that seemed wrong.
Screw you.
My guts says it's dangerous,
I want Evac now!
TEX: Dangerous?
We don't see any danger.
Keith, you just need
a little bit more sleep.
Hello? You hear me?
TEX: Yes, we hear you.
We can't authorize Evac.
What... the hell you can't!
TEX: We cannot. It's not possible.
All right.
Then, I'm walking out.
TEX: Just relax. Have a drink.
Fuck you.
(PHONE THUDS)
Hm.
(MUMBLING)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(WHISPERING)
What the fuck?
(BRANCH SNAPPING)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GUNSHOT)
(GUN COCKS)
Come on, come on, come on.
(PANTS)
(GUN CLANKS)
(PANTING)
Fuck!
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(WIND HOWLING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello...
(STATIC)
(DISEMBODIED VOICE)
Hello...
(STATIC)
(STATIC CONTINUES)
(DISEMBODIED VOICE)
(DISEMBODIED VOICES CONTINUE)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
You have my eyes.
(EERIE MUSIC)
(EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(EXHALES)
That bitch.
That bitch!
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(RUSTLING CONTINUES)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(THUDS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(KEITH SIGHS)
JESSICA: Look at you.
You're weak as a kitten.
Don't worry about me.
I'm fit as a farmhand.
(WATER POURING)
How long?
JESSICA: Excuse me?
How long have you been
poisoning me?
(JESSICA SCOFFS)
I'm not poisoning you, honey.
It's all in your head.
There's something in my water.
You must be tired.
That makes the mind play tricks.
Isn't that right?
No.
KEITH: Not like this.
You've done something.
What happened?
It's not worth this.
You have no idea what this is.
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(THUDS, CLATTERS)
(KEITH SCREAMING)
(SIZZLING)
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(JESSICA GRUNTS)
(JESSICA GROANING)
(KEITH GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(KEITH HYPERVENTILATING)
(KEITH GROANING)
(GROANING CONTINUES)
(KNOCKING)
(GROANS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(GROANING)
(DISEMBODIED LAUGHTER)
(KEITH GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(DISEMBODIED LAUGHTER)
(KEITH GROANING)
(THUDS)
(KNOCKING)
(DISEMBODIED VOICES)
VOICE 1: Open the door.
VOICE 2: I know everything.
Open the door.
VOICE 2: Unlock the door.
VOICE 2: We can help you.
Go to hell.
VOICE 2: We have your eyes.
Let us see you.
Go to hell!
VOICE 2: They're all the same.
VOICE 1: The key.
VOICE 1: Let us help.
Get the fuck away!
VOICE 2: There is trust between us.
(FOOTSTEPS SHUFFLING)
(CRASHES)
JESSICA: Help me.
(WHIMPERING)
JESSICA: Help.
(SNIFFLES)
(EXHALES)
(PANTS)
(CLANGS)
(CLATTERS)
(SNICKERS)
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(KEITH GRUNTING)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Did you come to save me?
JESSICA: Won't you join us?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)