Subtitles by explosiveskull
Can I get a pack of Morleys?
¿Cigarillos? ¿Comprende?
Sí, sí.
Yeah.
Truth or dare, Giselle?
Please.
Please, I don't want
to play anymore. Please.
Truth... or... dare?
Oh, no! No!
I'm sorry.
I don't have a choice.
You do have a choice.
And I can honestly say
the pure joy you will feel
from literally building
someone's home,
it will stay with you
for the rest of your life.
Unlike all the nights
you won't remember
and the hangovers you're
really gonna want to forget.
So, for a spring break
alternative
that is really good
for the soul,
please consider
Habitat for Humanity.
Okay.
Hey.
Hi.
So, I've been doing some
thinking, and I forgive you.
- For what?
- For saying you can't come on spring break.
I know you didn't mean it.
- Markie.
- Yeah?
I love you so much,
you know that.
But I can't. I already
signed up for Habitat.
- I know.
- Yeah. I'm a trip leader.
You know what, I know, I know.
It's just...
this is our last
spring break, ever.
And the thought of doing that
without my best friend...
that breaks my heart.
Since high school, you and I
haven't spent more than a week
away from each other.
This is our last chance
to have some fun
before life tears us apart.
I mean, when you
put it that way...
- Yeah.
- No. Still can't.
Okay. Olivia,
what ever happened to
"between you and the world,
I choose you"?
- I still mean that.
- Do you?
Yes, most of the time.
This just...
you know, isn't
one of those times.
Okay. All right.
You know, I really didn't want
to have to do this, but
you've left me no other choice.
I un-signed you up.
- You what?
- Yeah.
I told Habitat
you got shingles.
Which is kind of funny,
'cause roofs have shingles...
Markie, that is so...
- Brilliant.
- Thank you.
Okay, if you come with us
for this one week
of spring break debauchery, we
will all build houses with you
for two weeks over the summer.
- We said one week.
- We said two.
It'll help with your
med school applications.
- Like I need the help.
- He's in.
Full 14 days.
So what's it gonna be, Liv?
I mean, your feeble set
of hands for one week,
or all of ours for two?
I mean, you're really
just being selfish
if you don't come with us.
Oh, my God.
What did you put in here?
Shoes.
- It worked?
- Well, that depends.
Are you really gonna help me
build houses this summer?
You had me at
"boys with tools."
And Markie's nothing
if not persistent.
Yep, that is
her most annoying quality.
Glad you're with us,
Girl Scout.
Well, you know we've always
been a package deal.
Oh, yeah.
I'm well aware of that.
- Are you?
- Yeah. I'm okay with it.
Mm.
- You ready?
- So ready.
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's do it.
- Do we have everything?
- Yeah.
Now we do.
Ow, ow! Spring break, bitches!
That's right, bitches!
¡Viva la Mexico!
There it is!
We're in Mexico.
- Yay! - Rosarito! Spring break!
- Spring break!
Who's ready for some cervezas?
- Margaritas.
- Actually, this is, like, our fourth.
I love you.
- I love you.
- Such a babe.
- My God.
- What about me?
Mexico!
Tyson... is about to run
into the water
and get eaten by a shark.
- Spring break!
- Beer run. Let's go!
We're not drunk yet.
Are you straight? Are you
straight? Are you straight?
All poles, no holes.
You know that.
- Get a room.
- Lonely souls here at the bar.
- Drink. Drink.
- Oh.
Sand dollar!
Lucky charm.
- Sober friend right here.
- Huh? Not!
There, there. Yeah!
Oh, shit! Oh, my...
- I love it.
- Nice!
Mwah! Whoo!
If you guys watch this later,
- I love you, Markie.
- Soul brothers.
Love you, Liv.
- Love you, Pen. Love you, Brad. I love you, Ty.
- Yes, we are...
Let's leave these losers
behind. Let's go.
No, I just want to go
to one more bar.
- ¡Olé!
Oh, I want to lay you.
Let's go back to the hotel.
Come on.
¡Uno! ¡Dos!
¡Uno, dos, tres, cuatro!
Wow.
They are really going for it.
Well, if you can't beat 'em...
- Oh-hoo-hoo. - Mm-hmm.
- Just like that?
Okay. Tell me what's going on.
Uh, last night
in Mexico, and...
and we're the only two losers
not dancing.
Mm. If you can
call that dancing.
Definitely not.
Is that for your
YouTube channel?
No. No.
YouTube's for
my volunteer stuff,
and Snapchats are just for fun.
Um, I'm gonna go
to the señoritas'.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Come on, come on.
Hey, I thought you were
done with this shit.
- You're moving in with Lucas, to D.C., remember?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- What... what are you doing?
- I'm-I'm sorry.
I'm so stupid. I'm just...
I'm just drunk, okay?
You're seriously
the best friend ever.
Okay.
- You're good?
- Yeah.
Look who I found
trying and failing to salsa.
Cool.
- I wasn't that bad.
- Hey.
- I missed you.
- Welcome back.
I missed you, too.
So you weren't doing
too well with the salsa, huh?
- Olivia! What?
- Ronnie?
Hi. What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm just skiing. What
do you think I'm doing here?
I'm getting my spring break on.
Do you want to join me?
No. Thanks.
Hey, where's Markie?
Maybe we could do, like,
- you know, a little ménage à trois?
- You know what?
She's actually
with her boyfriend, Lucas.
What about, like,
a ménage à dos?
Not happening, pal.
Oh, yeah?
Is there a problem, pal?
No.
I'm just surprised she hasn't
punched you in the face yet.
- Guess she's nicer than I am.
- Oh, yeah?
How about I punch you
in the face? Huh?
Wouldn't be the worst thing
that's happened to me
this week.
Okay, Ronnie, calm down.
Seriously, you got to
let it go.
All right? I saw Delta Phi in
the back. They're doing shots.
So you should
really go check it out.
I can't say no to shots.
Everyone knows that.
That's why I'm gonna leave,
not 'cause of what you said.
You think I'm too nice?
It's a good thing.
Except when dealing
with guys at bars, so...
Feel free to tell me
to piss off.
Maybe I just like being nice.
Can I give it a shot?
- I'm Carter.
- Olivia.
Buy you a drink?
Yeah.
Another beer,
and... a margarita
for the lady.
Come on!
There's got to be an all-night
bar around here somewhere.
We still have that tequila
back in the room.
But it's our last night
in Mexico.
I don't want
to go back to the room.
I know a place we can go.
I'm... I'm sorry, who are you?
- Uh, it's a bit of a hike, but it's worth it.
- Hmm.
Or you can just tell me
to piss off.
I think, uh...
think the hotel room
sounds pretty good, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Oh, come on, it's our final spring break.
Before life tears us apart.
Right.
We're almost there.
I should have worn
my hiking shoes.
Um... okay.
Should I lay down
some bread crumbs?
Wait, guys, be careful.
Wonder what that means.
How's your Spanish, Brad? Ow.
Come on, guys, let's go.
Wow. This place is interesting.
- Kind of terrifying.
- Uh...
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
Promise.
Uh, yeah, this is
way better than a club.
Hey. You okay?
Uh, yeah. Yeah.
- Just a little tired.
- Yeah. We won't stay long.
Where's the tequila?
Hope you've had
your tetanus shot.
I got to piss.
- Nice. Thank you.
- Cool, cool. Thanks, man.
Oh!
Ugh.
Oh! Yo! Chill out, O-dog, it's just me.
Ronnie, did you follow me here?
You can't keep Ron-Ron
from a party.
What the hell?
This smells horrible.
What is... what...
Yo, beer me, bro.
Oh, great, Ronnie's here.
Sure thing, bro.
Um, you know, we got to
- get up early, so...
- Yeah. - Yeah. - Yes.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You guys just got here.
- You can't leave now.
- Yeah. What's the rush?
Um...
Yeah, let's, uh, let's play
a game or something.
Oh, yeah, like spin the bottle.
- And on that note, let's, uh...
- I was thinking Truth or Dare.
What, this a seventh grade
sleepover, or...?
I know it's a kids' game, but,
I mean, if you play it right,
it's a chance to expose
your friends' deepest secrets,
and... make them do
things they don't want to.
That actually does sound
kind of interesting.
Uh...
Great. We're in.
Okay, everybody, get behind me.
- And... one, two, three.
- Smile. - Queso.
Yo, will you tag me in that? Your boy.
Glad you're with us, Ronnie.
Well?
Olivia, truth or dare?
- Whoo!
- Hmm.
- Truth.
- Lame.
Um... aliens.
They land right now
and they give you a choice.
They kill everyone
in this room,
and then leave
peacefully, or...
they kill the entire
population of Mexico,
but we escape unscathed.
Choose.
What kind of ridiculous
question is that?
- It's a moral dilemma.
- I don't have morals.
- Of course you don't.
- Okay, well, obviously,
- she's choosing us.
- Sorry, guys.
- What?
- You're gonna let aliens kill us?
I love you, but millions
of people? Come on.
You have to tell the truth.
- I am. It's the only right answer.
- Eh, whatever.
Well, I'm bored
of this already,
so let's get
this party started.
- You brought us here.
- Ooh.
Yo, I know how to amp this up
a little bit.
- Why don't we get, like, a little girl-on-girl going?
- No.
- Ronnie. Truth or dare?
- I'd watch that.
Dare. Duh.
I dare you to give Tyson
a lap dance for 30 seconds.
- No way. No. I won't do it.
- Yes. - Yep.
Once you're asked, you're in.
That's the rules.
No, there's, like, three chicks
here. You couldn't dare...?
- Come on. - Ronnie.
- Yo, this sucks.
- Get over here.
- So wack!
- There you go.
- Get it.
- Yo, no tips, no touching, bro.
- Just do it.
- Don't make this a thing.
- Hold this.
- Don't make this weird.
- This is gonna be the longest
30 seconds of my life.
Let's go. Come on.
- Take it off!
- All right!
- Oh, my God!
- Oh! Oh!
He's done this before.
Ooh, I think
he kind of likes this.
We got a real pro here.
Look at that technique.
Ronnie!
- Ronnie! Ronnie!
- He's done this before.
Look at that.
- Make it rain pesos!
- I don't want your pesos!
Aw. Cheer up.
- Weird.
- Okay.
All right, Lucas,
truth or dare?
Okay, who's ready?
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yeah!
Okay, guys, I promise you, it's
just because it's cold in here.
- I have no judgment.
- Scarred for life.
Hold your applause, please.
Thank you.
Quite the show.
Okay, Markie's turn.
I got this one.
Truth or dare?
Uh, truth.
Are you aware that Olivia
is in love with your boyfriend?
- No, she's not.
- Come on, it's so obvious.
- Will you stop being such an asshole?
- Just being truthful.
- Hey, Tyson, shut up!
- Don't tell me to shut up.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- Dude, we're all here
because she's trying to make
you jealous, like, clearly.
Why are you always
starting shit, dude?!
- Somebody tell the truth, that would be great.
- Just stop it
with the agro-posturing and
just get to my turn, please.
- Brad, truth or dare?
- Yes. Truth.
If you had to make out with
anyone here, who would it be?
It's okay if you're bi-curious.
Scruffy boy over there.
- Come on!
- I'm flattered.
Tyson. Truth or dare?
- Dare.
- I dare you to stop
selling forged prescriptions
to freshmen.
- Oh, shit.
- Olivia.
Always with
the moral high ground.
Fine. I make more money
off upperclassmen anyway.
Oh, my God.
Uh, Penelope. Truth or dare?
- Dare.
- Make out with Olivia.
- Ronnie!
- Why not? Just try... It c-could be fun.
- Just...
- Didn't see that one coming.
It's okay, Liv,
just close your eyes
- and pretend it's Lucas.
- You know what?
Wow. Maybe I'm bi-curious.
Tight.
It's tight.
Carter. You're up.
Truth or dare?
Uh, truth.
What are your intentions
with our sweet Olivia?
I needed to find
someone with friends
that I could trick
into coming here.
I could tell Olivia
was a pushover,
which made her an easy target.
I brought you all up here
to play this game
because...
I'm okay with strangers dying
if it means I get to live.
Uh...
I'm sorry, but you should've
told me to piss off.
Wait, what's up?
What the hell?
Look, I know, it sounds insane,
but the game is real.
Once you're asked, you're in.
Okay? Wherever you go,
whatever you do,
it'll find you.
Hey, don't, don't.
Tell the truth or you die.
Do the dare or you die.
Refuse to play and...
Just... just-just
follow the rules.
Guys?
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Guy's a jerk.
Want to get out of here?
Yeah. Great way
to end the trip, Liv.
Yeah, I didn't like
that guy anyways.
Come on, we can go sleep in.
Hey, man, see you in class.
Coffee later.
Make sure you make it
home next weekend, son.
Gotcha.
Hi.
Hey.
All good with Officer Dad?
Oh, absolutely.
Now that he thinks
I spent my last week
belly-bumping my nonexistent
girlfriend in wine country.
Well, your Canadian lady, she
really does like a good Merlot.
Uh, her name is Kimberly,
- and her palate is quite refined, thank you.
- Oh.
Sorry. My apologies
to Canadian Kim.
Remind why I didn't go to
school thousands of miles away
from my overbearing
and homophobic father.
- Because you never say no to him.
- Hmm.
And you never would've met me.
Are you sure you don't
want to be my beard?
'Cause I really want to ghost Kimberly.
Yeah, I doubt that would solve
either of our problems.
- How is Markie?
- I don't know.
Haven't talked to her much
since we've been back.
Don't worry about us.
We're friends for life.
- Bye.
- See ya.
- Hi, Olivia.
- Hey.
- Here you go.
- God bless you.
Hey. We made mojitos!
Study party?
- Yeah, maybe later.
- Oh, okay.
Olivia,
um, Pen was saying that I was
a bit of dick in Mexico, so...
here's a little something
- to make it up to you.
- A prescription?
- What? You're not a freshman.
- Yeah, you're not a doctor.
That's... not
what my lucky pen says.
I thought I was your lucky Pen.
Oh, baby, but you are
my lucky Penelope.
- Oh, my lucky Pen! Oh! Oh!
- Tyson! Tyson!
Roy Cameron, 45 years old,
attempts to make dinner.
Take one.
A little faith, please.
Nobody makes a steak
like your old man.
Uh, Dad, I'm pescatarian now.
Right. And that's
why I meant to say...
swordfish steaks! Boom!
- God, you are such a dork.
- But you still love me, right?
Yeah, yeah, I still love you.
Good.
- Sorry.
- Hi.
Come bearing gifts.
Penelope said
you didn't want one.
I know you better than that.
Yeah, you're right.
Probably could use a drink.
So, I know things have been...
a little Bette and Joan
between us
since Mexico, but...
awkwardness stops here.
Okay? And since my dad
took his life,
y-you've been my only family.
The one person
I can really trust.
So I'm not gonna let
a stupid comment by Tyson,
of all people, change that.
Markie, I promise you,
I do not have feelings
for your boyfriend.
He's like a brother
to me, okay?
Okay. Yeah.
Between you and the world,
I choose you.
And I choose you.
Mm. Oh, my gosh.
- That is...
- Wow.
- ...very strong.
- Yeah.
Think about
your mom, and, like,
it just happens sometimes...
Hey, asshole.
Do you think that's funny?
Think what's funny?
I-I don't get it.
My desk and the flyer
were harmless,
but it's gonna cost me
a lot of money to fix my car.
Okay, I am so lost right now.
What are you talking about?
You keyed "truth or dare"
into my car door.
There's nothing on your car.
Except your idea
of a lame joke.
Okay, you're a little crazy.
But you know what?
I actually happen
to like crazy.
Do you want to maybe
get a drink sometime?
Will you just
leave me alone? Okay?
Is that a no?
Hey, Sarah,
have you seen Markie?
In the library.
Hey, Olivia.
Truth or dare?
What did you say?
Truth or dare? Truth or dare?
Truth or dare?
- Truth or dare? Truth or dare?
- Truth! Stop!
What secret does
your best friend make you hide?
Markie's constantly
cheating on Lucas!
That true?
Markie...
Luke.
Lucas.
- Wait.
- Markie, I don't know what's going on.
He's like a brother to you?
No, I'm serious.
I'm seeing things.
Touch me again,
and I'll break that hand.
- That's insane.
- Seriously.
Yo. 'Sup?
You want to play?
You look like a girl
who's good with balls.
Please do not talk to me.
No, look, uh, just one game.
- Like, I just want to show you my pool cue.
- Okay.
And by "pool cue,"
I mean penis.
I'm referring to my penis.
Maybe we could have sex.
You know, see what happens.
Truth or dare, Ronnie?
What, did Olivia
put you up to this?
Truth... or dare?
Uh, creepy... and sexy.
Let's do it. Dare.
Get on the table and
show everyone your pool cue.
I knew it. Okay. All right.
Hello, friends and neighbors!
This fine young lady here
has asked me
to play a little game
of Truth or Dare with her,
and like a real gentleman,
I chose dare!
- Go, Ronnie!
- Whoo!
Anyway, now I will
do you all the honor
of showing you my business.
Seen it before! Not impressed!
Oh!
- Who is that, Beth?
- No, but Beth said it was tiny, too.
No, uh, Beth would
never say that!
Okay, you know what,
screw this, I'm not...
- Oh, man.
- Oh, my.
Whoa, careful! Dude.
Hey, watch the pool cue, man.
Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Whoa.
Somebody call 911!
I swear to you,
people were talking to me.
It looked like
a messed-up Snapchat filter.
They were asking me
"truth or dare"
over and over again,
and... I-I panicked.
So you're saying
a mob of people
chanting in unison
made you tell Lucas
that Markie is
a cheating whore.
Look, I know it sounds insane.
- Just a little.
- But it happened.
Something really weird
has been going on
ever since Mexico.
Oh, come on.
Uh, keeping a secret like that,
it's a huge burden.
None of us would fault you
for trying
to get it off your chest.
I mean,
n-not maybe so publicly.
I wish you would have done it
for your YouTube channel.
- I will stab you with this.
- Calm down, baby.
Basic Beth again.
Holy shit.
Excuse me,
friends and neighbors!
This fine young lady
right here has asked me
to play a game
of Truth or Dare with her,
- and like a real gentleman, I chose dare.
- Go, Ronnie!
Anyway, now I will
do you all the honor
of showing you my business.
- Gross.
- Ugh.
Call 911!
Bad break.
- It's a pool joke.
- That's not funny.
- It's the game.
- What?
- It is. It followed us home.
- Are-are you being serious?
Carter told me
that it was real,
that we were all in,
and that it would find us.
We're really taking the word
of our mentally unstable
tour guide?
How else do you explain what
happened to me in the library?
- Huh? And now Ronnie?
- Oh, I don't know.
Maybe he was drunk
and he fell off a pool table,
- which is what happened.
- So, it's just a coincidence that
- he was supposed to be doing a dare?
- Let's just calm down.
- Yes.
- No. Carter said, "Tell the truth or you die.
Do the dare or you die."
Ronnie chickened out.
He did not do his dare,
and now he's dead!
Guys, tell me I'm not crazy!
Oh, no,
you definitely sound crazy.
Lucas.
I am so sorry
for what I said,
but I swear to you,
something forced me
to say that.
And I need you to believe me.
Please.
Kind of hard
to believe someone
who's been lying to you
for so long.
See you, guys.
Anyway,
now I will do you all the honor
of showing you my business.
Lucas.
That's very funny, guys.
Okay, this is insane.
Hey.
I believe you.
Something started burning
"truth or dare" into my arm.
- Oh, my God, are you okay?
- Y-Yeah.
Yeah, I mean...
it's gone now.
But... I felt it.
Olivia, it was really painful.
Yeah, and when I was
in the library,
I was surrounded by people, but
what we're seeing is not real.
Only the consequences are.
Did you answer?
Lucas, you have to answer.
I've had feelings for Olivia
since we met.
Sometimes I wonder
what it would be like
to be with her
instead of Markie.
And I wonder what it would be
like to wake up next to her...
and kiss her.
But I know
that can never happen.
Oh, God, please tell me
you didn't hang up.
We have to convince
everybody else.
I'm coming.
What is all this?
An intervention?
I always thought day-drinking
Penelope would be first.
Thanks.
Thank you for coming.
I live here.
So, what is it all about?
The game.
We're still playing it in the
same order we played in Mexico.
Carter told us the truth;
the game is real.
First, it was my turn,
I got asked in the library, and
it made me tell your secret;
then it was Ronnie's turn,
he didn't do his dare,
and it killed him.
Maybe you and Ronnie
shouldn't have answered.
Carter also said,
"Refuse to play and you die."
I got asked tonight,
and I tried to ignore it.
But then something burned
"truth or dare" on my arm.
Show me.
I mean, it's gone now, but...
- Th-There's nothing there.
- Because I told the truth.
- Oh, my God. Geez.
- Wow. Olivia.
I mean, this is next-level.
You can't take responsibility
for humiliating me
in front of everyone
and ruining my relationship,
so you come up
with some insane story
that a game made you say it?
Then you get Lucas
to lie for you.
- No, I'm done.
- Markie.
Markie. Stop.
- You can't be alone.
- Why not?
Because in the picture,
your turn is next.
Unknown number.
Of course it is.
- "Truth or Dare?" Wow, a text. Really?
- Huh.
I mean, there's no way a human
- could have sent...
- Just answer it.
Fine.
Dare.
"Dare you to follow through
with your promise.
Break Olivia's hand."
Obviously, this was you.
Do you see me
texting you right now?
No, but you were the only one
there when I said that.
Markie, why would I dare you
to break my own hand?
I don't know!
Okay, maybe you're making
a new YouTube video
on how to lose friends.
Oh, that seems
even less likely.
- What are you doing?
- You have to do it.
What?
You have to.
Ronnie didn't do his dare,
and now he's dead.
- Liv, this is so messed up.
- Even by my standards.
Look, as pissed as I am
at you right now...
and I'm so pissed... there's no
way I'm gonna break your hand.
Well, you don't really
have a choice.
So just take it. Please.
Markie, I don't want to find
out what happens if you don't.
Just do it.
- No, I-I can't.
- God, just trust me, Markie!
Do it. Please.
Oh, don't tell me you're
a fucking coward like your dad.
Oh, oh, my God.
I'll get some ice.
I can't deal
with this crazy right now.
I got a med school
interview tomorrow.
Uh, see a doctor.
- I'm sorry. Sorry.
- Guys!
Look, we got to go
to the hospital, okay? Come on.
You believe all this?
I don't know what to believe.
Come on.
Brad.
Truth or dare?
Truth!
Brad?
Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- Uh, my job.
Why are you here?
Friend of mine got hurt.
It's nothing serious.
I'm just here for...
for moral support.
Something wrong?
Yeah, no, I'm just, uh...
I'm just a little shaken up.
You haven't come by to see
your mother in a few weeks.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
I thought I was paying
for this school
so you could come home
every once in a while.
I-I know, I know, I just...
Things have been
a little crazy lately.
You know, I don't want
to hear excuses, son.
I want the truth.
There goes another thousand
dollars in credit card debt.
Oh, my God, Liv.
I just had my turn.
- You what?
- The game.
It made me, um,
it made me come out.
To my father.
Wha... Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
For the first time in my life,
I... I told him my truth
and I stood up to him,
and I feel...
I feel awesome.
Okay, hold on, your dad
didn't know that you were gay?
Your ringtone's Beyoncé.
Everyone loves Beyoncé.
Tyson's next.
Will do.
Tyson Curran?
Let's do this.
Right this way.
So, you come from
a family of doctors, then?
Yes, ma'am. Mother, father,
sister, uncle and grandfather.
Pretty much everybody.
Well, they must have
set a great example
for you to want
to take the same route.
Yes, uh, absolutely,
Dean Spencer.
You know, uh, growing up,
I would hear their stories
about saving lives,
and... I think...
I think that somehow
shaped me.
Pen. Where's Tyson?
His med school interview. Why?
You know...
I could do something...
self-serving, like become
a hedge fund manager.
The thing is, people need help,
especially in times like these.
That's very noble of you.
You know...
I just have one final question.
He hasn't had his turn yet.
Mr. Curran?
Your bag.
- Wait, Tyson, no. Wait, Tyson!
- Hey!
Can I help you?
Truth or dare?
I'm sorry, I beg your pardon?
Truth, I guess.
Did my friends
really put you up to this?
How long have you been
forging prescriptions?
I don't.
Did she actually tell you that?
- Excuse me?
- I don't forge prescriptions.
Why would you even ask me that?
Um...
- Ty! Ty! Ty! Open the door!
- Hey! Hey! - Hey, Tyson!
- Tyson! - Tyson!
- Are you okay?
- Open the door!
- Ty! - Ty! Hey!
What are you doing?
Oh! Oh, my... Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
My God!
Tyson lied
and then died because of it.
Just like Ronnie did
when he didn't do the dare.
Then my turn's next.
Yeah, pick truth.
I mean, listen,
we-we all should, right?
And then whatever question
that we get asked,
we just answer it
with a hundred percent honesty.
Okay? That's how
we're gonna survive
till we figure this out.
We got it?
Only choose truth.
Need more vodka.
You need sleep.
Okay, I'll put her in bed.
You guys find Carter.
He started all this.
Maybe he can end it.
He said that he went to USC.
Five Carters,
none of them our guy.
Maybe he meant the other USC.
All right, she's asleep.
Did you find Carter yet?
- No. Dead end.
- Did you try using Google?
Search "Mexico truth or dare."
Uh, guys?
"Suspect Giselle Hammond, 22,
an American college student,
"had gone missing while on
spring break in Rosarito Beach.
"The clerk recounted
Hammond's bizarre behavior
"before the incident,
which is backed up
with surveillance footage."
Pack of Morleys.
I don't want to play anymore.
¿Va a ser cash o crédito?
Dare.
Señorita. Qué...
Perdón.
- No!
- I'm sorry, I don't have a choice.
Holy shit.
- Did they catch her?
- Uh...
No, no, it says there's
still an ongoing search.
I just found her on Facebook.
- Oh, my God, it's him.
- Is he tagged?
No, I don't see him
in any other photos.
Look at her wall.
Maybe he posted.
Well, not that I see.
But... there's a bunch of posts
about people asking her
to turn herself in,
stuff like that.
Wait, do you think
she's checking this?
- DM her.
- Wait.
Just, uh, make a fake account.
- We don't want this shit traced to us.
- Yeah.
So, we're here on
our first vacation together.
- Is it our first vacation together? Kinda?
- The beach.
Um, I mean, there was
that time you came and visited
me and my family in Texas,
- but...
- You're from Texas?
I thought you were from Mexico.
I'm not from Mexico!
Tyson!
We're playing the game, too.
We need your help.
- Please meet me.
- This woman is wanted for murder.
Do you really think she's gonna
come out of hiding for
"We need your help"?
I know the game dared you
to set that woman on fire.
Tell me where to meet you,
or I'll wait outside
your family's house
until the game dares me
to do the same to them.
Markie, you cannot send that.
If you want to live,
you need to stop thinking
about other people and start
thinking about yourself.
Truth or dare, beautiful?
What? Hard to make a decision
without Tyson telling you
what to do?
Screw you.
Truth.
Truth or dare?
I said truth.
Sorry.
That's not how this game works.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
Be patient. She'll write back.
This is all my fault.
- Hey, no, it's not.
- No, she's right.
None of us wanted
to follow that creep.
None of us wanted to play
that stupid game.
The only reason I went
on that trip was for you.
Remember?
You said you needed
- your best friend.
- All right, come on...
No, but now I realize
it's not about friendship
or "I choose you,"
it was about me being there
to cover your ass while
you hooked up with randoms!
Hey.
Screw you, Olivia.
Was that necessary?
Guys. Come outside.
Now!
Shit.
Pen? What are you doing?
I tried.
It wouldn't let me pick truth.
I tried, I swear!
I have to walk the edge
until I finish this.
Pen, you're gonna be fine.
Okay, just go slow.
Take your time.
- Oh! - Be careful!
- I'm gonna go up there.
I'll try and grab her
if she loses her balance.
No, your hand's broken.
I'll go.
Pen, just walk slowly, okay?
Hey!
Just take your time, okay?
Walk slowly.
It's gonna be fine.
- What do we do?
- Be careful.
It's gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay.
We need to grab something
in case she falls. Go inside.
- I'm gonna clear a path.
- All right, let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go!
Pen? Be careful.
- You're good, okay?
- Hey, will this work?
What? Yeah. Yeah. Come on.
Just get under her.
- Get under her and follow her.
- Be careful, Pen.
- Oh, sh...
- Get back. Get back, get back.
No need to rush.
It's okay. It's okay, Pen.
Just take your time.
Take it slowly.
Pen, just put one foot
in front of the other.
Watch it, okay? Just go slow.
You can do this.
We're right here.
We're here for you, okay?
I see her. She's right there.
Go. Go. Go.
- W-Wait, she's on the corner.
- There she is.
Get that stuff out of the way.
Pen! Pen.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
No, no, no,
don't get too close.
If I, if I, if I cheat,
if I don't do the dare...
I know. I know. Okay?
But when you finish,
I'll be here to grab you.
Just got to go around
this corner now, okay?
Oh.
Come on.
Take your time, okay?
You're doing great, Pen.
- Don't look down.
- Wait. Stay here. Stay below her.
Okay.
Wait, where are you going?
Hey, Pen.
Don't look at the fence.
Okay? Look at me.
Okay? You're almost there.
Just a little more.
She's right above us.
Throw it on top.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
That's not gonna work.
That might.
- Whoa!
- Hey! Penelope!
Shit.
Guys, get back further!
- Go, go, go, move back.
- Get back!
One last sip.
No, no, Pen! Hey, Pen! No! No!
- Pen?
- She's not moving.
Pen?
Is this my bed?
Yeah.
You're okay.
I just got a Facebook message
from Giselle.
We're sure this is a good idea,
meeting her here?
What if the cops
trace her message?
No, she wrote us
on a fake account.
Yeah, but that chick
lit somebody on fire.
- She's probably nuts.
- I mean,
do we really have another choice?
I mean, we can talk
about this inside. Come on.
Let's go.
Inside?
Uh-uh. Okay, all right,
that's far enough.
Can you tell us
what's happening?
- Which one of you is Olivia?
- No, you answer
our question first:
How do you know Carter?
- Carter?
- You know, cut the crap.
We saw the photo.
He's the one who brought us
into this game.
Uh, yeah, right, okay.
- Carter, right.
- Did he bring you into this, too?
N-No, uh, he didn't,
he didn't start this.
He was just one of my friends.
We-we all went on a trip to
Mexico and got really wasted.
We-we found this old church,
and we decided to party in it,
and my roommate wanted to play
Truth or Dare, so we did,
but when we got home, the game,
it just, it kept going.
My roommate died first,
and then the other ones...
- How is this possible?
- I wish I knew.
You know, I thought
this was some kind of, like,
karmic payback for Sam
trashing the place, you know?
- Sam?
- Uh, yeah, Sam.
He-he was...
one of my friends.
He-he got really drunk, and
he just started breaking stuff.
I don't know, we were, we were
all being idiots.
Our friend
just had a turn in the game.
It wouldn't let her pick truth.
Do you know why?
It's how we played.
We called it
two truths and a dare.
If... if two people
picked truth in a row,
then the next person
had to do a dare.
Thought it was
more fun that way.
More fun? Your asshole buddy
gave us a death sentence.
Any more super dangerous rules
you want to tell us about?
Easy, Pen.
He-he told me he was dared
to find a new group to play,
and that it had to be
at the mission.
He didn't have a choice,
you know?
Of course he did.
Okay, so where is Carter now?
I haven't talked to him
since he went back to Mexico.
I thought that when he got
a new group to play
that we-we would be out.
I can't believe he only got
five of you to play.
If he would've got more,
then I would've had a longer
time before I had to go again.
You got another turn?
Okay, it's time to go, guys.
Is this why
you're telling us the truth?
No, I, uh... I picked dare.
Markie's right.
Let's get out of here.
Okay, we're leaving.
Come on, Olivia.
I am so sorry, Olivia.
How did you know my name
when I got here?
I... I didn't put it
in the message.
No! No!
- No! Pen!
- Pen!
No! No!
- Hold her down!
- I have to kill Olivia!
Hold her down!
Grab the gun.
Stop moving.
What the...?
What? No! No!
No! No! No!
Oh, shit.
What was she thinking?
It wasn't her.
Something took over,
like she was possessed.
She didn't finish her dare.
Like Ronnie.
This is what happens.
So what do we do?
We tell the truth.
- Yeah, right away.
- She was erratic,
said she had to kill me.
Then Penelope
pushed me out of the way,
she shot her and then
turned the gun on herself.
Were you aware that Giselle
Hammond was wanted for murder?
Yes. Yeah, we thought
that she knew someone
that we were looking for,
a guy that we met in Mexico.
- His name was Carter.
- You don't know his last name?
No.
Any of these people
look like him?
No. Who are they?
Five of Giselle Hammond's
friends... all deceased.
Three suicides, two accidental
deaths, all in three weeks.
And now you've lost
two friends.
I don't believe
in coincidences, Olivia.
I think this is all connected.
If you know how,
you need to tell me.
No, I promise.
If I did know, I would.
I hope so.
We'll be in touch.
Don't take any more vacations.
That did not go well.
We told them the truth.
As much as we could.
Guys, the cops should be
the least of our concerns.
I mean, Penelope's dead
and Giselle gave us nothing.
She did say a new game
had to start at the mission.
That place has to be the key.
Brad.
Catch up
with you guys later.
- No, we shouldn't split up.
- No, it's okay.
My turn's not for a while.
I'll deal with my father; you
deal with finding the mission.
Come on.
I think it was built in 1896.
Yeah, that really
narrows it down.
It's a start.
Oh, shit.
I got to grab my charger.
Uh, I think you left
your bag in my room.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
Check this out.
It says there was a massacre
a few weeks later.
Only one survivor, lives in
the area, Inez Reyes, 19.
Truth or dare?
Where is she? Liv!
- Hey! Hey!
- - Olivia.
- Are you okay?
- Where am I?
- Where am I?!
- What the hell are you...?
Who the... Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Was that your turn?
Hey, hey, come back!
Come back!
Olivia, what did he say?
He dared me
to sleep with Lucas.
Why would you pick dare?
Because of what Giselle said.
I-If I picked truth,
I was just forcing
someone else to pick dare.
How noble.
Markie, I didn't know
that's what it would ask.
I don't think
he knew where he was.
- Are you guys okay?
- Yeah, I'm perfect.
Well, hey, hey.
Where are you going?
- Anywhere but here.
- What is going on?
Why don't you ask Olivia?
Will you please tell me
what the hell is going on?
I got my turn.
Yeah, and?
Mm, oh, hey, no.
Wh-What are we doing?
Oh, this is the dare.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you pick truth?
I told Markie it was so that
you guys wouldn't have to,
but that was a lie.
I chose dare because
there is something
that I can never tell Markie,
and I'm really afraid
the game's gonna make me do it.
It can't be that bad.
You have no idea.
What?
No, you are just doing this
because of the dare,
because you have to.
No, you have to.
I don't.
Look at me.
Truth or dare?
Tr-Truth!
Who are you truly in love with?
I care about you. I do.
I'm in love with Markie.
Liv, I'm sorry.
It was the game.
No, it was the truth.
Roy Cameron, 45 years old,
attempts to make dinner.
Take one.
Whoa, a little faith, please.
Nobody makes a steak
like your old man.
Wait, Dad, I'm pescatarian now.
I know, honey.
Dad?
I miss you so much.
I miss you, too.
There's something that
I've been dying to ask you.
No.
She's not answering.
Wait. Come here.
Look at this.
There's no number,
but she lives in Tijuana.
That's less than
three hours away.
Who is she?
She's someone who might
be able to help us.
Come on.
Come on, sweetheart.
Time to pick.
Truth.
The gun I used
to kill myself...
why do you keep it?
Sometimes I think about
using it.
Maybe you should get it.
I'm worried about Markie.
I wish we would have
found her before we left.
Yeah, well, she doesn't want
to speak to me right now,
so there's nothing we can do.
You know that secret
that you're keeping from her?
Maybe if you got it out,
- the game couldn't use it against you.
- No.
No one can ever know.
Especially not Markie.
It would kill her.
I'll try her again
when we get there.
- Um...
- Can I help you?
S-Sorry. Um, we're looking
for Inez Reyes.
She's my grandmother.
I watch after her.
We were just wondering
if we could speak to her.
She speaks to no one.
No. Please!
Our friends are dying
just like hers did.
We-we just need a few words.
I will ask.
And if you could...
show her this.
Show her that we were
at this mission
and that half the people
in this photo are now dead.
Then maybe she'll talk to us.
She might see you,
but she will not speak to you.
She has not said a word
in 50 years.
Wait here.
She must have taken
a vow of silence, right?
She was 19 when her friends
were butchered.
- Imagine what that did to her.
- I don't have to.
It's been over an hour.
Yeah, for someone
who doesn't speak,
they seem to be doing
a lot of talking.
She will see you.
I'm sorry for the wait.
She has written
something for you.
What is it?
She would not let me read it.
Thank you for seeing us,
Miss Reyes.
"The mission was a convent
"where young women
went to find God.
"We were girls, so we played
silly games like Hide and Seek.
"But the priest
who ran the convent
"forced us to play
his own game.
"He let us hide, but then
he took the one he found.
"His pleasure was our pain.
"We suffered in silence.
"Then one of the girls
told a secret.
"She knew spells
that could call spirits,
"so she summoned
a demon named Calux.
He possessed our game."
Possessed the game?
"Demons possess people, places,
objects, even ideas."
Uh, uh...
"Calux is a trickster.
"That night, when the priest
found his victim,
"she was possessed by Calux.
"She hid the priest's body
in the mission...
"in pieces.
"It took them a week
to find his head.
"But Calux didn't want to stop.
"He made us keep playing.
Many of my sisters died."
Wait, how did you
and the others escape?
"The person
who released the demon
"can trap it
with a simple ritual,
but only by his own hand."
Uh, this is the spell?
Uh, it's in Spanish.
"The spell must be
repeated seven times
"and a sacrifice must be placed
in a pot sealed with wax.
"As long as the pot
stays sealed in the mission,
the door we opened for Calux
will also be sealed."
Wait, I've seen
that pot before.
Yeah. Look.
But when I saw it,
it was broken
and there was something inside
it and it smelled rotten.
"Whoever broke the pot
will have to do the same."
What was it?
The sacrifice.
It was you
who summoned the demon?
It's been a few years
since AP Spanish,
but I think it says,
"I have called upon an evil.
Silence my voice,
so the evil is no more."
So when Carter and his friends
broke the pot at the mission...
The demon was freed
and possessed their game
of Truth or Dare.
And we have to find
whoever broke that pot.
But Giselle said somebody
named Sam trashed the place.
And we have no idea who Sam is.
- Or if he's even still alive.
- And if we do find him...
What?
"Hi, Sam. Do you mind
cutting out your tongue
and sealing it in this
lovely handmade pot?"
I'll check
Giselle's Facebook again,
see if there's a Sam tagged.
Still nothing from Markie?
She's ignoring all my texts.
Her turn's next.
I'm gonna try
calling her again.
Brad? Brad!
It's your father.
Since Penelope, he's been...
I'll get rid of him.
Let's talk outside.
I'm gonna grab coffee.
Look, uh, I'm hearing
some things
about your, uh,
friend's murder.
Kranis in Homicide isn't
convinced it's so simple.
I know I don't need
to ask this, but...
is there something
you're not telling us?
No, I-I promise.
Everything we told you
was true.
Markie, thank God.
Why are you telling me
all this?
'Cause I know Kranis is wrong,
and I want you to know
what's going on.
Look, you don't have to worry.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
You're still my son, Brad.
- You gonna get that?
- Get what?
Truth or dare, Brad?
Yeah, I guess
I just needed some time alone.
No, no, no.
It's-it's fine.
Just get here
as fast as you can.
And please be careful.
Your turn's next.
I had my turn.
I chose truth.
So did Lucas.
And if the both of you
picked truth...
You only have one choice.
You sure there's nothing
you need to tell me?
I dare you to steal his gun
and make him beg for his life.
Son?
Thank you, Dad, for everything.
It's just, uh, there's just
one more thing I need to do,
and I hope you can forgive me.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Of course.
For what?
It's okay.
I need you to beg.
For your life.
- The hell are you doing?
- Beg for your life!
Brad, please, put the gun down!
- Just do as I say or I'll die.
- You don't have to do this!
- Get on your knees.
- We have to go. Now!
Do as I say.
I'll explain everything, okay?
- I know I've been hard on you.
- Listen. No!
- And I'm sorry.
- No.
That's not what this is about.
Beg! Please.
I'll explain everything.
- Just beg.
- I guess you think I deserve this.
No. No.
Just, just, just, just beg!
Please! Just beg
and I'll put down the gun.
- What's that gonna prove, Brad?
- Just beg,
and I'll put down the gun! Beg!
No, no, no, no!
- No! No!
- Brad!
Brad! No, no, no! No!
No! No!
Get a paramedic!
Come on.
Brad, Brad! No, no, no.
Stay here.
You're gonna be fine.
No! No!
I need a paramedic! Help!
I need a paramedic! Brad!
I'm so sorry.
Guys, can we get out of here?
I still need to talk
to the detective.
I shouldn't have picked truth.
No, it's not your fault.
I picked truth, too.
We shouldn't have
left Brad alone.
No, it wouldn't have mattered.
This game is smart.
It's too smart.
We're not playing it;
it's playing us.
And none of this
is a coincidence.
It waits for our most
vulnerable moments,
and that's when it asks us.
Yeah,
you got that right, Olivia.
And now it's your turn.
Truth or dare?
What?
What is it?
Lucas just asked me.
No, I didn't.
Truth or dare, Olivia?
O-Okay.
Okay, you have to pick truth.
Olivia, do it.
- Dare.
- Olivia!
I dare you...
to tell Markie
the secret you fear most.
What? Wh-What is it
making you do?
Markie, there's something
important I need to tell you.
What?
I was there
the night your dad died.
I know what happened.
What?
What are you talking about?
I had gotten into a fight
with my parents,
so I went to your house.
You weren't there,
so your dad let me in.
He... he was drinking,
and he offered me one,
so I took it.
We had a few,
and then he told me
that he had been fired
that day, 'cause he was,
he was drinking on the job,
and I just,
I felt really bad for him.
But I told him that you and I
would help him
figure things out.
And then he called me
beautiful.
And... I was drunk,
and I didn't know what to do,
and then he leaned in
to kiss me,
and I-I tried to push him off.
I didn't do it, but he...
he kept coming back stronger.
But finally, I-I got free.
He begged me to forgive him,
said that he needed help,
but I was so scared,
and I was confused,
and I threatened
to tell you what happened,
but he said that he would die
if you ever found out.
I-I told him that you'd be
better off if he were dead.
Markie, I am so sorry.
I wanted to tell you, but
by the time I got ahold of you,
he had already done it,
and you were devastated.
It broke my heart.
I didn't know what to do.
- Trust me, I..
- No.
No, I'll never trust you again.
- Markie...
- Don't!
Don't.
Miss Barron.
You're up.
"I know the game
"dared you
to set that woman on fire.
"Tell me where to meet you,
"or I'll wait outside
your family's house
until the game dares me
to do the same to them."
That is... quite a threat.
We traced the I.P.
to your laptop.
I-I know that that...
looks bad, but I...
I just needed
to get her attention.
Yeah, I know
you're playing some kind
of Truth or Dare game,
but what I don't understand is:
why are people dying?
There's only four of you left.
- I'd like to keep the rest of you guys alive.
- Four?
Everyone who's dead
was in Mexico.
That leaves you,
Markie and Lucas,
and Giselle's friend,
Sam Meehan.
Sam?
Wait, he's alive?
You know him?
No.
No, that-that's just someone
that Giselle had mentioned.
Ah. He's holed up
in an apartment.
Won't talk to anybody.
Said I had to arrest him
if I wanted to speak
to him again.
Olivia, what the hell
is happening here?
Could I get some water, please?
Thanks.
Marcus, I'm gonna
need a glass of water.
Yes, sir, right away.
Am I being charged?
Not yet.
Okay, then I need to go.
Carter is Sam.
He was using a fake name.
But Giselle acted like
they were different people?
Well, she was probably
trying to protect him,
but she slipped up and she
used his real name. Come on.
Markie? Markie!
Markie?
Markie, please open the door.
We need to talk.
What are you doing?
What my father did.
Markie, please put it down.
Why?
I don't have anything.
You have me.
No.
Now the game has us.
I hid the truth about your dad
to protect you.
But I was wrong.
Every single day,
I wish I could take back
what I said to him.
And he tried before.
It's not your fault.
We can't change the past.
But we can still have a future.
We can end this game.
How?
Carter... I know where he is.
Okay, so what's the plan?
- We just have to get him back to the mission.
- Okay.
So don't open with "We need you
to cut out your own tongue"?
Here it is. Six.
Go away!
I don't want to talk to anyone!
Screw this.
You...
- Wait, wait, wait!
- Carter!
Or is it Sam?
- How did you find me?
- We were motivated.
- What the hell happened in here?
- The game.
No contact with the outside.
Nothing in here can hurt me.
- This is your plan?
- My plan is to wait it out.
No, that was your second plan.
Your first plan
was to screw us.
Three of my best friends
are dead because of you!
I'm sorry.
I lost friends, too, okay?
If I could take it all back,
I would.
There is a way.
But we all have to go back
to the mission.
A way to what?
To what, end the game? How?
Just... trust me.
We have to go back.
Uh-uh. No, this is
another dare, right?
- The game's daring you to lure me out? Is that...
- No.
She's telling the truth.
And why should I trust you?
Because we want
the same thing.
We want to survive.
Look...
I'm gonna tell you what you
should've told me at the bar.
Piss off.
Okay, sweet little Olivia's
not shooting anyone.
Try me. I dare you.
- Come on, let's go.
- I am moving.
Right through here.
Go.
Is this ritual
that old nun told you about
actually gonna work?
There's only one way
to find out.
So we're gonna end this
with a séance?
We are not ending it.
You are.
Me? I tried.
We all know how that
turned out.
Stay down.
Here. Take this. Take it!
Say it seven times.
What are you
gonna do with that?
I'm giving it to you.
Take it. Now!
Now say the words seven times.
Go!
Uh...
"Hermaro almas..."
- Did you feel that?
- Don't stop.
- Just-just tell me what's going on!
- Keep going!
All right...
"...silencia mi voz para que
el mal no sea más.
Say it again.
"Hermaro almas,
silencia mi voz para que
el mal no sea más."
Five more times.
"Hermaro almas,
silencia mi voz
para que el mal no sea más."
Truth or dare, Lucas?
Dare.
"Hermaro almas,
silencia mi voz
mi voz para que el mal no..."
- Where are you going?
- Just got to get away from here.
Wait, wait, wait.
You can't go.
Your turn's next.
I just had my turn.
- Got to get away from you both.
- Why?
Because it dared me to choose.
You already have.
You love Markie.
Choose which one of you
to kill.
Luke.
What, so he's just leaving?!
Don't stop.
Two more times.
"Hermaro almas,
silencia mi voz para que
el mal no sea más."
Luke?
Luke? Why did you pick dare?
Because I knew if I didn't,
then one of you would have to.
And we're so close.
And I won't let
the game kill you.
You're such an idiot.
What can I say?
You do that to me.
"Hermaro almas, silencia mi voz
para que el mal no sea más."
That's seven.
We got to get out of here.
This place is coming down.
No, there's one more thing
to do.
Pick up the knife.
I can't do it for you.
Pick it up!
And do what?
I'm so sorry, Sam.
But you unleashed this evil,
which means you're the only one
who can stop it.
I need you to cut out
your tongue.
N-No, that's insane.
Please!
It's the only way we survive!
You take care of each other.
No.
- No. No.
- Do it.
- Lucas, stop!
- That's not Lucas.
Do it now, Carter.
Before it's too late!
Don't you want to live?!
You do not have a choice!
Do it!
I can't believe
I'm about to do this.
I will murder
everyone you've ever known!
No, they are not in this!
It's just us!
You're right.
But Lucas is,
and he didn't do his dare.
So now he dies.
No!
Lucas refused his dare
to save us.
We have to finish this.
Calux killed Carter.
The spell won't work.
No, we lost the second
we started this game.
The second we came here.
Carter was dared
to bring us here,
because this is where you can
add new people to the game.
I have an idea.
Your turn's next.
When you're asked,
I need you to pick dare.
Why would I do that?
Markie...
Truth or dare?
Now Lucas is asking me.
Pick dare.
- But don't do it.
- What? I'll die.
Markie, I am so sorry
for keeping that secret
from you for so long.
And I swear to you
I will never, ever keep
anything from you again.
But we survive this
only if we trust each other.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Trust me.
You have to pick.
Dare.
I dare you to shoot Olivia.
He wants me to shoot you.
You got to trust me, Markie.
Don't do it.
This is the only way
to save us both.
Okay. I trust you.
I won't do it.
No!
Dare complete, Calux.
Your turn.
Truth or dare?
I'm not in this game.
No, once you're asked,
you're in.
Those are the rules, right?
So, truth or dare, asshole?
Truth.
How do we get out
of this game alive?
You can't.
Carter was the only one
who could stop this.
So now the game won't end
until all the players are dead.
And your turn's next.
Unless you find
some new friends to play with.
But that's not
gonna happen, is it?
- Your arm.
- I'm okay.
Well, did it work?
It's not over.
The game will never end,
not as long as we're alive.
What are you doing?
I'm choosing you.
My friends and I
went on a trip to Mexico
for spring break.
We ended up in an old mission
where we played a game
of Truth or Dare.
We had no idea that we had
encountered an unspeakable evil
that wanted to play with us.
When we went home,
the game kept going.
It killed five of my friends.
The game is real.
Tell the truth, do the dare,
or you die;
refuse to play, you die.
It can happen anywhere,
and it can come from anyone.
I am so sorry,
but I have to ask you...
truth or dare?
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Truth or dare?