Subtitles by explosiveskull
(TURNS OFF ENGINE)
Alice?
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
Put on some...
Put on some clothes.
(DOOR OPENS)
ETHAN: I'm in here.
You moved.
Yep.
You didn't tell me.
(ETHAN SIGHS)
I haven't seen
you in years.
Well, I'm here now,
and that's what counts.
So, maybe, I could stay a little,
and we could chat, catch up.
(INHALES SHAKILY)
ETHAN: Okay.
Yeah?
You can stay
just one night.
(PUTS CUP DOWN)
- ALICE: It's beautiful.
- ETHAN: What?
- The house, dummy.
- Thanks.
It's huge.
Yeah.
- Upkeep must be crazy.
- What?
The upkeep must be expensive.
- All the bills and stuff.
- Yeah.
I'm not sure
how you pay for it.
Yeah, so, hey, I'm actually
in the middle of something.
So, I need to
get back to work.
Help yourself to a snack,
or something.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(RUSTLING)
ALICE:
I'm making tacos.
It's fake meat, though.
I don't eat dead things.
Okay.
So, what are you working on
that's so busy and important?
Drawings.
- What for?
- A book.
Whose book?
Mine.
Really? Your own?
Yes, and I have a deadline
that I'm way past,
so, I need to
get to work.
Alone.
What's it about?
It's a long story.
Ethan,
we used to tell
each other everything.
We need to become
siblings again.
Family.
Family? Really?
Family's complicated.
So, where do you live?
In the city.
With my boyfriend.
Does he take care of you?
Actually, I work.
Not everyone can just,
you know, fall into a mansion
without any explanation.
Besides, we broke up.
I thought
you said "boyfriend."
Was. It's recent. So, I'm
just not used to saying "ex."
Why'd you break up?
Because I caught him
fucking someone else.
- So?
- So, he was mine.
(SCOFFS)
It's just sex.
Besides, you've been
the other woman before.
Stop!
Don't be mean.
I'm already
really unhappy.
I don't know what to
believe with you anymore.
Why would I lie about
something like that?
People lie by saying they are
happy when they're not,
not the other way around.
Besides, it's over,
and I need to move on.
You're always moving on.
Well, I'll be moving on in the
morning, so, don't worry about it.
- I'm not worried.
- Great.
Great.
(GRUNTS)
Ethan?
ETHAN:
It's weird, right?
Some kind of sinkhole,
or something?
Right?
What?
Nothing.
This place is
fucking weird.
- What?
You said...
You said something?
Nothing.
That thing.
It's fucking weird, right?
(SNAPS FINGERS)
Hmm.
What made you
go out there?
I was...
(CLEARS THROAT)
I was just walking around,
and I stumbled upon it.
Right.
I don't know
what's happening,
but you'll be safe.
I'll keep you safe.
I don't know what's happening,
but you'll be safe.
I'll keep you safe.
Where did you go?
- Nowhere.
- But you did go somewhere.
Have you seen my pen?
What pen?
My special pen.
Why is it special?
Because I use
it to draw.
What's it look like?
Silver. I always keep it
in the same place.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
Sometimes, things
are in plain sight,
and you just need someone
else to look for you.
(OBJECTS RUSTLING)
ETHAN: Shit.
Hey, maybe it's
in a different room.
- Did you find it?
- ETHAN: No!
Go!
(GRUNTS)
- ALICE: No?
- No.
Yes? No.
(BOTH PANTING)
What are we looking for?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- Oh, it was the pen.
- Did you find it?
- No.
No.
You didn't come.
You didn't come
to Mom's funeral.
She treated you
like everything.
She treated me
like a mistake.
She wasn't right
when we were kids.
You should stay
a little while.
You can borrow
some of my clothes.
(DOORS CREAKING)
I can't focus
on my work.
Are you distracted because
we live on a giant sphere,
that's spinning in the
middle of nowhere?
Maybe.
Are you distracted
by the hole?
What if it's a portal?
(INHALES SHARPLY)
We'll start over.
Hmm?
You can come with me.
What are you
talking about?
(WHISPERING) I think there's
a better place than here.
Where're you going?
Please wait!
Ethan, come back! What did I say?
I'm sorry!
Hey.
You did this.
- What?
- You fucking witch.
You're tryin' to make
me think things?
- Huh? Just like when we were kids.
- (WHIMPERING)
- You were always so fucking...
- What are you talking about?
- What'd you do?
You're being crazy.
- I'm not crazy. You're crazy.
- I didn't do anything.
What'd you do?
- You're the one being crazy.
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
- Ethan, stop it.
- You're crazy.
- You're hurting me.
- Crazy!
Stop!
- What the fuck?
- Sorry.
Sorry.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
ALICE: (WHISPERING)
Ethan's crazy. I'm not crazy.
I'm not being crazy.
He is. He's crazy.
What happened?
You tell me.
I seem to be upsetting you,
so, I'm gonna go.
Alice.
I really don't want to
be here alone right now.
Stay.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(RUSTLING)
ETHAN: Oh.
It's just her.
Wanna go for a swim?
No.
(BALL BOUNCES)
Hey.
Who are you?
My mom's
cleaning the place.
Oh.
Yeah, she takes me to my
soccer games afterwards.
- Soccer.
- Yeah. Watch.
Cool.
(PANTING)
Look.
Danny, you aren't bothering
anyone, are you?
- No.
You look just like her.
Who?
Elaine.
You knew her?
When she
lived here, yes.
Whose house is this?
Huh?
Is this Mom's house?
Oh, fucking God.
How? How's that
even possible?
- I don't know.
- You're a liar.
- I got a call out...
I got a call out of the blue.
I had no idea.
She left it to me,
and I...
Doesn't make any sense.
She just left it to me.
I had no idea.
You could have told me.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I didn't know where you were.
I found you.
You could've found me.
Maybe I didn't want to.
I would've told
you eventually.
We used to tell
each other everything.
I know.
You said that earlier.
Ethan.
This makes sense.
Can you see it?
It all makes sense.
Alice.
She had a secret life.
- This house.
- Okay.
Me coming here.
She had a secret life.
- I didn't plan this.
- No...
- I didn't plan this, Ethan.
- Please.
I just got in the car,
and something drove me here.
Can't you see?
This is all meant to be.
Ethan?
You'll come with me.
There's a better
place than here.
Don't fight it.
Come on.
(COUGHS)
(RUSTLING)
(RUSTLING CONTINUES)
(ETHAN PANTING)
(CONTINUES PANTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(STRUGGLING)
Ethan! Ethan! Ethan!
Ethan!
(INSECT CHITTERING)
ALICE: Ethan.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- I thought you left.
- No.
Did you open
the windows last night?
No, why?
I thought
they were open.
Maybe you opened them.
Maybe.
What are you
doing in here?
Making coffee.
You want some?
Yeah.
What are you
thinking about?
Hmm?
Creatures grow
inside our bellies.
It's like we're technically upside
down, and yet, we don't fall.
But people think it's strange
to consider somewhere else...
Wait. Where'd
you get that?
I found it.
You shouldn't wear that.
You'd never
leave me behind, right?
Just promise you'll never leave me.
Please.
I won't leave you.
Just don't fuck me over
like you did to her.
She deserved it.
You're the reason
why she left, Alice.
Alice! Alice, wait!
Alice, stop!
(GASPS)
Hi.
What's going on?
- Nothing.
This is Alice.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Alice. Alice.
Of course. I'm so sorry.
Hi.
I'm Misty,
Ethan's girlfriend.
- Misty.
- Yeah.
Did you forget
I was coming?
Yeah. No. I mean,
I forgot. I'm...
No. I got caught up
in things. Sorry.
Right. Obviously.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
(ETHAN SIGHING)
It's good to see you.
MISTY: I'm gonna jump in the shower.
I feel crazy after that trip.
It was really
great to meet you.
I can't believe you didn't
tell me you had a girlfriend.
- You won't say anything...
- About what?
- About what's been happening.
- What has been happening?
- Just things have been weird.
- So, you will admit it.
Just... Just don't
tell her about it.
I can't believe you
didn't tell me about her.
I'm sorry.
No, I mean, I can't believe it.
It's literally unbelievable.
Very strange.
(MISTY GASPS)
(GIGGLES)
You scared me.
ETHAN: I'm sorry.
For what?
I didn't know she was coming.
She just showed up.
It's okay.
I mean, it was a bit of
a shock, but it's okay.
She's just staying for
one more night, I think.
- You think?
- I'll ask her to leave tomorrow.
No, I didn't mean
she should leave.
It's just, I was looking forward
to spending more time with you.
(GRUNTS)
There you are.
What are you doing?
Are you sure
she's your girlfriend?
No, I'm not sure.
Yes, Alice. What the fuck?
What are you talking about?
I've seen her before.
Probably saw a picture
around the house.
Yes, in the picture.
ETHAN: Where'd you find that?
In the closet, with the dress.
I thought it was her.
- Misty?
- Never mind.
It doesn't matter.
What?
Guess I'm gonna
leave, then.
Why?
- I don't want to get in the way.
- You're not getting in the way.
No, it's fine. Really.
I'm gonna leave.
I mean, I'm not sure where I'm
gonna go, but I'll figure it out.
Why don't you stay one more
night? Just one more night.
I've already told
her all about you.
We'll get to know
one another.
Why didn't you
tell me about her?
Didn't I?
- Don't try and make me feel crazy.
- I'm not.
Yes, you are. You didn't
tell me about her.
Why?
- I don't know. I don't trust you.
- Trust me to what?
'Cause you'd do
something weird.
You'd make fun of her,
you'd be mean to her.
Where'd you say you met?
- Nearby. She was up here on a film.
- Mmm.
- Didn't I tell you that?
- Stop saying that! You didn't tell me.
Is she an actress?
Yes. She was up
here on a film.
- Where?
- Los Angeles.
You just said
here, Ethan.
No, I meant that...
We met here, but she just
got back from Los Angeles.
- Hollywood?
- I don't know.
- It's the same thing, isn't it?
- Sort of.
What kind of name
is Misty, anyway?
I don't know.
Does she just mist about
from room to room,
just being all misty and shit?
- What's up with you?
- How long have you been dating?
I don't know.
A few months.
You sure seem confused
about your relationship.
You're making me confused.
Don't blame your weakness
on my strength.
She's nice.
I'm happy.
Can't you be happy for me?
But I can stay
a few more nights?
Yeah, I already
said that.
I thought she picked me.
I'm very confused.
- What are you talking about?
- Okay, fine.
I'll stay, okay?
Okay.
Just another week
or so, though.
I already said that's okay.
Okay. Okay.
You wanna help?
Sure.
Why don't you
break up the lettuce?
I like your hair.
Thanks.
Mount St. Helens.
What?
My necklace.
It's made with the minerals from
when Mount St. Helens erupted
in Washington state
back in 1980.
It's literally a piece of disaster.
I mean, can you imagine?
Where were you
last night?
Up there.
On a red-eye.
Why don't you go
set the table?
We'll have lunch
outside, yeah?
Sure.
(DOOR OPENS)
Who were you
with before Ethan?
- Alice.
- What?
Come on.
It's fine.
- No one, really.
- No one?
No, I wasn't really
the boyfriend type.
And then, I met Ethan.
Do you have
your own place?
No, I travel a lot for work,
so, I just stay here.
What about your stuff? Where
do you keep all your stuff?
I don't really
have a lot of stuff.
Can we just have a normal
fucking conversation, please?
Did Ethan tell you
about what's happening?
No.
You sure you don't know
what I'm talking about?
Yes.
(WHISPERING)
Hey, stop acting weird.
ALICE: Ethan.
You're the same as me.
We need to stick together.
ETHAN: You tore us apart.
That's why
I'm back now, okay?
She was awful to me, Misty.
- Truly awful to me.
- Who?
Mother.
That's why I ran away.
No, you ran away
because you...
- Because what?
- Nothing.
- What?
After I fucked her husband, she
just walked into the ocean.
Just walked and kept walking until...
(IMITATES WAVES)
The tide took her away.
There's no proof.
They never found her body.
She had a secret life.
ALICE: After everything
we just talked about,
she's gonna sit
by the fucking pool.
She has no stuff. She
grew up here and there.
- She has no past.
- She told us her past.
Where'd you meet her?
- I told you. Up here, on the movie.
- Really?
Why is that so weird?
She got into my head,
then yours.
What? I don't...
What do you mean?
She lives here,
yet, I don't see, or feel the
energy of another woman.
I don't know why not.
I don't understand. You're
acting like she has an agenda.
No. She's the one
acting, Ethan.
She picked me.
Now, she wants you.
What are you
talking about?
It's not fair.
She's gonna
take you away.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm really sorry
I tore things apart.
Alice...
- Sorry.
- Alice.
That's all in
the past. Okay?
We can move forward.
Looks great on you.
Sorry about earlier.
It's all right.
You don't think I'm terrible?
Everybody makes mistakes.
- What's Ethan's book about?
- I don't know.
He's not going to show it
to me until it's finished.
Are you in love, Misty?
Yes.
Both of you?
Well, I would assume.
- That's funny.
- Why's that?
I guess I didn't get
that vibe from him.
Why? What did he say?
Nothing. Just that
you were casual.
He didn't exactly
use the word, "love,"
but he was probably
just nervous to tell me.
Love is a big word.
Do you think
I'm a child, Alice?
No.
So, don't lie to me like one.
Hey.
Those are beautiful.
Thanks.
You gonna come with me?
Where?
Europe. The Geneva film,
remember?
Come.
Alice can stay here
and watch the house.
She can't come with us?
No, they won't
allow that.
Who are they?
The producers.
It's okay to leave her behind.
She's my sister.
She's not good for you.
She makes you crazy.
Let's just get
out of here. Okay?
(SIGHS) Okay.
ALICE: She won't get in our way.
I promise.
She won't get in our way.
Come on.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
There you are. Hi.
What are you doing up there?
There you are.
I knew it. There.
I knew it. I told you.
I told you.
Where is it? I told you.
Where is it?
Come on. Where'd you go?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
Calm down. What are you
fuckin' goin' on about?
- What is wrong with you?
- What are you talking about?
- Will you wake the fuck up!
Something's happening,
and you fucking know it.
I know you know it.
- Alice. Alice.
- What?
You want something to happen.
You're looking for a way out.
- Wake the fuck up.
- Calm down.
Alice, you just want
something to happen.
You're lookin' for
a way out.
- She's trying to take you away.
- Alice. Alice, listen.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Alice, it's only a work trip.
It's nothing.
- It's all right.
- She's trying to take you away.
Yeah, for work.
It's okay.
She's trying to
take you away from me.
Alice.
She's not one of us.
(SIGHS)
- We're in love.
- (ALICE GROANS)
You sound like
a fucking robot.
- She's got you programmed.
- Just stop it.
Wait. You gotta
believe me.
Why can't you believe me?
What do you want me to believe?
I'm confused.
You've never
seen her before today.
No, Alice. Don't
fuck around with me.
Think hard.
Where'd ya meet?
- Up here, on a movie.
- What movie?
I can't remember.
You'd remember
what she was working on.
No, I just can't think.
You're stressing me out.
Think hard about being with her early on.
Think hard.
- No, I can't think.
- Think hard.
You're stressing
me out.
Think hard about being with her, early on.
Think hard about it.
Be strong.
Where'd you meet?
I can't remember.
Feels like a weird dream.
What does?
- What does?
- Everything right now.
What's happening?
I'm still trying
to figure everything out.
Doesn't matter.
Everything's fine.
We're here together.
She's trying
to take you away.
They want you.
We're supposed to
tell each other everything.
Always supposed to
- Promise me again.
- Promise.
- Say it again.
- Promise you won't leave me.
- I promise.
She's not one of us.
- ETHAN: She's not one of us.
- We'll be together forever.
We'll be together forever.
She needs to leave.
There you are.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Did you tell
Alice dinner's ready?
Of course.
- Sit next to me.
- Right.
MISTY: Wow.
You look beautiful.
None for me, thanks.
- You don't drink?
- Not right now.
I quit smoking, too. I don't
like the taste anymore.
MISTY: What? Are you pregnant?
Are you?
I wanted to keep it a secret.
We're supposed to
tell each other everything?
- What else are you hiding?
- Nothing.
- Nothing!
That explains everything.
That's why
you've been acting so strange.
ALICE: Don't say that.
- That's why you're confused.
- Don't you do that.
You feel strange, too.
I know you do.
Don't tell me
how I fucking feel.
You know what
I'm talking about.
- Don't you dare fucking bring this...
- Ethan!
Hey. Hey.
What's going on?
Look at me. Stop this.
Don't go, Ethan.
- What's happening?
- ALICE: Don't look at her.
- Ethan!
- Stay. Stay with me.
- Hey. Look at me.
- Stop this!
- No.
- Ethan.
Let her go.
She's my sister.
You need to let her go.
Ethan. What's happening?
- We met down the street, right?
- What?
We met down
the street, right?
- I don't understand.
- Just tell me.
- I was making a movie.
- You were making a movie.
And then you moved in.
So, then you
walked across the street.
- Yeah.
- To say hello.
Yeah.
- Right?
- Yeah.
That's right.
Why'd you pick me?
- Pick you?
- Yeah, why me?
Because I was drawn to you.
I don't know.
Everything is
confusing right now.
It's not confusing.
You're allowing
this to be confusing.
You just stop letting her
get in your head.
You told me before
that this happens.
It's okay.
It's okay because
I'm here now.
You're okay because
I don't fucking need him.
I don't need him.
She can take him.
We don't fucking need it.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BOTH MOANING)
- What?
- Nothing.
(MISTY MOANING)
Do it, Ethan.
Do it.
- Do that.
- Do that?
- Like that?
- MISTY: Yeah.
Do it.
Yeah.
(MOANING)
Like that?
Do it.
Ethan.
(MISTY CHOKING)
(PANTING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(CONTINUES PANTING)
(ALICE GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY) Ethan.
ETHAN: What have we done?
ETHAN: They'll take her away?
ALICE: Yes.
They'll take her away.
Oh, shit. I forgot.
ALICE: What is it?
ETHAN: It wasn't real.
It's okay.
It doesn't matter.
I don't think she ever
walked into the ocean.
I think she just wanted
you out of her life forever.
Oh, yeah?
Is that what you think?
- So, where'd she go?
- I don't know.
Ethan, she came here
because she knew.
They took her
to a better place.
Then why don't you
go with her, huh?
So I can be alone.
Okay.
(WATER SPLASHES)
Subtitles by explosiveskull